Lots of chatting.
Such are our days and nights.
There something
going on every moment.
People call us mad.
Are you ready now?
Here we go.
By the way. All the way.
The life that we have got.
It sings. It laughs.
Its a bit crazy.
We fight. We kiss and make up.
Its new every moment.
Its moody. Its stubborn.
I have no idea what to do about it.
You cant stop us.
We fly like the breeze.
That's our life.
That's our style. What to do?
If someone minds, what to do?
Everyone's upset with us now.
Just forget it.
Exchange the rings.
'So romantic.'
'Isn't my aunt looking hot? '
'Actually, she always was.'
'She was Miss. India in 1 982.'
'And the best is, she
never let us miss mom.'
'Look at my colonel uncle.'
'He's so handsome, isn't it? '
'But Those moustaches.'
'He looks like the
villains from the 1970s.'
'You know, I introduced uncle
and aunt for the first time.. '
'.. at the Gymkhana club.'
'I made them sit at
the same bridge table.. '
'.. and uncle lost the
game but won aunt's heart.'
'Aaliya, my elder sister.'
'She had the same
boyfriend from school to college.'
'And she also married him.'
'So boring.'
'You know what? These days,
she only thinks about food.'
'Because she's six
months' pregnant.'
'All thanks to her one
and only boyfriend.. '
'.. and now my brother-in-law,
Karan Burman from Mumbai.'
'How will Aaliya ever
fit into her jeans again? '
Congratulations, Colonel.
'And that's my papa.'
'He's so cute, isn't he? '
'His small happiness
turns into a big party.'
'Add a few tears,
drama and butter.. '
'.. and anyone can be papa's guest.'
'Everyone's so happy.'
'It looks so nice, doesn't it?'
'I planned all this.'
'You know what? '
'When everything goes as planned,
it feels so nice.'
The story of the heart..
..I want to tell openly now.
You cant forget if you hear it once.
Hear it once.
'Pinky, my best friend.'
'We've been together
since kindergarten.'
'I would eat her lunch
and she would eat mine.'
'I would do her homework
and she would do mine.'
'Pinky does like boys.
But love? No chance.'
'Whatever. We're friends forever.'
"By the way. All the way."
When the friendship
is from the heart..
..both my heart and I..
..took this vow.
Whatever happens now
we wont be afraid ever.
I've decided. I want
to be a weather girl.
Read out the weather report..
..and collect a fat cheque.
It's so cool.
- It is.
Okay, aren't there
any cute guys here?
No way.
'Randhir Gambhir.
He's such a loser.'
'Total Yuppie.'
'He's always following me around.'
'His family owns
Ever Supreme Sweets.'
'The confectionary kings of India.'
'And he's their darling prince.'
'These days organising weddings.. '
- '.. has become a real pain.'
'Lt's seasonal, after all.'
'The real satisfaction comes
when two people come together.'
'I mean perfectly
matching two perfect people.'
I'd like to propose a toast.
Here's to aunt and my new uncle.
May you have all the
happiness in the world.
That's beautiful.
I'd like to propose a toast.
- Sorry, sorry, sorry.
'Who is she? '
'Right -That's Shefali.'
'Aunt told me that her aunt
and uncle brought her here.. '
'.. to get her married.'
'Did you see what I just saw? '
'They look perfect together.
Perfect.'
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'd like to make a toast.
Shut up, Randhir. Do
you know what a toast is?
I know it, Pinky.
So sweet..
Ladies and gentlemen. To Aisha.
Actually, Aisha's the one
who has done everything.
There was something
between aunt and sir..
I mean there was..
They had something going on.
But Aisha brought them together.
I mean, if it wasn't for Aisha..
..then aunt would've never met sir.
Aisha, you're a great girl.
Your heart..
Aisha, I.. - Aisha, you'll
certainly progress in life.
No one will be able to stop you.
I love my life.
Your..
Aisha, I'm saying something.
Cheers to you, Aisha.
Come on. Aisha's left.
It rained.
'What can I say about him? '
'He's been my
neighbour since I was a child.'
'At times, my best friend.. '
- '.. and at times, my worst enemy.'
'My Brother-in-law
Karan's younger brother.. '
'.. and our new family member.'
'He's so irritating.'
Arjun Burman, get your eyes checked.
Have you gone squint-eyed?
- It's not my fault.
I've got to look at you squint-eyed.
There happens to be a front
door to get in to the house.
Really? You've
become so smart, Aisha.
Oh, God. Why are you
always dressed this way?
Designer suits. Designer shoes.
Stuck up corporate snob.
- Hey, whatever it takes.
Sant Ram.
- Yes, sir.
Who is creating a racket?
It's none other than Arjun.
- Oh, Arjun.
When did you arrive?
- Just now, Uncle.
Aisha, let him in.
You shouldn't treat
guests like this, dear.
Exactly.
- What?
Guest? Since when?
Who gets 'Rasgulle'
(sweetmeats) From London?
You don't have a clue, Arjun.
I was passing by this shop.
There, I saw these 'Rasgulle.'
It reminded me of your face.
I grew slightly emotional. So,
I bought them for you.
That's pathetic.
Aunt's wedding was three days ago.
What is the point of coming now?
You said I'm a corporate snob.
You know I have work.
Emergency meetings.
But I'm here now.
And yes, one of my
friends is getting married.
I needed to get some
arrangements done.
You know tents, music bands,
and etcetera.
You've started some
wedding business, right?
Event management.
Are you making fun of you?
No, I'm not making fun of you.
All I want to say is that..
..everyone has their personal taste.
And it's not right to
interfere in their personal lives.
Give me one reason why
I should listen to you.
Because I'm bigger.
What?
Only your stomach's bigger.
- Hey, it's a 16-pack, okay.
Don't hold your breath
too long. Or you'll faint.
Aisha is jealous.
- No, I am not, Arjun.
Show yourself out. You
know where the door is.
So irritating,
annoying and self-involved.
It's okay to think
positively about yourself.
But to consider yourself the best?
What does he know about life? So
what if he's a Wharton graduate.
Who cares!
Lousy investment banker.
I was completely shocked yesterday..
..when aunt handed me your call.
Our uncles are such good friends.
So, it was obvious that
I'd invite you. - Aisha.
Where have you been? I've
been looking for you everywhere.
Pinky, Shefali. - Shefali,
Pinky is my best friend. - Hello.
Hi. - Hi. - By the way, the drawings
are really nice, aren't they?
Drawing?
- Thank you.
You know, I'm an artist as well.
That's why I did a
course in home decoration..
..at Bahadurgarh.
- Wow.
But I had to come here.
Time to get married.
My aunt is completely tensed.
You're here to get married?
It'll be real chaos if we
don't find a boy in Delhi.
And that too hi-fi (modern).
- Hi-fi.
So, you haven't found a boy yet?
- No.
Families come. They have
snacks and then leave.
And you know they
don't even send me a reply.
But there aren't any good guys left.
All the good guys
either are gay or.. Arjun.
I like this one.
- Him?
But don't worry, I will
find a nice boy for you.
You want to meet my friends.
That's Randhir.
Every mother in Delhi..
..wants her daughter to marry him.
- Really?
Randhir.
Hi.
Aisha, this is just too good.
- Thank you.
Sold. Sold.
We're constructing a
new hotel at Dariyaganj.
I'll put up all your
drawings in the lobby.
What finishing!
- Okay.
Randhir, meet Shefali.
She's a good artist as well.
Remember, at the wedding..
..you spilled wine on me.
- Oh, yes.
So sorry, really sorry.
My hair was messed up that day.
But I also wiped it.
- Sure.
Are you coming from
Chaddha's wedding?
You know Chaddha? I know Chaddha.
He's getting married today.
- Seeing your clothes..
..I could guess that you're
coming from Chaddha's wedding.
You're coming from the wedding.
- Randhir, hi. - Hi.
Congratulations, the artist.
- Thank you.
Hi, I'm Arjun.
- Shefali.
So, what do you think?
- You know what?
Very impressive.
If you keep practising like this..
..someday you'll
surely be a professional.
I.. I hope you lose your
polo match. - We'll see.
Aisha, you are coming, aren't you?
- Of course, I'm coming.
And Shefali is coming as well.
- Yes, please come.
You must come.
The dress code is western,
but you can wear anything.
Summer dress. Hat..
You can wear a hat.
Randhir, go get us some drinks.
Sure, sure.
- Thank you.
By the way, do we need to
wear something special..
..for the polo match?
Don't worry, we'll go shopping.
You've come to the right place.
I'll.. I'll see you later, bye.
Idiot.
Om.
Aisha, why are you getting
into this problem? - What problem?
Intentional interfering.
Poking your nose.
Why are you trying to
match two mismatches?
We can never turn this
pumpkin into Cinderella.
Aisha, why do you
want to do something..
..that no one else wants to?
- Let's do the 'Suryanamaskar' now.
I hate this yoga teacher's voice.
Isn't Mallika Sherawat a babe?
I mean she's from Hariyana as well.
There's something
called as grooming.
And Mallika Sherawat has something.
What does she have?
Just imagine what will happen..
..if we make her wear
Victoria's Secret thongs..
..and make her lie
on Venice Beach in LA?
What will happen?
Victoria Secret will shut down.
You're one in a million, Aisha.
You're so gorgeous, you
make others look pretty.
You think there should be
no evil in the world, Aisha.
You want to fill every
life with some colour.
Fill it.
You've set out to change
someone's life, Aisha.
Just tell us what this new hobby,
this obstinacy is.
You try to solve the
problems of others, Aisha.
Try to solve one of
your own problems.
Listen, Aisha. Try to understand.
Listen, Aisha. No matter
how much you desire it..
Listen, Aisha. No
matter how hard you try..
Listen, Aisha. There
won't be anyone like you.
She's easy to persuade.
She gets emotional.
First, try to
understand what love is.
It's crazy.
You do as you please.
You don't care about the world.
Aisha is one in a million.
She enters your
heart through your eyes.
Listen, Aisha. Try to understand.
Listen, Aisha. No matter
how much you desire it..
Listen, Aisha. No
matter how hard you try..
Listen, Aisha. There
won't be anyone like you.
Aisha.
- Yes.
What is this?
Credit card bill, Papa. - Yes, I
know it's the credit card bill.
But why is it so high?
If you spend money, they're
bound to send the bill, Papa.
So much?
- Rs.53,476.43 only.
Only! And what is 'Zest? '
'Zest', Papa. It's a nightclub.
I wanted Shefali to
experience the nightlife of Delhi.
So, I took her there. - But why
are you giving me sleepless nights?
And what is 'Ensemble? '
'Ensemble', Papa.
It's an exclusive boutique.
If you want to go to
a place like 'Zest'..
..you need to wear good clothes.
And poor Shefali
doesn't have good clothes.
I know, Papa, I should
understand the value of money.
Money doesn't grow on trees.
It's hard to earn.
It's difficult to earn money.
I know everything, Papa.
But for the last time..
..for the sake of Shefali.
Think of her as your daughter.
No, no, thank you very much.
- Two daughters are enough for me.
And if you keep
spending money like this..
..then there won't be any
money left for the wedding.
I don't want to get married.
- What?
I just want a live-in relationship.
I need to go now, Papa. Love you.
I know you love me but
I need to talk to you.
I hate this..
Yesterday, my aunt..
My aunt.
The one I came here with.
The one that was sitting
besides me at the wedding.
What's wrong with her?
- Oh, no. She's absolutely fine.
I was just saying that..
..she showed me
photographs of boys yesterday.
And you know some of
them were really sweet.
Tell me something..
..have you seen 'Kabhie Khushi
Kabhie Gham? ' -Yes, I have.
Why? - The dress Kareena
Kapoor has worn in that..
Its neither red nor maroon.
It's some amazing colour in-between.
I'll wear the same, exact
dress on my wedding day.
Will you help me get it?
- Of course, I will help you.
Thank you.
Only for me, though.
- Okay.
Promise.
Yes. Hello, girls.
I'll get the papers to you.
- Okay.
By evening.
- Okay. Thanks.
Bye.
- Yeah.
Excuse me.
- Excused.
Someone's got a
serious case of bitchitis.
The polo match passes.
- Yes.
Yes, in my office.
So, what do you think?
Isn't she looking cute?
I think, Aisha, let's
change Shefali's name.
Why?
You've changed her completely.
When you've given her a
personality like yours..
..then she should have
a similar name as well.
Let's think.
Aisha, Zaisha, Waisha.
Aisha. How about that?
Are you mocking me?
No, you're making fun of Shefali.
- How is that?
That is once upon a
time there was a Shefali.
And now, there's just
another copy of you.
What's wrong in that?
One of you is
enough to take on Delhi.
Stop it.
Get a job.
- What does that mean?
Are you satisfied by matchmaking?
Yes, I believe in social work.
What could be better than
making someone's life better?
And anyway, I don't
even take money for that.
What do you know about girls
anyway? - No, just about women.
Come on, Randhir.
Isn't he looking like the
Maharaja (King) of Jodhpur?
His pants are really strange.
They don't fit right.
They're called 'Jodhpuris.'
And he's looking very nice.
Well done, Arjun.
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Idiot
Its okay, it often
happens in polo matches.
Here. - Yes. - Thanks so much,
Shefali. Thanks.
Really.
Did you play hockey on the
horse for the first time?
No. Polo.
- Really?
Pinky, don't do that.
- Stop that noise.
You stop torturing animals,
otherwise I'll call PETA.
Come, meet my friends.
Pinky, let's go to the bar.
- Yes, let's go.
Everyone. Meet my friend
and colleague from New York.
Aarti.
- Aarti, this is.. everyone.
Well, hello, everyone.
- Hi.
How are you feeling now?
- Little injured.
There's a recession
going on in New York, right?
That's why people are
leaving New York and coming here.
Is that why you're here..
Ankita, right?
Ankita.
- No, it's Aarti.
Sometimes people return..
..because they miss their
family and friends. - Excuse me.
Okay.
Shefali, it's done.
- It's done? - Yes. - Are you sure?
Yes. Thanks, thanks.
Take care, Randhir.
- Thanks, Aisha.
Poor guy.
Aisha, will we die single?
- Please, Pinks.
We three. I'm single as well.
You lost.
You never told me
that we were racing.
You cry so much when you lose?
Come on, Arjun. Come on, Arjun.
What?
That New York returned.. Anita.
- No, it's Aarti.
Yes, whatever.
Something's burning.
What?
I can't believe this.
Aisha, are you mad?
This time around, I think you've
totally lost it. - Chill, Pinky.
You have to do it. - What do
you mean You have to do it?
Your plan is really risky, Aisha.
This is so going
to work, Pinky Bose.
Just watch.
Bye.
- Hello.
What's the name of the restaurant?
It must be around here.
It's a very nice restaurant.
It was right here.
- How long ago?
Two years ago, Randhir.
I'm going to kill her?
- Who?
She came here two weeks ago.
God. Oh, no. Oh, no.
Aisha, how can you
ever listen to Pinky?
You know her.
- Because she's my best friend.
Behave yourself, Randhir.
Best friend. Look.
There's no network.
- Can you please take a look inside?
Fine.
- Thank you.
But what's the name
of the restaurant.
Randhir, you'll know
that if you go inside.
Okay. Stay inside the car.
Aisha, close the doors.
Don't worry, go.
- Okay.
No network.
Wonder why Randhir
is taking so long.
Yes.
Shefali, go inside and take a look.
- I should go too?
Yes, go.
- Okay.
Go, Shefali.
- I'm going. - Yes.
There's no restaurant here.
You will only find
rooms in a guest house.
But.. there was one last week.
Sir, I can guarantee
you there hasn't..
..been one since
the last four years.
Ask why.
- Why?
Because for the last four years..
..I've been doing the
same job in this same place.
Pinky Bose.
If I don't teach you a lesson..
..my name isn't Randhir Gambhir.
There's no reception here.
Shefali, please call Aisha.
- Yes.
Please. - Fine, fine. -
This is too much. - Excuse me.
Excuse me.
- Yes.
Are you Randhir Gambhir?
- Yes. Why?
Restaurant. Here. 504,
there's a booking for you.
I have a booking?
- You're Randhir Gambhir? - Yes.
Look, we've a booking in your name.
Why would I book a room?
You would know that, sir.
- How would I know?
You don't know?
- I don't know.
- What don't I know?
Fine, pay up Rs.2500.
What for?
- Sir, I blocked the room for you.
Just a minute, just a minute.
- Learn to speak respectfully first.
Do you know who I am?
- Who are you?
The owner of Ever Supreme Sweets,
okay. - So, what should I do?
Do you want to open up a
branch here? Quietly pay my Rs.2500.
Saurabh.
- Saurabh.
Randhir. Randhir.
Aisha isn't outside.
- What?
I wonder where she went.
Where is she? - I don't know,
I looked everywhere for her.
What should we do now?
I have some money.
- It's okay.
Madam is with me right now.
I'll come again tomorrow. - Sir,
you're needlessly getting annoyed.
The room was booked.
- You could've used it for an hour.
Oh no.
Yes.
- I've a flat tyre.
Where?
- What do you mean Where?
Here, in Defence Colony.
Near the park close to aunt's house.
I'm in C.P. It'll take me at
least 45 minutes to reach there.
C.P.? What are you doing in C.P.?
What do you mean by What I am doing?
I don't know. Please come
here right now. Quickly.
Okay, look, that area isn't safe.
Just lock the doors and
stay in the car. I'm coming.
Listen, Arjun, I'm not going
to wait here for 45 minutes.
I'm walking to aunt's house.
- Aisha.
Is there something wrong?
- Yes, Aisha..
I have to go, do you mind?
- Okay.
Where did he hide?
He's almost left me behind.
Walk faster, Shefali.
- Fine.. fine.
Shefali, please.
Please. No one can walk that slowly.
I mean.. what do you think I am?
I'm wearing high heels and
mosquitoes are biting me.
And it's so late in the night.
- Relax, don't yell.
Aisha left me alone as well.
- Please.
I mean.. I want to go home. - I
mean.. - I want to go home as well.
I don't have any feelings,
isn't it? - No, no.
No emotions, isn't that it?
Just like that..
- Okay, fine.
Let's walk slowly.
- I don't want to go with you.
No. - I can understand.
I can understand everything.
- Please don't scream.
This is a dangerous place.
I surrender.
You can take whatever you want.
My Aunt?
Aisha?
Dhruv?
'Dhruv Singh,
colonel uncle's only son.'
'As a child, studious, spectacled,
bookworm and very boring.'
'And now, hello, hottie.'
Wow.
You were supposed to
come next week, isn't it?
Ok, I can always leave.
And come back next week?
- No, I didn't mean that.
I just meant that you know..
- Should I leave?
No. I mean..
- Kidding.
Aunt's asleep. Dad too.
Thankfully. We'll
get a chance to talk.
Come in.
Actually, Dhruv, I need your help.
I can't believe that you..
You're the same Dhruv that
would weep in grade school..
..for coming in second.
How do I convince you?
- I don't know.
So?
After all that hard work..
..will you at least
buy me a cup of coffee?
Sure.
So, is this our first date?
Do you want this to
be our first date?
Do you want me to want
this to be our first date?
I don't know.
Do you want me to want that you..
..want this to be our first date?
Absolutely.
- Okay.
Oh, you're alive.
Very funny.
Sorry.
You know who I met last night?
- Who?
Dhruv. At aunt's house.
We went for coffee.
After he changed my flat tyre.
Unlike others who
don't come on time.
Fine. Next time, call your
Dhruv when you need help.
I came there leaving my party.
By the time I reached,
you had already left.
Party?
Please. You're fast asleep
at 10 o'clock every night.
Hey.
Give me the remote.
- No.
Hi, Shefali.
Hi.
- Hi.
We're going to the
animal rights centre.
Animal rights centre?
What happened with you
and Randhir last night?
Nothing.
We couldn't find the
restaurant and you left as well.
We kept walking all night.
- Really.
How romantic.
Middle of the night,
beneath the stars.
It must have been fun.
It was fun, but my feet are hurting.
We're here. We're here.
We're here. Move.
- Doctor, a bike..
Saurabh.
Saurabh..
Shefali, you?
What are you doing here?
A bike ran over that poor thing.
So, I brought him here
at the Animal shelter.
Not Animal Shelter, its ARC.
- Yes, that.
You look like a true
Delhiite (Delhi resident).
And you? Have you
started modelling? - No.
Shefali.
Saurabh, I'll have to go.
- Yes.
Take care.
Who was he?
- Him.
He's my uncle's friend's son.
Saurabh Lamba.
What does he do?
He works in the BPO sector.
Oh, the people who
call us in the afternoon..
..and ask us whether we
need a credit card or a loan.
Come here.
How middle class..
Come on.
What is the animal rights centre?
- ARC.
I thought I should do
something for the animals.
Please. At least,
leave the animals alone.
No, nothing. I'm proud of you.
I love animals.
The poor things can't
stand up for their rights.
So, I thought I should
do something for them.
Maybe I should turn vegetarian.
Listen, Randhir is
organising a river-rafting trip.
Are you coming?
I don't know. I'll see.
Randhir is such a
nice boy, isn't it?
Poor Shefali will
look so good with him.
Both the poor things will
be so happy with each other.
Everyone is unfortunate for you.
- What?
I mean did you ask poor Randhir..
..and poor Shefali whether
they like each other or not?
Of course, they do. I know it.
You know everything.
What does that mean?
You're just dumping
your liability on Shefali.
Are you trying to say
that I am manipulative?
I just want to help them.
You need help, not them.
Arjun, I know that
you think I'm stupid..
..and that there's
no meaning to my life.
But that does not mean that
you constantly criticise me.
Stupid, fool!
Yesterday, he proposed to me.
Who? That mama's boy.
So soon.
When? How?
Last night, he called
and was getting emotional.
Last year we went for
a picnic to Manesar.
He was saying..
- Just a minute.
Who are you talking about?
Saurabh. The son of
my uncle's friend.
He was saying I should
say yes or no, first.
And then he'll talk
to aunt and uncle.
Saurabh!
Tell me what I should do?
It's your life.
Do whatever you want to. Lf
you don't value your life..
..then what can I do?
But where is the comparison
between Randhir and Saurabh
Shall we go home?
Aisha.
'Elle' magazine,
beauty editor, Pinky Bose.
And the weather report?
- Boring.
That chapter is closed.
Shefali.
- Yes.
You know, Randhir keeps
talking about you. - Really?
What was he saying?
He was saying, Shefali
is such a nice girl.
She's so hot, she's so fashionable.
Really, he..
Oh, no.
- Oh, my God.
Shefali, are you fine?
My foot.
Please don't bleed everywhere
- It's nothing, she's gone crazy.
Drama queen.
Get some ice.
Sant Ram. Sant Ram.
- Aisha, it's hurting.
How will I go to boating now?
Don't worry Shefali,
everything will be alright.
The boat will come
here to pick you up.
Randhir, stop it. I hate this song.
Shut up.
- Shut up.
Yes, shut up.
You know, Randhir, Shefali
twisted her ankle badly..
..but she still came.
- Really?
Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm fine now.
It was a slight sprain.
Yesterday..
- She fell five days ago.
Even if she had broken her
leg it would've healed by now.
Pinks, stop.
- It's true.
"This heart's made me useless."
Randhir, do you know the way?
- No.
No, I don't know anything.
I don't know the way. I even
don't know to drive a car.
You only know to
make sweetmeat balls.
Pinky, don't insult my family.
I bet, you.. - I don't know
to make sweetmeat balls.
If we reach there,
there won't be any camp.
Randhir, stop the car!
What's going on here?
- Why are you in my car?
Randhir, we're lost.
For the past one hour, we've
been going around in circles.
We're going to die here,
and it's all your fault.
You're a fool.
- Shut up, you ham.
You know, Pinky, you
look like a bouquet.
Where do you get your clothes from?
Do you make your
clothes from circus tents?
You're responsible
for all the problems.
I can't sit anymore -I need to pee
My back's killing me
- And you're driving me insane
Will it make you any less of a man..
..if you ask someone for directions?
Enough, Pinky. That's all.
Guys, I've got the directions.
I was begging you.
- Guys, I know the directions.
And Aisha, what are you doing?
Talking to
strangers in such a place.
It's dangerous.
Just a minute.
Here.
For your protection. Pepper spray.
My brother got it for everyone.
It's really good. It's very good.
Are we enacting a scene from a
period drama here? - Let's go.
Randhir, you could've
given this in the car.
Nonsense.
- Idiot.
I'm leaving, Pinky.
Sit in the car if you want
to otherwise I'm leaving.
Oh, boys.
Finally some fun in this jungle.
- Is it?
That's not a boy, that's Arjun.
Welcome Girls..
..And Randhir, hello.
- Hi.
Hi. - Hi.
- Hi, everyone. - Hi.. Ashima.
It's Aarti.
- Sorry.
You know what? I'll
see you in the tent.
All right, bye.
- Bye.
So, what are you doing here?
Lost your way to the mall?
- What?
You're looking nice, Shefali.
- Thank you.
Ready for the rapids?
- Rapids?
I'm a bit scared.
Don't be scared. It's very easy.
- I'll show you. - Okay. Come.
Don't worry. I am with you.
Randhir.
- Aisha, you left your bag.
Actually, Randhir.. this is for you.
Hey, that's me.
This is Shefali, isn't she?
Wow, Aisha. Thanks.
- You're welcome.
See you at the camp.
Game, set, match.
The evening's like a flowing river.
It's flowing like the waves.
It's narrating an untold story.
Somewhere.. desires are awakening.
Somewhere.. you and I are lost.
We both are intoxicated.
The ambience is serene.
The eyes are speaking.
Isn't it?
What is this moment?
What is this ambience?
The evening is fading away.
Everything's so beautiful.
Everything's so alive.
Life is bubbling.
There's a glittering
dream in every eye.
The winds hum a wonderful song.
We both are silent.
We both are intoxicated.
The ambience is serene.
The eyes are speaking.
Isn't it?
Aisha, is Saurabh
really not the right guy?
Shefali, it's your
choice to say yes or no.
But you tell me, Aisha. Please.
Shefali, you're a sensible girl.
It's your decision.
Fine, I'll say no to Saurabh.
Go back to sleep.
Okay, I'll say no to Saurabh.
Anyways, what
difference does it make.
What is your problem?
- What?
Shefali is going to
say no to Saurabh.
Who are you to
interfere in her personal life?
She asked me for my opinion
and I gave her, that's it.
Yes, but you're ruining her life.
The poor thing needed my help.
So, I just helped her.
God, Aisha, Poor thing, poor thing..
She isn't unfortunate.
She's not unfortunate,
understand that.
I'm not your project.
Just leave me alone.
So, you think that
spineless Randhir is right for her?
Nice.
You're an expert, aren't you?
A man who runs after a
New York returned wannabe.
You're so straight. So
straight that you can't even bend..
..down to tie your shoe laces.
So are you, Aisha.
And yes, better tell that
New-York-returned that..
..it's bad manners to eavesdrop.
Oh, my God. Shefali, Shefali.
- Randhir. Randhir, save her.
Do something.
- Why are you hitting me?
Randhir, go after her.
- Arjun's got her.
Shefali, don't worry.
Grab my hand. Don't worry.
She's fine, she's fine.
- Are you a fool?
She's all right. The water
is just three feet deep.
Relax, almost there.
I kept drifting, and
drifting and drifting afar.
And my entire life
flashed before my eyes.
I thought I'm going to die.
And all I thought was, God save me.
Please save me and I'll..
I'll completely change myself.
I'll.. turn into a really
nice person, promise. Really.
Finally, now, I've
learnt the value of life.
Such experiences
completely change life, don't they?
Yes, of course.
It's such a deep philosophy.
- Yes.
Deeper than the water she fell into.
Wrap this around you
or you'll catch a cold.
Arjun..
..you're braver than everyone
in the whole of Bahadurgarh.
You're my hero.
Guys, cheers.
Oh, no.
Are you okay?
- Yes. - Sure?
So The entire social scene of
Delhi is having a ball here.
Hi, everybody.
Hi, Aisha.
- Hi.
How are you?
- Good.
When did you get here?
I got it, I got it. I got it.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Lucky shot.
I got it, I got it. Good job.
Yes. Yes. Go and sit there.
Why are you threatening me?
Aisha.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
Caught you! - This is too much.
Are you mad, Pinky?
Have you gone crazy?
I'm not playing with this idiot.
- Randhir, let it go.
Forget it. She's crazy.
You play alone.
Nobody will play with you.
Aarti, want to join us?
Me?
- Yes.
Sure.
- Break her face.
Yes, yes, come on. Make
our team better-looking.
What the hell.
She can't play.
- Why not?
It is girls versus boys.
- And.
Let her play. We'll
teach her a lesson.
What's wrong? Scared?
Let's just play.
Come on.
Superb.
What a game, guys!
Pinky.. get water for me.
- Forget it, dear.
It's a game. Come on.
You okay?
- Perfect.
After such a nice night..
..beating you on the
volleyball court.. Come on.
No smiles left.
This is me.
I was thinking.. You know, we get..
- Aisha.
What's up, Dhruv?
- Hey.
Aisha, just a minute.
I need to tell you something.
- Sure.
Okay.
- Okay. - Goodnight. - Goodnight.
Hi.. Shall we go?
Aisha, just mind your head. Okay?
Actually, Aisha.
I was thinking of telling you
something for a long time, but..
Randhir, I know what
you're going to say.
And I'm very happy for you.
Really?
- Really.
Wow.
Randhir, what are you doing?
Randhir, are you crazy?
- Yes, Aisha.
But I'm crazy for you.
Aisha, I love you.
No, you love Shefali.
Shefali? No, Aisha. I love only you.
I always follow you.
I do so much for you.
You never felt anything?
- Felt.. what?
What's wrong with you, Randhir?
You even took that sketch from me.
I took that sketch
because you made it for me.
Of me. Finally, you
made something for me.
And.. Shefali?
What have I got to do with Shefali?
She's so uncool.
What do you mean uncool? '
She's got more style than you.
Don't be an idiot, Randhir.
- Aisha.
Aisha.
Aisha, please.
Aisha, I know you love me
just as much as I love you.
Tonight, under these stars
and amidst these valleys..
..we should be one, Aisha.
Let's just do it.
Randhir, I won't do
anything with you..
..even if you are
the last man on earth.
God Aisha, my eyes!
Sorry, did the hero get hurt?
- No, and you?
What happened?
Nothing.
Randhir was only asking
about the fuel expenses.
I see.
Didn't he say anything else?
What else could the poor guy do?
He was tired.
He just went off to sleep.
Goodnight.
I was thinking..
..why didn't he jump
into the water to save me?
Come out whoever's inside.
If you're suffering from
diarrhea then come out and do it.
I need to go now!
- It's me.
Randhir!
Oh, no. It'll take 40 minutes now.
What's wrong?
Suffering from constipation?
Fine, don't tell me.
Pinky.
She said no.
- Who?
Shefali?
Shefali. Shefali. How does
her name come up every time?
Aisha. I love Aisha.
Sorry.
Come on, it happens.
It happens.
Everything will be fine.
Nothing's going to
be fine, Pinky. Okay?
No one likes me.
I'll remain single
all my life, that's it.
Join the club.
Did you check the tent?
I didn't check your tent.
- You should've told me.
Keys.
- Yes, thanks.
Shefali.
- Yes.
You're coming with us.
- No, but Arjun..
These are your bags, right?
- But.. - That's my bag.
Come on.
- Aisha. - Get inside.
I'm going with Dhruv.
There are already
two people in that car.
Sit in. - Aisha, come back.
- See you in Delhi, Pinks.
You go in the other car.
You're coming with me?
- Yes.
Oh, yes.
Just a second.
So, Pinky, it's just you and me.
Come on.
- It's destiny.
Hey, you like R.D. Burman as well?
Me too.
Are you fine?
- Absolutely.
Absolutely fine.
I can't believe Randhir
did that to me in Rishikesh..
Poor Shefali.
Oh, God. Aunt, I'm such a big idiot.
What now?
Why didn't I see it before?
But I always felt it.
- Really?
At times, things are right in
front of us but we don't see it.
It's okay, honey. Don't worry.
What's done is done,
Aunt, but I've decided..
..I'm not going to
do matchmaking again.
Don't blame yourself.
You just wanted to
do good for someone.
I know, Aunt.
But Arjun is
fighting with me as well.
So, what's new in that?
What will I tell Shefali now?
Tell her the truth.
Just be gentle, okay.
Shefali.
Shefali, Randhir's an idiot.
Shefali, I made a mistake.
In fact.. a big one.
Oh, my God.
It's okay.
I'm so sorry.
Did you see the photographs..
- Chopsuey.
It's Randhir's favourite, isn't it?
The American one.
Oh, my.
Blue.
That's Randhir's favourite colour.
That's.. Aisha, isn't that Randhir?
That's Randhir on television.
Poor Juliet.
Romeo ran away in
the first Act itself.
Hi, Arjun.
Hi, Shefali, Pinky.
- Hi.
Where's uncle?
- In the backyard.
Can I have some popcorn?
Why are you ignoring me?
Ignore? Who's ignoring you?
- You are.
Are you a kid?
Actually, I'm not a child.
But you've grown up.
Don't think I've
come here to apologise.
I didn't think that
you're here to apologise.
What if I am?
Then you can.
Sorry.
Aisha, I can't ignore
you even if I want to.
Because you're always in my face
What can I do? Where are
you taking me? I've to work.
Beautiful.
What colour is it?
- Green.
Mine?
- Red.
Mine is better than yours.
Really.
Aisha, I met Saurabh.
The one I keep talking about,
Saurabh Lamba.
Where?
- I was crossing the road..
..when suddenly a bus appeared..
'Aunt. I.. '
'Oh, no.'
'Careful.'
'Your.. sandal is safe.'
I swear I thought I'd
surely lose my sandal that day.
But then I said..
'Thank you, Saurabh.'
'You know it's my favourite sandal.
- Really? '
'I bought it at Janpath.
- I see.'
'Yes!
'Thank you.
- No, it's a very nice sandal.'
'Buy one for me too if you
find one for boys. - Yes.'
'I play football here everyday.
- Really? '
'With my friends.'
Aisha, isn't he sweet?
He's also romantic.
Look. Shefali..
..just because a stupid
boy didn't appreciate you..
..it doesn't mean
you walk away with..
..the next guy that comes around.
You will find a nice boy.
There surely is a sweet and
lovable boy for you somewhere.
You just have to be patient.
- Really?
For sure.
I want to play squash..
- Do you have an insurance?
Give me one more like this.
Paste it in it.
I like this.
Aisha!
Should we talk to
Randhir about the website?
He has done web-designing.
Pinky, there's a huge difference..
..between operating a
deep fryer and a website.
Just imagine what would be written..
..on the poster that he designs.
Come one come all
- Elastic pants a must.
That's really nice.
- Is it? I made it.
There's a party at
Chaddha's farmhouse tomorrow night.
Shall we go?
- Of course.
Dancing is always fun.
- Yes, I like dancing too.
But we had planned a
girl's night out tomorrow.
Aisha, shall we
invite Arjun as well?
Then we'll have to
invite Aarti as well.
But Aisha..
Guys.
- So what, Pinky?
If we all go together it
will be fun. - It will be fun.
What's wrong with you?
- Spit it out. Are you a dog?
Sorry, I can't come tomorrow.
- I've a lot of work to do.
Interviews, you know.
You got a job at 'Elle.'
Look, I'm going to go now.
What's wrong with her?
She's strange, isn't she? - She
always seemed a bit strange to me.
A bit jealous.
And she wears such
strange clothes, doesn't she?
Where should we put this up?
Here?
Only.. only..
Those capricious eyes
make my heart restless.
So this is love.
The wait.. makes me impatient.
Memories torment the heart.
The breath feels heavier.
Eyes are filled with dreams.
You're scared to say it.
Nights are sleepless.
Frantically you feel
like its slipping away.
Let it happen.
Fall in fall.
"Just move it."
If your eyes search
for a beautiful face.
With a desire.
So you're destination is love.
With your heart in tow.
The heart seems like melting away.
The body smolders.
The heart beats and
gives rise to desires.
You lose your senses once you
fall in love. - Let it happen.
Fall in love
Those capricious eyes
make my heart restless.
So this is love.
The wait.. makes me impatient.
Memories torment the heart.
The breath feels heavier.
Eyes are filled with dreams.
You're scared to say it.
Nights are sleepless.
Frantically you feel
like its slipping away.
Let it happen.
Fall in fall.
Thanks.
Give me a drink.
Hi.
- Hi.
I hope you're serious about Aisha.
Why are you so concerned?
If it concerns Aisha,
it concerns me.
Don't play with her feelings
Come on, Arjun. We both
can share her as well.
Oh God..
What's up.
Oh my God, Dhruv.
- Is he okay? - Dhruv..
You act as the most
sensible one around.
What's wrong with you, Arjun?
Are you okay?
- Yes, ma'am.
Thank you, Aunt.
Don't worry, dear.
It's a minor wound.
I know, aunt.
Do you like Dhruv?
He's just a good friend.
- That's all.
Nothing more.
- Aunt.
Aunt, you know..
..I thought when I start liking
someone it'll change my world.
It'll change me.
Aisha, love is not a tempest..
..that will change worlds.
It's in the little touches of life.
It is good, isn't it?
- Yes, it is.
I didn't have any training
but everyone says that I give..
..the best massages in the world.
- First-class massage.
Very nice. - Want me to
do it harder? - A little.
Want some salad?
Yesterday.. Shefali
and I were with Dhruv.
And Shefali was applying
ice on Dhruv's forehead..
..and he was smiling so much.
He was looking so cute.
Papa, no..
Dhruv couldn't come. - He had
to go for golf. - Hello, Uncle.
Hi.
- How are you doing? -
Hello, son.
- Aunt Chitra.
Aisha baby. - Late again.
- Yes, I'm really sorry.
Aisha invited me to
lunch for the first time..
..and didn't even wait for me.
You're a part of our
family and not a guest.
You didn't bring Aarti along.
You didn't ask me
to bring her along.
Anyway, she's busy.
The poor thing must
have lots of work.
Sant Ram, get some white
butter for Arjun Baba.
Baba Arjun -Little Arjun.
- Right away. - Get it quickly.
Uncle.
Aisha Baby doesn't like it
when someone else gets importance.
What do you mean?
- Let him eat, dear.
Arjun, why don't
you bring Aarti home?
Why not tomorrow for
'Diwali' (festival) dinner?
Yes, yes.
- That's good.
We'll get to meet her.
- Yes, yes.
This is a good idea.
Beloved keeps me awake all night.
He troubles me.
My beloved troubles me,
doesn't listen.
He troubles me.
Beloved keeps me awake all night.
Wonderful.
Excuse me.
She sings well, doesn't she?
Please. It seems like some parents..
..are showing off their
child who's in kindergarten.
Baby, read out a poem for uncle.
Baby, dance on the 'Kajra Re' song.
Baby, go drown
yourself in the river.
What's wrong with the
ever-optimistic Aisha?
I've never seen this
cynical side of yours.
You haven't seen anything yet.
Arjun, ask the
driver to drop me home.
I'll drop you.
- No, it's okay.
I'll drop you. It's Delhi, Aarti.
Thank you.
- Welcome.
Where did these two go?
Is there a curfew in Delhi..
..that she can't go home alone?
Why didn't Pinky come?
- I don't know, Aunt.
Pinks, I didn't tell you earlier..
but I really, really love you.
Me too.
Come in.
Look what you made me do.
What?
Sorry.
What do you want?
I want to apply that
pink nail polish. - What?
I'm here to talk to you, what else?
Why? Did you find some time
from selling Aarti's CD's?
That's what I'm here to tell you.
- You buy one as well.
Why not? I believe in charity.
I can donate 200 Rupees for charity.
You're so smart, Aisha.
I heard that Dhruv
is going to Mumbai.
What will you do now?
What do you mean?
Who will you play squash with?
You were here to say something.
- Yes.
I want to talk to you.
- What?
Randhir got engaged.
Really?
- Who's the unfortunate one?
Why did you hide it from me?
Because you aren't
interested in my life.
You've other
important projects in life.
Shefali. Dhruv.
There are so many people.
I'm not interested.
What should I be
interested in, Pinky?
That my best friend
hid the truth from me..
That she's going to
marry a person..
..she kept insulting every time.
No, no, just stay. - I'll
just be back from the bathroom.
See, that's why I
didn't want to tell you.
Why do you feel that
only you are right?
Instead of being
happy for your friend..
..you're being judgemental.
I'm being judgemental?
But isn't this what you wanted?
The only difference
is that this South..
..Delhi circus
tent is marrying him..
..instead of that
villager from Haryana.
What nonsense are you talking?
Little Ms. Perfect, Aisha.
Who roams around
with her ugly friends..
..to make herself look better.
The truth hurts, doesn't it?
At least..
..I don't control others'
lives to assert my rights on them.
Now, please, you may leave.
Hey, are you okay?
Pinks, why are you crying?
I was being insulted. So,
why are you crying?
First, you did it,
and now she's doing it.
Come on, come on.
Randhir is getting married now..
..so I have some of
his memories, few things.
But I want to forget him.
I want to destroy everything.
- Okay.
Which memories do you have
with Randhir? - No, please.
Stay close to me.
Anyhow.
What is this?
This umbrella.
It was in his drink
on the polo ground.
It's very difficult to
forget all this, Aisha.
You know, this is from
the river-rafting camp.
He was scribbling something alone.
I kept it safely.
Look, it's so beautiful, isn't it?
Look.
And this CD.
When we were
traveling to Rishikesh..
I took it from his car.
Shefali, calm down.
Dhruv is going to Mumbai
tomorrow and we're going as well.
You didn't tell me
anything about our plan..
..to go to Mumbai.
Saurabh.
- Hi, Shefali.
Papa.
- Yes, dear.
Aisha, he's Saurabh.
Our Accountant's son.
- Hello. - Hi.
Papa, Shefali and I
are going to Mumbai.
Mumbai? - I want to stay with
Aaliya till she goes into labour.
Labour? Aaliya?
Papa, not now.
This girl keeps
scaring me all the time.
Hey, sit down.
Shefali.
You are going to like it.
They know everything.
What is this?
Hey Aisha! Where are you going?
We are coming along.
You guys carry on.
I'll be right back.
Tell me something.
Dhruv is a nice boy, isn't he?
- He is.
And handsome too.
- Yes.
Any girl would be very happy
with him? - Yes, any girl.
Make an exception.
More difficult thing to do.
Good morning, Sleeping Beauty.
Surprising, you
woke up before midday.
Arjun, you are here?
Did you get bored
in Delhi without us?
Aisha, say hello first.
Then ask me how am I doing
to which I'll reply I'm fine.
Let's start from there.
Hello, Arjun. How are you doing?
- I'm fine. How are you?
Perfectly fine.
So, Arjun, did you get
bored in Delhi without us?
That's not it.
- I'm going to be an uncle as well.
I won't miss this for the world.
It is full.
- Excuse me, guys.
Shefali, how do you like Mumbai?
I'm having fun.
And especially, your apartment.
It's really nice. - Thank you.
Yes, Aaliya. Dhruv is
spending so much time with us.
We're having a lot of fun.
You know, today, we're going
for lunch with Dhruv to the Taj.
And then we're going to
the mall for shopping.
Good morning, everyone.
- Morning.
Shefali, let's go.
- But let me finish breakfast.
Hi. - Hi. - How are you?
How is the baby?
Can I pour you some coffee?
By the way.. - Yes. - The
client cancelled. - Why?
Come on.
Five down.
Five more.
No, no.
- Yes, yes, yes,
Enough, enough.
- Yes, yes, yes.
Are you okay?
I need to go to the bathroom.
Okay.
Hi, guys.
- Hi.
Are you okay, Shefali?
- Toilet.
Aarti, I'll just be back.
Better?
Are you okay?
Aisha.
Can I say something?
- Yes.
I'm in love.
- I know.
Really? - Don't worry.
I'll take care of everything.
Leave everything to me.
Should we leave?
How am I looking?
Perfect.
I'll take her to the car.
- Fine.
I'll be right back.
- Yes.
Dhruv.
I liked you.
But you didn't show
any interest in me.
It's okay.
Life moves on.
I hope you find what
you're looking for.
I'm sorry.
- Forget it.
Shefali.
I want to tell you something.
Shefali, Dhruv's an idiot.
- What?
First, he tried to flirt with me.
- And when I didn't respond..
..he went straight for Aarti.
We'll find a better guy for you..
- No, Shefali. I'm so sorry.
First, Randhir, and now, Dhruv.
But it isn't your mistake. It's
okay. - It's entirely my fault.
How could I think that
Dhruv and you would be happy?
Dhruv and I?
I thought you and
Dhruv would be happy.
Aisha, I love someone else.
- Who?
The one who is the best.
The one I danced with for
the first time in my life.
The one who looks after me.
And has a dimple here, just like me.
He also saved me
from drowning, my hero.
Arjun?
But Shefali, you and
Arjun are different.
He's not your type.
Why?
- You two are so different.
You're not his type, Shefali.
I need to brush.
What do you mean by different?
Aisha, what do you
mean by different?
Because I don't wear
good clothes like you do.
Because I don't speak
English like you do.
My father isn't as rich as you are.
I'm middle-class.
- No.
Because I'm a villager, right?
- No, I..
What are you saying?
- You're misunderstanding. - No.
I understand everything, Aisha.
You never considered me your friend.
What are you talking about,
Shefali? - I'm just a project.
Cut that poor thing's hair.
Give that poor thing some clothes.
Take that poor thing to Mumbai.
What?
- Shefali, Randhir is nice.
No, Shefali. Randhir isn't nice.
Shefali, Dhruv is nice.
No, Shefali. Dhruv isn't nice.
Enough, Aisha.
You never considered
me an equal to you.
Isn't it, Aisha?
One more thing.
Arjun loves me as well.
What?
If you don't believe me
then you can ask him..
Aisha. Aisha.
Aisha, get ready. We're
going to the hospital.
Congratulations, it's a baby girl.
- Really.
I have to go to the hospital.
But don't worry, the
driver will drop you.
She's so cute.
Anushka, that's nice.
Take good pictures of Anushka.
Anushka or Sameera?
Didn't I say Sameera?
But Ann is cuter than Sam.
Hi, guys.
Hi.
- Hi. - Hello.
And here comes uncle Arjun.
Smile, Arjun.
Ann hasn't peed on you yet.
Why are you sulking?
May I?
- Please.
So cute.
Welcome to the family.
You sent Shefali back to Delhi.
- I didn't send her back.
It's not like you think it is.
You had found a new hobby.
A new game..
..other than shopping and
spending your daddy's money.
Why are you favouring Shefali?
Because Aarti left you?
You stay in your own
little bubble, don't you?
Shefali is my friend.
She's my friend.
You use your friends, understand.
That's not very nice. - I was
just trying to help her. - How?
By making her shallow like you.
Shallow.
You think I'm shallow.
You've so much potential, Aisha.
There's so much you can do in life.
But everyday, you
develop a new hobby.
Social service or animal rights.
Have you ever taken
anything in your life seriously?
Your life is very deep, isn't it?
The way Shefali is
my project, I'm yours.
Have you ever thought
anything about nice about me?
You know what? I
don't know you anymore.
I thought I understood you..
..but now, I feel I
can never understand you.
No, Arjun. You
understand only Shefali.
Get in.
I'm going to Delhi.
I'm so lost.
Why is my heart in such a condition?
The dreams have faded.
Thoughts are confused.
The flowers have withered.
But their colours
still prevail in my memory.
All the sand-castles..
Were washed away by the waves.
My path was so
enlightened yesterday.
My path was filled with flowers.
Who do I say it to?
There's no one to listen to.
Why did I choose pain?
Why have I lost dreams?
But my pain is still alive.
The flowers have withered.
But their colours
still prevail in my memory.
All the sand-castles..
Were washed away by the waves.
My first grandchild.
My heart is sad.
No one's close or far.
It's not the same anymore.
The days and nights
don't feel the same.
The past seems like a dream.
My heart is restless.
The flowers have withered.
But their colours
still prevail in my memory.
Hello.
Thank you, thank you very much.
You've got the job.
You've to join next week.
Pinky, I..
- Aisha, I..
May I speak first?
Pinky, you're my best friend.
And I don't want to lose you.
I really miss you.
I know you'll never forgive me.
I'm very selfish.
- Yes.
And self-centred too.
And slightly arrogant.
- Slightly?
I missed you too, Aisha.
I was absolutely wrong.
I'm very sorry.
It's okay, Aisha.
I was wrong as well.
I should've told you.
Randhir is a really nice guy.
- I Know.
Actually, I'm not the most
beautiful girl in the world.
I'm not the smartest as well.
But for him, I am.
You're very lucky.
You don't know how lucky you are.
Aisha, life isn't that simple.
This isn't a fairytale, it's Delhi.
They are no rainbows, only smog
If you can see one clear
star in the sky at night..
..then that's more than enough.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
- Me too.
Hi, Saurabh.
- Hi, Aisha.
These papers are for sir..
I'm sorry.
Sorry for what?
Just like that.
You're very nice.
Thanks.
Saurabh.
- Sir.
Give it, give the papers quickly.
Where are my spectacles?
- Sant Ram, get my spectacles.
Daddy.
Aisha, I'm so happy.
Dhruv is getting married.
Dhruv and Aarti.
It's so surprising.
But they look very
nice together, don't they?
It's your turn next.
Aunt. I want to say something.
Yes, tell me.
Did you meet Arjun?
- Yes.
He's on his way here.
Why? What happened?
Aunt, I..
Give it to him, son.
- Hi, Aunt. - Hi.
Hi, Aisha.
Tea.
- No, thanks.
How was Mumbai?
- Good.
Aisha, did you meet Shefali?
- No.
Why?
- Just like that.
Aunt, I have to go.
- Where?
I just need to go.
Take care, dear.
We'll talk whenever you want.
Okay?
- Okay.
Bye.
Bye, Arjun.
- Bye.
Sant Ram.
Papa.
- Aisha, you?
Papa, dessert? - I felt
like having something sweet.
Me too. Give me some.
Don't you want to go to Mumbai?
- No, I do.
Look, don't go if you don't want to.
You won't get such
delicious dessert there.
No, Papa. That's not it.
Then what is it?
12 o'clock in the night
sharing a dessert with papa.
Hey, is everything
all right with you?
Papa, I think I'm in love.
You think, or you are?
I don't know. I don't know.
I really, really don't know.
- I really, really don't know.
It's 100% love.
Now, tell me who is he?
Who is he?
It's Dhruv, isn't it? That dude.
- No, Papa.
Then who is he?
School friend?
Someone you met in Mumbai.
Then who is it?
No. It can't be Randhir Gambhir.
No, no. Impossible..
No, Papa.
- Then who is it?
Arjun.
Arjun? Our child.
Wow! Wonderful!
What a correct choice!
Very good. I'm very happy.
Tell me when did this happen.
Just now.
- Just now?
Did you tell him?
- No.
Then call him right away.
But Shefali?
- Shefali?
That Bahadurgarh girl.
Come on, I've known
Arjun since his childhood.
If you aren't made for Randhir..
..then Shefali can't be
made for Arjun as well.
Call him. - But Papa, he's at
Dhruv and Aarti's engagement.
Then you go along as well. Go on.
No.
- Look..
..it's very important to
express your feelings, honey.
You have to, honey.
I know, Papa.
But what if he.. says no?
A beautiful,
compassionate, kind, caring..
..and sweet girl like you.
Only a fool would say no.
Look, honey.
Kapoors don't brood.
We believe in action.
Get up, my brave girl.
And go tell him that you love him.
- Okay.
Go. Get up. Run.
- Okay, okay.
"Are you ready now!"
"Here we go!"
- Keys.
I love Arjun.
"By the way. All the way."
"The life that we have got."
"It sings. It laughs."
"It's a bit crazy."
"We fight. We kiss and make up."
"It's new every moment."
"It's moody. It's stubborn."
"I have no idea
what to do about it."
"You can't stop us."
"We fly like the breeze."
"That's our life."
"That's our style. What to do?"
"If someone minds, what to do?"
"Everyone's upset with us now."
..will sing next song..
I welcome on to the
stage Rocky Bhatia.
Don't want to run..
Excuse me.
Sorry, it's urgent.
Arjun.
Arjun, I know you're here.
And you don't want to talk to me.
But I want to tell you something.
For myself and my peace of mind.
Remember when I
broke the hotel window..
..with the cricket ball at Kasauli.
You said it's your fault.
When I broke papa's golf clubs..
When I failed in chemistry..
You said It's all right.
And you turned my 'F' into 'A.'
And during Aaliya's wedding..
..when I mixed
vodka into the punch..
..you took the blame.
You would cover up all my mistakes.
And scold me when we would be alone.
And I would quarrel with you.
But Arjun, you were with me
in every mistake, every game.
You alone were with me.
Arjun, you've shown me
the right path in life.
You've shown me the
difference between wrong and right.
You taught me to
endure and to understand.
abide by friendship.
And also to love.
Arjun, if I lose you,
I will lose myself.
Please.
Please don't let me lose myself.
This is called love.
You've made me emotional.
If only people could
understand love the way you do..
..then everything will
be fine, it'll be perfect.
By the way, you've given us
the best wedding gift ever.
The Best.
By the way.. Who are you?
- Aisha?
I'm Bunty Kumar and
this is my wife Gurpreet.
By the way, are you
from his side or mine?
Whose marriage is this?
Call Arjun.
Arjun is here.
I'm Arjun.
Your Arjun is right here.
I'm Arjun as well.
Aisha.
I heard everything you said.
I saw you entering the wrong room.
I followed you, but..
I'm so sorry, Shefali.
For all I've done.
I hope.. I hope you
two stay happy together.
Aisha, it's very
difficult to find love.
But if you do find it,
then you shouldn't let it go.
Shefali, let's go. The
car is here. Quickly.
Bye.
You're going to Mumbai tomorrow?
You should've told me.
Why didn't you tell me?
Will you come down
or should I come up?
Poor neighbours.
Why?
- Why?
Because this ladder
has rotted in the rain.
If I slip, I'll land on my head.
Why, Arjun?
- Because I want to say something.
What?
Aisha..
..you taught me to laugh and cry.
You taught me to
endure and to understand.
You taught me to abide
by friendship and to love.
You know.
You won't come down, will you?
Fine, I'm coming up.
But Shefali..
- Shefali left with Saurabh.
How?
I've learnt some
matchmaking from you.
But you love Shefali, don't you?
I love someone else
with my heart and soul.
It's you. Only you.
And it always was you.
- Really?
Really.
I loved you..
..when you broke your
papa's golf clubs in Nehru Park.
I loved you..
..when you made everyone's
life a mess with your acts.
Even when you got rude
because of your jealousy for Aarti.
And even when..
..you fought with me on
the sofa for the remote.
Even when we danced the
whole night in the party.
And also when I gave
you a lift in my car..
..on the rainy night in Mumbai.
That day, today and always..
i've loved only you.
I love everything about you.
Your eyes.
Your piggy nose.
Your hands.
Everyone makes mistakes.
We fight so that we
can make up later.
My existence depends on you.
If I lose you, I'll lose myself.
I love you.
- I love you too.
Want to go?
- Let's go.
'And a year later, on
Dhruv and Aarti's marriage.. '
'.. I grew a year older and wiser.'
'So, Shefali got Saurabh,
Dhruv got Aarti.. '
'.. and Pinky got Randhir.'
'And me. I realized.. '
'.. that love cannot
be planned by anyone.'
'You cannot assert love on someone.'
'You just fall in love.'
'Anywhere, anytime.'
'And with anyone.'
Let the drums play.
Say something sweet.
Let me hear it.
Let the drums play.
Fill my life with joy.
Come, dance with me.
Love's unique.
The heart's invaluable.
Don't compare it with wealth.
Let me adorn you with
the glitter of the moon.
Let me bring you
home in a palanquin.
Say something sweet.
Let me hear it.
Let the drums play.
Come, dance with me.
Your fatal attitude.
It's mesmerizing.
Your vibrant skin
shines like the moonlight.
I can't get enough of you.
It makes me restless.
I would steal you
away from the world.
Surrender my life to you.
Say something sweet.
Let me hear it.
Let the drums play.
Come, dance with me.
Fill my life with joy.
Love's unique.
The heart's invaluable.
Don't compare it with wealth.
Let me adorn you with
the glitter of the moon.
Let me bring you
home in a palanquin.
I love you.
Look at me once.
If you look at me once I
will thank God thousand times.
Look at me once.
I will dedicate my life to you.
I love you so much. You
couldn't know it till now.
Say something sweet.
Let me hear it.
Let the drums play.
Fill my life with joy.
Come, dance with me.
Love's unique.
The heart's invaluable.
Don't compare it with wealth.
Let me adorn you with
the glitter of the moon.
Let me bring you
home in a palanquin.
Say something sweet.
"Are you ready now?"
"Here we go."
"By the way. All the way."
"The life that we have got."
"It sings. It laughs."
"It's a bit crazy."
"We fight. We kiss and make up."
"It's new every moment."
"It's moody. It's stubborn."
"I have no idea
what to do about it."
"You can't stop us."
"We fly like a free bird."
"That's our life."
"That's our style. What to do?"
"If someone minds, what to do?"
"Everyone's upset with us now."
"Just forget it."
"The story of my heart.."
"..I want to tell openly now."
"You can't forget it
if you hear it once."
"This age is dangerous."
"It drives you crazy."
"You will know if you will
think why we chose this path."
"By the way. All the way."
"When it's the
friendship from the heart.."