Some people have money
written in their fate.
For some, it's love.
For some, fame.
Hey, Champak!
What are you doing?
I'm wondering whether I should
play on my front foot or back?
But in my fate was written...
Confusion!
Champak, what will you
become when you grow up?
Inspector?
Bandit?
Lawyer?
I was so confused...
...that it was easier to remember
the moments when I wasn't confused.
And these rare moments
occurred only thrice in my life...
The first time was when I saw Rashi.
I had no confusion at all.
I want to continue
studying after marriage.
I'll buy you the books you want.
No, I mean a post-graduation degree.
What for?
We have a sweet shop.
You can be the boss there.
The second time was when
I held my daughter in my arms.
I had no confusion at all.
Don't worry...
...It'll be a boy next time.
I always wanted a daughter.
I only wished for
her to be like Rashi.
But Rashi passed on and
once again I was confused
Whether to be the girl's father,
mother or friend.
What should I be?
Papa, shall I use
a hairclip or a hairband?
Hairband.
That pulls my hair
Then the hairclip?
I don't like clips.
Papa, when will we
go see the Eiffel Tower?
Dreams are of two kinds.
Some that fade away like
mine of becoming a cricketer.
We'll go, we'll go.
And some end up becoming
the ultimate goal of one's life....
...like Taru's obsession
of going to a foreign country.
It was beyond me.
- Papa?
- Yes darling?
When will we go meet the Queen?
We'll go, we'll go.
- Papa?
- Yeah?
When will we go to Hollywood?
We'll go, we'll go.
But when?
When you grow up. C'mon.
Silence.
C'mon. Let's go.
I didn't think then that
one day she'd grow up.
And her mad obsession
would be the third time
when I would have no confusion...
What was unimaginable
was the bizarre journey...
...I would have to
undertake to get there.
Hello...
Good morning.
Why don't you open your shop on time?
Why don't you mind your own business?
Hail Lord Ram!
None of you are worth
using the family name.
Excuse me, is this the GHA-SI-TE-RAM?
Yes. Yes. First original Ghasiteram.
What's first original?
This is first original.
Oh, this shop.
Mr. Foreigner! Mr. Foreigner!
That is a fake one.
This is the original one.
He's lying.
I'm not lying, he is.
- Check the Lonely Planet.
- This is my shop.
- Oh, this
- Come on in.
Hot oil trick!
That's no trick...
I can do it too, let me show you.
This way, please.
- This is the original one.
- No, no.
You'll come again and again. Try it.
No, not from his hands.
His hands are dirty.
You'll get diarrhea, hepatitis...
or maybe die.
You called my sweets shit?
I said your hands have shit on them
You called my sweets shit!
Now try your trick on him. Go ahead.
- Not like the shit you make.
- Go, get your act together.
These cheap tricks won't help you
Go dip your head in it.
What the...
Champak,
isn't that Gajodhar's son, Ankit?
What's he doing there?
That bloody...
Try it.
What are you upto, Bheluram?
Mind your own business...
You can't even handle a customer.
Atleast I have customers.
Why don't you mind your own business,
you're not getting any, clearly.
I have customers coming
from all over the world.
Why don't you sell me Ghasiteram?
I'll make it an International brand.
No thanks. We have too
many branches in Rajasthan.
Need to shut some down.
Listen, you are a Chandiram
and that's all you will be.
However big you make your shop,
you can't be a Ghasiteram.
Because I'm the only
Ghasiteram, get it?
You come with me.
You really think you
can buy the Ghasiteram name?
Seriously?
Son, however much we
fight within our family,
we will never do
business with Chandiram...
Where are you going?
Where are you running off to?
Huh...
What were you doing at Chandiram's?
He gave me a decent offer.
I'll give you one rap,
and if your father found
out he'd give you another.
You're not the only Ghasiteram.
I'm also one.
He was my great grandfather.
I'll do whatever I want
Wow! You'll do whatever you want?
Aah.. Uncle, it hurts.
Hello grandpa.
Grandpa, please keep your glasses on
or everyone will get conjunctivitis.
- Where are you?
- I'm here.
- Let's go.
- Aah.. Uncle.
Look at this, our family tree.
You'll find everyone's
photo here except Chandiram's.
Do you know why?
He didn't like being photographed?
No, you idiot.
Listen...
Once upon a time in 1920...
A ruthless British officer
got a craving for Indian sweets
in the middle of the night
and wondered where to go.
He landed up at Ghasiteram's
...but our great grandfather
did not let him set foot in the shop.
He kicked him out.
And do you know what he said?
- What did he say?
- What?
Oi my foreign brother...
It's my business to sell sweets...
...but my loyalty to the
country is not for sale.
- Woah! What a line!
- Bravo.
Yeah but his brother
Chandiram was an ass-licker.
He took the British to his shop and
fed them all the sweets they wanted.
That's why there's no
place for him in this house!
And look at you, your great
grandfather would be ashamed of you.
The court date is out,
you're coming right?
Of course, no doubt.
C'mon get going.
Studying?
Is this the wrong house?
Where's my daughter Taru?
Go on, you also make fun of me.
Who else made fun of my daughter?
The Principal.
Don't talk about that witch.
Never gives a single day off...
We could never go for
any of the family weddings
And now she won't let me go to the UK.
UK? Uttarakhand?
Not Uttarakhand Papa,
the United Kingdom, England.
Our school has a tie
up with Truford University.
The top 3 rankers will
get a placement there.
I went to the Principal
asking for details...
...and she told me
not to stress about it,...
...only if 30 kids don't want to go,
you might get a chance.
Okay.
Tell me the part where
she made fun of you.
She wasn't making fun of you Taru.
That is the truth.
You've never got above 50 percent.
Do you know how much you've got to
score to get a top rank?
Ninety.
It's not a parliamentary election. You
can't steal extra ministers from...
...another party if
you don't win by majority.
You have to earn it all by yourself.
Let it go, forget about it!
Listen.
Listen to me.
There's a sale on at the night market.
Let's go shopping.
Papa, I'm talking to
you about something important.
Why are you changing the topic?
Because this topic needs changing.
Papa, I've decided.
I am going to London.
Why don't you go to Jaipur if you
just want to get out of here?
Your aunt has a house there.
I could also come and stay with you.
Papa, why do I have to stay with you?
I've grown up.
Give me a little freedom atleast.
It took India 200 years
to get freedom from the British.
You can wait till you turn 18 atleast.
And what's so great about London?
The British came running here.
We had to kick them out.
They have quality of life, Papa.
We have that here.
Every morning the
milkman delivers milk.
Someone clears up our trash.
The maid does the dishes.
What more quality do you want?
That is called
exploitation of the poor.
What?
Quality of life is different,
this is exploitation.
You're confusing me.
- Let's just drop it.
- Don't confuse me.
- I am not confusing you.
Okay, okay. We'll go, we'll go.
You've only been saying, "We'll go,
we'll go"!
Now when I'm getting a chance,
let me go.
Will you be able to live without me?
Now you're blackmailing me emotionally,
don't digress and promise me.
You can't score 90
percent without cheating.
If you're so sure
of it then promise me.
I...
I'll work hard, papa.
I swear on mum.
If I work hard and get it,
will you let me go then?
Okay. If you manage to earn it,
I will drop you to London myself.
Really? Promise me.
Promise. Alright?
Okay, now go get your marks.
I'm hungry.
Go now.
Miss, lay the table.
I will have one passion
fruit mojito with crushed ice.
Ma'am, it has rum mixed in it.
I know.
Sorry.
- Enjoy your meal ma'am.
- Thank you.
What happened to you, Taru?
When did you start drinking?
Habit...I'm cultivating the habit.
Habit.
It's not funny. You just
have to develop a taste for it.
When my friends in London
offer me vodka shots...
India's reputation will be at stake.
Wow! You're the only true patriot.
India's proud of you, Taru.
Cheers
Cheers!
Where were you?
I've been trying your number.
I was at Maya's house, studying.
Where are your books?
I don't see any books.
Why are you up so late?
Late?
Its only 9.
- Have you been drinking?
- What?
I can tell from your eyes.
Let's not go there.
Your mother used to tell me,
my eyes are intoxicating.
You're missing mum. That means
you've definitely been drinking.
- That's not good.
- No. I have fixed days for that.
Thursday, Friday and bank holidays.
That's it.
You don't believe me?
Check my breath.
Where is the smell
of alcohol coming from?
I drank 3 days ago.
Are you saying, I've been drinking?
No. I didn't say that.
Since you can smell it,
somebody has been drinking...
...which means you have been drinking.
Prove me wrong.
Walk in a straight
line with your eyes shut.
You're one hell of a taskmaster!
Even the cops don't make you do that.
Walk in a straight line, papa...
Walk with...
...with my eyes shut...
- a straight line, right now.
- I've closed my eyes.
Which way?
Not this way, go that way.
C'mon.
There you go, eyes closed.
Here, I am walking straight.
There you go. Happy?
Okay.
Here, I can even walk backwards.
Shall I turn around?
Good boy, Papa.
Now go to your room and sleep.
I'm supposed to say that, silly girl.
I'm your father.
Okay. Goodnight.
Okay, very goodnight!
- Let's go, let's go.
- Hurry up. Come on.
That fool's also coming along.
Come on.
Come on, let's go.
Oi Champak!
Champak, first please
let's sort out my payment...
...otherwise my bus is not moving.
Hey. Talk with respect, first.
Get out of the way!
-Hello. Hello.
-We give you so much business.
That is the problem.
You give me business
but you never pay for it.
What?
Really?
Listen up, all.
Whoever hasn't cleared Gajju's bills,
his old ones,
his future ones, for this bus,
please pay him all his dues.
- Are you happy now?
- Yeah.
Shall we?
- Will you clear my dues for sure?
- Will you let us leave for now?
Driver, take them.
How are your studies going?
Superb! Studies are going superbly.
You don't worry.
- They're going well, uncle.
- They're going well, right?
She started studying
only two days ago.
Ignore him.
If you need any help, let me know.
Don't worry.
As much as I hate your father,
I will always love you.
Today, I'll make sure you retire.
Your Ghasiteram sweet
shop is going to be shut down.
You see that. He's provoking me.
- Ignore him.
- What? What are you talking about?
All rise!
The Honourable Judge is arriving.
Case number 432/1, 336/1.
Champak Bansal from Udaipur versus
Gopi Bansal versus Lagnesh Bansal-
Hold on.
This endless list of names has
been taking up all the time so far.
Let's move on with the proceedings.
Yes...
Sir, people from all over
Rajasthan have come here today.
There's one from
almost every district.
You can refer to this family
tree to avoid any confusion.
Out of court settle-
Settle down you guys
and let the case begin.
Stop this chatter.
You are in a courtroom.
You also settle down and stop being
a nuisance, the judge is waiting.
Last time I had recommended
an out of court settlement.
Did you all manage
to meet and sort it out?
Your honor, if I may... Let me speak.
Your honor,
I'll tell you what happened.
You asked us to have a
meeting so we decided to meet.
Everyone came.
Now he said, I should get
the booze and he'll get the snacks.
Do you know, what he got as snacks?
Am I here to discuss snacks?
My lord, my lord,
let's talk about the booze first.
It was Lagnesh's
turn to get the booze.
- My turn?
- Yes, you.
Do you know what he did?
He got country liquor
in a bottle of Scotch.
He's talking about the snacks bro.
Country liquor causes so much acidity...
...I couldn't drink for three days.
We are not talking about the booze.
We're talking about the snacks.
I'm still getting an acid reflux.
If it wasn't for the snacks
we could've settled the matter.
- Order, order
- Tell him what you got as snacks.
I brought...
What did I bring?
It was by mistake.
I got fish eggs, accidentally.
Really? You got fish eggs?
That day you told us they were sweets.
I didn't intend to...
- Order! Order.
We're not discussing the snacks.
- He brought booze, and I...
- It's not about the booze...
- It was his turn
- Order!
- You're such a...
- Order, order
Maintain the decorum of the court.
Do you wish to say anything?
Sir, I've been drinking
country liquor since my childhood.
It never caused me acidity.
We're not talking about the booze.
We're talking about the snacks.
Suits you but doesn't suit us.
That's impossible.
Shut up! Shut up!
The judgement has been made.
I'm announcing the verdict.
Going by Late Mr. Ghasiteram's will,
which he couldn't sign
before breathing his last,
the court grants Gopi Bansal,
son of Shyamlal Bansal
and his family the exclusive
rights to the family name.
If the name is used for a commercial
purpose by any other party,
it will be deemed illegal and
considered a punishable offence by law.
How can a will without
a signature be valid?
This is Gopi's conspiracy.
Gopi is innocent. Stop blaming him.
This verdict isn't fair.
We'll appeal to the higher court.
Shut your trap.
The judge is a fraud.
The judge is corrupt.
"Love's become a trade."
"Only money can buy you love."
Atleast, return the
bail money I paid for you.
You're like family, Gajju.
It's all yours after we're gone.
Except for the name, Ghasiteram.
I've already lost a pair of slippers,
otherwise I'd whack you with another one.
No, Champak.
You know the rule.
No fighting when we're drinking.
We're all buddies here.
I feel so disappointed in myself.
I'd stooped so low
for the sake of this name.
I got Gopi's shop raided.
You did that?
Yes, I did.
You want to hit me?
Hit me.
Champak, you have no
idea of things I've done.
You too? What exactly do you mean?
What? Who?
I don't know. What did you do?
Who did what?
I bribed the municipality.
I made them dig the entire
path around your shop.
Not a single customer could
get to his shop for 3 days.
How could you stoop so low?
He's your cousin. Man, that's nasty.
Hey. He's my brother.
Champak! Champak...
Champak...
It's okay. It's alright.
Sit down. Sit!
He's my brother.
He can do whatever he wishes to.
Champak, did you hear what he said?
You're my brother.
You can do whatever you want.
You're my brother and you're
a far better man than me.
He whisked the catering deal for
Chauhan's wedding from under my nose.
That is my expertise bro,
but the sweets I made
for the wedding got stolen.
All of it.
I stole them.
What?
I swear, I stole them.
- Nah.
- I swear.
Are you serious?
Gopi got quite a thrashing for that.
They beat him up for two long hours...
And the two of you
stood there watching?
Why didn't you come save me?
I had to sell
the sweets I stole from you.
Right. Makes sense.
It's a neck-to-neck competition.
That's nothing.
You can't imagine the extent to which
I've gone even in your wildest dreams.
Is it? What did you do?
I bribed the judge.
I got him a Rolex
worth 900,000 rupees.
- What? Really?
- You gotta be kidding.
- I'm not kidding. It's true.
- That can't be.
Yes. Hang on. Look at this.
Show it to me.
Rolex for nine hundred
thousand rupees.
Forgive me, Champak.
You're my brother.
I'll never do such a thing again.
You're the only true Ghasiteram.
- No, you are.
I am giving you the permission.
Do not remove the Ghasiteram
board from your shop.
Remove it! Remove the board!
All boards should've been taken
down by 9am, as per the court order.
It's 5 past 9.
Take it down.
Can't you see, it is being taken down.
It's 5 minutes past 9.
Every other board must go.
You're right.
Grab it and yank it off.
Useless!
Take it down.
So shall we start tomorrow?
Huh?
Exam prep!
I have to rank in top 3.
I don't get it.
You're helping me, right?
I have to be among top 3 students
to get to Truford University.
Don't you pay attention in class?
I'll pick you up from
the coaching class tomorrow.
We'll go to my place and get started.
And when will I study?
You've been a topper.
Why do you need to study?
You're helping me study, right?
No.
Look Anmol, I've taken
up a challenge and I must win it.
I'll pick you up after
the coaching class tomorrow.
Please bring these books along.
- Thank you.
- But...
Hello
"I will fly across the clouds."
"And I will sing to my own tune."
"All my crazy, crazy dreams."
"I make into my one desire."
"I know I don't belong here."
"I need to make my own life."
"I've got one life."
"with hundreds of dreams."
You'll have to learn
these two diagrams.
Papa!
"So many obstacles in my path"
"And so many battles to fight."
"But my heart beats with hope."
"Ain't that right?"
"Life is a bit hard."
"Who knows what the
future holds for me."
"But I'm no less than a star."
"Ain't that right?"
"I know I don't belong here."
"I need to make my own life."
"One Life."
"Hundreds of dreams"
"I shall make them all come true."
"I got one life"
"And hundreds of dreams"
"And each and every
one will come true"
"I shall make them all come true"
Is this a new one?
You might be the first ever father...
...who is bothered by
his daughter studying so hard?
Why would I be bothered
by her studying?
You're not getting it Gajju.
Why don't you use a bit of your brain?
Taru wants to go
to London at any cost.
It's only London. Not Mars.
London.
You're confusing me now.
You've been confused since birth.
Look, if she gets the marks,
I'll have to send her away.
I can't let that happen...
...but after studying so hard,
if she doesn't...
...she'll be heartbroken.
That'll be the end of her dream.
Gajju.
What kind of a guy are you?
You are confusing me too.
Think Gajju, think.
Please think.
I am thinking.
Here.
What's this?
Your examination paper.
You've been working so hard.
You can't trust the teachers
to give you the marks you deserve.
Take the question
paper and get full marks.
How did you get the question paper?
That's not important.
You've been studying so sincerely.
Take it.
Look at it and get the marks.
No, papa. I've sworn on mum.
I'll go to London only
if I earn it honestly.
Otherwise I won't.
Take a look
No, papa.
Give it a glance.
There's no harm in it.
No, papa. Let it be.
I won't tell anyone.
No, papa.
Alright then.
"So many obstacles in your path."
"And so many battles to fight."
"But your heart beats with hope."
"Ain't that right?"
"Your life is a bit hard."
"Who knows what the
future holds for you."
"But you're no less than a star."
"Ain't that right?"
"I know I don't belong here."
"I need to make my own life."
"One Life."
"Hundreds of dreams"
"I shall make them all come true."
"I got one life."
"And hundreds of dreams."
"I shall make them all come true."
"Yes, I'll make them all come true."
- Taru scored 85 percent.
- Congratulations, brother.
85! She got 85.
Taru got 85 percent.
That's a miracle!
You did it. 85 percent!
Nobody in the entire Ghasiteram
family ever scored that high.
And nobody ever will.
Why are you looking sad?
I came 4th.
You scored 85 percent.
I lost the challenge, papa.
It's your principal ma'am.
Principal.
Hello?
Mr. Champak, congratulations!
Please give Tarika the good
news that she is going to London.
- London?
- No, but madam...
Mr. Bansal, try and understand,
Anmol Shekhawat who
ranked 1st isn't going.
Why ma'am?
Oh, Tarika... Congratulations!
Anmol always wanted
to go to IIT, right?
Yes, sorry. Thank you, ma'am!
Am I going for sure, ma'am?
Yes, definitely.
And Mr. Champak...
Yes?
You have to come for the annual day
and give a speech as well.
Are you pulling my leg...
Hello?
She hung up.
Papa... I'm going to London?
We'll have to go shop...
- I am going to London.
- My child...
You're going to London.
My daughter's going to London!
You're looking handsome.
Yeah, right.
Perfect!
I know that.
- Dear principal madam...
- Hi Tarika.
- Hi uncle.
- You...come here.
Above all...and honourable...
Mr. Bansal!
Come on, quick. Hurry up!
Give that to me.
Is that...
Papa, let's go.
Go on. I'll join you in a bit.
Go ahead.
I'll join you in a bit. Go ahead.
Come soon.
Hey Gajju.
The other night when you,
me and Gopi were drinking...
Remember what we were talking about.
Dear students,
there's nothing more precious
than the seeds of honesty...
...and ethics sown by this esteemed
institute of knowledge, 'Vidya Sadan'.
Could you move your leg a bit?
Bathroom...
Move your legs, please...
One moment please.
This is the very school
where honesty and hard work...
...became the fundamental
values of my life.
I'd just like to say that regardless
of what you become in life,
the most valuable thing
to treasure is honesty.
Papa, clap.
Thank you.
Now it's time to
felicitate our 3 students...
...who have got the
opportunity of admission...
...in the esteemed Truford
University in London.
We shall begin with Tarika Bansal...
...and I would request her
father Mr. Bansal to say a few words.
You may take your seat.
Take one. Take one of ours.
Okay. Okay.
Mr. Champak, your speech?
No, no.
No, no, everyone's waiting for it,
you'll have to say something.
The stage is all yours.
You go.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Good morning dear principal madam,
dear students, dear...dear...on top of...
Above all most honorable
and honest Judge Chheda.
Inside I'm very...
I'm very emotional
and outside I'm very happy
for my daughter Taru.
I...
Yeah?
The box of sweets has
to be delivered at the office.
Yes, I'll be there!
That's all the English I know.
One moment, madam.
One moment.
The honourable Judge
spoke about honesty.
I'd like to add something to that.
There are three kinds
of people in this world.
Those who always score
90 to 100 percent marks,
and God only knows how.
There are some who push
their limits from 55 to 85 percent
with hard work and honesty,
like my daughter, Taru.
And the rest who make
it to the top through cheating,
like our Honorable Judge Chheda!
And if I say that I've
never seen anyone so corrupt,
it wouldn't be an exaggeration.
His Rolex watch is proof of this.
I know this because my
own cousin gave him the watch...
...to get the court's
ruling in his favor.
And my cousin doesn't
lie when he's drunk.
That's the truth.
Look at this. I have proof.
You tell me.
How does a district judge afford a
car like BMW
unless he takes bribes?
Papa.
Papa!
What?
Judge Chheda is the
Principal's husband.
What? No.
We have Mr. Gopi with us.
Could you shed some
light on this matter?
The honorable judge is
an honest man.
Yes.
This video that's gone viral is fake.
That's not me in the video.
It's my lookalike who's been drugged.
He is talking nonsense.
Justice has prevailed and
these rich folk can't accept it.
I don't have the money to get a shave,
let alone afford a Rolex.
The allegations against
Justice Chheda are grim.
Storming out of the school function
alone proves that...
You did this on purpose, didn't you?
Why would I, Taru?
Ninety-One... Ninety-One...
Excuse me?
What is it?
I just wanted to have
a word with you, madam.
How dare you come here?
Madam, please come down or if you
grant me the permission, I'll come in.
Why do you need to come in?
You like putting on a show.
What are you ashamed of?
Go ahead.
Speak from there.
I made a mistake.
If I had known that the
Honorable Judge is your husband,
I would not have dreamed
of doing such a thing.
Teachers are godlike.
You know that better than anyone.
And even God forgives our sins.
I beg you to forgive me.
I'm no God. You can leave.
No please, I'll do anything.
Shame me publicly, if you like.
But please don't punish
my daughter, please.
Stop this circus and get lost!
I beg of you madam,
please let my daughter go to London.
She's worked very hard for this.
If she loses this opportunity...
...I'll never be
able to forgive myself.
You want me to handover
Tarika's approval letter, right?
Yes. Yes.
Fine.
Here.
What you've done is not right, madam.
You've said your part.
Now hear me out.
The truth is that your husband
was corrupt, is corrupt...
...and will always remain corrupt.
As for my daughter, she will
go to Truford University anyhow.
Or I am not worthy
of the Ghasiteram name.
Mark my words!
Taru, Open the door.
don't do this.
Go away, papa.
Please open the door.
Please go. I'm coming.
Come on, open the door.
You never really wanted me to go, see
the world, make something of myself.
You'll marry me off in a year or two.
I had almost made it, papa.
I thought you understood me...
my dreams.
Had mum been alive, she would have.
Tarika, don't say that.
Please don't say that.
Don't ever say that.
I've made this mistake once
with your mother.
She was very smart.
She won gold medals in academics.
Her father married
her off to an illiterate like me.
She must have felt
suffocated in this house.
I crushed all her dreams, unknowingly.
When you kill a person's dream,
he has no purpose to live.
- That's why at a young age, she probably...
- No, Papa.
Don't.
My child, you are my dream.
Just wait and watch.
I've ruined one life already.
I won't let it happen again.
Wipe your tears and get ready.
I've challenged your principal.
You have to make your father proud.
Don't... my nose is running.
Come here.
You're my brave soldier.
Right.
If you're finding it
difficult to read, shall I?
I know a bit of English.
A-1... Service.
Why'd you eat up the middle word?
So that you can be of some use,
Miss English Medium.
That's a lot of pens for
someone who can't read!
Is it looking over the top?
Let's go.
One second.
This one.
Your S.A.T.
and I.E.L.T.S. scores are pretty good.
Thank you, ma'am.
You can apply for the
foreign students' category.
Can I?
See.
Are you single?
Beg your pardon?
I mean, are you a single parent?
Single, double,
yeah, I guess I'm everything.
Must be lonely?
I mean, it must be difficult for you.
Tarika, can I please speak
to your father for a moment?
It's okay ma'am.
- I'll understand, and I can explain...
- Thank you. Thank you.
I can understand some English.
Stop worrying.
Pay attention...
Please...
Go, go...
Outside.
Yes ma'am.
Mr. Champak, do you have any idea
about the fees for studying in London?
Don't worry about that.
I'll even sell my blood if I have to.
Wow....wow.
But the cost of blood is
only rupees 200 per bottle...
...and the tuition
fees at the college,
along with hostel charges,
medical insurance...
...food, transport,
all together is a bit expensive.
How much?
Considering the college you want
and including the cost of living...
...there for 3 years would approximately
come up to ten million rupees.
Ten million?
Ten million.
Ten million. Yes.
Think about it...
You'll manage?
I've got some land I can sell.
Don't worry about it, just do it!
Just do it?
Wow.
Papa!
Yes?
The Truford University email has come.
Papa...
Hang on. Don't open it yet.
I'm coming there.
Show me. That's great.
Wait, don't open it yet.
Okay, now.
Wait. Wait. Where shall I?
- Hurry up.
- It won't break here, wait.
Open it.
Oh wait, it didn't break.
No need.
What?
Sorry, papa.
My child...
All of the twelve seats...
...have gone to Chinese students.
Don't worry...
The Chinese have been trying to
steal our right since the time of Nehru.
Yeah.
Right.
Nehru?
Apart from the Indian herbs,
everything these days is 'Made in China'.
Exactly.
That's how it is.
There are other
universities in London.
Do you have to go
to this particular one?
It's a matter of pride.
I've given my word.
There must be another way?
No way. The foreign
students' quota is full.
Isn't there any other
quota we can apply in?
There are seats available
but that is specifically...
...for citizens of the United Kingdom,
British citizens.
And you know how stringent
immigration laws have become?
Hold on. I'm confused.
What are we supposed to do?
What...
With the chaos surrounding Brexit,
even tourist visas are
difficult to come by these days.
How on Earth will you
manage to get a Citizenship?
I haven't visited my brother
who lives in London for 2 years.
If I can't get a tourist visa, how
will you manage to get a citizenship?
Right?
"O forgotten memories,
don't haunt me..."
Say something.
The only dream my daughter had since
she was a kid has been crushed by me.
Gajju, she's a piece of my heart.
At least you have
someone to care about.
My wife left me right
after our wedding night.
At least your wife is alive!
I didn't give my wife
a chance to live.
My gambling addiction
has ruined my life.
I lost the family name.
I'm not able to send
my daughter to London.
My life is nothing
but a big fat failure.
It's not that bad, Champak.
I have a sexually transmitted disease!
What?
STD!
What's going on?
Just to win the competition,
you'll make up any crap?
Why don't you just say that you're
dead and this is your ghost talking!
- Okay. I'm sorry.
- What a bastard!
- This is the limit!
- Champak's got bigger problems.
I'm sorry. I lost.
People think I'm no good.
They tell me, "You thought you could
take your daughter to London to study?
Who do you think you are?
You're a nobody."
Who says so?
Tell me who?
If that loser,
Bablu can go to London, why can't you?
Who's Bablu?
He's in London?
Bablu, our Bradman, Don Bradman...
He played cricket that well?
No. The bat and the
ball belonged to him.
If he got out,
he would take them and go.
That's how he had a high run rate.
He's on our school's chat group.
He posts some porn once in a while.
The stuff you forward to me?
Yeah... He could help us.
- Here, talk to him.
- Here.
Talk to him.
Oi Bablu!
It's me, Champak Ghasiteram.
Champak... careful.
Talk...
Speak to him.
Hey.
Bablu, this is Chunnu from Udaipur.
Remember me?
I had rubbed cow dung
on your face when we were kids.
Hello? He hung up.
Is that how you introduce yourself?
'Rubbed cow dung on your face?'
Obviously he'd hang up.
What did I say?
Try again.
What, cowdung?
Phone.
Call him again.
You talk to him.
Hey! Yo yo Bablu!
Bablu?
It's me, Champak Ghasiteram.
That was Gopi, that bastard...
on the phone earlier.
I needed a small favour.
Do you know anyone at
any university in London?
My daughter needs
to get enrolled there.
You're like a brother to
me so I thought if you could...?
What? You want to
come here and discuss it?
He's saying he'll
come here and discuss it.
- Call him over then, go on.
- Come over.
Come over? See you then.
Business class?
Business class? Yeah, so?
Your whole family business class.
Yeah, yeah, call him.
- Business class?
- Call him.
Come, come.
He said it'll be done.
- He said it'll be done.
- Done?
I told you.
Champak, London is done?
Buddy...
Congratulations, Champak.
It's done!
It'll get done!
Champak?
Will you be able to
manage without me?
Will you come along?
Well, if you insist I will.
My daughter's getting
admission in London university!
This one..
Okay. Weather's hot outside.
You're looking smart.
Just for you.
Champak?
- Gajju.
- Oh, sorry.
- Bablu?
- Yeah, yeah.
Start the music!
Stop the music!
I'm Champak.
Oh! You've grown tall, mate!
That's my wife, mate. My daughter...
Namaste!
London Bridge is falling down.
Listen carefully.
Give it your all.
Cover the entire field.
Don't spare any corner.
Play as if this is the
last match of your life.
Whatever may happen,
Bablu cannot be bowled out!
Do you copy?
God bless us!
To your places.
Come on.
Bloody hot, eh?
Out!!
Shut up! Shut up!
Gajju, you should tell
him when it's a trial ball.
Trial ball... it's a trial ball.
- What do you think you're doing?
- Clean bowled him on the first ball Gopi!
Is that how you bowl?
You're not the cricketer, Murlidharan.
I'll cut the number of
wickets from your bus fee.
Go easy on him.
I'm not used to a spin.
In London the ball tends to swing.
- Is it?
- Yeah.
- That's a four!
- Clap, clap for papa.
Come on. Come on.
You sure, you can get it done?
Look Champak, you only have
to invest 100 thousand pounds,
generate employment for 10 people...
... and they'll give
you citizenship anyway.
Come over and we could
do business together.
Okay.
Invest half your money now
and the rest later.
And, my fee will be 5% of the total.
Fees?
These guys never pay fees to anyone...
I'll be leaving then.
What are you talking about?
Wait, you're not even out yet.
You really think these
guys can get me out?
At least finish the game.
Champak bro, times have changed now.
I've shown you all some great
innings...100, 200, 300 runs.
- Did I ever ask for any fee then?
- No, never.
Never.
- C'mon, put it back.
- Things have changed now.
I can't offer you my services
unless you pay me for it.
Okay then, take a commission.
Why 5, take 6 percent.
I mean it.
Very good! Let's play on then.
Set it up again.
No problem then.
Gopi and you could
travel on business visas
and Tarika could get a tourist visa.
In no more than 2 months, you'll
become an Englishman just like me.
We don't want to be Englishmen,
we just want admission.
One more thing, you guys don't
have any cases filed against you, right?
Case?
I mean court case...litigation.
Case...
Listen carefully.
This is an affidavit.
You all have to sign it.
It says, we are dropping all
the cases filed against each other.
I give my permission to every one of you
in Rajasthan to use the Ghasiteram name.
Really?
But I haven't given my permission
to let Tarika study abroad yet.
Oh god, Grandpa...
Papa...
- Hold on, sit down...
- Papa, no...
We don't need your permission.
We've wasted all
our life behind a veil...
...But you cannot stop her.
She will go see the world.
Heard that?
Everyone got it?
No more discussion on this now.
All hail Ghasiteram!
Could you please place your
thumb and four fingers on the scanner?
Look, we have to put our thumb there.
Thank you very much,
and just look into the camera please.
There you are, thank you very much.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Let's go.
- Go ahead.
- No, you go first.
It's your turn.
You go.
My brother.
Passport please.
Thank you.
Can I have your thumb print please?
Could you just look
into the camera please?
Thanks.
How long will you be
staying in England sir?
What?
How long will you
be staying in England?
Long... Very long.
What's the purpose of your visit sir?
- Business...business, both of us.
- Sir please, step behind the line.
- His English is bad...
- Behind the line sir!
My big brother...
Thank you very much.
- Champak, your turn.
- Next!
What's that dog doing?
Hey, control your dog, brother.
Sir, are these your bags?
Is this your dog?
Sir, sir, you cannot leave
your bags unattended here.
Get the dog off our bags.
There're food items in there.
The dog might pee over it.
Listen to me sir, are these
your bags is what I'm asking you.
There's pickle in a glass jar.
If it breaks...
What? What do you mean?
A glass jar with pickle
inside...might burst!
Woah...Woah!
Sir, calm down, calm down.
I'd like you both to come with me.
- My daughter.
- Sir, now!
Let her come, and we'll go together.
You need to come with me sir.
With me, now.
Papa?
Uncle Gopi?
Now where were we?
We do big business with Bablu.
Baba-who?
Bablu...
And what kind of business is he in?
What did he tell us? He had mentioned
something about his business.
Medicine.
What do you call that in English?
- Ayurveda?
- In English?
He won't get it.
Wait a minute.
What is medicine called in English?
Stop, stop!
Drugs!
Drugs?
God promise!
His name is Balashankar Tripathi.
He's a big name in the business.
We came here to become partners.
Yeah.
He's our childhood friend.
Guv?
You got to see this.
Gentlemen.
All okay?
By your own admission,
your friend's a drug dealer,
and you're working with him.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
Sir, drugs are very important.
All people should get drugs.
We'll help Bablu to get big drugs.
What's there to it?
It'll give jobs to your people.
We become big.
Bablu becomes big.
All families...rich, poor, all...
We're going to search your bags.
Oh man!
Let him search. Let him.
Careful, the pickle bottle will break.
Don't touch it! Don't touch it!
- Sir please calm down.
- You don't need to pull out a gun.
We're not some terrorists.
This is not ketchup.
This is pickle.
We're not strapped with a bomb!
Hands where I can see them!
That's it.
Sit down.
This is not America! Put
this gun down. We've been so polite.
Gopi, they say, never finger the police.
I never thought that the
police would finger us so badly.
Neither did I....Aah!
You are allowed one phone call each,
then you're going back
to India on the first out.
- My daughter is outside
- No, stop.
Don't mention her name.
These guys here are all crazy. Imagine
if the same thing happens to her.
One phone call each.
Make a call to Bablu.
Hello.
Bablu! We've got stuck here.
Looks like we're in some kind of mess.
Listen to me!
Taru is at the airport.
Please take care of her.
Stop talking and listen to me.
What's he saying?
Are you out of your mind?
He just kept blabbering.
He's just not listening.
He didn't hear you?
What did he say?
He said done but...
- He said done, right?
- Yeah, he did.
Do you want to make a call?
Gajju!
You're going to be deported,
and your passports will
be blacklisted forever.
You cannot set foot
in the United Kingdom, ever!
Do you get that?
This number is not in service.
Tarika, how are you?
Your father had called.
He was missing some crucial documents,
so he's on his way back to India.
India? But I'm here...
Wait there.
Bablu will come pick you up.
Bablu uncle isn't answering
his phone and I don't have any money.
Oh God!
He's not answering my
phone either but don't worry.
Don't lose heart.
Champak told me to...
...deposit money in your HSBC account.
You can go to any branch.
Book a good hotel room
with an attached toilet and bath.
And don't worry at all.
Yes, uncle.
So what if those people
speak in English, we are no less.
Yes uncle.
- Hello.
- Hey, its Advait.
I got your message on the University page.
- Is this Tarika.
- Yes, I am Tarika.
You. Get in the car.
Who are you?
- Give me your bag. C'mon.
- Leave my bag.
Leave my bag.
Get in the car.
Jesus, Tarika!
Damn...
It's just me, Advait.
You called me.
Gone mad?
Damn it!
I'm sorry
Um...its...
I am fine.
I'm sorry
We thought we'd break
the ice with a prank.
Guess, it went wrong.
Also, I love Chinese.
He's Korean.
Where's the party at?
- So I'm just going to leave your stuff here.
- Addy.
Get out of here!
Yes.
Yes, come now. Everyone's here.
Yeah.
Hungry?
I'm non-veg.
Okay. It's vegan.
I love that.
Okay.
Leave them in the sink,
the maid will do them in the morning.
Madam, there's no maid here,
we do the dishes ourselves.
Sorry.
Here you go.
You'll be fine, yeah?
Yes.
- Sleep well.
- Thank you.
- Goodnight.
- Night-night.
This number is not in service.
Hello, Uncle Gajju?
I can't reach anyone's phone.
Tell Papa, I tried Uncle
Bablu's phone but he didn't answer.
I'm staying in a Student house.
There's a boy named
Advait who brought me here.
He lives here as well.
There are other girls as well,
all foreigners.
Gajju. I have to get
to London at any cost...
- Yes. Yes.
- My daughter's stuck there!
Yes, Champak, calm down.
I've thought of something.
What?
I'm going to send
you two back to London.
Take this. Take it.
Flight tickets for this evening!
- This evening?
- You're the best. You're the best.
Wow!
Wait, what's this?
It's a ticket to Dubai?
What do you expect after you've
shut the doors to London forever?
But why would we go to Dubai
when my daughter's in London?
My cousin Tony is in Dubai.
After being blacklisted only
one man can get you back.
And that's Tony.
Only he can find a way.
But please clear his payment right away.
You're the best...a true friend.
That's fine,
but Tony is not your friend.
Don't keep his dues pending!
If you would speak to
Tom from admissions...
...he will sort it out for you.
It's not bad, is it?
Here you go.
Also, got this for you.
Wow... Thank you.
You're very welcome.
Once papa's business is
set up and we get a citizenship...
You'll be sorted then.
Hungry?
- Hi D'.
- Hi.
Your dad is on TV again.
Your dad's a politician?
Come.
Why don't you live with him?
My dad is a politician, not me.
I can't afford that lifestyle.
Do you guys not get along?
No. We're like buddies...
...but it's not like in India.
It doesn't matter who your father is.
Once you're 18, you're on your own.
You make your own life.
Nobody's going to
do your life for you.
Listen, why don't you take a seat.
And I'll just be back, yeah.
Two minutes.
What will you have?
What?
Part-time job.
I have to pay my college fee, right?
Even that your father doesn't pay for?
Depends.
My father probably would...
...but why would I be a burden?
Wow.
I've never thought of it that way.
What can I get you?
A job?
And a room...
...on rent please.
Good choice.
You'll have to suck up to her, and maybe
you'll get both the job and the room.
Mrs. Kohli can be a bit difficult.
Actually, a bit too difficult.
Alright Mrs. Kohli? What's up?
Arthritis, blood pressure, gout,
back pain and I'm a tad depressed today.
What about you?
Ma'am, you two look so good together.
So nice.
He's dead.
Gajju told us...
if there's anyone who can get
us out of this mess, it's you Tony sir.
Yes.
Look there.
If it's not messy, it's not for me.
So what if you got blacklisted?
I'll get you guys back there.
How?
Nigerian, Japanese...
This one will suit you better.
Here are 2 Pakistani
passports with UK visas.
We just need to switch
the photographs.
Pakistani?
No, we're Ghasiterams,
how can we be Pakistani?
Please give us some other option.
Water?
No, thanks.
- We've had some.
- Some tea?
Tea will be nice.
Water, water...
Sorry buddy.
Isn't there another way?
The chances of being
shot here are too high.
That happens sometimes.
You're in a vessel.
A vessel?
A boat. Boat!
You're on a boat.
The coast-guard is also on a boat.
Your boat will rock.
Their boat will also rock...
so the chances of getting
shot are very slim.
Dude, even I have studied math.
If their boat will rock,
and our boat will also rock...
Their motion will
cancel out our motion.
What?
The motion will get
cancelled out.
We'll get shot
right between the eyes!
Oh! Tony sir, this is not
a video game where one has 3 lives.
Please value the one we have.
Any other option?
Air!
Air?
Gopi.. It's too cold..
I can't breath..
Do something.
No...
Any chance we could
try an option via land?
We're from Rajasthan.
We have the stamina of a camel.
We can cross vast deserts with ease.
Did they only teach
you math in school?
Not geography?
England is an island,
surrounded by water.
I can swim across this with Champak
on my back in one stroke.
Idiot!
This is the English channel,
not a TV channel.
You can't cross it in one stroke.
Okay no problem,
show us another way.
Yes, give us an
option.
Something better.
Gentlemen,
this is not a shopping site,
where you can keep
swiping for options.
I gave you 3 options,
explained two of them and the
third one is to take those passports.
If you want another option,
come back after 6 months.
- Now get lost.
- No, we have to go now.
We don't have that long.
Take it.
No problem. Pick it up.
Remember your names
Abdul Razzaq
and Saqlain Mushtaq.
I knew the Pakistani
cricket team is in a bad shape...
...but I didn't expect it to be that bad.
No, those are not the
cricketers' passports.
Only the names are the same.
The people aren't.
Yeah, they look different.
How will we pull off being Pakistani?
It's no trouble at all.
Just remember.
If anyone asks you,
all you have to say is, Inshallah...
Inshallah...
- Boys played well!
No laughter.
Inshallah...
Inshallah
Boys played well!
Inshallah boys played well!
Yes. Happy journey, happy journey.
Get well soon!
Hello.
Tony sir, we're at the immigration,
what should we do now?
Go to counter number
6 and nowhere else.
My man is expecting you.
Okay.
And listen...
The passport only has your photos,
not your biometrics.
What does that mean?
If you get caught,
chop off your fingers
but don't give your fingerprints.
What are you getting us into?
Why should we chop off our fingers?
How will we make
sweets without fingers?
Idiot.
There's a lot more you won't
be able to do without your fingers.
Hang up now, you idiot!
The younger one is a big idiot.
Hello?
He hung up?
Why should we chop off our fingers?
Number 4 please.
Sir, please, number 4.
Number 4.
You okay?
Number 4 please.
I'm not feeling well...
Number 6 please.
Sister, let me go... I'm unwell.
Hey, that was easy!
No more Hindi.
We should speak in Urdu now.
In every breath we should spew Urdu.
How?
Marhabha! (Marvellous)
Marhabha!
Where have you got me?
You got us here.
How will we get a taxi on a rooftop?
- There are cabs but...
- Tell me what you're hiding Jason?
Stay out of my business, bitch.
How can you do this?
Is he crazy?
How dare he hit a woman?
- Don't interfere in their matter.
- Wait here.
- Where are you going?
- Champak!
- Hey you...
Don't try to be a hero.
Hey! How dare you hit a woman?
Now, I get it. Champak!
They're being filmed
by hidden cameras!
- What's going...?
- Madam, no kissing, hidden cameras!
You're a cop?
Yes, I'm a freakin' cop!
And don't you ever touch a girl again.
- Naina!
- Asshole
You couldn't stop those buffoons?
What were you guys doing?
I told you,
we don't have anything on him.
Naina, Naina leave him!
Three months.
I was undercover for 3 months.
Thanks to your heroism,
the whole operation is busted.
What are your names?
Saqlain Mushtaq.
I'm also an all rounder..
the one Jadeja had thrashed.
Take a guess. C'mon!
Jacques Kalis?
Carl Hooper?
Glen McGrath?
How is Glen McGrath an all-rounder?
The one from our motherland...
Abdul Razzaq?
That's right!
Jadeja beat him badly.
You can't leave till
we verify your background.
On what grounds?
Is it because of the way we look?
No... Please...
How do you think we got here?
That we came here, got
blacklisted, then went to Dubai,
got fake passports with our
photos and came back here?
No, you idiot,
she's not saying that... you are!
Ma'am, we're very decent people.
What happened to your hands?
Arthritis!
This cold weather makes it worse.
Naina, the Superintendent
is on the line.
It doesn't look good.
When did this happen?
Keep talking to me.
Take their details and let them go.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- Yes sir.
Since when...?
- I'm sorry.
- Tony...fingerprints.
Why are you making these sounds?
I'm practicing Urdu.
Don't start in Urdu here.
I'm getting really confused,
when to speak Urdu and when not to.
How are you sweetheart?
Now that you're here I'm fine.
Careful.
Why are you both looking different?
Are we?
- What?
- Why?
No we aren't.
Ah, yes... we removed our earrings.
An astrologer told us to remove all
our accessories to improve our luck.
Ohh...
Come, let me show you the house.
Papa, did you get in
touch with Uncle Bablu?
Bablu? Oh, his number had changed.
But we got in touch
and it's all sorted now.
We had such a tough
time finding his new number.
Here you go.
Champak! Look, a swimming pool!
Wow! You have a swimming
pool inside the house!
Where do you sleep?
In the room there...
Come, I'll show you.
Lovely place.
Let's see her room first.
Then we'll see ours.
There's a fireplace too? That's nice.
And look at this.
How soft this bed is!
Where should we put our luggage?
You can't stay here.
This is a student house,
you won't be allowed here.
Wait a second.
You can check with
our landlady, Mrs. Kohli.
She has rooms in her outhouse.
There was one vacant room.
You can shift in there.
Okay, so let's all move in there?
No papa, you go there. I'm fine here.
Ohh, you want to be cool huh?
Oh, please.
Go quickly and book the
room before it's given away.
- How can I...
- Only you can do it!
- How will I find Mrs. Kohli?
- She stays close by.
- Go get it done.
- Why do I always do the dirty work?
Take a left after you
step out of the house.
Hmmm...
I don't need to look cool. I am cool.
Hello?
Come in.
Yes?
No!
What?
Who's this girl?
Is she a tenant?
Who puts up photos
of their tenants?
Then?
That's my daughter.
Hello....Hello? Hello?
Why are you shouting, I'm coming.
Who?
I can see the steam
but it's not hot.
It is hot, papa.
Did you add ginger?
Champak, we can't stay here.
Why? It's such a nice house.
Not at all. Nothing is
right according to Feng-shui.
Since when do you
believe in Feng-shui?
Don't be so orthodox.
We're in London, be modern.
Look, a bird!
Where?
Come here.
The lady cop who wasn't letting
us go is Mrs. Kohli's daughter.
And this is her house!
What happened, Papa?
The vibe
of this house is not right.
But you just said...
These concepts were made
for our own good.
The bed in the room is so soft,
it can damage your back.
And there's a swimming
pool right in front of the house.
This place is not safe.
We better go. Go pack your things.
I can't just leave.
I've paid the rent.
Forget about the rent.
Don't worry about that.
It's my money after all.
No papa, it's my money.
I took up a part time job.
What did you say?
- What?
- Job?
A part time job.
Job?
You are working?
I thought you wanted to study here?
Papa, my admission will be in Fall.
Till then I'll pick
up my own expenses,
And I'll also repay you
my college fees as and when I can.
What...
What did you say?
You will return me my money?
You should be happy.
I'm being responsible.
Are you? Or are you
calling us irresponsible?
I can't really figure.
Now is not the time to argue.
Go and pack your bags.
- Papa, I can't go.
- Haven't I made myself clear enough?
- Please speak softly, papa.
- Calm down, Champak.
Whoa, what's going on? You alright?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- Sure, you're alright?
Yeah.
Does she also have a job?
Let's go inside... Please let's go.
Papa, what's the problem
with me staying here?
I have a problem and I don't
need to explain everything to you.
Please speak softly.
You're not old enough to live like this.
Get into college first. Then we'll
find you a decent flat-mate...
...from a good family.
It's a roommate, papa, not a husband.
It's not like I'm getting married.
Don't teach your father.
I've seen more of the world than you.
No, you haven't, but I want to...
I don't want to be like a
frog who's whole world is a well.
What did you say?
You mean we're like frogs in a well?
Papa, whether you
are in Udaipur or London,
your view of the world is the same.
This time I won't
sacrifice my freedom.
I'm living here on my own terms,
you can't tell me what to do.
Is this how you speak
with your father?
Just because you're in London,
you've forgotten all your manners?
He's your father!
Even today,
he's the one folding your clothes,
making tea for you,
fixing your punctured bicycle.
I've never asked him to.
He does these things on his own.
And didn't I manage
when he wasn't around?
I found this house
and a job for myself.
He left me stranded at the airport.
He didn't even call!
Do you even know what we've been through.
Shut up!
Now you listen to me.
You want your freedom, right?
It doesn't come for free.
You have to pay a price for it.
If you want to stay here,
you can't call me papa anymore.
I'm nobody to you and you're
nobody to me. That's it.
- You're overreacting, Champak.
- Let her do what she wants.
Once she gets in the college,
we'll go back.
Let her stay here.
I don't understand...
Champak.
Hey.
What's happened to you? Huh?
Aren't you stretching this too far?
Don't you get it?
I'm completely confused, Gopi.
What if the policewoman
finds out that Taru's my daughter?
We'll deal with
whatever comes our way...
...but what about Taru?
How will she deal with it?
It's not even her fault.
She's always wanted only one thing,
"Papa, when will we go abroad,
when will we go abroad?".
And now that she's here,
imagine if she gets blacklisted.
What do I do, Gopi?
Poor thing, she's upset
- What?
- She's hurt, poor thing.
What do I do?
Nevermind. Let's go.
Sorry.
This is for one week.
Come on, let's go.
Everyone...let's do a shot.
One shot everyone, c'mon!
Tarika?
Not supposed to speak Urdu,
we can barely speak English,
no one speaks Hindi,
your daughter isn't listening,
Bablu is missing,
the policewoman is after us....
Welcome to London!
This is locked and sealed.
The moron's phone
and house are both shut.
Should we go to the police station?
Yes.
To file a missing person's report.
Are you out of your mind?
We're here on fake passports.
How can we go to a police station?
Oh, yes.
We can't even go
near a police station.
Hello. Good morning.
Not this way.
- Just follow me.
- I'm nervous.
Look, a Sardarji!
- Sardarji, Indian Sardarji!
- Hello
- Sardarji...
- He'll hear us when he comes out.
Can I help you lads?
It's Marhaba!
I mean Mohtarma...
- Inshallah! Boys played well.
- Inshallah! Mashallah!
- Praise the Lord.
- I love the Lord.
- Hello
What's your friend's name?
Full name is Balashankar Tripathi.
Bablu bro.
He's a Hindu but has a great heart.
Yes, that's true.
How do you know him?
He's our friend.
We played together as kids.
Don't mention that.
You say you all are decent people...
...but your friend, "Bablu bro"
...is in jail.
Oh god!
Couldn't we get him out on bail?
Sure.
3000 pounds in bond security.
Ask your lawyer to
come and get it done.
Where are you running of to?
- Gopi, mate!
- Champak, here he is.
Welcome to London mate!
- Where's our money?
- What are you doing mate?
I have the money. It's at home. Relax!
- Let's go home then!
- Relax!
Move it.
Bablu, buddy,
just give our money back.
Just get my money back...
Where is it?
Stop acting dumb!
Give my brother's money back!
Go, get it!
You can beat me as
much as you want
But I don't have the money.
Forget money, I have nothing.
My wife runs the house
doing a part-time job.
We're in a bad shape.
Your wife!
Oh!
Hi...
Hello!
Hello.
Bablu got emotional seeing us.
Please, come in.
It's Champak.
I owed money to a local
gang and had no way out,
They would've killed me.
That's when I got your call...
...and you invited me to India.
I gave away all your
money and saved my life.
I didn't have any money left,
not even for my bail.
If this is the life you were living,
why didn't you return to India?
Champak...
...you can't even imagine
the humiliation if I go back.
I will be stamped as a failure.
It's not easy to go back.
Bablu, take this money.
No, not again...
Champak...
So this travel agent Soni...
He...
Not Soni, Tony.
Whatever...
He told you...
...to come here on Pakistani passports...
...convert your religion,
change your name,
and then adopt your daughter,
spend 100,000 pounds
to get citizenship.
And then get her enrolled
in the college?
That's what he's saying.
He fooled you, this Sony.
Not Sony, it's Tony.
Whatever his name is, he's fooled you.
How are you so sure?
I know because even I fooled you.
I mean, that was then, not anymore.
What will I tell Taru's
mother after I die and go up there?
How will I face her?
How do I get Taru into this college?
Champak bro,
that's my responsibility now.
Give me 10 days and
I'll sort something out.
What is it?
Spying on someone is a crime.
It's called invasion of privacy.
I'm looking around at London.
If you happen to be in London,
what can I do?
Fine...Keep looking!
"Never thought you would
ever make me cry"
"Never thought my most precious
thing would grow apart from me"
"I know I'm away but
I haven't left you"
"Yes, I am helpless
but I'm not that bad."
Mr. Champak?
Please don't litter the streets.
We keep them clean here in London.
Let's go.
Look what she called me.
"Mr. Champak!"
Did she say "Oi Champak"?
No, "Mr. Champak".
Mr. means she's addressing
you with respect.
We use it while filling forms.
Mr. Champak.
"No, you'd never get it"
"You will never really understand me."
"Whatever I do..."
"...is never good enough for you."
"Am I asking for too much?"
"You are all I have"
"It's only you for whom
I left everything behind"
"At least turn towards me.
Take a few steps my way."
"No, you'd never get it"
"You will never really understand me."
If the mother and
daughter don't get along,
why is there such a big
photo of them in her house?
What exactly is your problem?
Is it the photo or is it the size
of the photo?
She said she doesn't get along with her
daughter. That's the end of the story!
- Something doesn't seem right.
- Everything's all right
"No, you'd never get it"
"You will never really understand me."
- Champak bro.
- What is it?
There's one more chance
for Taru's admission!
- Really? How?
- A Fundraiser.
Fundraiser? What's that?
The university invites rich
people to give big donations.
The one who donates the
biggest amount gets a seat.
I'm figuring how to get the invitation.
"No, you'd never get it"
"You will never really understand me."
Excellent.
My husband had a great stock.
Really?
He didn't drink much but when he did,
he drank the best.
It's the other way around for us.
Whether it's the best or not,
we always drink a lot.
With my hands...
I'll get it. You won't get up, I know.
Please come in.
Saqlain.
- Please sit.
- Welcome
You've met before, Saqlain?
Yes, unfortunately.
Can we talk in private, mom?
Naina, please don't start now.
You're embarrassing my friends.
Do you even know these people...
...and the kind of people
they're friends with?
I am not answerable to you.
Abdul!
Like you have all
the freedom in your life,
I too can bloody
well do whatever I want.
If they've committed a crime,
arrest them.
If not, then tell
me what you're here for?
Tomorrow's your birthday, and I'm busy
so I thought I'd wish you today.
Oh I'm deeply obliged!
Now that you're here,
get yourself a drink or go.
You're making my
friends uncomfortable.
Are these guys more
important to you than me?
Am I important to you?
That's why I'm here mom!
On your own time, right?
It's always been about you.
Why a day before,
you could've wished me a month ago,
what difference would it make?
You know what?
Keep it or trash it.
Do what you want.
Happy birthday mom!
You have to light a candle,
clap your hands and you know
the happy birthday song, right?
Of course.
It's just one line.
"Happy-birthday-to-you"
She had a bit too much last night.
She's too good.
I would've never imagined
meeting someone like her in London.
Hey!
She's lying on the floor.
- Look! She's on the floor.
- Where?
There.
Mrs. Kohli!
- There's no other way in.
- Call someone!
Open the door!
- Madam Kohli!
- Break it open.
How?
Kick it.
Are you shooing away a dog?
Break it down, kick it hard!
Not like that. Harder!
- Let me take a run up.
- Wait.
Okay, go!
Mrs. Kohli?
- Is she breathing?
- Kohli madam?
They're so going to jail for this.
Stop, Stop!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Woman die...
Please! I don't want to die...
...take the car!
We have sight of the described vehicle
heading north towards Paddington, over.
Received. Maintain pursuit, over.
You're arrested for breaking
in and entering private premises.
Where's your partner?
Forget my partner!
Go check on your mum.
She was lying unconscious.
We brought her to the hospital.
Naina, her BP had dropped severely.
How long had she been unconscious for?
I...
I'm not really sure.
But thankfully,
you brought her just in time.
I'm sorry.
When your mom wakes up,
you should say sorry to her.
The nurse was saying she's
had a heart attack before.
And you let her live alone?
I've been on my own since I was 18.
I didn't want to be a burden on her.
Independence at 18 is fine...
...but come back when
your parents need you.
What sort of a deal is this where
you use your parents till you're 18
and then you go away
in the name of freedom.
The only expectation parents
have is that their kids are...
...around to hold their
hand when they need them.
Give it a thought and you'll realize...
...how much she needs you.
Let's go.
You still doubt us, don't you?
Well, you're right to do so.
But we aren't bad people.
We're in a difficult situation,
we're not here to stay.
I've come to leave that little hand...
...I held and taught to walk.
Happy Birthday to you.
From old friends and new.
May good luck go...
You said the song had only one line.
They're making up their own lines.
- Thank you so much, darling.
- Great, see you tomorrow
Excuse me, could you check for Mr.
C. Lal on the list?
C. Lal.
Yes.
You might find him somewhere here...
Oh I'm sorry, so sorry.
Where did he go?
And let him do the talking in English.
Do we look okay?
You look like a gold mine.
And me?
You look like a beggar outside the
mine.
Rubbish!
What do you know what
a rich man looks like?
You're at Truford University,
England's most renowned university.
Please behave sophisticatedly.
You're looking fantastic, trust me.
C'mon, lets go.
And now for the final
auction of the day,
the proceeds for which will go towards the
restoration of the Austen Library Block.
- This one's ours. This is the one.
- This one.
Yeah...
The starting bid is 90,000 pounds.
Oh, how very keen sir, thank you.
90,000 pounds from the gentleman
in the glamourous jacket.
Champak bro,
90,000 pounds means 9 million rupees
Please think twice
before lifting the paddle.
120,000 from the beautiful
lady in the leopard print.
Are we back in the
room with a 180? 180,000!
Thank you so much.
200,000 pounds! Thank you.
That's wonderfully generous...
What are you doing! 200,000
pounds means 20 million rupees!
How is it 20 million rupees!
I had said I'd do everything
but I'm not robbing a bank.
- What exchange rate did you check?
- I thought it's 200,000 rupees.
100 rupees per pound!
How much is that?
Champak, forget about it.
Let it go.
No, Bablu. Now that we're here,
we're not leaving empty handed.
Champak bro, don't lift the paddle
now or we'll get screwed.
- Let me figure something else out.
- You take.
Going once...
Going twice..
- 260,000
- Let it go.
Forget we're here.
300,000 pounds!
Going once, going twice...
Gone!
A round of applause for
the gentleman in the gold jacket.
Congratulations sir, and thank you
so much for your extreme generosity.
What?
You have a week to transfer
the relevant funds.
Until then please enjoy yourself.
Thank you.
What did he say?
Is he cancelling it?
He said we'll have to
give the money in a week's time
or else they'll give the seat away.
So we have to get the money!
From where will we get it?
Lucky number seven! Lucky number...
33, black
I can't believe it.
How could my lucky number betray me!
Just hold on.
One moment. Listen to me.
I'm getting a tip off.
Pakistan is going to lose.
Is it fixed?
Yeah. So shall we
put our money on India?
Yes, go ahead.
Mate, you put everything on India.
Pakistan! Pakistan!
The more expensive the car,
the more money we can ask for.
I'll come in front of a big car.
You negotiate accordingly.
I'll go now.
Where are you going?
If you get hit by a car,
how will we negotiate in English?
It's not just about English.
To claim for insurance the person
has to be a resident of England.
So are we not human?
He's my brother, I will go.
Champak is more than a brother to me!
- Champak!
- Champak bro!
Let go off me! Leave me.
Are you crazy? What were you thinking?
Let me go.
The cars are going at such a speed.
What if something were to happen to you!
Why were you going on your own?
Whatever we do, we'll do together.
I need the money.
Why should you
put your lives at risk?
What for?
I'll tell Taru tomorrow that
I couldn't get her admission done.
That's it. Let's go back.
Go back to sleep.
Champak
I thought a lot about it last night.
You, me and Gajju,
we've spent the best
time of our lives together.
You're not my own brother
but you're more than that.
Have you been drinking
early in the morning?
I'm not drunk.
I'm saying this from
the bottom of my heart.
We can't afford 30 million rupees
but our late great-grandfather
Ghasiteram could've.
Yes, so?
I was thinking,
if we sell Bheluram the
rights to the Ghasiteram name,
he would easily give
us 30 million rupees.
I knew you'd sell our family name,
you bastard!
- What? What's this?
- Hang on... Hang on...
- I've tied you up.
- Why have you tied me? Untie me!
- You'll beat me up.
- Gopi, untie me!
- I know you'll thrash me.
- I won't just thrash you.
I'll bury you alive.
- Listen to me.
- Untie me first.
You're forgetting one thing.
I have won the case.
I own the family title.
I can sell it to whoever I want.
You have no right over it.
Oi! Champak!
Listen to me carefully.
Our great-grandfather Ghasiteram must
be watching from above and weeping.
You can't educate your daughter...
You don't deserve to
call yourself a Ghasiteram.
If anyone in this world can beat you,
it has to be a Ghasiteram.
And no one else.
Do you understand that?
You're my brother.
I won't let you lose.
What's in a name?
We'll earn it again.
We have to get Taru the admission.
Shall I untie you now?
You are my brother.
Untie me, you idiot.
You're sure about it?
Grandpa is about
to put his thumb print.
Go ahead. Do it.
Do it.
Bheluram will wire the money.
From that can
I take what you owe me-
Brother...
Why didn't you...
It's gone now.
Idiot, this was your idea.
Hi Troy!
Where are we partying?
Partying!
Partying?
Taru. Come on.
Coming.
Whoa.
You look...
...hot!
Hey mate.
You should knock
before you enter!
Your admission was done so
I brought sweets to celebrate...
Sorry, sorry.
Sorry, sorry, sorry. Sorry.
What a weirdo.
Papa, can I talk
with you for a moment?
You were going out somewhere.
You'll get late.
No, papa.
I'm sorry. You can come anytime.
I didn't mean that.
I don't mean to
interfere in your life.
It was important so
I thought I'd come and tell you.
You don't worry about me.
Your friends are waiting for you.
It doesn't matter, papa.
I want to talk with you.
It's such a big occasion.
Let's celebrate together.
Please wait,
let's have the sweets together.
That's not necessary.
I haven't really done anything great.
It's just a college admission.
And listen.
I don't have a problem who you hang
out or go out with.
It's your life.
Live the way you want.
You're smarter
than I thought, Taru.
Tomorrow your admission will
be finalized and then you'll be free,
I'll be free,
we'll all be free, right?
Whenever you feel like coming home,
just barge in.
You don't need to knock.
The door will always be open for you.
"Hey little bird."
"Fly away tomorrow"
"But stay with me tonight."
Gopi...
...my little girl has grown up.
Fathers eventually understand.
"The path to your home."
"Awaits your return"
"We shall miss you."
"Don't make us wait too long..."
"My dearest one
You are always welcome"
"My darling daughter
You are always welcome."
"My dearest, oh my sweet, lil' girl"
"I'll never leave your hand."
Do these foreigners
also launder money?
Keep your mouth shut.
Let me do the talking.
Naina, you maybe
right about those guys.
We've just got a tip that they have
picked up 300 thousand pounds, cash.
Let's go.
We have to go to your college.
What?
Forget about it. Come, let's go.
We're tailing the suspect vehicle.
It seems to be heading
South of Brenton, over.
Hello?
This is Officer Naina Kohli.
You've reached the voicemail of Babs,
brother love Babs.
Leave a message after
the beep. Beep...
Stop this nonsense!
Give the phone to Abdul Razzaq.
Ma'am, there's no Abdul Razzaq here.
This is a wrong number.
This is the right number madam.
It's Abdul Razzaq speaking.
Good afternoon.
Who is this girl in the car?
Nobody. Yes, somebody.
This my daughter, Tarika.
Tarika?
How can your daughter be a Hindu?
No, she can't but she is.
What can I do?
Papa, when did you become a Muslim?
No, no...
Why didn't you tell me
you have a daughter?
Who is she?
Are you having
an affair with her?
Are you two getting married?
Don't stop the car or you'll not only
lose 300,000 pounds but also...
...get deported to Pakistan.
Pakistan? 300 thousand pounds?
What's going on?
There's no weed in the car, right?
Weed?
Papa, I'm going to faint.
I should be the one fainting.
Keep quiet for a bit.
Bablu, head to Brenton scrapyard.
- That would be a detour.
- Just do what I'm saying!
If you get caught you won't get deported,
you'll be put in jail for life!
Take the inner circuit.
I think we're onto something big here.
Get me backup at Brenton scrapyard.
Mom, are you at the store?
Will someone tell me what's going on?
I don't know.
Only Champak can tell.
Where do I start?
Papa, when will we go?
We'll go, we'll go...
I have to show my face
to Taru's mother after I die.
What will I tell her?
I have to get her into the college.
My daughter is stuck there.
Don't worry. I can even
sell my blood to get the money.
You are my dream, my dear.
I need the money.
Where will we get the money from?
It's just a name.
We'll earn it again.
Papa, no...
Papa, Ghasiteram!
It's gone now.
What would I do if something
were to happen to you?
And you did all of this for me?
Do you know, I was ashamed
to introduce you to my friends?
Sorry papa.
It's alright.
Forget about it.
It's not alright!
You should be scolding me!
That never did anyone any good.
And what good have I done without it?
There are many colleges
in India where I can study.
If I want to study outside, I can move
to aunt's house in Jaipur.
It's already sold.
We might have to sell ours as well
to repay the debt.
Papa, don't worry about the money.
I'm with you.
We'll figure something out.
I'll help you.
I just don't want to study here.
London is alright.
London is good in its own way
but it's not for us.
You don't have to come to London
to be cool.
That's not how it is.
You have to be cool from within.
Papa, you are cool.
But what about your freedom?
What do I do with this freedom if
we aren't together to fight over it?
It's pointless coming home late if you
aren't there waiting at the door...
...to shout at me.
Papa, my life is all about you
and me together.
We're so close that
it gets irritating at times.
Yes, it does.
It does.
But that is our strength.
I have made my mind.
We are going back. That's it.
I'm sorry that you had to
go through so much because of me.
Please papa,
let's go back. I'm done here.
Tarika's absolutely right!
Even I'm leaving everything
and going back to India!
I won't live a dog's life here anymore.
I'll go there and do whatever I have to.
Something's not right,
let's get out of here.
- Something is definitely wrong.
- Is the cop car coming after us?
- Bablu, what have you done now?
- I've done nothing, shut up!
We have a twin intercept approaching
from the north side, over.
- Copy, over.
- Oi what's in front of us?!
No...
We're safe, we're safe.
What have you done?
- The Police is after us.
- I can see that. Shut up.
That policewoman is back!
Cut them off from the north side.
- Armed police!
- Get out of the car!
Get out of the car! Now!
Get out of the car!
Put your hands on the roof.
Where is the money?
Where the hell is the money?
We gave it...
- We gave it to your mom
- Sorry Bablu...
I'll have to hit you so that they
don't suspect that I'm on your side.
Give him 2 more slaps then.
Slap him hard.
Naina, there's nothing here.
They're clean.
What do you mean
there's nothing here?
Calm down.
Okay? It was the informant, I'm sorry.
Okay gentlemen,
everybody needs to move back.
She can't touch me like this mate, this is
police brutality, 'Geneva Convention'.
Okay. There's been some
kind of misunderstanding.
- Can we all just forget this ever happened?
- I want compensation, man!
Yeah well,
we can deal with that at the station.
Listen, shut up and Whatsapp
him the rest.
Okay mate.
Think about it Taru,
this is your last chance.
We're Ghasiterams, uncle Bablu.
Our great-grandfather used to say,
"It's my business to sell sweets...
but my loyalty to
the country is not for sale."
Now's the time to show our loyalty.
I will study there and make Ghasiteram
an international brand one day.
Champak, today our great-grandfather
would've been very proud.
Taru proved to be the real
Ghasiteram - first original!
So this was the third time when
I had no confusion.
I came here to educate my daughter
but I'm the one leaving with a lesson.
When children are young,
we hold their hand
so that they don't
get lost in a crowd,
and when they grow
up and leave our hand,
we end up feeling completely lost...
But the truth, my friends, is...
if you don't let
go of your child's hand,
how will they return to embrace you.
Hot oil trick!
Try, try... Don't feel shy.
As sweet as you. Eat.
Oh, Bablu!
Don't take that.
Your tummy will go for a toss.
No thanks.
"No thanks."
What's up Tarika?
Hello uncle Bablu!
How are you doing?
That's the song. Check it out!
What? No,
you should come to Udaipur once.
We'll treat you to
some real Indian sweets.
There's a lot to see here.
Bring Mrs. Kohli along.
It'll be a good change for her.
Okay. Bye.
How dare you guys put up the
Ghasiteram board?
I'm going to sue you.
You'll sue us?
We'll hammer you with 127 cases!
We hold the Guinness Book
of World Records at suing, you fool.
You are a fool, I have
the signed documents.
I've paid the money for it.
So take it back, with interest.
I'm Ghasiteram now.
I won't let go of the title.
What did you call yourself?
Or else my name isn't Chandiram.
Gajju, get your luxury
bus service this time.
This case will go on for long.
And who'll pay my fees this time?
Shut up!
Nobody will take the Ghasiteram
boards off from their shops.
- So say...No, you say it.
- No, you say it.
- No, no, you say it.
- No, no, you.
Okay... so all hail
Ghasiteram Todarmal Bansal!
All hail!
- All hail Ghasiteram!
- All hail!
"Why does the beautiful girl..."
"...keep her face veiled?
Tell me why? Oh, tell me why"
"The girl is full of brilliance
if only the world let her be."
"So let her be...just let her be"
"She is so amazing,
she can do wonders..."
"Let her dance to her own beat."
"Let the girl dance..."
"Just let her dance..."
"Let her be free"
"Let her fly"
"Let the girl dance...
Just let her dance..."
"Leaving all her troubles behind."
"Let the girl shine."
"Let the girl dance...
Just let her dance..."
"Let her be free"
"Let her fly"
"Let the girl dance...
Just let her dance..."
"Leaving all her troubles behind."
"Let the girl shine."
"Let the girl dance..."
"All your big talk..."
"...don't judge her
with your small mind."
"Why do you frown upon the girl?"
"Smile and the world
will smile with you."
"That's right..."
"Let the girl get on the floor
and dance to her own beat."
"Let the world dance to her beat."
"Let the girl dance..."
" Just let her dance..."
"Let her be free"
"Let her fly"
"Let the girl dance..."
" Just let her dance..."
"Leaving all her troubles behind."
"Let the girl shine"
"Let her dance"
"Let the girl dance..."