Hey, first ask me
how I am.
Let it be.
Eat or you'll be hungry.
Who are you?
Why have you kidnapped me?
What do you want?
I don't have any money.
Who are you? What do you want?
Why did you kidnap me? Let me go.
What's going on?
Will I be sacrificed in a ritual?
I'm a journalist.
If my friends find out,
they'll come after you.
Untie me!
Untie me right now.
Untie me now, come on.
You look like a good person.
Please untie me.
Tell them to let me go.
What are you doing?
Will you kill me now?
Bring that cylinder here!
Untie me.
Did you steal my kidneys?
What have you done?
You don't approve
of the marriage?
They forced me to marry..
She doesn't listen anyway.
Now all hell will break loose.
Vishu, come here quickly!
This is too tight, Mother.
Give me a minute!
Don't shout, Mandy!
Listen to me, for God's sake.
Please, it's not what you think.
What am I supposed to think?
What? What's the problem?
Mandy, listen... Mandy!
Look at this, uncle.
Look at your son.
Are you aware of what he has done?
Mandy, please listen to me.
He is married
to that girl over there.
And now he's pretending
like nothing has happened
and is enjoying her performance.
It's not what you think!
I'll explain everything..
Don't talk anything!
What? What happened?
Daddy!
What happened, my child?
Vishu, what's going on?
Mother, they kidnapped me.
I was unconscious.
Is this a joke?
We can talk about this.
How dare you!
Listen to me, for god's sake!
Move aside, Mother.
We'll talk about it later.
You've married that girl;
now you dare to bring her here?
It's not what you think.
Not what you think!
I'll make sure
you don't get your degree!
Just get out of here.
Everything is over!
What is left to discuss?
Let go of her hand.
Are you waiting
for them to call the police?
You should treat all girls
the way you treat your daughter.
I'm not upset that
the wedding got called off.
I'm angry
because I'm not upset at all!
Everything was going smoothly.
Clear the medical exam at 24,
become a doctor at 28.
Get married at 32,
buy a house at 35.
Be a good son to my parents.
Everything has suddenly changed.
You have changed everything.
I have never felt this way before
like I do now.
Never cried like a fool...
like I'm crying now.
You'll soon leave with
your boyfriend. What will I do then?
Thinking of this makes me upset.
I shouldn't be upset, right?
You get what I'm trying to tell you,
don't you?
Why did you have to come
into my life, Rinku?
Why?
You belong to someone else,
then why...
I'm not angry that
the wedding got called off.
I'm falling for you.
I don't know what to do,
and this is driving me mad.