The fielder's running after the ball...
but the ball's already across the boundary line.
This has happened often.
If Pakistan wants to win the match then they
don't have a better batsman than Afridi.
Shahid Afridi will
have to take charge here.
No one can doubt his ability.
But today is his opportunity
to show the world..
Yes...the game can change any moment.
Slow ball and Afridi has hit it...
Excellent shot...
and the ball's across the boundary.
And that's a four.
Bravo
Looks like your son is really eager.
Pakistan needs four more balls to win.
Have you thought of a name?
Shahid!
Why are you laughing?
What if it's a girl?
Girl?
- Hmmmm
Last ball...and Shahid
Afridi has swung his bat.
Congratulations.
What is your name?
It's Shahida.
Shahida! What a cute name?
Where are you from?
You will only talk
to your mother not me?
No...it's not that.
She doesn't talk to her mother either.
Why?
Shahida, it'll be dark soon.
Go home.
I'll bring your kids home
Rauf.
Rauf, where's Shahida?
She hasn't returned home yet?
- No, she hasn't.
Shahida!
- Shahida!
Rauf!
Rauf! Shahida!
- Shahida?
Shahida, Rauf
- Wait.
Rauf! Shahida!
- Just wait.
Since when have I been
telling you to take her
...to Delhi's Hazrat
Nizamuddin Auliya's shrine.
Even the mute start talking there.
I was five and hadn't spoken a word.
And I was taken there.
And you began to speak?
Would you like to
hear me say something?
But Delhi's in India now.
So what?
It's not in America, is it?
It's easier to go to America, father.
It was different earlier,
it was the same country.
And you're forgetting that
I served in the army for 5 years.
The Indians won't give me a visa.
I will take her.
At any cost..
I'll do anything so that
my girl can speak, go to school.
I have decided.
I will take Shahida to Delhi.
"There are many aspects
of the benevolent Lord."
"He who is blessed by His grace.."
"..fortune too smiles on him."
Goodbye.
- Goodbye.
"Have mercy on me."
"The Benevolent one
is my only refuge."
Shahida Rauf
Yes.
"Nizamuddin Auliya!"
"Bless me with your grace."
No prayers have ever gone unanswered..
...from Memboob-e-llahi's threshold.
Just see.
Your daughter will chirp like a bird..
...as soon as she gets to Pakistan.
God willing.
God willing
Why has the train stopped?
It's nothing, Ma'am
The tracks ahead
are undergoing repairs.
It'll be fixed soon, don't worry.
Go to sleep!
Fine, let's all sleep.
Shahida.
Shahida!
What happened?
I can't find my daughter.
Shahida!
Pull the chain!
The Indians are saying
they didn't find your daughter.
But they will look
again in the morning.
Sir, please listen to me.
It's just five minutes away.
Please let me go,
I will look for her myself...
It maybe 5 minutes away,
but it's across the border.
In a different country.
So what if it's a different country?
I want my daughter back.
Try to understand ma'am,
you'll need a fresh visa to go back.
Be patient,
your child will be found.
How?
You don't get it.
My child can't speak.
She's absolutely alone
in an unfamiliar country.
You all can do nothing.
I will find Shahida myself.
Stop her.
- Shahida!
Shahida!
Calm down! Have faith in God.
Calm down, dear.
There must be some god-sent in India.
...who will look after our Shahida.
Calm down.
"Ram Lakhan Janki.."
"Glory to Lord Hanuman."
"Glory to Bajrang Bali."
"Break the bones of the enemy."
"The drums are echoing hard."
"Whether it's London or Lanka."
"It's resonating all around,."
"Glory to Thee."
"The drums are echoing hard."
"Whether it's London or Lanka."
"It's resonating all around,."
"With Your blessings
conferred on us."
"We've no fears or apprehensions."
"We'll dance up a storm."
"When He works His miracle."
"You'll know the difference."
"Come and take learn
this mantra from me."
"Come and take it."
"Give a hug to anyone
you come across."
"Come and take it."
"Let's take a dip in the sea of fun."
"Now let's take a selfie."
"I'm a simple guy,
with no crooked ways."
"You won't find anyone like me,
on the moon or on China".
"I always did what my heart said.."
"..but never broke anyone's heart."
"Always immersed in the
devotion of Lord Hanuman."
"I never make tall claims."
"I never brag either."
"I am happy in my own world,
everyone watches me."
"I am always immersed in
the thoughts of Bajrang Bali."
"I've a big heart like
Lord Hanuman's mace."
"Just like you'll find Lord
Ram residing in Hanuman's heart."
"You will always find
Lord Hanuman in my heart."
"You're my drama, you're my cinema."
"if You're with me."
"You're my earning, and my policy."
"Since you're with me."
"No boundaries can ever stop me."
"if You're with me."
"My elated heart says..."
"Feel the waves of fun."
"Again.."
"Come and take it."
"One, two, three.."
“Louder?
"Come and take it."
"Give a hug to anyone
you come across."
"Come and take it."
"Let's take a dip in the sea of fun."
"Now let's take a selfie."
"Glory to Bajrang Bali."
"Break the bones of the enemy."
- "Now let's take a selfie."
Brother, what's a selfie?
When you take your own'... picture
That's a selfie.
Brother, you were dancing like a star.
I always get immersed
in the devotion of Bajrang Bali.
Yes, brother.
Please get bread for the kid.
But she's asking for two.
You must have a name.
Sita-Gita.
Payal-Puja.
Brother, I think she's deaf.
She heard me order the bread?
Yes, that's true.
Let me ask.
Name?
She's illiterate.
Why don't you write
it in Sanskrit instead?
She's a 5 year old kid.
Eat all you want.
Why are you following me again?
Oh...
...here you are.
Did you get separated
from your parents?
Say something.
What is this mess?
Now you're under
Bajrang Bali's refuge.
This is a miraculous temple.
Your parents must be looking for you,
just like you are looking for them.
They will come here.
Just join your hands...and sit here.
Like this.
And I...
I'll be seeing you.
If it takes them longer,
then eat that apple.
Don't stay hungry.
Come on.
Stop the bus!
No, no, no, no!
You can't leave this child here.
- Why not?
Her parents will come here
to file a complaint, right?
And what if they don't?
If they don't? Why?
Why not?
Look at her face.
That's fine, but still..
...you can't leave her here.
- Why not?
Look at her face.
And now see their faces.
Criminals,
thieves, drunkards, pickpockets.
And this is a Police Station,
not an orphanage.
But.. - Well, write down
your details on this.
If I find out anything about this kid,
I will call you up personally.
And till then?
Till then...
Hail Lord Ram!
Hail Lord Ram?
This isn't your home?
Where is it?
Must be somewhere.
I know, I'll tell you names of cities.
And if your home is
any one of these places..
...then just raise your hand.
How?
Okay.
Delhi.
Meerut.
Faridabad.
Gwalior.
Jhansi. Patiala.
Amritsar. Jodhpur. Jaipur.
Srinagar, Pathankot, Shimla, Ambala.
Baroda?
Rampur?
Is it Dehradoon?
Kasauli?
Pratapgarh.
Are you from Pratapgarh?
- Yes.
Me too.
- Really?
Swear on Bajrang Bali.
I live next to Neeli Phatak.
That's where my in-law's home is.
That makes us relatives.
These days I am staying in Delhi.
Why Delhi?
Job...or girl?
It's a long story.
Tell us, It's not like
we are waiting to catch a bus.
Yeah, tell us.
Tell us.
You don't say anything?
Would you like to hear our story?
I am Pawan.
Pawan Kumar Chaturvedi.
But everyone calls me Bajrangi.
You can call me brother..
How old are you?
Six!
Then you call me uncle.
Uncle will be right.
My father, Diwakar Chaturvedi..
...was the postmaster in Pratapgarh.
"Come and take it."
His name justified his qualities.
My father knew all the four Vedas.
But I couldn't even
remember the 4 times tables.
Four eights are..
Twenty Two.
No!
Twenty-five.
No, twenty-seven.
Twenty-eight...Thirty.
Father!
For father, physical health
was as important as mental wellness.
Bravo. Come on.
Scholar plus Wrestler. Wow!
But I failed in that too.
Hold him.
Stop laughing. Pawan.
Forget it. You will never learn.
You can never do anything.
How can I help it
if I feel ticklish while wrestling!
But this glory wasn't enough for
Mr. Chaturvedi.
My father was also the chief
of the Pratapgarh branch.
Neither education,
nor wrestling or politics.
I wasn't interested
in any of father's subjects.
That's why he gave me a special name.
What?
Zero!
What happened?
Fail!
It took me 20 years
to pass 10th High school.
Between High school and graduation..
...I failed 10 times.
By now father had also given up on me.
What happened?
Fail!
Did you pass?
Oh, God!
Fail!
My friends told me to cheat...but, I was
A devotee of Bajrang Bali after all
I said, I would rather
fail than cheat.
So I attempted the exams 11th time.
Welcome.
I am sure you've broken
your own record in failing.
Father... - When you have
already failed 10 times..
...why did you have to humiliate
me again, for the 11th time.
Why?
I've accepted that you're a fool,
that you're stupid and useless.
You're a zero.
Listen.
- What? Hear what?
You have failed 10 times.
And failed me 20 times.
Listen to me, father.
- What's left to hear or say anymore?
If you want to do something for me..
...then do me a favor and go away,
to Delhi.
I have heard that there is a dearth
of useless people in that city.
I have a friend there.
Dayanand.
He will get you a job some where
Father, I passed.
Wonderful.
What did your father say?
I am sure Mr. Chaturvedi
must be shocked.
I knew he would be shocked.
But I never thought he
would be so deeply shocked.
Why? What happened?
Father...
...I am going to Delhi.
And left for Delhi to
fulfill my father's last wish.
To see Dayanand.
"That's our brother Bajrangi."
Mister, I don't have change.
Give five rupees to madam.
Madam, please take 5 rupees from him.
Hail Lord Ram!
Do you have 5 rupees change,
so I can give you 10?
No, I don't.
What now?
- It's okay, you can keep it.
How can I do that?
I must give you 5 rupees.
Then give it to me.
- I can't do that either.
5 rupees are mine too
Look, mister.
It's okay. You can keep it.
I can't do that.
But of this, 5 rupees is yours.
Then give it to me.
But 5 rupees are mine too.
Sister! Sister!
Sister!
What?
- It's your money.
I don't want 5 rupees.
Take it please.
Then give it.
Took all of it?
Half of it is mine.
Do one thing,
get change from that stall.
Please give me change.
Hold on.
Come on.
Stand up.
Straight.
Come on. Come on.
Sir...break the arm-lock,
break the arm-lock.
What?
Up...up...up!
Up!
Wring his arm.
Wring it.
Pin him down!
And one, two...three!
"Come and take it."
Hail Lord Ram!
My self...
You!
You! Here?
Are you following me?
No, madam, l..
- What?
I said I don't want the money.
Do you know him?
He was in the same bus as I.
Followed me all the way home.
Neither am I following anyone.
I swear on Bajrang Bali.
I am from Pratapgarh,
here to meet Mr. Dayanand.
Who are you?
Pawan Chaturvedi,
Mr. Chaturvedi's son.
Chaturvedi's son?
- Yes. Bajrangi!
Put him down.
Here you go.
- That's all.
Eat some more, it's our specialty.
We sprinkle salt while
boiling the potatoes.
That's why they are so good.
Please eat.
Is someone cooking meat?
It's the house next door.
They're Muslims.
Start cooking early in the morning.
In my manor,
that is the Harvansh Trivedi Manor..
...I made it clear, no rooms will
be given to people from other caste..
Brother...tell us what you do.
I've come to Delhi in search of work.
Can't he get some job in your school?
Wow, you too.
What?
You still study in school?
No, I teach there.
Go with Rasika tomorrow to her school.
She will definitely get you a job.
Yes.
Hail Bajrang Bali.
There are a lot of monkeys here.
Will you keep bowing to them all day?
Here.
Take this...Keep this under your
cot before you sleep.
Along with monkeys; you will
also find a lot of mosquitoes here.
Give me a minute
Give me your hands.
Excuse me.
Trust me.
Come on.
One, two, three, four, five.
And yes.
Please don't call me sister,
My name is Rasika!
Good morning, ma'am.
Hail Sri Ram.
Bajrang Bali.
Break the bones of the enemy.
"The heart's looking for sanctity."
"A wish that needs to be fulfilled."
"Something I never...
ever wished for."
"Why do I want it now?"
"The heart wants the
feeling of your existence."
"I want...you."
"Day and night, all I want is you."
"I want you."
"Every time, All I want is you."
"I insist that every
time I want only you."
"I don't want anyone
else other than you."
"I want you to be my guardian,
in every journey."
"You're the one I want
for the rest of my life."
"if you're the sweet
pain in my heart.."
"I don't want any cure."
"I want you coursing through
my veins like blood."
"No matter what the consequences.."
"..but this is the beginning I want."
"I want you."
"Day and night, all I want is you."
"Every time, All I want is you."
"I insist that every
time I want only you."
"My wounds need to be touched by you."
"My flames need your heat."
"I want you in the
world of my dreams."
"I want to see only
you when I open my eyes."
Then what?
What?
Then one day... Mr.
Diwedi and his son Purshottam arrived.
Come, Mr. Diwedi.
Welcome.
Take a seat.
How are you, Purshottam?
Sit.
Please, sit.
Pawan, please go get Rasika.
- Yes.
Rasika.
The boy and his family are here.
If Bajrang Bali someday
graces you with His presence..
...what will You ask him for, Pawan?
Me..
Do you know what I'll ask for?
Give me your hand.
Don't you trust me?
Where's Rasika?
- She's coming.
I think my daughter's feeling shy.
Father, you've always said..
...every girl tries to see the image
of her father in her future husband.
I see your image only in Pawan.
Rasika!
Forgive me, Mr. Diwedi.
We cannot go ahead with this alliance.
My daughter doesn't want to.
You could've told us earlier.
Why invite us home and humiliate us?
Forgive me.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
Who wants to stay here?
Sir...
You cannot get engaged to Rasika.
Until you're worthy of her.
And my first condition is...a house..
...which you'll buy with
your hard-earned money.
You only have six months.
Otherwise...I'll find
someone suitable for her.
By the way, I never asked you before.
What's your age?
Bravo, Bajrangi. Congratulations.
You did it.
Wow!
In a couple of months..
...I'll arrange for
the rent and deposit money.
You will. You will.
Of course.
Don't worry.
Dhanbad.. Etah...Kalmganj...Agra?
Hail Bajrang Bali.
If she can't speak...
then how do you know she's a Brahmin.
She's so fair, must be a Brahmin.
How long is she going to stay here?
Until we don't find her parents?
And when will they be found?
When Bajrang Bali wills
Have you ever travelled
by an airplane?
I did, once.
Do you know what they say?
When the pressure drops..
...first put on your own oxygen mask,
then help others.
How long will you keep
doing social service?
Think about your own life.
Get a decent job.
Find a nice home.
And if you can't, then tell me now.
So you don't waste
your time nor Rasika's.
Will this fit a six year old?
Yes.
- Pack it.
By the way, Pawan..
...if we don't find Munni's parents,
will she stay with us..
...even after we're married?
Why won't we find her parents?
What if she doesn't have any?
Who doesn't have parents?
Orphans!
Who is your favorite player?
Dhoni!
Virat Kohli.
Yuvi!
Shikhar Dhawan?
Sehwag?
These are the only players.
I bet you know nothing about cricket.
Munni is not an orphan.
Otherwise Lord Bajrang Bali
would've given me some indication
Pawan.
When did He tell you
that she has parents?
Munni!
- What happened to Munni?
What happened to Munni?
Where is Munni.
Well...l can't find her anywhere.
What?
We were just eating together,
suddenly she disappeared.
Munni isn't
on the terrace either.
Oh, God!
Munni! Munni!
Munni!
Mun...
Pawan!
Chicken barra,
Chicken Muglai, chicken hariyali..
...chicken lollypop,
chicken kadai, chicken tawa..
...chicken tandoori, chicken masala,
chicken kohlapuri, chicken afghani..
...chicken kashmiri, chicken
hyderabadi, chicken fried rice..
...chicken noodles,
chicken Manchurian, chicken 69..
...chicken Kofta,
Chicken Korma, Chicken Chaudhary..
Mister..
- Yes, sir.
Serve your best item to her.
- Okay.
She's so fair,
I thought she must be a Brahmin.
Must be a Kshatriya.
They eat meat and also
have a fair complexion.
Yes, she must be a Kshatriya.
Why is Munni crying?
"I am hungry."
"I very am hungry."
"The rooster's croak
sounded melodious to me."
"Chowk Chandani,
Choudhary restaurant."
"Day and night...
the place is always crowded."
"Chowk Chandani,
Choudhary restaurant."
"Day and night...
the place is always crowded."
"Half the food's non-veg
and other half is veg."
"Tell me clearly...
what your intentions are."
"Do you want Nan or Roti."
"Do you want Rann or Boti."
"Order whatever you want,
this is going to difficult."
"A little Biryani Bhukhari,
and a little Nalli Nihari."
"Bring everything...so I can
break the norms today."
"The chicken's clucking from
the kitchen, cuck-a-doodle-doo."
"The only cure to your hunger
is the chicken, cuck-a-doodle-doo."
"The chicken's saying today,
cuck-a-doodle-doo."
"The only way to fill your stomach
is a chicken, cuck-a-doodle-doo."
"The chicken's clucking from
the kitchen, cuck-a-doodle-doo."
"The only cure to your hunger
is a chicken, cuck-a-doodle-doo."
"The chicken's saying today,
cuck-a-doodle-doo."
"The only way to fill your stomach
is a chicken, cuck-a-doodle-doo."
"My stomach churning,
I am really hungry."
"My throat's really dry."
"Every part of my
body is getting weak."
"And my entire body's shivering."
"My hunger's growing."
"Like making a mountain
out of a mole."
"My face has turned pale too."
"Every part of my
body is getting weak."
"And my entire body's shivering."
"Get me the Koftas and the Kormas."
"The Shorbas and the Shawrma."
"Let break all the fasts."
"A little Biryani Bhukhari,
and a little Nalli Nihari."
"Bring everything...
so I can break my norms."
"The chicken's clucking from
the kitchen, cuck-a-doodle-doo."
"The only cure to your hunger
is a chicken, cuck-a-doodle-doo."
"The chicken's saying today,
cuck-a-doodle-doo."
"The only way to fill your stomach
is a chicken, cuck-a-doodle-doo."
"The chicken's clucking from
the kitchen, cuck-a-doodle-doo."
"The only cure to your hunger
is a chicken, cuck-a-doodle-doo."
"The chicken's saying today,
cuck-a-doodle-doo."
"The only way to fill your stomach
is a chicken, cuck-a-doodle-doo."
Mandi?
Ayodhya.
Patparganj.
- Muradabad?
Jhumri Talaiyya?
Asansol.
Come, dear.
Look, I've so many colorful bangles.
They're really nice.
Come, dear.
Take it.
My bangles.
Mister, please pay for the bangles.
Please.
Munni.
We don't want them.
Forgive her, she's just a kid.
It's okay.
- Munni, it's wrong to steal.
Come, let's apologise to Bajrang Bali.
Lord...you know..
Lord, you know...l went to
a non-veg restaurant yesterday.
Because of Munni.
But I swear I didn't eat anything.
Munni did.
Munni...concentrate.
Please forgive me.
You know...l feel helpless
in front of Munni.
What to do?
Bajrang Bali,
you've already hinted..
...that Munni is a Kshatriya,
and not a Brahmin.
Right..
Munni?
Munni!
Munni! Munni!
Bajrang Bali, please forgive Munni.
After all she's naive.
She doesn't know the difference
between temples and mosques.
Come on, go in.
Munni!
Are you crazy?
What happened?
Munni..
Where's Munni?
What?
- She's that.
She's a Muslim.
Munnni?
- Yes.
Didn't you notice how she
was eating chicken last night?
And now, she's in there..
...she covered her head with
the veil and was reading something.
But where is she?
What will your father say?
Pawan, where is Munni.
She cheated us.
She cheated us?
She's just a 6 year old.
Away from her home,
separated from her parents.
The poor girl can't even speak.
What will your father say?
She belongs to a different caste.
Pawan, don't be silly.
Do you know why I love you?
Because you have a clean heart.
Different caste...different people,
it's all nonsense.
Don't waste your time
in these stupid things.
I can't explain to father.
But I can at least tell you
Come on. Munni is all alone inside.
Where is Munni?
Munni.
Pakistan needs 10 runs in 7 balls.
He picked that up...
and the ball's in the air.
Caught. He's caught it.
Come on, India. Munni clap...
Amazing, boys. Really amazing.
Father will throw Munni
and me out of the house.
Only if he finds out.
What do you mean?
Who will tell him?
I will.
Are you crazy?
Oh no...Afridi's back on strike...my god!
Oh no!
Have you read the Mahabharat?
You must have seen it on television.
What does Lord Krishna say to Arjun?
What?
One must have an honest heart,
and that you do.
Your job is to get Munni home.
After that you can tell
father anything you want.
Afridi is trying to stay on crease.
The ball's in the air again,
will it cross the boundary?
There's a fielder positioning himself
under the ball, but it's across the boundary.
Pakistan needs 3 runs to win.
Munni, what are you doing?
It's the wrong team.
Be quiet everyone.
This is a tense situation.
The ball's across the boundary again.
This is a magnificent
win for Pakistan.
Oh...God! What has he done?
Munni, what are you doing?
That's the enemy's team.
What's wrong with her?
I wonder what's wrong with her.
She doesn't get it.
What is Munni doing?
Munni.
Why is she dancing?
Munni, what's wrong with you?
What is she doing?
Munni...Pakistan!
You brought her home
saying she's a Brahman.
Are you the only kind-hearted
man on this planet?
The only benefactor of
sad people around the world.
There must have been other
people in Kurukshetra.
Why didn't they take her home?
Sir, I didn't do anything.
She was following me.
Tomorrow morning you will
take her to Pakistan embassy
Father..
Look, the people of her country..
...brutally kill
the people of my country
But father, what's Munni's fault?
- I know.
But she belongs to that country.
Look, I am not cruel.
But I can't tolerate
her in my house anymore.
Make arrangements to send her back.
Immediately.
"Pakistan, come to your senses!"
"Release Karamjeet Singh."
""Pakistan, come to your senses!"
"Pakistan, come to your senses!"
"Release Karamjeet Singh."
Next
Please application passport.
I don't want to go to your country.
I just came to drop her here.
Send her back home, she's a Pakistani.
Hello, dear. What's your name?
She can't speak.
Where's her passport?
- I don't know where her passport is.
Then how do you know she's Pakistani.
Yesterday when Pakistan
won the match..
...she started dancing
in front of everyone.
In front of Sir too...
And she even kissed the
Pakistani flag, on television.
So that makes her Pakistani?
How do you know her?
I met her in Kurukshetra.
What was she doing there?
- How do I know?
Go away, we cannot do
anything without a passport.
Why not?
I am saying she's a Pakistani.
Send her home.
Have you lost your mind?
Don't you have any common sense?
Go away, there are
other people in the queue.
I don't care, I will leave her here.
Look, this is my last warning,
if you don't leave..
...I will call security
and throw you out.
And I'll call my people and..
...throw you all out of the country.
Throw me out?
I am Indian myself. A Jaini! Go away.
I work for the Pakistani Embassy.
Security. Security.
Throw him out.
"Pakistan, come to your senses!"
"Release Karamjeet Singh."
Some people tried to scale
the walls of the High Commission.
Around 14 people were
injured in this scuffle.
Pakistani High Commissioner,
Abdul Bashir..
...has said in an official
statement, that..
...keeping the security of
the High Commission's staff in mind..
...he's shutting down all counselor
and visa services for a month.
Wonderful, Bajrangi.
I told you to send the girl back..
And you shut-down the embassy instead.
So Munni will live
with us for another month.
There's no need for that.
Govind was saying that..
...there's a travel agent close
to his office, on Purani Sadak.
He'll make all the arrangements.
No, mister,
we don't make Pakistani passport.
Why not?
- Why?
Well...l have never made one.
People come here
for American passports..
...Canada as well.
England, Germany...even Japan.
But if Munni's from Pakistan,
then why will she go to Germany?
True.
But sorry,
we can't make Pakistani passport.
Strange.
Let's go, Munni.
Mister...
I have a 'without-passport' route.
Meaning?
I mean I know some people..
Who can help cross the border...
Really?
- Yes.
I can request them.
Please do it.
I am in real trouble with this girl.
Fine, I'll have a word with them.
But...do you have 150,000?
150,000?
4-4-4-4...
5-5-5-5...
25,000!
26, 27...
What's this, Rasika?
I withdrew it from the bank.
What have you done, Rasika?
This money was..
I know.
This money is for
the deposit of our house.
But right now...it's more important
to send Munni home.
No, Rasika.
If I don't buy a house, father
will get you married to someone else.
My innocent Bajrangi.
You still don't understand, do you?
Even the Lord...can't separate
us in this lifetime.
Swear on Bajrang Bali.
How will those agents
find Munni's parents?
These agents have many connections.
Look, mister. Don't worry.
I'll call you once we're there.
Here's my number.
As soon as Munni is
united with her parents..
...please call me.
- Of course.
Well...we should leave now.
Come on.
Don't cry, Munni.
Uncle's taking you home, to Pakistan.
He's taking you to your mom.
Come on, dear.
Munni, this isn't your country,
you cannot stay here.
And I can't go there.
Come on, dear.
Since I met you things
have been getting worse for me.
Finally you have an
opportunity to go home.
Now let go of me.
I beg you. Let me go.
Go back to your home.
I beg you!
"You let go of my hand."
"I am no longer in your company."
"I've lost myself looking for you."
"Why does my heart beat so slowly?"
"Why are my eyes filled with tear?"
"What have I become for you?"
"Since we met...l feel capable."
"Since we met...l achieved everything."
"With great difficulty...the
destination became easy."
"Because you're the heartbeat
and I am the heart."
How much?
25 rupees.
"The way you would get upset."
"And I would console you."
"While looking for your
smile...l found happiness."
"Every time you drifted apart."
"And I brought us close."
"While looking for your footsteps,
I found myself."
"Since we met...l found my destination."
"Since we met...l found my shore."
"Since we met...my
destination became easy."
Mister, where is that kid.
- Which kid?
The same one who was on your rickshaw
- There.
Hey, boy.
Hail Sri Ram.
Did you see a small girl here?
Her name is Munni.
She just arrived here.
Come here.
I'll be your Munni..
- Let go, sister.
Sister?
Do I look like your sister?
Munni!
Are you crazy?
Munni! - Why the hell you
going on screaming for Munni?
Munni!
Not yet, close the door.
Where are you going?
- Stop him.
What are you doing?
Munni!
Who is he?
Get the girl back.
Let's sit down and talk, please.
Now?
Now I'll take Munni home myself.
Don't be crazy, Pawan.
You don't have a passport or a visa.
Nor do you know anyone there.
We'll find a way.
'All comforts of the
world lie at your feet.'
'Devotees feel fearless
under your benign Protection.'
'One is freed from all
the sufferings and ill fates'
'He who adores and
remembers Shri Hanuman.'
I don't have a passport
or visa...nor any connections.
But just like Bajrang Bali,
Lord Ram resides in my heart too.
And nothing is impossible
for such a person, Rasika.
Hail Sri Ram!
Stop right there...
Who are you?
This is my area.
So when did I say this is my area?
Are you trying to cross the border?
Let's see how you cross the border...
It'll cost you 25,000...cash.
If you have the cash,
then come along.
Otherwise get lost.
- Come on, Munni.
The border's got electric
fences all around.
440 volts.
It reduces anyone to ashes.
Listen... Look here.
Mohammad Ali Jinnah!
Have you ever seen him?
This is Pakistani currency.
Gandhi isn't going to work there.
Come, Munni.
- Listen.
Don't you get it?
If you go this way,
the BSF will spot you.
Listen here...
They will shoot you first
and then ask your ghost
...whether you're from here or there?
Listen...it's not easy
to cross the border.
I have...connections.
On both sides.
Come on, get in the car.
It's for the best interest of the kid.
It'll only cost you 50,000.
But you just said 25,000.
25,000 for one person.
Why will Munni pay, she's going home?
Going home?
That is when I decided that I myself
will take Munni back to Pakistan.
Wow!
I knew the moment I saw you
that you re a very righteous man.
Listen...on the other
side of the fence..
...the Pakistani army takes
rounds in every 10 minutes.
There are four tunnels
under the fences.
We'll have to crawl through
the tunnel within 10 minutes..
...and get to the other side.
You see those sand dunes
we need to get behind them.
And then...Welcome to Pakistan!
Come!
I will go only after
taking permission.
What? What will you take?
I'll take permission
from the Pakistani Army..
...and then go into Pakistan.
This isn't the place to crack jokes.
Let's go. Come on.
I am a devotee of Bajrang Bali.
Never do anything on the sly.
Are you crazy?
They will shoot all of us.
Come on, let's go.
Munni.
Munni, we'll first take permission.
We'll take permission..
I knew the moment I saw you...
that you're crazy.
Munni, you tell him.
You fool,
the camels are coming this way.
Come on, run.
Come on, or you will die.
You won't live through this.
Munni, we'll take permission first.
Who are you?
Hail Sri Ram.
Are you Indian?
Yes. But Munni is Pakistani.
She got separated from her parents.
I am taking her to Pakistan
to reunite them.
Sir, this is a story
we've never heard before!
Then why didn't you just leave?
I am a devotee of Bajrang Bali.
Never do anything on the sly.
I was waiting here
for your permission.
This is the Pakistan border
If at all you wanted permission...
then why didn't you
go to the Pakistan embassy?
I did go to the Pakistan embassy,
the one in Delhi.
Isn't it, Munni? Didn't we?
But they threw us out.
So how did you get here?
Boo Ali brought us here.
- Boo Ali.
Boo Ali is an agent.
He was saying that he has
connections on both sides.
What nonsense.
How did you get on
this side of the fence?
Through the tunnel.
We crawled all the way.
It's a straight tunnel.
Tunnel? Where?
He is standing on it.
Take a look.
- Sir.
Look
Sir, he's definitely a spy.
Shall we arrest him?
No.
Throw them back into the same tunnel
And fill the tunnel with sand.
Run away or else we will shoot!
Go on.
Hail Sri Ram!
What..
Beat him.
Munni...don't worry.
It's nothing.
Doesn't hurt at all.
Doesn't hurt..
It does hurt.
All this is scaring her, that's why...
Leave him!
How did you come back?
There's another tunnel over there.
Who told you about this tunnel?
- Boo Ali.
Boo Ali.
Sir, I've promised Bajrang Bali..
...I won't rest until I
reunite Munni with her parents.
I will teach you..
- Rafiq! Stay back!
Look, I wouldn't have
allowed you through here..
...even if you had
a passport and a visa.
Go back right now.
It's for your best interest.
Sir, I promise I
will return to India..
...as soon as I find Munni's parents.
Look, exactly 10 minutes later..
...we'll come back
here doing our rounds.
Within those 10 minutes,
whether you go this way..
...or back there, we don't know.
But, sir..
- But.
But if I see you again,
I will definitely shoot you.
Come on.
And find out who the hell is Boo Ali?
- Yes, sir.
Hail Sri Ram.
Sir, he's definitely crazy.
You don't care about your life,
but think about this girl.
Sir, I could've disappeared
into the night before you returned.
But I am a devotee
of Bajrang Bali, and..
Yeah, we know.
You don't do anything on the sly.
And you've made a promise.
Don't you have anything else to say?
I promise you,
I will return to India..
...as soon as I take
Munni to her parents.
Just give me permission.
I told you to go, so why didn't you?
That wasn't any permission, sir.
It would've still been on the sly
Sir, he's completely crazy.
Fine, go.
Sir?
Sir? Sir?
Can I go, sir?
- Yes, go.
Munni, let's go.
If you truly are Bajrang
Bali's devotee, then do come back.
It's a promise, sir.
Hail Sri Ram!
You're right.
He's definitely crazy.
"You're my path."
"You're my companion."
"I found myself while
looking for you."
"I am your voice...you're my words."
"I heard what you never said."
"Since we met...l feel capable."
"Since we met...
I've achieved everything."
"With great difficulty...the
destination became easy."
"Because you're the heartbeat
and I am the heart."
Mister.
Yes, brother.
Can I get something vegetarian?
- What?
Vegetables.
Veggies.
There are vegetables in this.
There's beetroot, capsicum, peas.
Spinach too.
Full of vegetables.
No...only vegetables.
What's wrong? Is the kid unwell?
What's wrong, dear?
No, she's absolutely fine.
Then, are you unwell?
No.
Then why do you want only
eat vegetables?
Well, keep that one
and take this one away.
And get me some tea and bread.
Bilal.
If you serve me cold bread
again like yesterday, I'll whack you.
Understand.
Eat quickly,
Munni and let's get out of here.
Did you eat your fill, Munni?
Now we'll find your
parents very quickly!
Stop!
Wait.
Munni, why is that cop
coming this way? - Wait.
Where are the handcuffs?
- What handcuffs?
The one you stole from my belt buckle.
Who steals handcuffs?
Search his bag. Check it.
Wait. Wait. Look...Look...take a look.
Are there any handcuffs?
There are no handcuffs in it.
Not there?
And hers?
What will a small
girl do with handcuffs?
Show them, Munni.
Give it, dear.
Here...take a look.
Check it.
What's your name?
Pawan.
- Pawan what?
Pawan Kumar Chaturvedi.
People call me Bajrangi.
- We won't.
Are you Indian?
Yes.
Show me your passport.
I don't have a passport.
You don't have a passport.
Then how did you get into Pakistan?
I crawled under the fence.
- Under the fence?
Yes, but I took permission.
I don't like lies.
I don't lie,
I am a devotee of Bajrangi Bali.
You entered our country in
the dead of the night like thieves.
Do you know who does that?
Rats or spies.
I am not a spy.
And Munni is Pakistani.
She's Pakistani.
I see...she's Pakistani.
I see...she's Pakistani!
Yeah...and I am Sachin Tendulkar.
Arrest him.
Bring him along.
Come on.
People are coming from
Karachi to celebrate Eid.
He's back again.
Please...we'll miss the train.
People are coming Karachi..
What are you doing?
Stop them.
Please...we'll miss the train.
People are coming
from Karachi to celebrate Eid.
What an ungrateful man..
Go that way.
People are coming from
Karachi to celebrate Eid.
What are you doing, madam?
Please go that way,
we'll miss the train.
People are arriving in Karachi..
People are arriving
in Karachi to celebrate Eid.
What are you doing? Stop them.
Please go that way,
we'll miss the train.
People are coming from
Karachi to celebrate Eid.
This is Chand Nawab from Chawra
along with cameraman Kamil Yusuf.
What a rascal..
Why are you standing on the
middle of the road?
What nonsense.
You're blabbering here like a fool.
The police just caught an Indian spy.
Indian spy? Where?
At Bilal's eatery.
They are taking him
to the police station.
Come on.
This is breaking news.
Did Pawan call?
- No.
But he will soon.
He must have helped
Munni board the train by now.
Didn't you tell him to
call as soon as he got to Wagah?
I did, maybe he forgot.
Then you could've called him instead.
Hamid Sir...
We've reached the police station,
please come quickly.
Greetings.
Yeah, greetings.
Tell us about your mission.
- Mission?
Yes, I did take permission.
No, tell me in detail.
Start from the beginning.
How did you get into Pakistan?
I crawled under the fence?
How much are they paying
you for this dangerous mission?
Pay? Why will I get paid?
I am doing this willingly.
I see...so you're a patriot.
- What?
What do they call it?
Patriot!
You're a patriot.
- Without a doubt. What? Patriot, patriot
What's the role of the kid?
Get the kid in frame.
Munni's the main reason.
That's enough, get lost.
Get in front.
Hurry UP-
As you saw in our exclusive footage..
...An Indian spy was arrested
along with his 6 year old companion..
...from Chawra district.
The child's been trained so well..
...that she didn't even speak a word.
This is Chand Nawab, along
with cameraman Kamil Yusuf, Chawra.
Shall we do it once more?
- Got it.
Flabby police man.
Stop recording.
Sir.
It's an Indian number.
What happened?
His phone's switched off.
Sir, I just got an
explosive interview.
Of an Indian spy.
I swear...this will make
your channel no.1 in Pakistan.
It's Chand Nawab.
Says he has interviewed
some Indian spy.
What nonsense.
Tell him I am not here.
Shamsher sir isn't here.
- Oh no. that's a problem.
Anyway, ask him to call
me as soon as he gets back.
Until then I'll prepare a report.
Hello. Hello.
Hello.
What's your motive
behind coming to Pakistan?
How many times do I tell you?
I came here to unite
Munni with her parents.
Keep lying and you'll
never see daylight again.
I don't lie.
Where are you going?
What happened, Munni?
Do you know that place?
Is that where your home is?
Munni...
This is Munni's home.
What's going on here?
- We found it, sir.
We found Munni's home.
- What's this charade?
What's your name?
She's can't speak.
Can't speak?
Why? Has the cat got her tongue?
Let me see.
Show me.
Open your mouth.
According to our sources..
...the Indian spy is being
kept under tight security.
It's being said that he'll
be shifted directly to Islamabad.
Where are you shifting to?
Look.
Come quickly.
Come on. Get on.
I have the camera,
how are you going to shoot?
There...in the bus.
Come on.
Pedal harder!
You can't do it.
I am going to spy on this spy.
Let's take this, it is faster.
Where are you going?
Let's go on this.
Ticket.
"Thank god we got away Munni."
Hello.
Sir, this is Chand Navab,
from district Chawra.
That Indian spy is in the bus.
- Which bus?
The same bus I am in.
He's right in front of me,
come quickly.
You fool, which bus is it?
It's en-route to Alipur,
it's called Chhammo Diwani.
Ticket.
Do you recognize this place?
Don't joke, mister.
Just tell me where you want to go.
This child is from Pakistan.
I don't know how
she got to India. Alone.
I think she got separated
from her parents.
She can't speak,
but she recognizes this place.
I am sure she belongs
from somewhere here.
You're from India?
Yes!
How?
I crawled under the
fence of the border.
But with permission.
You came all the way to Pakistan..
...to find the parents of this child?
- Yes.
Why?
Surprising, brother.
I wish there were more people
like you in both our countries.
Show me the picture.
Sir...
- Speak properly.
Stop stammering..
He escaped, sir.
- What?
Does anyone recognize this place?
Take a good look.
Brother?
No.
There? Must be that one.
Quickly.
That one.
That way. Come on.
What's wrong, sir?
Did a man in a brown sweater
get on this bus, along with a kid?
No, sir. No such man got on this bus?
Has anyone seen a man
along with a small kid?
No, sir. We haven't.
No.
Chand Nawab said it was this bus.
Get down.
Sir, that girl was pointing
towards a picture of the mountains.
Maybe that's her home.
Where's the photo?
They took the photo.
Check all the buses on the highway.
Come on.
- Yes.
Either you're very
brave...or a big fool.
You just entered Pakistan,
without any fear...
This was the only way
to bring Munni to Pakistan.
Yes, that's okay.
But how will you find her parents?
Bajrang Bali will help me.
Even in Pakistan?
You'll be safe here tonight.
But brother, be sure to leave by dawn.
Goodbye.
- Goodbye.
What place is this?
- Mosque.
Forgive me, Bajrang Bali.
Forgive me.
Greetings.
What's wrong, young man?
Are you sick? You look restless.
What's wrong with me?
I am absolutely fine.
Then why are you standing out here.
Let's go in.
Hey...listen.
Why didn't you come yesterday?
Go on.
Sit in the class, I am coming.
I can't go in.
- Why?
I am not a Muslim.
So what, brother?
This place is open to everyone.
That's why we never lock the mosque.
Come on.
Come on, children, to your places.
So that's the case.
I've never been to
the mountainous regions.
But there are some children
in my class, who belong from there.
Let me ask.
Children.
Yes, teacher
Yes.
Everyone take a good
look at this picture..
...and tell me where it is.
And whoever gives the
right answer will get a reward.
Me! Me! Me! Me!
Stop.
Reverse...reverse...
Wasn't he with Chand Nawab?
Come here.
Listen.
Catch him.
Teacher, this is Switzerland.
Arshad, if you don't
know pass it to someone else.
Honestly,
teacher, this is Switzerland.
See...it's written here in English.
SWITZERLAND!
Munni, are you from Switzerland?
Catch him.
- Stop.
Stop.
Where are you going? Stop.
Such mesmerizing mountains
are found in Kashmir.
Kashmir?
Will I have to go back to India?
No, mister.
We have a part of it too.
What?
- Kashmir.
Dean
Stop, please keep these
weapons in your car first.
Priest, did you see
a stranger lurking around?
There are no strangers
in the house of God.
This stranger can be dangerous.
He's an Indian spy.
You think I have the
formula for the atom bomb..
...which he'll come here to steal.
But if you see any strange,
then do inform us.
Of course.
It's difficult to get out of here.
What now?
I have an idea.
Bajrang Bali how much more
are you going to test your devotee?
You made me sleep in the mosque.
Made me wear this burqha
Please help us find Munni's parents
before I get circumcised.
I'll be indebted to you.
What?
- Oh, God!
He's gone to Pakistan.
You said he'll take Munni
to Attari station and come back.
How could he go to Pakistan?
Who gave him passport and visa?
He's gone without them.
Without..
He's gone to Pakistan
without a passport and a visa.
Please calm down, you'll get sick.
You don't know what those
Pakistanis will do to him.
I can't handle even one.
And the priest has two.
The police must be
patrolling the roads.
Walk through the fields
to get to Khanewal.
Thank you.
You're doing a good deed.
I'll pray to Allah
that you find her parents.
Goodbye.
What do you say?
Hail Lord Ram?
Hail Lord Ram!
Shall we go?
This is all your fault.
If you hadn't been obstinate
about sending Munni home..
...Pawan wouldn't have gone himself.
He's badly in trouble because of you.
Now do something.
What can I do?
If you don't do anything, then
I'll go to Pakistan looking for him.
What?
Oh, God!
Without a visa!
I can't wear this anymore.
I can't breathe or walk.
Look, one of us has
to pose as the wife.
The police are looking
for two men along with a child.
Then you pose as the wife.
I see.
If anyone asks,
you will readily tell him..
...that my name is Pawan
Kumar Chaturvedi, I am from India.
I am a devotee of Bajrang Bali.
I took permission to get here.
And I have come crawling
under the fences.
Right, Munni?
Look, people are coming.
Cover your face. Come on.
And walk with some grace.
Munni...will you do one thing for me?
Munni is going to get caught.
Mister.
- She's safe.
This is wrong?
Things always go wrong when you lie.
You wait and watch.
You spoke again, dear.
Cover your face.
This car's just..
Mister, can I help you?
Come on.
Sit inside.
You hit the ignition,
when I tell you to.
Yes, did you find anything?
Takes time, mister. Takes time sir,
to find the right nerve.
Are you a mechanic or a physician?
Turn it on?
What did you do?
Again.
This is what I did.
You fixed it.
It's our duty to
help fellow companions.
Thank you very much.
- Goodbye.
Can I drop you somewhere?
What's your name, dear?
She can't talk, sir?
She's mute.
Yes.
How does a mother feel?
What do the doctors say, ma'am?
She can't talk either?
Same-to-same.
It's hereditary.
Oh my.
It's fate.
Yes, that's true.
You're heading towards Khanewal,
aren't you?
No. But don't worry,
I'll get you home.
No, no, no need to take the trouble.
Just drop us at the highway.
It won't be a problem at all.
I will tell one of my constables
And he'll drop you home in his jeep.
Yes..
Constable
Yes, I am the area inspector.
I was on leave today
But I am going back because
there's an emergency.
Emergency?
An Indian spy is at large here.
Let's see how long he can escape for!
Where's Chand Nawab?
- I don't know.
You don't know.
I don't know.
I swear I don't know.
The last I saw him,
he was boarding the bus after the spy
I tried calling him.
But his phone's switched off.
Call him right now...
in front of me...
It's switched off.
Come, mister.
I've reached my destination.
Now my man will take you to yours.
Sir.
- Sir.
Sir..
Come.
Hasan.
- Yes, sir.
Come here.
- Yes.
They are my special guests.
And he is a great mechanic as well.
Take them to their home in Khanewal.
Yes, sir. Come.
Thank you, sir.
No, thank you.
You really helped me a lot.
How about some snacks before you go?
No, we'll go.
- Come.
Come.
Come. Sit.
Carefully.
Goodbye.
Keep calling him every hour.
He'll pickup sometime.
Where is your house?
- Just a little ahead.
You don't know the way.
We're coming back after a long time.
Actually we ran away and got married.
So her father's angry with us.
This is it.
Stop here.
- It's this one.
Thank God we found your home.
You even forgot your home.
What can I say?
- It's alright.
Call Waqar.
Yes, sir.
What's the information
on that spy from headquarters?
Sir the spy's name
is Pawan aka Bajrangi.
And there's a local
journalist accompanying him.
Chand Nawab.
Come, I'll see you in.
- No, thank you.
Thank you for bringing us here.
Goodbye.
- Goodbye.
Take care.
Father. How are you?
Who are you?
- Forsake your anger.
Look, I've brought your
daughter and granddaughter.
Come, dear.
Who is this child
and what is she doing?
But I don't have a daughter.
There's no point in
arguing on the streets.
Let's go inside and you can scold me
as much as you want
I don't know you..
- We got married without your permission.
You're angry with us.
- But..
Hit me. Hit me. Hit me.
Hit me. Hit me.
- Uncle, forget it.
Oh come on. Hit me.
Hit me.
Let's go in.
Why do I go in?
- Forget it uncle.
Dean
Get my shoe.
Someone's barging in our house.
Oh God!
Come on.
Goodbye.
- Goodbye.
And there's a little girl with them.
Little girl? How old?
Around 5 or 6 years old.
5-6...years.
And she can't speak!
- She can't speak?
Yes, sir.
Don't just stand
there and stare at me.
Radio Hasan immediately.
Uncle.
- Who is it?
Uncle. Open the door.
Don't break down the door.
You?
- Where are they?
Who?
Your daughter and son-in-law.
How many times do I have to tell you..
...I don't have a
daughter or a son-in-law.
Where are those people..
...who were calling themselves
your daughter and son-in-law?
I don't know.
They left as soon as you did.
"One day draped in the color of love."
"On the corner of your lane."
"I'll write my name along with yours,
on your palm."
"Then you'll stop being formal."
"Lower your eyes.."
"..and rest your head
on my shoulder, O life..."
"Tell me something, O life."
"Where do I find you, O life."
"On a star filled night...we'll
read your letter together."
"And the page that you left blank."
"You can fill in your complaints,
and I will do it too."
"Just don't get angry, O life."
"Tell me something, O life."
"Where do I find you, O life."
"I exist where you do."
"Everywhere I see, I see you."
"You're the dawn of love."
"You're the prayers in my heart."
"You're the only one I speak of."
"You're the sights,
you're the breeze."
"You're the beautiful ambiance."
"You're peace, you're serenity."
"I exist where you do."
"Everywhere I see, I see you."
"You're the dawn of love."
"You're the prayers in my heart."
"You're the only one I speak of."
"You're the sights,
you're the breeze."
"You're the beautiful ambiance."
"You're peace, you're serenity."
"I exist where you do."
"Everywhere I see, I see you."
"You're the dawn of love."
"You're the prayers in my heart."
Chand Nawab, I was thinking about..
...turning myself over to the police.
Then somehow the police
will find her home.
Don't even think about it.
You will rot in jail
for the rest of your life..
And no one will ever have a clue.
And what do you think the police..
Are going to try as hard as you,
to find her house?
They will look for a day or two..
...and then they will
send Munnni to some orphanage.
I won't let that happen.
I promised Bajrang Bali..
...that I will take Munni home.
And I will.
Listen..
- I can clearly say that..
I challenge all of you..
There is one way to help you.
TV!
TV?
There is no weight in the story.
What are you saying, sir?
An Indian is helping
a Pakistani mute girl.
According to me it's
an explosive story.
No, but your story
on the spy was much better.
What about that?
But, sir, he's not a spy.
- That's that, then.
Goodbye.
Hello. Hello.
Sir..
What's the point
of showing this story?
A child will be re-united
with her parents.
Reunite with her parents?
Look, we sell news..
...this is not Hazrat
Amin Shah's shrine..
Where we re-unite the separated.
But, sir..
- Goodbye then.
Hello.
Hatred is easy to sell.
But love..
What is Hazrat Amin Shah's shrine?
It's a famous shrine.
It's said that everyone's
wishes get fulfilled there.
Why haven't we gone there yet?
- I see.
Every time you see a shrine or mosque,
you turn pale.
Remember when we
were in Alipur mosque.
You ran like you had seen a ghost.
I am willing to go
to any shrine for Munni.
Then let's catch a bus tonight.
It's ringing.
Kaamil.
- Hello, brother Chand.
Thank God. I was worried for you.
Where are you?
Is there anyone around you?
- No. There's no one.
Where are you? With that spy?
He's not a spy. He's a very nice man.
What do you mean by he's not a spy?
He only came here
to bring a girl home.
But where are you now?
We're going to Hazrat
Amin Shah's shrine.
It's said that everyone's
wishes get fulfilled there.
Okay, brother, take care.
Goodbye.
Come on.
"He comes to Your threshold
with a heavy heart."
"O Prophet,
you beckon anyone you want."
"I've come to thee
with my head bowed."
"if you're willing,
you can make all wrongs...rights"
Go on, I'll join you.
Where are you going?
"Fulfill my wishes, O Mohammad."
"I won't go back empty-handed."
"My eyes are filled with tears."
"And my heart's full of sorrows."
Move aside...move aside
Greetings.
This is Chand Nawab.
And today I am going
to tell you about a man..
...who entered our
country without a visa..
...by crawling under the border fences,
and his name is Bajrangi."
"I won't go back empty-handed."
"Fulfill my wishes..
- O Lord."
- Everyone's."
"Fulfill my wishes..
- 0 Prophet."
"Fulfill my wishes,
O benevolent master."
"I won't go back empty-handed."
Just like the police,
even I believed..
...that this man is an Indian spy.
But now...l know he is not a spy.
Then who is he?
Why did he come to our country?
What does he want?
Bajrangi is a common
man like you and me..
...and he has just one
motive for coming here.
Love.
His love for a 6 year
old Pakistani mute girl..
...who got separated
from her parents in India.
When all other options failed..
...Bajrangi had only this one option
left to reunite her with her parents.
"Look at what's happened to me.."
"..while searching for you,
0 Prophet."
"Look at what's happened to me.."
"..while searching for you,
0 Prophet."
Every channel has refused
to show this story.
They say it's nonsense.
No one's interested in it.
So please help Bajrangi Bhaijaan..
...so that he can take this kid home,
and return to his country..
...safe and sound.
"Console my heart, O Prophet."
"I've come from far...with
great expectations."
"Console my heart, O Prophet."
"I've come from far...with
great expectations."
"Bless me with your grace as well."
"Until you.."
"Until you...don't answer my prayers."
"I won't leave your threshold."
"Fulfill my wishes,
O benevolent master."
"I won't go back empty-handed."
"Fulfill my wishes, O Mohammad."
"You know what's in my heart."
"You've been counting heartbeats."
"My sighs will reach the moon."
"Your stars will answer my prayers."
"Someday the dawn will come,
O Prophet."
"Until you...don't answer my prayers."
"I won't leave your threshold."
"Fulfill my wishes,
O benevolent master."
"I won't go back empty-handed."
dum dum ali ali dum ali ali
dum ali ali dum ali ali
dum ali ali dum ali
ali ali dum ali ali dum
ali ali dum ali ali
dum dum ali ali dum ali ali
dum ali ali dum ali
Ya Ali...
Call him.
He's brought the police along.
Come here.
Ya ali...dum dum ali ali
Dum dum ali ali dum alia Ii...
dum ali ali dum ali
They are closing in...
He isn't answering.
Answer the phone.
- Why?
I'll tell you.
He picked it up.
Hello, brother Chand. Are you okay?
Yes.
Did you go to the shrine?
- Yes, I did last night.
To pray for Munni.
I see, so where are you now?
Now...we just left for Gojra
You left for Gojra?
I see.
- Okay, I'll call you later.
Goodbye.
- Take care.
Brother, finally you lied.
- No, I didn't.
But you made me lie.
- So what?
Haven't you see
Mahabharat on television?
Is it a movie?
Is it a new movie?
If you recognize this girl,
or know anything about her..
...then please leave your
phone number on this website.
We will definitely call you.
With cameraman Chand...
I have put shots of both
of you two in the video.
The internet is a powerful tool,
brother.
Did anyone leave their number?
Only a Few people have seen it so far.
It will grow soon.
Munni, do you want to watch?
Let me rewind it.
Move aside.
What happened, Munni?
What did you see, Munni?
Rewind. Rewind.
What happened, Munni?
Pause.Pause.Pause.
You know her?
Is she your mother?
Rewind. Rewind.
Look Chand Bhai, she got off the bus!
What time did that bus arrive?
Around 8:30.
Find out where the
8:30 bus comes from?
It's here. It's here.
Brother,
where is this bus coming from?
Where do you want to go?
We want to know where
it's coming from?
You're a strange man.
Strange or not, first tell
us where the bus is coming from?
Jehanabad.
Munni, is your village's
name Jehanabad?
And before that comes Ursa“.
Ursa“.
And before that comes Karimabad.
Karimabad.
And before that..
District Sultanpur.
District Sultanpur?
Munni, you're from Sultanpur!?
She is from Sultanpur.
Munni's from Sultanpur.
Sultanpur.
Sir.
Sir, take a look at this video.
Chand Nawab posted
this video yesterday.
And today I am going to tell you about...
This is just outside the mosque.
Sir, they never came to Gojra.
We checked all the houses,
offices and shops.
They aren't here.
Send pictures from this video
to all the inspectors in the area.
And stop all vehicles and check them.
Immediately.
- Yes, sir.
Did you spot your village?
Brother.
Listen to me carefully.
Come on, get down.
Bring the vehicle forward.
- Everyone get in a line.
Come up.
Hurry UP-
Come on.
Go ahead.
Take off your shawl!
Take it off!
Catch him. That's him.
Hey wait.
Catch him.
- Come on.
Where are you running off too?
Surround him.
Stop.
Catch him.
"Give me your slumber."
"And take my sights."
"May no one cast an evil eye on you."
"Give me your slumber,
take my sights."
"Your night has
finally seen the dawn."
"Since we met...l feel capable."
"Since we met...l achieved everything."
"With great difficulty...
the destination became easy."
"Because you're the heartbeat
and I am the heart."
Greetings.
This is Chand Nawab.
And today I am going
to tell you about a man..
...who entered our
country without a visa..
...by crawling under the border fences,
and his name is Bajrangi."
Just like the police,
even I believed..
...that this man is an Indian spy.
But now...l know he is not a spy.
Then who is he?
Why did he come to our country?
What does he want?
Bajrangi is a common
man like you and me..
...and he has just one
motive for coming here.
Love.
His love for a 6 year
old Pakistani mute girl..
...who got separated
from her parents in India.
When all other options failed..
Bajrangi had only this one option left
to reunite her with her parents.
Every channel has refused
to show this story.
They say it's nonsense.
No one's interested in it.
So please help Bajrangi Bhaijaan..
...so that he can take this kid home,
and return to his country..
...safe and sound.
If you recognize this girl,
or know anything about her..
...then please paste your
phone number on this website.
We will definitely call you.
This is Chand Nawab,
with cameraman Chand Nawab, Kashmir.
I don't care what the press, the
media and the common man are thinking.
For us he's an Indian spy.
But Sir, the child's
parents have confirmed
that she did get separated in India.
But, sir, the people of Pakistan
...are growing sympathetic towards him.
So then...tell the press and the media..
...that he has admitted
that he's an Indian spy.
Then we'll see about
the people's sympathy.
Tell your men to get
information from India quickly.
Sir.
This child couldn't speak,
I remember that clearly.
Yes, and this man brought her here.
He was saying she's lost.
Stop it.
Hello.
Sir, Kurukshetra Police Station..
...and our men at the Delhi
Commission have verified his story.
He did go there with this girl.
This man can't be a spy.
You don't get to decide who's what
That's my job!
Your job is to make him confess
...that he's a spy.
- But, sir..
And yes, if you can't
do this job then tell me now.
We have other capable officers.
And I think you might need a vacation.
They want Pawan's
confession at any cost.
All my life I've worked towards..
...the glory and protection
of this country.
But if this man..
If this man is thrown in Pakistani
jail for the rest of his life..
...then that will be against
the glory of our country.
And I won't let that happen.
Hello.
Who?
Hamid sir.
Yes, sir.
Yes.
Thank you.
Very good, sir.
Thank you, sir.
Get the camera out. Come on.
Get the camera out .
Come on.
Sir.
Sir, there's a new video
on the Bajrangi story.
Okay, roll the bulletin.
- Okay, sir.
Sister Rasika.
Brother Bajrangi's on television.
Pakistani reporter Chand
Nawab has posted a new video..
...of Pawan Chaturvedi,
aka Bajrangi Bhaijaan..
...who is locked up in Pakistan jail.
Pawan Chanturvedi,
or better known as Bajrangi Bhaijaan..
...is an Indian who risked
his life to reunite..
...a small child with
her parents in Pakistan.
Run this story immediately.
Why did Bajrangi do such a thing?
For money, fame...
No!
Bajrangi did this because
he has a clean and honest heart.
He did it because,
he didn't see Shahida as a Pakistani..
...but as another human being.
But unfortunately, this godsent
...is stuck amidst the
hatred between the two countries.
And today,
this hatred has forced Bajrangi..
...to hide like a criminal in Pakistan.
Let's end this hatred now.
And we need to do this.
We the people of both the countries..
...who want to raise our
children with love, not hatred.
So come, let's finish this hatred.
Tomorrow morning...let's together
head towards Narowal Checkpost.
What nonsense is this?
Seal the Narowal border.
Let the people from both the
countries come there and see to it..
...that no one stops Pawan Charutvedi,
my Bajrangi..
...from crossing the border!
Or stop him from going home.
With cameraman Kamil Yusuf,
this is Chand Nawab.
Chand...Munni?
Brother, we have fulfilled our
promise made to Bajrang Bali.
Munni...
Shahida.
Shahida is with her parents now.
Shahida?
Yes, Shahida.
Shahida.
Pawan.
Let's go, Pawan.
Come on.
Come.
Do come back.
And this time don't
crawl under the fence.
But with a proper visa.
I promise.
Come on.
Bajrangi Bhaijaan!
Stop.
Open the gate.
Sir, we have orders to arrest you.
If this man had risked his life..
...to bring back your lost child,
wouldn't you have opened the gate?
You know...l can't open the gate.
Bajrangi Bhaijaan!
Do you hear these voices?
It's the voice of
the people of Pakistan.
If they can see the difference
between right and wrong..
...then why can't you?
You're a soldier.
You know better.
We have orders, sir.
To stop this man from
crossing the border.
But...
There's just a handful of us..
...compared to the thousands of you.
Bajrangi Bhaijaan!
Do you understand?
- Shahida.
Bajrangi Bhaijaan!
Pawan.
See Pawan.
Pawan!
Un...cle!
Uncle!
Jai Shree Ram!
"Because you're the heartbeat
and I am the heart."
"Your abode."
"And your company."
"As I found your lane,
I found your home too."
"Your hand's still in my hand."
"You let go of my hand."
"Since we met...l feel capable."
"Since we met...l achieved everything."
"Since we met...
my destination became easy."
"Because you're the heartbeat
and I am the heart."
"I am your hope."
"And you're my sky."
"While looking for your stars."
"I found my dawn."
"You're close to my heart."
"I am your hope."
"While looking for a kin...l found your refuge."
"Since we met..."
"I've lost my mind."
"Since our heart united."
"I've gained everything I wanted."
"It was difficult...
but my destination's become easy."
"Because you're the heartbeat...
and I'm the heart."
"Since we met..."
"I've lost my mind."
"Since our heart united."
"I've gained everything I wanted."
"Since we met..."
"My destination became easy."
"Because you're the heartbeat...
and I'm the heart."