Dedicated
Ghetto
Come on, I'm coming again-
What Dad?
We are late
بريم بريم
They say that Rocky is the feast of brothers and sisters, but in our place (sister covenant of brotherhood)
A trick to make young boys brothers
Caim Eshid
..We are more afraid of magic than that
Do not let the girls of the neighborhood or their families turn us into brothers of the girls of the neighborhood
For all of us boys, we wake up at 5 in the morning and stand in the temple
But the bad news does not delay. See another boy martyred
Brother .. Brother
what happened?
I have bad news
Take a deep breath
Brother Bora, I have bad news that four boys have been martyred
The ghetto became his father's friend
Did his father come? Who brought it?
Your local kid, Aurora
The executioner came every year to see Aurora
Dadash Jaidio Uncle Notial
Please let me go carefree
Shall I worry?
Are you a taxi for me to be carefree?
Mr. Sharma and Pandy, come on
I did not do anything, please let me go
How do I let go? First, what is your relationship with Rito?
Reto J? Cdum Reto?
Grandmother is lying
I saw it myself and kicked it up to here
Are you kidding or not?
wait
Go call Rito
Now I understand who Rito is, I have nothing to do with him -
Shut up! Are you lying to your grandmother?
Dad, what are you doing? بفرما ريتو اومد -
The bride's chest is rocky
Take it
Take Eki and tie her hand
Yalla with a clause
What are you doing, Rito?
No, I do not want to
Close Close
Close it tightly
Rito No, what are you doing? ! این راکیه
no no
So sweeten his mouth
Sweeten your mouth
Congratulations .. Congratulations
Take it, I will not see you again, this is your sister
You made a bad nose at me! I will settle with you later
Uncle Notial was from Rito and I have three
Prepare the raki
I asked the fish what it's up to you
But he did not dare to answer, he was dumb
I said I dared to remember your grandfather, he was brave
He said to the English with a roar
If two states do not belong to me, I will set fire to London
Your grandfather was a cheetah; چیتا
Grandmother, my cheetah will come one day
Just like Grandpa
I saw these girls myself in the vegetable market, in the Gupta market
Everyone knows that there were two others before the fish
I say this is to release many girls
Everyone listens to English songs and shouts on the phone
I say look for the groom soon
And marry the nose with Rito
Otherwise, one day he will run away with one of the local boys
Don't tell Dad, the girls of the place of sisters and mothers
Isn't it a ghetto?
When God did not give me a sister, why should I call my nose a sister?
Aurora nose, the love of my shorts (childhood)
It is not an ordinary cracker
We used to go to school together from Atsheh brand every day
As children, we used to play with dolls and aunts
I did more homework than playing cricket
I was at their house every Eid
But I could never tell him what I wanted
Everyone here is sick of making boys brothers to other girls
But now is the time to fall in love, not to become a brother
If I did not get a nose tattoo, change my name
Do it right as if it were not breastfed today
Brother, should I send a friend request?
Send him brother without delay
It is not unlikely that he will not make a covenant of brotherhood with me at one time
"There is nothing to be afraid of in love" (referring to Sultan Khan's film)
If it was my sister's nose
I was your brother-in-law a long time ago
..Get it ... you opened it in our paws
Is it okay to go far?
They say 50
Then it is time to hit the yogurt
See you there! I took his name and your brother arrived
Agu
Brother, will you let me play ghetto today?
To play?
Your father is the captain from today
Really?
I told you
Honestly, if necessary, I will consult you
How can I contact you?
Give me your number
Dad, where was my cell phone?
Yes, where was your mobile phone?
Give your sister number
Ghetto I do not give my sister's first law to anyone
Your sister's number, isn't it your bank card password that you do not give to anyone?
So how do I text you?
Brother, if the law changes, I will give it to you
Wow, you have rules of flexibility
Okay, no problem, go warm yourself
Thanks Dadash Ghetto
Tirt hit the rock
Okay, don't make fun anymore, let's go
Well, let's win the game first
Brother, write a letter in the window
Then it will be clear what he thinks
It's a good idea, but what if we reveal it?
Haven't you written a letter yet?
When reading it, in fact, unlike the movie, the author's photo is not seen
I will tell him my heart first
I will send my name later
how are you? Excellent -
Bollywood Cinema Proudly Presents Www.Bollycine.Info
Aajo Breem Cheetah Briam
Brother Notial, Brother
Han
...that
You collect it
right Now?
Goto .. this .. Goto .. Goto
This card will be restored
You do not have to worry about leaving everything to me
what happened?
Geto go home
Where?
Go home, see your mother
Do not worry, I will bring the doctor
Go quickly
I don't know, he was walking and Yahoo fell
It will be good
What happened to Grandma?
Say something grandma
wake up
Ghetto .. Come here
what happened? See Grandma tasted, give her air -
Why do you blow it? Give mouth-to-mouth breathing
By mouth?
Give him mouth-to-mouth breathing soon
Well, I'm giving
Hurry, breathe through your mouth, let me breathe -
Give her a breath soon, Grandma?
What do you do in the ghetto? Why did you stare at your nose?
Look at Grandma, I'm breathing -
What are you doing? Give him mouth-to-mouth breathing
Please tell, whats the story of them big puppys .....
Ghetto, why are you licking? Go away
Let the doctor check
Doctor, see her, my daughter, be calm
Grand mother
!My God
I'm sorry, Mr. Notial, let your family know about this death
Dear Mom
Sister, do not cry. Where is Jaydio?
Jaydio Gone Mirat for three days
I have to say come back
Don't worry, take care of your mother
Rito, be with me, we must inform all the family
..Doctor died certificate
If you send one, I will give it to the clinic
Do not be upset I am
Take care of your mother
nose
Ghetto
Don't be afraid
: Specialized translation of our cultural and artistic media Translators: Bingsa and Huzair
I wish this night would never end
You and my grandmother's body will stay together for a long time
And I just watch and watch and watch
Bora Bora
Where is the ghetto? We have a competition
Are you crazy? Cancel quiz
Nose grandmother died
How did my grandmother die? Did you compete with us because of Gita?
Understand bore, my chance to get close to my nose in just 13 days
You manage Kara
Okay, but this time you finish the job
You win the game, I win the nose
go
Do not worry about anything
See Yes Dad -
Get all the items on this list
Eye
But you can't take your sister-in-law with you to the market alone
Go to the ghetto again, I brought home 400 rupees
Any papa
What a second? -
How long will this be?
In my lifetime, I made money by selling tickets or donating in general
2 minutes
Long live the mother goddess
Brother Jagren, we have some help
Of course
How much should I give you?
200to
Solve it
Solve it? Solve it -
Long live the mother goddess
Brother Jagren, we have some help
Well, give me 200 receipts
Long live the mother goddess
400 Rs
Morsi
Come and pack the equipment for 400 rupees
It takes ten minutes to collect them, right?
You see, you haven't eaten anything since last night, have you?
Shall we eat biscuit tea?
Yes, let's go
Two special
My nose I am very saddened by the death of your grandmother
But for 13 days I will not be by my side, I will stay
See what the funeral is said in English?
Funeral
You were rejected twice in the tenth grade
Not twice, not just once
Oh
I took a recruitment test this year
eh? this year?
But less than two years have passed since graduating from college
Yes, I took the IM test last year
As you know, private companies do not have job security today
Well listen to my Facebook post
My dear and old friends, tell me ... with tears
And I will send it to you from the bottom of my heart
I wrote that my grandmother died
Come on
Today is 4 pm for the funeral
We need your support and prayers for your grandmother's salvation and paradise
Is it good from the point of view of Aurora?
The best view
Post it?
Sure
My nose says
Can I send you a friend request on Facebook?
I also share more people in between
Send Han
Let's have tea
When the grandmother of the dead
Grandma's story ended and my story began
: Instagram and our official media telegram @BollyCineOfficial
Baby, if you want, I will give you my happiness so that I can be us
"Leave me in your heart and close the gaps"
I prayed and I just prayed that we would be together every day
"Do not protest in the slightest and be yours"
"I will be yours"
What I wanted for years "" He wanted, you .. you
"That dream in your eyes, you .. you"
"Peace of my soul"
"And your madness that exists"
I prayed and just prayed "" that I am more and more present day by day
"Let me not protest in the slightest and be yours"
"I will be yours"
You should have been to God
We set fire to Grandma on the sandals
The Ghetto Notial was the seat of parliament there
All the families were just ghettos ghettos, do this ghetto, do that
In other words, we have never had such a Barat in the place similar to the mourning of the grandmother (Barat: the groom's caravan)
You should have died
I had an order, but next time "we will dance at a wedding"
Waesta
Brother, today we have the right to water and flowers here
Yes, we are right
Without a doubt
You see, you have to leave the engine and go with the rickshaw
Yes, careless
Oh come on come on
good luck
How are you?
Who?
Pia .. Pia
What?
come
get on
Why are you laughing so much?
Brother, all your grandeur was questioned
I threw the whole ghetto
I will go first, you are the third and Bora is the eleventh
Did you drop your plan? Now gather up and go
What is it today, brother?
Are you a captain?
He does not know how to take the handle and becomes a captain
: The second law of life I do not tolerate insults, be careful
Take this one, otherwise I will empty my knots on this head
Go, otherwise you will see badly
be careful
go away
Unconscious brother
Its fragrance is still in my nose
He passed me so close
Unconscious comrade; It happens in love
پاشو بريم
No you go. Go
I do not want to start the game with you -
This is how my life started, now let me start the game
Ghetto .. he plays cricket. Aunt
Guto .. don't play cricket today
He plays, you said he must play
I made Ajoo the team captain
Yes, you are very kind
Listen to the ghetto
My responsibility has increased a lot
Grandma has just died and Rito has to get married
listen
Get these thoughts out of your heart. Goodbye
You see, I did all this at my grandmother's ceremony .. did you remember?
Han?
You helped me for four days, now you want to leave me alone?
Rocky tie my hand?
Today I will finish your story with Rocky
That's right
nose
What? Do something
Close Rocky and finish the game
I wasted years of effort
Bring and close
It is as if you are expressing love to a girl for the first time
That's why I forgive you this time
But ghetto requires a lot of courage for this love
You are so brave, tell me, what should I do?
Well, I'm standing in front of your house tonight
You see my bare feet all night
Bye
But come on
Where are my sandals?
I went to the bank today, but I did not go to the temple
Dad, I brought you chocolate bread
I have indigestion
I did not come through the back door
Dad, don't be angry
I decided to put this on the back of a big tattoo
What? Do you want to get a tattoo? Shah Rukh Khan Shi?
It is as if we have not punished you for a long time
In the same way, the mouth of the nation is called the boy of grass
Do you want to look for a job or just dust off?
Dad's not even offered to study -
Look, my son is going to be an officer
Tattoos are not suitable for your job
Mom, when should I get a tattoo? Only spend 5 thousand more
5 Hazar?
Have you ever seen 5000 rupees together?
5000 rupees 24 hours just go
Lekno tourists also see you and turn their way
5000 rupees, see Wangen's son going out and what are you doing?
Everyone lives here
It looks like a big house
They do not know what is going on in the world
What are you looking for?
Sandlam! I did not find them in the morning
Be sure to put it under the bed
I was not there at first
Dad that blue chair?
Yes, so which one?
The ones I gave to Bora had his seat torn
Did you give the chair?
Did you give it to Bora?
Yeah
Why didn't you give him your chair?
Are your two legs decorated with diamonds?
Did you give me sandals?
If you worked, you would buy new sandals for your dad every week
And he gave me my chair
If you were a worker, you would pay for tattoos
You just yell at me
Yeah! why not? So why sandals?
Give me my clothes too, Bora, I walk naked in the street, go
!Nude
Pashoo Pashoo and go out
Here is an example
Okay Dad, I'm going out and staying out all night
Yes, go out
Let's do it again
No, my mom is dying
And if you are right, why not come all night? -
Well, I'm gone, I do not want your food
Go and get out
I do not want to stay with you
Is it all your fault? -
So what? Do you fight, do you think I'm afraid of you?
The right place for Mardesi and Ann Salad Row?
Do I do everything?
I make salad
what is this? A shirt full of water will not be available from tomorrow
What do you say madam?
Go
Stupid
Give it to Shirinash
Give me one
Speed ​​up the next one
I eat too much
Give me the first one. I already stood here
I do not eat muftis, I pay
Did you think you were the hero of an old Indian movie?
And you go out at night and I get bored?
This is stupidity, not courage
What is your nose? -
Let me talk to you for a moment
What?
Respect the neighbor, come for a second, I have a card
I do not like to chase you, I am civilized
I say today what I have been preparing myself to say for years
I love you, you decide what to do?
Do you only know how to whisper or do you have the courage to work?
I will do whatever you want
Come with me
Where do you see me?
this? Yeah -
Do you want to kill me?
Are you from Asqi?
Go offer your love
Bini, look at his arms, it suffocates me
Go
OK
Run your nose
Ghetto I do not like fugitives
You want to do something, do it right
You love to express love
No, look at all these girls ... go
What?
Express love
What the hell? -
My last nose is killing me
OK
You will destroy us in the end
..I think so
No problem, my son, next time
Listen to the nose
I say I am going to express my love to one of the girls in the park
Well, let me tell you
I express my love to you, huh?
Bin .. Bin
Ok be friends with me at least
Bye
My neighbor, you are comfortable
From house to house
That was nothing
The principle of courage must be done now
All these tests that you take from me were not even in Sita's courtship
Go and propose to my brother
What if I did then?
Do not retreat
I do not! Go courting first
Go
No, I'm seeing
The one who made six blades?
Oh, this beard, yes, thank you, aunt
say
No
Brother, how long do you see the profile on the site? Now is the time to marry a girl
Well, I'm doing this, you're very worried, ‌ oh?
Who?
this?
Yeh again
Is it over?
Yes look now -
Do you have anything else to do?
No then I go?
Yeah
OK
The ghetto of this fraud
What fraud? You said talk about marriage with my brother
You did not say talk about our marriage
You are looking at Rito profiles
I beg you to ask me out of all the cities of Lucknow
"I do not know what happened, but something has changed."
"If I do not know anything"
"Tell me what happened?"
"What is going to happen is me and you are"
"You are in front of me, but there is also sadness"
"The reason for my tears and the smile on my lips is you"
"I broke up with you in your memory"
"In your memory"
God forbid we see each other somewhere "" that there is no one
"The place and the way that were not important to us before"
"I woke up to the feeling of the night's morning."
Why do I feel mine when I see you as an alien?
"I want to understand you, but the words are incomplete."
"Tell me what happened?"
"What should happen? I am and you are"
"You are ahead but you are still sad"
"The reason for my tears and the smile on my lips is you"
"I got lost in your memory, I got lost"
"I broke up with myself"
"I'm lost in your memory, too."
Ghetto You know our cousins ​​are facing each other (wife's parents house)
I know about my childhood
I'm very lucky, right?
Sometimes you call this mom Saddam, sometimes that mom .. nose .. nose
I also make noises. nose
What does this nose have to do with you?
not your business?
What did it have to do with you? You made my love my sister
You had no offer, if you had something to say
I did not have it that day, but I have it today
I curse you in front of everyone today
See your brother now
What fish do you have for us?
I did not break, I said this is over for your brother
What do you do in the ghetto? Go break his curse
Break the curse brother fish
What happened to the nose sister?
The ghetto went after the fish
Why are you looking for fish?
Let's go .. I tell you
Eat hard
I came from the office today and saw you in the nose market
Behind the storm Bora
Bora? Un sharefresh?
Han
Son of a bitch gangster?
Tell Jaydio?
No, it makes you think badly
His daughters who are on the way to Badr
"Religious hymn"
Your daughter has a beautiful voice
Raj .. Aunt, if you have any questions, ask
What do you want to ask? I sent the profile of Rito to them
Raj, I will send you this movie as well
Sit down and watch and make a decision
Is that right?
Yes aunt
Rito's wedding ghetto was almost certain
Then it's our turn
eh? Are you in a hurry?
Break the roof and come here soon
I will go to work to pass the exam
Then see, our wedding will be the biggest wedding in the place
Look behind the ghetto
Come on, where did you go after another ghetto?
24 hours by phone
I will call later
Where are you wetting your nails? Crow chicks
Dad, why are you cursing yourself?
I curse myself
Because you failed, the test result came
Now where does the car come from with the red light
You took my honor
Give me the phone, show me
The battery is empty
Did I really get rejected?
.. وايستا تو رو
Ghetto
Do you see here?
I am not afraid of anyone, I brought you food and medicine
Are you in a lot of pain?
I'm not upset that Dad beat me, but I'm sad because he beat me in front of you
Do you want me to say something?
I did not even dream that you were in front of me
Yeah Al that sounds pretty crap to me, Looks like it aint for me either
But ghetto, I was upset to see you beaten
No, he was my father
Otherwise no one can touch me
I passed this year, there is no problem, I will test again next year
The one who removes the nose will never be rejected
See .. I'm a little tired
Ghetto?
Okay, give the French a cold kiss
After the wedding
Okay, listen
Let your windows open and boot
هوي چيتا
چیتا
The name of that idiot was rejected in the test
My shoes were worn here to pay my tuition
And Aghazadeh wants to get a tattoo
Play cricket and call 24 hours a day
That's right, uncle, but the punishment is like this
"A baby's feet are seen in a cradle in infancy" (Proverb)
But he got off the cradle, but he did not get up
I'm tired of it
Uncles are upset
You tore four more shirts than me
But hit it like this, sprout it .. it won't take long to spoil
So you tell me what to do?
If you agree, send him to me for work
He studies during the day and worships at night
As much money as I put in your hands
You think, of course, if you agree
It does not want to think
You are heartbroken like a family member
nose
Han
You became like our family
Now, as an adult, I want to tell you something
جانم
Sitting outside, he watches the nation ghetto
Come on, Aghazadeh
Touch his brother's feet, you are going to work with them
No, it is not necessary
And now tell them everything about the nose .. Yala
What Daddy?
Your sister, your sister, your sister ... Tell me
Say exactly
Hello Uncle, Hello Brother Hello Aunt
The ghetto is going to be late for the race
how are you? - I'm fine - Can you give me some yogurt?
Get the ghetto
Hey, what is the problem in the ceremony? Are you working or playing mobile?
Check the microphone is ringing, go
Why did you do this? Where is Mandip?
Do not play the role of Shiva on this first day. Go and see where Mandip is.
I see the eyes
No ghetto, I came to talk to you
Ghetto Two, I'm upset for three days
What happened bro?
Tell the truth, who are you and Bora related to?
I do not know, brother
Isn't this the same as selling milk?
Who is milking us? say
Our brother?
Look at the ghetto, you see for me and you are no different
You are my brother
Brother? How about
Aren't you a brother?
!No! what happened? Tell me, brother
For the last time I ask, tell the truth
Bora and Bini from whom with the same?
Do you say
I know you do not call me friendship and purity, but this is your silence
He said everything
..Bora no brother
No, I did not understand enough
It's not your fault you brush the card
Son of Dapi Dada and Bini?
Brother, is this the same milk seller?
But we had not bought milk from him for a long time
We have been closed since then
How did you find out?
From the ghetto
Brother, in this wedding riot, I will be notorious
You do not have to worry about this happening
But no one should be informed
Jaydio is the truth of crap and people who say infamous sisters
We are upset as a neighbor, but how can I say that?
What do you say, Aunt John? I'm right
He saw himself riding in a Bora car
Come on .. my son, today's generation, not with breast milk
Instead, it should be kept on the line with the enlarged mobile valve
I tore four more shirts than you, so I say do nothing
Because love in your youth is normal
What happens if you close the top of the Ferrari engine?
He smokes nothing more and goes to the tree in front of him
So just watch it
How do I monitor it? Do I work or ..?
You made us neighbors again, we are families
Let Rito's wedding be over and see you later
..If in front of all the place
I did not force Dapi Dada's son to tie a rock, I am not older than you
Jaydio, you simply do not understand that you are not married yet
Remember today
Bini does not have two brothers but three brothers
So, Aju and Gato
Come to the meditation house and get out of the ghetto
Ghetto .. The girls of this place are the sisters of the boys
From today, be very careful about your nose
Take him to college in the morning .. and bring him home at noon and yes
Be careful not to meet Bora, do you understand?
What time does he go to college in the morning?
8 oclock
See you later -
I hit your brother in the face and he told me to take you to college
What? Sarkar? What did you do
We are now in the heart of your whole family
Ghetto, someone is watching us, tell his brother; OK?
I tell your brother to look at your superstitious time
You were mine and you will be mine
I have two good news
First, liking Rito means connecting
Long live your mother goddess, sweeten your mouth
We sweeten my mouth, listen to the second one
Aunt Raj and Aunt Husband came that day
Their son Rahul works in France
I like my nose
I sent you my profile for two weddings together
..Aunt .. nose
Is he studying? Is that what you want to say?
Well, going to France to continue your education is not important
Think about it
The family does not get along so well
No, your aunt ordered Matin and the family is very good
So what is the problem?
Invite you to their temple tomorrow
Bring the two to the wedding immediately
Now we sweeten our mouths
Bora, do not worry
This is an opportunity to put a class in front of his brother
He thinks I solved the problem
What does he want to do? Rocky closes well close-
I think it is not a problem, great plans
Jaydio wakes up
Oh, only the sisters are not infamous, the whole neighborhood is becoming infamous
coming
My sister
Hello Uncles Hello Brother
See my son
Uncle
Knox, are you kidding me? Han?
Who do you think you are? No bro -
If I see you around my sister again, I will kill you
I brought my money, take the money for your shirt, ghetto, understand this
You are a nose brother, be
How dare you raise your hand against me?
Not a job
get lost
My mother has not raised her hand in Rome yet
Oh dear pain you do not know I am the son of Kiyam -
No one is afraid of you
I will cut your shirt from all over the city, then drink your tea and drink it
Yes, I do
The property works
Go Daddy, wait for me
Dude, what are you doing? -
You should not criticize firmly
Dapi Dadash's son
What?
We brought a coward to beat me here
No carelessness
So far no one was able to send in the perfect solution, which is not strange
I know
Leave your nose until the night of this dead
This family is crazy
Calm down
You said I was going to close Rocky, I came too, but he knocked under my ear
There is no problem, I will solve it, do not cry
Is the meat good?
Where is it good? Is whistling
Well, let me see, not good meat
Bora, my brother-in-law is going to come, I will compensate you
ميزنمش
Miznimsh Bora carefree .. Do not cry
Do you hate beer?
No, I do not drink beer, I want juice
Okay, let's go to Juice
Why don't you tell me what you have to do with Bora?
My God, the standing fortune teller whistles the flesh
close
You are not human
What are you doing, Judeo?
what do I do? You see what mommy is doing
My grandmother's life, I swear I have nothing to do with Bora
Let go of Grandma, swear by my life
Mom for a moment
Brother, I swear to you, I have nothing to do with Bora Sanami
Did you see mom? I also killed
Where is your mobile?
ایناهاش داداش
Stay in front of you, don't take it, take it with you
Rito is not your wedding issue
Break your mobile
Rito Shut up-
Everything is under your head
Silent
Everyone listen to me
See, tomorrow is Rito's engagement and my fiancé is coming for you
Please do not be your sister's enemy, her connection has been confirmed
You see your fiancé, no father sees you
Mom, let's go somewhere
my son
Han say
You too, go with your mobile
Didn't you read Mandip?
Come back
Okay, call the ghetto
Aunt John?
Hello, I will walk after dinner
say
Grim Shirawali is crooked, go and see him
I inadvertently hit Bora Ghetto
I raised my hand to my nose
Hands out of control
I just want everything to be right
And Rito's wedding should not be canceled
Did you talk to Bora?
No, brother, I did not speak
My decision is absolutely right
I will nominate Rito Bini tomorrow
Do you see a fiancé?
Yeah Al that sounds pretty crap to me, Looks like BT aint for me either
I'm careful there, be careful here
One brother there, one here
Ok ghetto?
Please, I will make a nomination and come
... desired subscriber
The brothers and sisters are now coming to visit the canker
Begwan Shiva is attending
Where is Hey Benti Shiva?
Get up, aren't you dizzy? stand up
No, no, thank you
Thank you what?
You hit the master car and you say thank you?
Where did I hit? You were very fast
Mizanamata
Brother, the subject of love and my departure is obligatory
Where do you want to go? Wash it in the car
See the master. He wants to hit the lamb
No, I will not go to the account and I will send it to you tomorrow, let me go
Close it
No sir I have to go What are you doing?
You brought Shiva here last night
I came to talk to a lawyer
Bora Bora
Are you okay?
Bring me out
Mr. Gupta
What happened to Gupta?
They are leaving, don't worry
Give me your engine switch, but what happened? -
Give me the switch first, take my mobile from them
Ghetto
Mom, how can you do this?
Listen my daughter
What are you doing? Mom, go, I'll talk to her -
What are you doing? Why are you busy?
You did not even tell me
Listen to the reputation of your family in your hands
Quietly say yes, good boy, please
Benny Pia
Is coming
: Instagram and our official media telegram @BollyCineOfficial
Hold the ring in a hurry
good job
Congratulations
Benny Haqiqq shortened it
Why is it your fault? It's my fault I had to tell them
I should have told Jadio too
Ghetto, do not cut off communication with me no matter what happens, right?
I can not see you without you. I apologize from the bottom of my heart
Why do you apologize? It is not your fault
Shall we escape the ghetto?
My bride's guardian, Ritu, have Mikhora
what do I do?
I was called a firecracker but I was extinguished
No, you are not a firecracker
Okay, I'm talking to Jadeio
No, Rito's wedding is going to hurt me, you think
Find a way to make the nose yours and Rito the groom
Look, I got a notorious ghetto, he's with his brother Bora
What are you doing, please?
Come take my son
Maderjan does not need this
Take my son
I have something to say
After hearing your voice, I realized where your daughters' voice went
Brother Mandip called and said he could not come at night
Let him know
The path of this ghetto is the child of my own family
Neighborhood
Hello ghetto
Shio
Oh shit
Is this an iPad?
Hey iPad respect
No .. No need, yes iPad
Is there a game?
Yeah, let me show you
What are you doing?
دامادمونه مامان
come
Thanks sister-in-law
Really, Uncle Raj sent a gift to Rito, should I give it to him?
Yes, why not
Guide your sister-in-law up
Raj's nose is coming
بینی ببین اومد؟ ببين .. اومد؟
Go see what you are doing.
bride
Hi, I was not annoyed
No, do not say that
Ratios in their place and literature in their place
Brother sent you a gift
Really?
Yes, he said .. a moment
Give it exactly like this
A gift for you from Brother Raj
Thankful
Actually, I brought this for the nose
Well .. give me?
Wow, very romantic, but you know your fiancé
it's true
Hello nose, how are you?
I am fine
So I finally saw you
Thank you for showing me your face
Because I became a fan of your singing in France
My mother sent the clip, I saw it
Then I saw him and I saw him again and then
Anyway, this gift is yours, iPhone
If you record a good song, send it to me
Thankful
Are you proud of me for my coffee?
In fact, it is better to ask his brother
Well, I came to ask my brother
And you are so beautiful
Brother, let's sit down and go down
The food is ready in ten minutes
Brother, I do not eat, but I want your permission
Can I invite my nose for coffee?
If you know
Do not take the one who did not say he will not come?
No, he did not say anything
So nothing I say thank you -
I really have a problem, brother
Shio
Excuse me, the problem is that
I got a phone for my nose but I did not get a SIM card
I will be happy if you buy Tony a SIM card
Thank you so much
ID card?
ID card? what is it?
nothing
I'm sorry, thank you very much
Please be patient
Thankful
So goodbye kids goodbye sister husband -
Will I come next time?
Yes, I will take you
Goodbye buddy
: Specialized translation of our cultural and artistic media Translators: Bingsa and Huzair
The ghetto was in good spirits
Return the rest of the money to me or I will tell my son-in-law
Dear brother
"This is what I asked to reach you"
"I can tell you and you will understand me soon"
Bini: What should I do? Ghetto: Rahul is with me
Ghetto: Is he with you or are you constantly clinging to him?
"Yehoo Az Square Didit Ghayb Shhem"
"And no one can find me"
"This is what I ask God to do for you."
"I can speak my mind and you will understand soon"
Luck was on, a first-rate boy was caught
Exactly from the husband of God
Everything is getting right, ghetto
Yogurt is closing in on them
Bora left the field, be ready
"If you are not with me, I will lose my purpose."
"I'm heartbroken to not see you for a moment."
"I do not want to live without you"
"You were the only purpose of my life"
"No one is mine except you"
"This is what I asked God to do for you."
"And I can speak my heart and you will understand"
Your fortune does not match
Bora I do not understand anything
Why is a person named Rahul clear? Han?
That movie was the bond of friendship in that movie. When did you get the girl out of Salman's clutches?
Rahul
And the film is so crazy, do you even get caught?
What was Delwaleh that he sold for years?
دیلواله! I saw him
That comedy movie
When did he take his wife from that husband?
To the wind
Rahul
No, no bro
He was Raj
Raj Rahul both start with "R" and have the same horoscope
Both are similar
It's over. Everything is over
If your story is not romantic but it becomes a crime
Brother, the only cure for the Rahul virus is something
What?
Death .. The cure is death
What are you saying
No
بیخيال
You have no supply to shoot, we will kill him in an accident
Do you have a problem with an accident, huh?
It's over, Bora
Nothing is over
I kill myself and solve the problem
No, brother, nothing is over
Romeo Bade Maryah
No
Go to the nose and tell Romio he must die
Do not talk about these things, brother, I will kill Rahul
From now on, Bora will be the first young name in every movie
Where's mecha? Gatu Rahul -
Ghetto .. Ghetto opens his hand
The ghetto opens its hand and the ghetto brother-in-law becomes Bora
Bora becomes a ghetto brother .. my sister's brother
And that guy himself could not get a wife, he tells me
You are the brother of your house
From Shuhrkhwahrsham
Brother, you take it and I dance at your wedding
No, I do not wear a robe (men's wedding dress)
And the girl does not die on top of the Eiffel Tower
The girl goes to the top of our clock tower
The girl goes to the top of the Eiffel Tower at nine o'clock
Girl, not my sister, she goes to the clock tower and you bring her down, brother
Guto noise
Geto
And Rahul?
Rahul who died in an accident
ميکشيمش
Mishimesh is a friend
listen
Who is there?
Hey boys, did you drink wine?
We did not drink wine or beer
What?
Uncles, we were heartbroken today, we drank some wine, what happened?
Bora, rest, I will answer
what happened?
You sleep .. you sleep .. okay?
Well, Uncle John, I'm dying
Is V Darren Gargar Makenin?
Gargar?
Omujan Bora shortening Dusit Rundle realistic from it
A true friend
Bora wanted to kill him today for love
Yeah Al that sounds pretty crap to me, Looks like BT aint for me either
Our childhood
Don't worry, what happened?
Bora, sleep well
I sleep
Well, my uncles, I'm going, I'm a gentleman, I'm going home on time
Hey ghetto, first tell me who this nose is?
Benny Omujan?
The nose of love is right
Yes love
Uncle, when you order milk, then do you understand who you are?
Order milk?
The father of Shanker Jay's daughter is a religious figure
Excuse me, my uncle, let me go
You too sleep cold air, sleep
I will not kill Bora -
Good night Uncle John
What made you growl?
Uncle, his heart is broken
Uncles, the news is true
Everyone knows their love
And they are forcing the girl to marry and her brother Bora
How dare he touch Bora?
I take all his family and dry them
Uncle John, I will destroy them
Bashin Baba Bashin
You see, we can not marry outside our own tribe
That's why we go to see his brother
And I tell her in favor of your sister
To give her husband to someone else sooner
Otherwise, Kara will be ruined
And if Bora is seen on the other side of the girl's house
I peel it myself, yes
Good morning, Amujan
English bulgur
Does your mouth hurt? Say Hindi Ram Ram Hindi?
Who is this nose? come here
From Nameam
I say come here
I'm not you, you're busy, you're coming .. I'm not
Who am I? Dog eggs
Escaped stupid
Take me to my daughter's brother
Han Bibin Jaidio
Jaydeo
See Jaydio .. The point is that your sister
Listen to your first uncles
Bora had blown up my sister, that's why I hit her
If you were me, you would do the same
You see, we are poor but honorable and we have a place of honor
And you are from a family of criminals
In farming, everyone knows what you do not do
Now we can not connect with such families
I'd better kill my sister instead
See uncles are the truth of crap
Hey, how dare you say this?
Hey Vijander pull aside
What's going on?
What was your son's name?
Jaydeo
..Jaidio, the first word
Accept that our family is not respectable
And what do we do under the cover of the farm?
Now no one really gives his daughter to such a family
Yes
it's true? So listen properly
Your sister can only be our bride and nothing else
Now he wants to get married to his body
Or we close a farm and marry him
If she is going to get married, she should be our bride
Why uncles? how are you?
eh? What was he saying?
Omujan
Uncles, listen, you are getting older
Uncles on your side are smaller
Hey, why are you begging him to leave Uncle?
We inform the police
Do you know the police? Do
Uncle, the police will not stop talking to the army
How do they take our local girl?
Aren't we in your hands? (Unless we are cowards)
So what? The bracelet that comes on the wedding day, let's see how we do it
I raised my sister like my daughter, how are you?
Touch it and see
What are you doing wrong? What's wrong?
See what kind of person this is? You are the executioner of the executioner
Do not touch my husband
Is this your husband?
Are women stronger than men here?
Who threw the slippers?
Bro? Uncle .. run away -
Hi Uncle
Live is the subject of a girl
What is their house? there-
: Instagram and our official media telegram @BollyCineOfficial
Now it comes down to them
Bora and this girl's wedding is certain
If anyone tried to object
I paint the whole neighborhood with blood
Just be
Let me bury him
I just don't want to see Bora
Lightness Shu
Mom, let the blood get in front of my eyes
See what happens here with your blessing?
The younger brother has blood in front of his eyes
And threatening his older brother
I have never seen a selfish girl like you
How many times can I tell you that I have nothing to do with Bora?
Call the ghetto and it will tell you the truth
The ghetto told his brother that he had fallen in love with Bora
What?
Yes, the ghetto has been saying that your mast has been closed for a long time.
Ghetto said?
Susan Gertrude? Goto, goto
Ghetto Nutial said that he also met Bora
See you canceled because of your wedding
If my wedding is canceled, I will not let anyone get married
Open all your ears
How can I marry my sister? They steal and take them
How to steal? Han?
We are all here, everything is solved
Today we must unite
Do you know the police?
Monga, I'm talking, can I finish?
Thanks, Han I was saying
What happened to Jadio can happen to us tomorrow
Yes its true
Right or not?
As long as we are oppressed, they will continue to be oppressed
For this reason, it is obligatory to protect our place
You are absolutely right
The nose of the bride leaves
If someone else looks left in the nose, we will open their eyes
Yes, we open his eyes
If this neighborhood wants a house, we are ready to donate blood
I am ready
Do you hear Jaydio? We are all with you
You are accompanied by siblings
Now should we pray to our mother to fight these monsters?
Yeah why not? We pray
Long live mother
"Everyone sit politely"
"The mother who is breastfeeding is coming"
"Mother, meet all needs"
"Your followers get your hands on you"
"We sat under your feet"
"Take away our sorrows"
"Very beautiful .. - Long live"
"Your face is so beautiful that we see"
"We put a red scarf on your head with dancing and singing"
We have come to your court to satisfy you with hanging necks
"Let us see you, our lion"
"It 's so beautiful when everyone is dancing for you from the bottom of their hearts."
"Long live the cymbal of the mother"
"Your court is my home and I have no family but you."
"I have no family but you"
Hear everyone's prayers. "" Take me to the shore, mother of the ship
"Because of your name, all our organs have moved."
"It is very beautiful"
"Your face is so beautiful that we see"
We have come to your court to satisfy you with hanging necks
"Viva"
"It is very beautiful"
"Your face is so beautiful that we see"
"Your face that we see"
How are you?
Yes how?
No
Let them close the door on you
Should I close it?
Come on
His lower nose became very donkey
But do not worry, I will solve it
You sit down first, you solved everything
So tell me, do you eat yogurt?
I also eat poison from your nose
Well, then we go up to the roof
roof top?
From that kind of yogurt?
The so-called French kiss
Yes, French
It's called a French kiss
Are you sure?
Yeah
Well, we eat yogurt here
Not if anyone remembers
Isn't the roof more fresh now?
Yes, it does
Let's go?
Han Barim
Ghetto
Han
Has your mother told all the locals about this process of milking yogurt?
yogurt? No, my mother did not say anything
Is this your family habit a family habit?
What do you see?
Well let it go
Did anyone come down to the cover of the mother's ceremony?
Let go of the mother
Ghetto, tell me more
Did the mother come or not?
no how?
I'm not going to come
Mother is coming here today
Mother
nose
Ghetto Tell me, who told everyone about Bora and Bini, huh?
I did not say
Ghetto You are not brave and you will never be brave
Long live the mother
Did you tell Jaydio? You said ghetto
You betrayed your nose, huh?
No
You are a coward
My mother did not say
Are you lying?
No, mother, I am not lying
Shut up ghetto, why did you do that?
We were going to win the world together
And today you defeated me
How many times have I asked you about Bora? several times?
Do not understand the relationship between siblings? At least you respected him
Why do you see me? -
You destroyed my life
I wanted to tell you
Nasal eye? Ghetto?
The mother came in her skin
Wow, what a misfortune my sister has come to bring the ghetto water
Call your brother's ghetto
Nasi Pashoo sister
the doctor
Nothing, do not worry, you are worried
The mother who came in her skin is now in season
I will give you a pill
Do you have the right to visit your doctor?
No, my mother should pray for me. In my mother's case, I do not get paid
Say it with love
Long live the mother goddess
بريم
No my daughter, no one cares do not worry
Everything is fine, calm down
Not two sticks
Two guns in front of the nose room ... then you
Look, Tircho .. How many clubs do we have and how many riflemen do we have?
Ten batons and 5 riflemen Ten batons and 5 riflemen -
Hey Ghetto, pay homage to Uncle Tircho
Be alive, my son
Tircho, the stick that everyone has, make 7 gunmen
Well, give me 2,000 rupees for the boys and 2,000 rupees for the gun
Prepaid and the rest after the wedding, but the guard is strict
Both for the nose and for the jadeo family
Do not worry about the court guard
Hello
Get the ghetto alive
what happened?
You have a misunderstanding about the nose
nose?
What misunderstanding are they our daughter?
... Bora's uncles
Do not worry, Dapi has just come out of prison
She is playing with her son, she is your friend, you go too
Babajan, my legs hurt
Do you marry outside the tribe?
How do you make yogurt if you mix water with milk?
Did you think about it?
..veto
Bringing in the neighborhoods of Tircho?
Dapi dies of a wind blowing on himself
I know Uncle
I came out of prison for a week, will I go on leave for sure?
You two are Jing Hamid's friends, aren't you? Like a flame movie
You and Bora ate together
Behold, I do not like to be an orphan
Tell Babat to stand back
..It's his uncle, did you understand? -
And where is the girl who caused the controversy?
Let's see the girl
.. Uncle John Oun
Take me to the girl, otherwise I will steal and bring her
No, Uncle John, I'll show you
Bora, tell your father to solve the problem
My brother went to my mother since I was a child and I have no connection with my father
I only saw him in prison two or three times! It is not clear how he got out
My little uncle ran away and married a girl
He buried it in front of my mother
It is a normal honor killing for us ... if I say something
Honorable Mention Honor Murder Dishonesty is also a coincidence
I see three corpses of you, me and Bini .. There is also a fourth
Uncle Notal
What can I do now? Make it yourself
At least save your father
Look, Monga, in difficult times, no one is the president or the vice president
We all fight together
Accept this, but we have not killed a single fly to date
And they are accused of 100 murders right now
Well, we have to start somewhere, the first murder, the second dimension, the third dimension
Dad say -
Hi Uncle
what happened? I have a cartoon moment -
What?
Now I'm coming from Dapi's house, he said he will kill you, you are my only father
Do you like me as an orphan and a widowed mother?
You have never slapped anyone
Why are you talking about giving blood, please, Dad?
come
what is this?
..this
The White House, the home of the President of the United States
I want to be president, not vice president
Who remembers the vice president? No one
The lemon with which they cook hot chicken
Nobody mentions it, everyone mentions chickens
Who am I?
نوتیال؟ I'm a lemon and I want to be a chicken-
There is nothing better for a chicken than war
..That is to make the war bigger and smaller
Give them a war whenever the nation gets bored
From that war a new leader is born
After the war, no one could stop me from becoming the head of the neighborhood
And you were scared of a threat, little Notil?
Are you surprised?
But we also created a controversial college course
We closed the whole city with a nationwide strike
So do not be afraid and continue your friendship with him
Because the presence of a secret spy in the enemy's tent is very necessary
Tell me whatever happens there
مونگاجي
Han is beautiful, but expensive, not mom?
Are you going to pay for it? Cutter
..this
this? I think expensive
Hello Uncle Ghetto-
Hello مUncle ‌ Please see it from a distance today if possible
Go away ... why from afar? I want to see close-ups
One more thing, if I like the girl, accept it
Otherwise the wedding is canceled
Loving Bora has no effect
... Okay, uncles, if you talk too much, shut up -
Which girl? Is this
No uncles here
Which one? Where?
They are uncle
Where? She is in a yellow dress -
Yellow? This girl? Is this a girl?
Is that so cute?
The lover of such a girl must have four or five murders for her
Tell the truth or you will be killed
Does this girl really like Bora? Han?
I had heard that diamonds are found in the middle of charcoal
But how did this diamond fall in love with my charcoal?
What is the flow?
I greet my bride now and come
No, uncle, I pray for him -
Uncles now no
The first time I saw him, I had to give him something
Omujan
How about not meeting the bride? Uncles are a matter of family reputation -
Well, give it to him, brother
Be sure to give it to my bride
Ok uncle
I have a nose for two minutes
Failed Uncle Notial Boy Do not follow me, you are unemployed
Spread syrup on your bride and move the chair
nose
Please Go
Mom, this one is good, isn't it?
"Beno Khal is beautiful on the forehead"
"Beno Bindiat is beautiful"
Answer my phone
I'm coming
Ghetto brother, please answer the nose phone
Aloo Han Rahul
"Where are you? Come to me to find out where I am."
Tell me the truth, did you buy it?
Yeah
Well send a photo
What photo?
Photo of clothes
Oh well, but you do not give us a kiss?
How are you here?
If you are new to France, you must love French
Won't you make such a small request?
Now no, make a list of them
You see, my list goes on and on and on
No
Ghetto; what happened?
What happened to the ghetto?
Did you bring a weapon?
I brought it but chatted Yahoo?
You were right that day, we have to kill this path
You just talk, give me the gun
Come and get it, but nothing happened by killing Rahul
Nini's sister's wedding is not with Rahul, now her wedding is with me
Why did you show my nose to my father?
He even went crazy and chose the name of my children
Granddaughter of Dapi Dada Pepi
He sent Uncle Vijander to take a nap
Brother, the end of this riot is happening to me
The gun is in your hand .. hit me
No Bora
what's going on with you? Only you, my friend
Ghetto, I have to remember this calamity
You mean, like, all the bridesmaids except me?
Bini says I lie and put everyone to work?
Now look in front of his eyes to fool everyone
Remember him as long as he lives
Bora's wedding with the vision of this God can not change
And Dapi does not forget disrespect
One of the women in your area attacked her with slippers
And last night he was beaten like a dog
Why did your father become their leader?
The other father is dead, we must kill the father
I'm killing my dad's wedding morning, okay?
Okay, kill your uncle
But he sent this letter to Bora's father
Who is Baba Bora? Dad
I am the father
My uncle reads it
Respectfully yours, Uncle John
Be alive
Uncle Vijander and Gojinder Hello
I'm fine here and I ask God for your health
At this moment, the brave, smart and reliable young man is just a ghetto
After consulting with the ghetto, I came to the conclusion that Rito's wedding .. Rito is his older sister
After my sister's marriage, I run away and come to marry Bora
it's true
You just have to be careful not to bleed
He apologizes for beating Uncle Vijander
See your future bride
Wow sweet letter written
So far no one was able to send in the perfect solution, which is not strange
Bora, your flag went up to me
It sticks diamond and paper together
The girl is so beautiful .. I'm smart
You see, we do what Bini suggested
Yes that's fine
come here
You make Bora your real brother
But Dapy's the groom's father
I said this is over
My uncles are just neighbors
Your real brother
The angel of my nose
I will start with a poem, say guidance
guidance
I show the fire inside my heart to everyone
If your wedding dress gets up from Josh, I will set the world on fire
Luckily, your brother does not have a wife, because if he did
No .. Read
Because if he was, the bride would be a widow
Do not be afraid of anyone, especially Baba Ghetto
My father has been carrying bullets in his gun for a long time
I told you
My cute nightingale, tell someone who wants to stand between you and me
Even if they imprison you or close a wall in front of you
Bora and her family pulverize every wall
And you can be stolen from that hellish cage at any moment
We have a person around us
Who will inform you in time that we are coming
Who?
I do not know
Lover displaced and dearer than Janet Bora
Telling me to give a tiger to the nose
I took a chance and brought it to you
Nose is crazy, I'm afraid to run away from home
Dadash for a moment
I die but I do not let my nose go out of the neighborhood; I am
Get in the ghetto and don't move
He wants her to not even be able to talk to anyone on the phone
ولي داداش
Shut up! What a pity for the wedding, otherwise I would have taken your account
Dadash said
Turn off the light
Hello Ganj Free Police Station?
For a moment, you did not fulfill your promises
A gunman with no truncheons
What are you saying do not worry
Ghetto, I told you to stay ahead
They are making up their noses
Well stay tuned please
The police came out
police?
police? ... A moment with me
What happened, sir?
We had a general telephone threat. What is going on?
What happened, Captain?
They blow up the neighborhood with dynamite
How do they explode?
This is a wedding, not a ridiculous game ... I'm them
I will solve it
The police have arrived
When a girl gets married
Neighborhood lovers spread these rumors
See, what else do you want? What are you going to do to us?
... Brother, tell me what happened? I'm news
..Hit
Brother, talk, do not raise your hand
Why are you interfering?
..I love him
Don't I like it? She is my sister
Brother
Do whatever you want
what happened? Nothing .. I will solve it -
I go? Go -
I do not go to the ghetto-
Please go outside
What do you see?
What's going on? Wedding .. make up -
Do not worry, I sent the police
This wedding is done in security
No you do not understand Uncle
All the games are played by the police
Dad, how are you with them?
! عه پلیس
!police
You be careful, I'm coming now
Come with me, brother, what are you doing? -
Do not crowd your nose
What is it, brother?
Groom's convoy with the police
What ? police?
Yes, threatening to steal from you
What are you saying bro?
See Rahul
Ghetto
Ghetto, this time there is no problem to make everything right
I leave the reputation of the family to you
Take your sister to a place where no one knows
..But brother you do not know everything
Please, please
Please see
Listen, say whatever the ghetto says, eyes
When it calms down here, I will call you back
Brother no please
بريم بیني
What do you do in the ghetto? Get me a ghetto
Where did you bring me?
See you with me
Ghetto, please leave me
Mahesh, Mahesh Pashu Yala
Take back your curse
Did he get it? Take it back -
Are you getting married or running away or getting married?
Stupid
Do not curse anyone from now on, sometimes it takes
Pour acid on my black tongue
His sermon held
: Instagram and our official media telegram @BollyCineOfficial
Do you have tea, brother?
We eat poison
You are so beautiful nose of this jewel of your nose
You must be surprised that you and I sat together
I was like that
When your brother asked what is between Bini and Bora?
I thought the story would come together
But see where he got to?
I should have told Dadasht
I agree, I'm not brave, but I love you very much
You have been sitting next to me since I was a child and now in a wedding dress, I am not a donkey
I will be brave like you
I know you will marry anyone in India today except me
..Everybody even sells tea
No, this tea sale, no
You have to choose
Do you have an Eiffel or a cow? Or facing the house?
I admit I made a mistake, but do not punish me like this
Do your thoughts beautifully, I'm not in a hurry
Dear Uncle
You arrived in the middle of our wedding
No, no, my uncle, is my engine broken?
Is your engine broken? Where are you now?
I sat in Fountain Park
You stay there with our bride
How much time do you want to see? Not you ... okay
... your desired subscriber
The subscriber you want is not available
Dada, we did not visit the whole park
So where to go?
Dadash said this
Did you see a girl in a wedding dress?
I saw
Was anyone with him?
He was a boy
Go
It became a criminal matter
Our bride was taken hostage by her family ... and that poor ghetto too
Uncles, we have a problem, the ghetto phone is off
..Don't give it to Daddy
Where is the nose?
That's with the ghetto
Shoot the guns
Let no one be saved
: Presented by Bollywood Cinema Reference Www.Bollycine.org
Where is the ghetto?
Where is the nose?
I asked, "Where are the ghettos and the nose?"
Parrot, why are you repeating?
They have ghettos and noses
Well done, bring your sister here
Bring your sister ghetto here
No, bring your sister here
Bring your nose here my son
The sister of you all is not my sister
You did it by force of my sister! 15-year-old Rocky Day I hang out with the boys in the neighborhood
Lest they tie a rock to us
And what do you keep saying?
"Girls of the Mother and Sister Neighborhood"
Daughters of the country of sisters and mothers
Why sisters? What about force?
Our father came! In the presence of this mother sister
This marriage contract is divorced
Why is it that Rocky Zorki, who is a brother and sister, is divorced?
Is there a court for this?
Brother, can I protect him? Do I have to be his brother?
The husband also protects
Find a boy in the world for me to see a girl
Tell me, I wish she was my sister
Find one to look for the groom for the wedding
You brought the groom imported from France, don't the boys of the neighborhood have thorns?
You opened the window once
Facing our home shorts was drying
No girl has the right to force anyone on her brother
Liver Ma Brothers Zorki Mesoza
He sees girls well and likes logic .. Hormone
If you do not accept it, reject it
What a form of brotherhood!
Han Bini?
My nose in front of the whole neighborhood I boldly say I love you
I love you so much
I have loved you since I was a child and I will love you forever
Now if anyone dares to tell me, brother
Didi showed my offer
That's why I wanted to be dumb
I love you
If anyone dares to come, I will push him forward
This cardboard item?
I fell in love with words
Give me your hand
Marry
Thankful
Get this Knox
Bedouin
The boys are no longer hiding on Rocky Day
And if anyone wants to force a rock on them
They call it
What do they say?
Your sister is not me
: Specialized translation of our cultural and artistic media Translators: Bingsa and Huzair
: The most complete archive of Indian cinema and television Www.Bollycine.org
"My dear soul, I am your sacrifice."
"You are mine and I am yours"
"You are mine, everyone knows this in India"
I'm a simple man. "" Let the bridegroom and brother-in-law play together
"I love your sister"
"Do not imprison your sister"
I love your sister "" and I do not have a bad thought
"From Mepramt to travel the role of Dunia"
"I will prepare food for you"
"I build bridges over the valleys"
"I miss your sister, I will marry her"
"Your little bride is famous baby"
Do not weigh me with your eyes "" Use your heart
Someone who has you "" Why name someone?
A small letter became the sentence "" and the sentences are stories
We forget all the words "" and laugh at the night of love
"My dear soul, I am your sacrifice."
"You are mine and I am yours"
"Everyone knows India"
"Square"
In the news came "" In the announcements came
"That your sister proposed to my friend"
"Now engagement and wedding together"
I will be your sister-in-law and you will become my brother-in-law
"Satisfied mother, satisfied father, why are you upset?"
"If anyone disturbs your sister, I will kill her father."
"Keep the sanctity of our relationship"
"You are mine, everyone knows this in India"
"دلبر"
First Edited - Farsi Version Norouz 97 - By BeingSa Copyright© Bollycine.Org