What is this sir?
You guaranteed that
you'd teach me in a week!
My promotion's going
to be announced today.
Which means life will
be moving forward...
But look at my reverse! It sucks!
Relax, you'll be fine...
See this watch?
A student gifted
it to me yesterday...
foreign... not the watch,
my student.
A teacher's reward...
don't you forget.
C'mon try again...
Man...l'm getting an automatic!
Why are you wasting my time
teaching me on manual gears?
If you learn on
the manual stick shift,
you'll be able to drive
any car in the world.
Who knows,
today you're driving an automatic,
tomorrow you may not
even own a cycle!
Sir must you think such evil
thoughts aloud early in the morning?
My promotion is up today...
Say something positive.
Well if the teacher's
reward is in my fate,
you will surely get your promotion.
Sir if you keep sharing
these wise thoughts..
..instead of teaching me
how to drive,
I'm never going
to reach the office...
then no promotion, no car.
- Got a girlfriend?
How does it matter?
- What did you say her name was?
Mayera ...
Put it in self...
Now focus on her,
see her face before your eyes...
take her name lovingly
and leave the clutch...
Mayera...
Ya baby Mayera
- See the girlfriend's magic!?
Hey jigida jigida
Hey hey jigida jigida
Te;; the stars not to bend for me,
The sun ;ike a cand;e
shines on my night.
Each goa; waits for me patient;y,
The ;ines of my pa;m
change when ; ;ike.
; have a b;ank sheet in my hands,
To write whatever ; ;ike.
My days wi;; be ;ike this,
My friends wi;; be so,
Even my God makes a;;
my wishes come true.
Hey jigida jigida
Hi hotness... is it new?
Zara... you like?
Very hot... Shall I gobble you up?
Hey jigida jigida
Hey hey jigida jigida
Ok... See you at lunch.
Today is promotion day right?
So eat in your cubicle.
- Ok
Keep working... look extra busy...
Usual tactics dear...
- Bye bye bye bye
Hello
- Oh sorry...
Bye love you..
- Bye..see ya... Have a good day
Fingers crossed. Bye
Mornings rise when ; gesture.
The moon revo;ves
around my roof-top.
- We';; get a good bargain sir.
Start with your price,
then come to ours...
That's how we build relationships.
Our horizontals, your verticals...
Can only integrate them
both with forward planning..
..and long term thinking sir!
Strategise Sir!
; have an account
in the shop of desires,
Even destiny is designed
to fit my form.
Like ba;;s of woo;,
My ways unfo;d.
Be;ow my feet,
;f ; find my dream,
;t wi;; try to come true-
And fo;;ow my ;ead.
Congratulations sir,
you made the right decision!
I'm mailing you the contract
right away sir!
I got it...
I'm a little too cool man...
Hi
- Wassup?
Promotion?
Post lunch
Cool
No, no, no, this is not working...
See, over here...
Those better than me,
Try a hundred tricks,
But ; am not afraid, no way.
;f they b;ock my road,
; wi;; jump, ; wi;; jo;t.
; wi;; get ahead some way.
; wi;; bo;t my p;ans in p;ace,
; wi;; turn the spanner strong,
; wi;; tight;y screw my victories,
To the so;id ground.
Take away the sky,
; wi;; sti;; f;y, high...
Hey jigida jigida
Hey hey jigida jigida
Go to hell!
What a crap raise!
Hey what about you?
What a shame
it took them this long..
...now if they'd done
this a year ago..
I'd have easily doubled
productivity by now...
Meet the new Senior Executive,
Marketing and Sales.
Wow! You're really cool bro...
Thanks... thanks guys
Guess what?
- What?
Check this out.
Wow... Gold!
- Guess the credit limit.
Hmmm... two?
Hunh! Three!
Wow!
- Mayera no Mayera ...
you bought sandals
just last month...
What do you think?
- Very hot...
Shall I gobble you up?
It's slightly expensive...
Should I?
Go for it.
- Here you go.
Hang on...
Wow! Platinum!
When did this happen?
- Today!
And the credit limit... four lakhs?
Wow... the four
lakh platinum card...
And here I'm showing
off my three lakh gold...
Why didn't you tell me dear?
Sweetheart... I didn't want
to ruin your excitement...
This is why...
- Your card ma'am.
Mayera... you're too...
Love you.
- I love you too...
-Your signature please...
Thanks
Thank you
- You are welcome sir
Enjoy your cheesecake
Uuuhh.. nice
- This is yumm
So where do we go from here?
Back to office
No silly...
we've been together for two years,
now what?
What?... Now?
Papa is looking for proposals...
all multi millionaires.
Hmm...
Multi-millionaire ha!!
Not bad!
Not bad.
Ok, I will say yes
to the richest guy.
Done?
- Done...
Excuse me.
Cheque please...
My turn!!....
Wow!!
Ok Mayera Sehgal,
if I was promoted a year ago,
I would have proposed then
and saved you from
Papa Osama's bombardment
Anyway, now that
I'm a Senior Executive,
So...
Will you marry me?
Yes...
Let me tell papa...
Mention Senior Executive
Mohit Chaddha...
Osama will be impressed...
If you call my dad Osama once more,
I swear I'll mix RDX in your coffee!
Tell him about my car... my car...
- Ok.
Hey, tell him that...
- Shush... ringing...
Hi papa
- Why didn't you call at lunch time?
I was in an important meeting...
I sent you an sms,
you never read them...
Should I read my transfer orders
now, or your messages?
Transfer... Oh no, not again!
Bloody...
Just a month away from retirement...
and they've transferred me
to bloody Animal Husbandry...
Animal what?
Husbandry...
It's under the Ministry
of Agriculture...
isn't there one decent
posting in my fate...
I will resign, today itself...
I'm going to write such a stinker
of a resignation letter,
lt'll shake up the whole
Government... you see...
Like you've sent any
of the resignation letters
that you wrote after
the last six transfers!
Ok!
This time I'll do it!
I'll send in the resignation...
you wait!
Ok bye... bye I love you
Hmm.. so
He's very jumpy ya...
More than normal?
Animal husbandry ya!
Not fair no...
I know, poor animals...
But when he's in a better mood,
you have to come over officially,
to ask for my hand in marriage.
Hello... I'm not coming over
to ask for your hand!
I can't do this please...
Please ask for my hand...
He is old school.
He'll be happy, we'll be happy.
I love you.
You know how to get me
to do everything..
..and anything just
by saying 'I love you'
I love you...
- Ditto.
Gursharan... Dictation...
Sir, dictation...now?
We need to vacate this office
and shift to Animal Husbandry, Sir!
No, first dictation.
Come here.
- Sir!
To the Honourable Cabinet Secretary,
etc etc ...
Subject... Resignation...
Dear Sir...
Gursharan don't ever
let your son do IAS.
Sir, he's very interested.
He is fully preparing
for the entrance exam...
But he's just twelve...
Sir, only if he starts
now will he be in the IAS.
And he'll keep getting
pushed around like me!
No Sir, my son is very bright,
he will definitely reach the top...
And I'm not bright?
No no...
You are very bright sir,
you are shining bright.
You came fifty eighth in
the All India entrance exam Sir.
Only if there was some smartness
to go with the brightness Sir...
You mean, ''fill my pockets then
I will do your work''
kind of brightness...
If I had that I'd have gone
very far, right?
Right...
Wrong Sir...
Filling of pockets very wrong sir.
Hmm...
That's why, I've encouraged
my daughter since nursery
to take up a job
in the private sector...
Mayera's salary at
this point is more than
What I get after thirty-five
years of service...
You write...
Dear sir,
I have to bring to your notice...
Sir one humble opinion sir...
- Yes?
Sir, you're just a month
away from retirement...
Why resign?...
You'll lose your pension sir...
It's just a matter of one month...
But as per your dictation...
What dictation...
Let us shift office...
Let's move to Animal Husbandry...
Shit shit shit, it's ten thirty...
papa's gonna kill me
Listen...
I will come with you,
he wont lose it in front of me...
Really?
- Of course!
Let him just try saying
something to you...
Osama, Obama whatever-
don't worry I'll sort everything...
Of course.
What is he... a dinosaur?
Who sets deadlines these days?
I'm not afraid of anyone, ok!
Mayera...
How many times have I told you...
Sir there's very very
very bad traffic out...
Is anyone talking to you?
No, right?
Who is this?
Mohit Chaddha papa, my friend!
That's me.
He'd got you cake
and wine on New Year's eve...
Come on papa,
he was here on my birthday...
he'd got me those expensive shoes,
and you'd said what kind of
fool gifts shoes on a birthday...
We had a fight over that...
Oh... right... airline boy...
Right... Air Connect...
Junior Ex...
Senior Mayera, Senior...
have you forgotten?
Sorry!
How dare you reprimand my daughter!
Err.. ma'am...
Senior what?
- Sorry?
Senior peon, senior clerk,
senior typist, senior what?
Senior executive sir ...
So good night Mr. Senior...
it's very late,
I'm sure you're sleepy too.
No no... Not really sir ...
Do you like cars sir?
I've bought a new one
...it's automatic ...
Would you like to check it out?
It's so cool!
Mayera...
Thank you for dropping
my daughter...
Good night...
God damn these executives...
Bloody Osama!
Chill it's me..
Now what?
- I love you
Ditto
Mayeru I love you,
but today is Sunday!
Get up...
we're going on a picnic...
Are you good at Frisbee?
Flush? Three two five?
- Three two what?
Never mind,
it's a card game, I'll teach you...
You reach Humayun's Tomb by ten.
You're wasting my Sunday on a picnic?
No way!
Mohit, papa is in
a good mood after ages...
he's retiring in two days...
God knows how jumpy
he'll be then...
If you want to marry me,
you have to ask for my hand... Ok?
Picnic?!
Ask for my hand...
How can I?
- Go... ask...
Oye Mohit!
- Sir
Give me a hand boy... please
- Coming sir
Just fix this...
- Sir right away...
Hmm that's it. Just press it down.
Trying sir
Bloody Duffer
Mohit...
- Yes Sir!
Once again...
It's just a frog, not a crocodile...
What a coward he is!
Ohh... so nice of you sir.
Mayera ready
- Thank you... welcome...
Ask for my hand...
What are you thinking so much for...
Why aren't you asking?
Ask for my hand...
What are you doing?
- I can't do it
Ask for my hand...
What are you two whispering about...
Are you cheating...you two?
No, no...
I'm telling him,
to ask you for the hand...
Yes yes... he lost the last hand...
ok ask...
Come ask for the hand...
Sir, I...
I was just wondering that...
Sir I was saying will you please...
Give me the third last card...
Third last...
One, two,
is this it?
Ace... that's an ace...
Ace Mayera...
Oh bloody Ace.
I am not playing this game.
You bloody cheats.
I'm going for a walk..
You bloody cheaters...
All cheaters.
- What's wrong with you...
You just have to ask for my hand.
You can't do this much?
Humayun's wife got this tomb built.
After that Shahjehan got
the same made in white marble...
for his missus, madam Mumtaz.
Taj Mahal, Agra.
- Yes Sir... Agra..
And after the Taj Mahal,
such a grand tomb was never built.
You know why?
- Why?
All the craftsmen
who made the Taj...
you know, the workers...
Shahjehan lined them up,
took out his sword and whack,
cut off their hands...
...I mean it was a mean thing to do
but having said that..
You know I think.
Papa, Mohit wants to marry me...
What?
- Didn't you hear me?
What did you say?
Not me, Mohit... Go ahead Mohit...
Sir... sir I love you ...
I mean ...
I love your daughter Mayera ...
Humayun's tomb or Taj Mahal,
even my love will
stay rock solid like
these monuments for
centuries and centuries...
Sir, you quoted the
hand cutting incident,
but I want to ask for
your daughter's hand Sir...
I want to marry her.
Oh papa... why are you packing up?
We've not even eaten dessert...
Papa makes very good 'halwa'...
Papa... crap...
Papa... papa wait...
Pick that up...
Papa, Mohit asked you for something,
at least give him an answer...
Mohit come on...
Papa...
Mohit say something!
Sir at least talk to us...
Sir we so coolly asking
you for permission...
others just elope and get married...
Mohit!
You want to marry him... him...
he's talking about eloping...
criminal minded.
Don't even think about it!
The Home Secretary is my batch mate,
the Police Commissioner
of Delhi sends me naughty sms's...
I can trap you in such a case,
you'll keep rotting in jail...
Bloody!
Papa
Uday Singh...
- Sir.
Put all this in the car...
and the rest of the stuff from
that boy's hands...
Check everything before we leave...
Come on Mayera...
No... first say yes...
We'll go home and talk please...
Look Mayera, the entire IAS crowd
shows up here to picnic...
if this news spreads
in the ministry...
there will be unnecessary gossip...
So come...
Ok then,
I will never speak to you again.
Mayera!
- Come on Uday Singh.
Sir.
Good girl,
I'll solve all your problems.
Don't worry!
Come on.
What is this? Emotional blackmail?
What emotional blackmail?
It's just saffron chicken biryani,
and then some delicious,
sweet halwa... that's all.
You think you'll make
my favourite dishes
and get me to agree?
Forget it!
Ok..ok...
just enjoy your chicken biryani
and forget that bloody loser.
Papa he's a Senior executive!
So... how does that matter?
A senior executive doesn't
own the company, does he?
How does that matter...
as long as he loves me...
Nothing happens with love...
Love is everything..
If I didn't have your love
after mummy died..
..what would I have done?
Why did you play mummy's role too?
The other IAS daddy's ...
spent their evenings at
the club with their friends...
but you stayed home
to play with me and my toys.
There was no money, but I had you,
I had your love.
That was enough for me.
Just like Mohit's love
is enough for me.
What more do you need for happiness?
Money! You need money...
And I'm saying this from experience.
Look, I had a government job..
l-A-S, I had a big post
but empty pockets.
All my life I have
been depriving you...
never gave you the pocket money..
or clothes or toys you deserved...
You wanted to go
to the U.S. for an MBA,
I couldn't even give you that.
But now I'll get you
married to a rich boy
who can make your every
wish come true...
And you'll refuse my biggest wish?
Yes... but Mohit
is an absolute no...
Who's asking you to blindly
get married to just anyone?
I have a whole file,
go ahead and choose yourself,
each one has at least a turn over
of twenty five crores... yes.
Papa... I'm going to marry Mohit!
Fine... then do what you want...
Whether I live, I die, I'm sad,
I'm unhappy, what do you care...
Mohit ya... papa is not
ready to listen at all...
he's being so stubborn!
Fourteenth floor please...
Do you know Mohit Chaddha?
From marketing?
How is his character?
Mohit sir,
he's always stuck to one madam..
Always stuck to madam?
She comes here too...
no scoop, no scandal.
But why are you enquiring about him?
Survey ... Family planning!
Mohit Chaddha.
- I was passing by your office...
had some work...
let's have a cup of coffee?
Who the hell are you?
I'm Sehgal...
- Sehgal, who?
Sehgal from Income Tax...
I've come to file a case on you...
Sir but I have filed
all my tax returns...
I'm Mayera's father Sehgal,
you bloody...
I'm calling from
your office reception.
So sorry Sir...
I couldn't recognize your voice,
because I was talking to you
for the first time on the phone...
Sir, you had some work here?
What's your salary?
Sir Sixty five thousand.
Sixty five only!
Sir my Hindi counting
is a bit weak... Sir.
Your salary is even weaker...
My daughter, Mayera...
Seventy two...
her salary is seventy
two thousand...
I know Sir... so proud of her...
You know!
What kind of a man are you?
My daughter's salary is more
than yours and you have no problem?
Come on Sir, what problem...
I love her and she loves me...
It's all cool!
Look Mr. sixty five, sit here...
you know that song about
'let the love never be less,
I will take every other loss',
is all nonsense.
I don't know from which
angle you look good to Mayera.
Till I don't give my approval,
Mayera will not marry you.
You know that right?
So your probation, your inquiry
period starts from today...
During this probation,
I will examine your every molecule.
If I don't detect
any problem in you,
I will say yes for the wedding.
But if I find anything
wrong and I reject you,
then I want no
complication from you.
Understand Mr. Sixty five?
Just vanish, quietly...
You ready for it now?
How can I agree, just like that?
You will take the exam
and give the result as well...
I don't think I stand
any chance of passing...
You have no faith in yourself?
I have full faith
in myself... but...
But? You think I'll cheat?
Who knows...
It's not written
on anyone's face, is it?...
Look here you...
I was being polite
and pretending to give you a choice,
actually you have no choice.
If you're ready to go on
probation speak up,
or forget Mayera. Forever.
Bloody fool!
- I am ready Sir.
Sir.
Good.
Mayera was saying
you have no family,
your parents died a long time ago.
Then at least if I reject you,
your family won't be insulted.
Let's go.
Sir, you had come for coffee..
we serve some awesome capp...
Another thing,
if you're not interested in sports,
then get interested...
Sports is my middle name sir.
TT, Tennis, squash.. anything.
Squash?!
- Squash!
Listen... Papa hates to lose...
he will never let me get married
to a man who defeats him...
He's testing me. If I play badly...
Trust me Mohit. If you win today
you will lose forever.
Hey, come on...
Best of luck
Ready?
Oh no...
Go go Mohit
Shot!
Go papa!
Poor guy...
Service!
The ball has to be
picked up like this...
Game!
Well done...
very good...
Well played sir ... good one.
How were you playing!?
- Super papa super!
I beat you in three straight games.
Sports is my middle name.
You lied, right?
I hate lies. Ask Mayera.
Papa hates lies.
Where did you find this guy?
There are at least seven
boys in my file
who've played
national level football,
Badminton, tennis and cricket!
Papa please.
You are hopeless yes, hopeless!
Absolutely hopeless. Miserable.
You must practice with me, daily.
Chances are slim but
if there is some improvement,
we will see.
Tomorrow same time, here.
Sir tomorrow I have...
- Tomorrow what?
He'll come papa... he'll come.
Hmmm...
Get my kit,
I'm going to the locker room.
Oh god!
I am telling you...
I'm not going to leave you,
whatever he might do.
Your Papa Osama!
Oh yeah!?
What?
The staff has called me... why?
Please just come...
- Sir..
..a small farewell
gift from all of us.
Oh, what was the need for this...
Sir it's just a little something..
- Gursharan..
..oh... thank you so much
Please open it sir, open it...
Ok...
Just a minute sir..
Here it is!
What is this?
Sir, your retired life
begins tomorrow,
right?
- So?
You wont be going out as much,
your movement will
be quite restricted sir...
So?
- This is for your fitness.
It helped me a lot...
one, two and three...
Amazing isn't it Sir?
Th th th thank you...
P p p please stop this...
- Welcome Sir, welcome!
It's a strange gift..
but the entire staff
got together for it.
Now I must get them something
in return, shouldn't I?
Sir, including the peons..
there are seventeen
staff members...
How will you get
something for everyone?
Lets get one thing
that is of use to everyone!
How may I help you sir?
These seem very big and expensive,
can you show us a medium sized TV?
Sure sir... This way
Sir, are you looking
for a specific brand?
Something cheap,
charming and long-lasting...
Breaking news.
The turbulence in the Airline
Industry has grounded many...
Sir this is our
smallest 22 inch LCD...
Increase the volume please...
For the last two years,
airline companies have been bearing
the brunt of the unreliable markets.
But Air Connect is
the first company that
has ousted 1200 employees at one go.
That's right, 1200!
Cabin crew, technical, ground,
marketing staff included.
Marketing!
She's not answering her phone...
Neither is Mohit...
Gursharan, Mohit's job is gone!
Congratulations Sir.
- Thank you,
and congratulations to you too...
This will be your apartment,
sea facing,
on the Dubai Marina...
One of the most posh
localities in Dubai.
It has four bedrooms...
Look at the kitchen...
Look at this.
Rent is totally paid by the company,
plus double salary.
Mind you in UAE dirham
and overseas perks...
Sir, what if I say no?
I'll send you to a mental asylum.
Sir I'm going to get married...
Oh wow, really? Mohit?
Yeah.
Well I didn't think you would
refuse such a great offer,
to get married.
Sir we love each other,
we can't stay apart.
I am really sorry Sir. Thank you.
Wait, don't you want to see
what car they're offering you?
Sir I am really Sorry... but
Yeah ...
Your papa is here?
Papa?
Papa!
Mayeru!
Mayeru? Are you feeling ok?
Are you ok?
I'm ok.
Mohit has lost his
job and you're ok?
Mohit lost his job?
Didn't you watch the news?
If a big company like Air
Connect couldn't save its employees,
then what about the smaller ones?
Demands for safe and secure jobs
in the Government
are increasing...
Applications for Civil Services entrance exams have risen by 21%...
In these tough times of recession,
private company jobs are...
When he had a job,
I was willing to compromise.
But I will die before I
let you marry a jobless man...
Please understand this...
It's over!
- Mohit ...
Hey Mayera, lmmy here...
Mohit, you haven't
lost your job have you?
Hey... this is lmmy!
Tell me seriously ...
Honestly ya, I'm lmmy speaking.
Mohit has gone to
fight with the boss,
he left his phone behind.
So everything is safe?
Yes, my job is safe...
but Mohit's is gone...
What?
See I told you... I told you
Thank God.
I'm so relieved
that your job is safe.
I know ya,
but really sad about Mohit...
Even papa was so worried.
He came to my office!
He's right here.
Mayera are you okay?
Okay bye. I Love you.
Papa please go home and rest now.
I have to attend
a very important meeting.
Papa, Mohit has not lost his job
and neither will he ever lose it.
We will get married
and he will be very successful.
Ok come on. Bye.
No... look..
- Bye.
I heard them say myself...
all the marketing guys..
listen... marketing...
Oh God!
Look I'm sorry about this.
But I was just promoted!
What can I say Mohit.
The salary you get after promotion
can save the jobs of three people.
I don't know... consider this
a sacrifice for your juniors.
Why don't you sacrifice?
Your salary could save
the jobs of at least eight people.
People who don't know anything
about Operations,
shouldn't be sitting tight as CEOs!
Just watch it Mohit...
there's no need to be rude!
If I'd been allowed
to run Air Connect,
I wouldn't let the company even
in this time of recession
lose a single penny...
In fact I was going to quit myself...
because you guys don't deserve me.
What?
I am too good for you...
bunch of idiots!
How dare you call me an idiot!
Like this...
I'll get a job like this...
Double salary... mark my words.
Mohit you better come
back and say sorry...
Mohit!
Mohit relax...
don't get so agitated.
What did she say?
- What will she say?
You say thank you to me,
I've saved your job.
How did you?
I was promoted, I was sacked...
If you'd been promoted,
you'd have gone!
Thanks bro...
- Come on, buy me a beer.
No beer right now.
Stay with everyone, shout slogans,
what if they are pressured
into withdrawing the orders...
Why don't you say sorry to the boss?
I've never said sorry
to anyone in my life,
why should I say it to this moron?!
C'mon, buy me a beer.
Okay, okay, don't say sorry...
But the media is
very hot right now...
news channels are gathering here...
at least give interviews, get famous
and I'll check out the girls.
We want our jobs back...
We're telecasting from outside
the Air Connect offices...
give us our jobs back...
- People are really worried,
and here with me
is Mr lmran Rizvi...
Mr lmran Rizvi,
how are you feeling?
Very bad...
- Can you tell us in detail...
How did you feel
when you lost your job?
I haven't lost my job,
my job is safe...
Stop stop...
If you haven't lost your job then
why are you giving this interview?
Because my friend here
lost his job...
How are you feeling?
Scared...
- I am sorry, what was that?
He says he's scared...
Scared... what are you scared of?
For Mayera...
- Mayera... Mayera your sister...
who will commit suicide
if she doesn't get married, right?
If you use even one shot of his,
I will sue you...
come away from here...
What did you say your name was...
Why were you giving an interview?
Everyone was...
Is everyone getting married?
Is everyone's father my papa?
With such difficulty I've convinced
him that your job is safe...
if he sees this interview,
he will never let us be married...
So let him not ya...
I'm fed up of his
terms and conditions...
There's a world economic crisis on,
the recession has killed
the airlines industry,
the company I work
for is bankrupt today...
Mayera, I'm jobless...
and you're worried about
the lie you've told your father!
Mohit... please don't panic.
You're so smart...
You'll get a job immediately.
But one lie will
save our relationship.
To hide one lie,
one has to tell a hundred others...
I know ...
Come on, let's get out of here.
Hello... I'd like to speak to..
the Police Commissioner
Mr. Khattar...
Me? I'm V K Sehgal!
Secretary to the Govt of India...
Now retired...
Hey Khattar. VK speaking...
How're you doing?
Ok listen.
I have a favour to ask...
I need you to
investigate a guy...
write the name down...
Mohit Chaddha,
Yes Mohit Chadha.
Murder, rape, robbery, molesting,
eve teasing, rioting,
sending dirty texts...
Or any other public offence
or criminal activity...
Please report to me...
It's a matter of
life and death for me.
Hello, yes sir?
Where are you?
- At the office.
Whose office?
Sir, my office.
Then why are you whispering?
Sir I'm in a meeting,
shall I call you back?
I'm retired, not useless...
You think I have
nothing better to do?
I'm a busy man, I have no time...
Ok, do one thing.
Give me your Pan Card number.
Sir why do you want
my Pan Card number?
Why?
If you want to marry my daughter,
I have full right to ask
for your Pan Card number.
And if you don't
have a Pan Card number,
you have no right to marry
my daughter... do you understand?
No, no Sir...
I'll give you my Pan Card number...
I'm giving you my Pan Card number.
And your Passport number,
Voter ID Card number,
your car registration number
and most importantly
your Identity Card number...
I want it all! Got it?
- Yes sir
Ok, now bring the photocopies
of all documents
..to the gymkhana this evening.
And remember,
without document verification,
the marriage is cancelled.
Mr Chaddha... you may please go in.
- Yeah.
Trainee! Are you serious?
Sir I was a senior
executive at Air Connect.
And they fired you.
I'm at least giving
you a trainee's position
and you are not even thankful.
Oh, thank you so much sir.
I think I deserve much better.
Where will you find something
better in this worst-case scenario?
I will, I will get much better...
Much much much better!
Junior Manager- Global Assist,
salary 50000,
Sales Manager- Bling Entertainment,
Salary 40000,
Assistant Marketing Manager...
Inner Beauty ...
salary 85 to 90000...
Inner Beauty,
you mean lingerie and underwear?
Right!
No no... I can't sell underwear...
Refuel for how much sir?
- Fill up the tank...
What's wrong with selling lingerie?
Inner Beauty is even
offering a higher salary..
and before papa finds out.
I don't want to take
any stupid decision
because of Osama's fear...
And come on, I'm in no way going
to sell bras and panties.
Sir, Rs 2865.
- Yeah.
You know airlines is my thing ...
It's just a matter of time,
I will definitely find a job...
I'm good ya...
Hey.
This is new right?
Ya
Zara?
Yes
Very hot... shall I gobble you up?
Look I will play two
games of squash with Osama,
let him win both...
And I will sort everything...
I can handle him.
Sir sign
Our worries tied to
tai;s of fire-crackers...
Our spirits free as kites...
With wonderfu;;y wi;;fu; privi;eges,
We take on our troub;es with pride...
We teach a;; the funsters,
To read, to write,
The meaning of fun.
Our who;e wor;d
is soaked and spoi;t...
Our pockets are
fi;;ed with good times...
Our on;y wea;th, good times...
They strut, they shine, good times...
They f;y in sty;e, good times...
Good times, they f;y...
Hello Jet Airways...
Hello Spice Jet...
Ya I had spoken to you yesterday
I had just called an hour ago...
Mohit Chaddha speaking...
I am very sorry,
better luck next time.
I am sorry..
it's not going to workout.
Sorry.
The posters of dreams,
Can be seen in day-;ight.
;n co;ourfu; packets,
They are so;d in markets.
;f we can he;p it,
And if it's on sa;e.
We wi;; not ;eave
the moon and stars,
We wi;; buy them without fai;.
We make sense of nonsense.
We ;augh at our sorrows.
We are not a;one in this game,
The who;e wor;d is p;aying,
just the same.
Our pockets are
fi;;ed with good times...
Our on;y wea;th, good times...
They strut, they shine, good times...
They f;y in sty;e, good times...
Good times, they f;y...
Why shou;d we think of tomorrow,
today?
This moment is enough to ;ive in.
That which we have
not seen ourse;ves,
Why shou;d we be;ieve in?
Not years,
Things happen in a moment...
Like nood;es, everything is instant.
Joys are momentary...
They are transitory...
A;; you have to do
is ask and you get them-
Our pockets are
fi;;ed with good times...
Our on;y wea;th, good times...
They strut, they shine, good times...
They f;y in sty;e, good times...
Good times, they f;y...
Mr. Chaddha!
You may Please go in ...
Sir...
Yes Sir... But Sir..
Shit!
Mr. Chaddha! Mr. Chaddha...
He ran away sir...
Pickup Pickup Pickup
Pickup Pickup...
Immy man, I'm so screwed..
Alright, listen up guys...
Mohit's dad-in-law
is coming to office.
So just pretend like
Mohit still works here. Ok?
Ok?
- Ok
Nice!
C'mon move ahead...
Is it your father's wedding...
Yes, move it back...
Come on! Move the car!
Move a little ahead.
What's going on man?
- Don't know man...
What's going on?
Oh... aunty..what is this...
Let go off me please...
Brother, please...
Mohit Chaddha, 14th floor...
Thank you
- Yes Sir...
God...
Get to the side...
Move on...
What are you fighting over?
Will you take me?
I'm dead!
Hello sir.
14th floor, please.
People came, people left...
But Mohit sir stayed
strong in his seat...
Hello sir.. how are you?
Who are you?
Sir I'm Mohit's best friend lmmy...
OK..OK...
- Ya ya...
Mohit's cabin is that way...
- Sir not that way...
sir coffee is this way...
Sir lunch plan?
Son in law,
father in law, surprise lunch plan?
The mad... the mad...
the mad son in law...
Oh my God!
Isn't it funny?
Sir, the boss has
called for Mohit...
Why don't you come to my cubicle...
Sir you like Chinese food?
Going somewhere Mohit...
or have you come to apologize?
Mohit's cabin was somewhere here...
- It's on the other side!
No, it's there...
Yes, this is it...
And you're here too...
- I am here...
Good job lmmy...
I will surely recommend
your name for a promotion...
Aah... No... no promotion.
I'm very happy in my cubicle.
Ok bye, see you. Bye.
Very irritating man...
I have to talk to you... come in...
- Sir over lunch?
Lunch?
- Ya
Good idea... come on, lead the way.
After you, please sir.
You have been fined
three times for driving offences,
once for breaking a signal...
and you always file your
IT returns after the due date.
Your US visa was refused
after the first attempt...
I'm sure something is wrong
with you only...
Otherwise one gets
it in the first attempt...
The detailed inquiry is in this...
RTO file, Income Tax,
Police inquiry, passport office.
So many criminal cases.
How can I marry my daughter to you?
Sir, you did this
research all on your own?
Obviously, it's a confidential
matter... what if it gets leaked?
You are so cool Sir!
Excuse me sir, but how
did the government let you go...
How could they retire you,
seriously...
It's a rule, retirement at sixty.
It's a damn useless rule sir.
At sixty a guy comes into his own.
There's a job opening
in our company,
General Manager
Research and Analysis,
age limit is seventy...
Seventy?
- Salary, three lakhs...
Teen lakh per annum?! Good
Spoken just like
a government official.
Three lakhs per month sir,
per month.
Three lakhs rupees per month..
- Ya.
Your bill sir
- Thanks
Let me..
- I insist sir.
Sure... okay
Sir you are an unutilised
resource of this country...
You are wasting the talent
and knowledge of V K Sehgal.
Sir, guide youngsters like me,
India needs you Sir...
You can win the Padma Shri,
the Padma Vibhushan.
You could get an Oscar...
I mean you can definitely
get Bharat Ratna...
Difficult to get the Arjun Award
by merely playing squash sir...
Yes... I'm not going
to sit idle at home...
I get many job offers, many...
I have to take care
of something important,
then I will think about my job.
I'll think about it.
Sorry sir your card
has been declined.
What... something must be wrong
with your machine, try again...
Sir you must go for it.
Sir the machine is fine,
the transaction
is not being approved.
Let me pay, I have my card.
No no Sir, I have cash...
No sir, I don't have cash.
No cash...
let me pay,
why you creating a scene...
how much, how much is it?
Sir, only two thousand
rupees more...
I will just withdraw it
from the ATM and give it to you.
Two thousand... here it is.
Thank you sir.
Sir who keeps
so much cash nowadays?
How can Mayera be the
daughter of this terrorist?
Always ready to drop a bomb!
What?
Shit!
I don't know sir...
My credit card is not working...
ATM card is not working...
I am going to bloody
change my bank...
What bank is your account in?
That means you
didn't get the money?
No...
Are you bankrupt?
Ha ha... so funny sir...
what a thing to say...
Not bankrupt sir...
I'm in a hurry right now.
This matter of offences is pending.
Of course...
and I have to return your money...
Squash at the club, this evening...
You better.
- Yeah.
Hello...
Yeah...
Yes I will pay this
month's EMI by cheque...
Ok I will give you cash...
Yes, I'll give
it to you tomorrow...
I'm telling you I will...
Or else what?
You'll take the car away?
Take away your damn car then!
Hello Mayera...
Busy or what?
Nothing ya, just needed some help...
Here
- How much is it?
Fifty thousand.
I had asked for forty no?
Extra ten.. Pocket money.
- What pocket money?
Am I a kid to be given pocket money?
Of course you're a kid!
All your money is over
and you didn't even know?
Listen, you should
maintain detailed accounts,
I will check at
the end of each month.
What do you mean by every month?
You mean I'm such a big idiot
that I won't find a job for months?
If you're stuck on airlines,
then you surely won't get a job...
I have mailed you a new job list.
The Inner Beauty position
is still available.
If you get the job,
I will get free lingerie.
This is like saying
if I became a waiter,
you'll get free food...
So Mayera ma'am,
what would you like to order today?
On today's menu
we have plain paratha,
plain butter paratha,
plain ghee paratha,
aaloo paratha, aloo butter paratha,
aloo ghee paratha, gobhi paratha,
gobhi butter paratha,
gobhi ghee paratha..
Today's special is
mix vegetable paratha.
Shut up you clown!
I've left my meeting half way...
I have to go...
Ok bye!
Mayera!
What?
What if I really become a waiter?
Standing at the cross-roads,
Will you marry a waiter?
When someone asks a question.
You won't become a waiter.
- Why do a;; answers,
You never know...
- Seem unre;iab;e.
What if I have to?
Nothing seems rea;
Even then I'll marry you...
Now I really have
to get to work, ok...
On these crossroads
I love you
Except an imaginary indifference.
Papa. Papa
- I am so sorry sir
Are you ok?
- Papa are you okay?
Yes I am
Yes darling I am ok.
So ironical that you want
to marry the man..
..who wants to make you an orphan!
How wonderful is that?
Papa, don't over react...
please go and change, come on...
I am sorry sir!
No problem,
sports is your middle name huh?
Taking out your
frustrations on the ball?
I have tried all the
companies on your list,
looks like I'll have
to become a waiter after all.
Your girlfriend is too good...
I've already made a new list.
Go and change now...
Listen,
what is this 'new job' tune that
you're teaching papa to sing?
''I'll take on a job,
I'll take on a job'',
he keeps saying excitedly.
I've shut him up.
He's worked hard enough
for the last 35 years,
from home to office and back again.
He's worked very hard
all his life...
It's his time to relax now.
Why does he need to work anymore?
I can take care of him.
Don't hoist him again on the
'three lakh pay-package tower'
Ok, promise?
Ok...in any case,
who's going to hire him?
Very funny!
Mohit... Hey Mohit
- Sir...
I'm ready for a new job.
Sir Mayera has forbidden it.
Who's going to tell her?
You frighten me all the time,
and now you'll lie yourself?
Nobody is going to lie, you fool...
When I get the job,
we'll tell Mayera.
Till then start job hunting for me.
Why should I?
Because it was your idea,
you will do it.
No sir, I won't do it.
Mayera has categorically said no...
OK, then the wedding is cancelled.
Go shower bloody...
Osama!
Hey Mohit.
Let's send the application
by registered post.
Post is so uncool.
You'll never get a job if you send
a letter in this day and age.
Email sir, email.
Actually, the real problem is that
I don't know how to use a laptop.
Not a big deal sir,
it works just like a computer.
I don't even know how
to use computers!
You don't know to use the computer?
I don't ok...
Do you know to make chicken biryani?
You don't, right? Similarly
I don't know computers, that's it!
Oh Sir...
Then for you Sir,
we'll have to look for one...
that even a fool can use.
You called me a fool?
You bloody fool!
Mayera!
- Where?
Hello...
Yes, actually I'm in a meeting.
Yes in an interview...
Baby just listen...
I'll just call you back. Ok.
Love you. Bye.
Ok...You stop the car here.
Right here.
Sir here?
- I'm telling you, stop the car.
The house is ahead...
- You argue too much man...
Sir but why?
- Again why!
Do one thing-jump the wall,
then hide and cross the garden...
Yes hide, and come in
through my bedroom window.
Sir isn't this story absurd...
Romeo hides from Juliet's
father and goes to meet her.
He doesn't hide form
Juliet to go meet her father.
Does Radha work in Juliet's house?
- No!
Radha will see Romeo,
she'll inform Juliet,
Juliet will ask her father
'what was Romeo doing with you,
out of office,
in the middle of the afternoon'?
That's correct logic!
So do it.
- Yeah.
Let me send Radha
out for some work...
Then I'll signal you to come inside.
Got it Commando?
Aye Aye Captain!
- Roger!
Bloody hell.
Radha, Radha!
- Yes papaji
Come here...
A few of my shirts and trousers
are lying outside the cupboard,
take them to the washerwoman
and get them ironed nicely.
And don't come back till they're
all done, even if takes an hour.
But Shah Rukh's film on TV...
Hey, don't talk nonsense with me...
till the job is not done,
stay with the washerwoman.
What can I say...
I'm missing the film...
There's always so
much work around here...
Have you seen it?
- Not yet, I'm not that lucky...
Oh, you haven't?
I'm crazy about Shah Rukh...
But ever since papaji has retired,
he just doesn't let
go off the remote control...
Bloody duffer!
Hey
Hey lovebirds!
Hi
- Hi
Are we the love-birds
or are you guys the love-birds?
lmmy's record-breaking
relationship...
Two months and still
going strong, yes?
Yes...
Just when Mohit lost his job,
Swati came into my life...
What? Now everything will
be with reference to my job?
Before Mohit's job...
After Mohit's job?
Bad mood huh?
Come on show us your dimples man...
C'mon show us...
Hmmm...very bad mood.
Immy let's go dance!
One Long Island ice
tea and one rum-n-coke.
No rum-n-coke.
Yes rum-n-coke.
I'm on antibiotics....
Do you have the flu?
Best medicine, Rum n Coke!
One Rum n Coke please.
Sir, if my girlfriend
would tell me so lovingly...
What would you do huh?
Shower in Rum and Coke?
Go, shower...
You just...make your drinks...
Mohit... I'm paying...
Why do you keep ranting
about paying all the time?
I don't want it, that's it!
Is there some compulsion?
Ok, no compulsions...sorry.
I am sorry.
Hey
I am sorry dude!
Hey listen...we both are going
for the rock show on 25th, ok?
But aren't the tickets for Rs 5000?
- No if's and but's...
I'll pay right now, you can return
the money when you find a job!
By then I'll be a bus conductor...
Better if you take someone else.
If you'll be a bus conductor,
then I'll become the bus driver.
And I'll kidnap you
and your bus forever.
And what if I become
an ice-cream seller?
Then I'll buy the van...
And I'll gobble up
all the ice-cream, and you!
Look, it's my job to gobble up...
And what if I end up as
an auto-rickshaw driver?
Then I'll be the traffic cop...
I'll cut you a ticket
and lock you up in my jail for life.
Ok...And what if I land up
being a postman?
Need;ess;y, you make and break.
Need;ess;y, you count each penny.
Need;ess;y you're afraid of ;ove.
Need;ess;y you push me honey.
Need;ess;y, you make and break.
Need;ess;y, you count each penny.
Need;ess;y you're afraid of ;ove.
Need;ess;y you push me honey.
;'m the heroine of your every story.
;'m the happy ending
of your every ta;e.
When the storm came,
You packed up your things,
You emptied my heart and ;eft.
;f ; cou;dn't pay the rent,
Of your heart my ;ove,
You wou;d throw me out instead.
Hey, ; made a promise for ;ife,
When the dea; was made.
But my pockets are empty,
how can ; repay
This debt that ; have raised!
; wi;; stake my c;aim
and take you home.
First ;et me prove my worth,
my ;ove.
Need;ess;y,
you make promises of ;ove...
Need;ess;y, you raise your hopes.
Need;ess;y you dream crazy gir;,
Need;ess;y, our story's done.
;'m the heroine of your every story.
;'m the happy ending
of your every ta;e.
;f you were booze,
;'d knock you down.
;'d make myse;f your addiction.
;'d be that c;oud,
That stayed with you,
;f you became my sky!
Sweet to the ears,
Not easy to do.
To co;or yourse;f in another hue.
Co;ors fade,
Just ;ove remains,
Everyone e;se changes-
Red orange ye;;ow b;ue and green.
Need;ess;y,
you make promises of ;ove...
Need;ess;y, you raise your hopes.
Need;ess;y you dream crazy gir;,
Need;ess;y our story's done.
;'m the heroine of your every story.
;'m the happy ending
of your every ta;e.
Need;ess;y..
;'m the heroine of your every story.
;'m the happy ending
of your every ta;e.
Not bad Sehgal Sir...
You must've thought
of an email ID...
Vinod Kumar Sehgal.
No No its too long?
How about...VK Sehgal?
SehgalVK ...sounds cool!
Cool!
..s..
..e..
..h..
..g..
Wow so many jobs?
Yes, but around 80% are useless...
What is this now?
It's a game... just...
Video game?!
- Yeah
Move then... move, move...
Start it please...
Enter click, right here.
Wow!
I killed the damn...
Super cool game man...
Ok, do one thing...
let's see how you play!
Me Sir?
- Play this game
Tell me one thing...
You come here every
other day under..
the pretext of
a client meeting, right
Ok then, I won't come from tomorrow.
No no...I was just asking...
My job shouldn't create
problems for your job.
My job...
Nothing will happen. Don't worry.
Radha!
Come on, come on and take your coat.
Coming, coming...have patience!
What took you so long papaji...
What were you doing?
We are an insurance
company Mr. Chaddha,
and your experience
is in airlines marketing.
Won't work for us.
Sir just give me a chance.
Not just insurance,
I can even market the Qutub Minar!
Qutub Minar!?
It's not that easy Mr. Chaddha...
It's the era of specialization...
Thank you for coming.
Sir I think I have potential sir...
Sir just give me the job,
I will become a specialist.
You become a specialist,
we'll give you the job.
Sir please sir...
Sir one chance sir...
Just one chance...
Sir I'm a star performer...
I have the potential....
Sir I was an MBA topper...
I'll do it Sir...
I'll prove it to you sir!
I will prove myself Sir...
I'll work really hard sir!
- Mohit...Mohit Chaddha...
Are you asking for
a job are you begging?
Please!
I am sorry ...
Hey listen...
Only six tickets are left...
Should I book tickets
for both you and Mohit?
Yeah, book them!
- No listen, this is red lounge...
You guys ditched us the last time...
700 rupees were wasted...
Please confirm and tell us Mayera...
Excuse me ... your phone ...
Hey
- Hi baby..
Six thirty movie...
- I can't come...
Why, what are you doing?
Everyone is going, let's go?
Everyone is so worried
about my job...
That's the reason why
I've come for this interview,
to end everyone's worries.
So I should avoid watching
the movie with everyone
and focus on my interview.
I'm sure everyone will understand.
Mohit, these are your friends.
That's why they're
so worried about you.
There's no need to be so sarcastic.
Anyway, no chance for
the six thirty show right?
No chance...
There are around 10-11
candidates before me
The interviews are extensive,
in-depth.
But in case it gets over earlier...
Damn it! I said there's no chance
Ok...best of luck.
Hi.. brother
- Hi.
Sister is in her room.
- Ok.
Mohit! Mohit..
Hello
Hey did you email
my application properly?
There's no reply from anyone!
Why are you getting stressed?
You'll get a response soon.
Hey, where are you going man?
- It's her birthday.
Assault mission game...cool huh?
Where did you get this from?
Palika market. Six hundred.
If you'd told me, my guy
would've got it for three fifty
Your guy wouldn't even
get the cover for three fifty.
I have a reliable source in Palika.
Mohit?!
- Ya Coming!
Coming!
Hi
Happy birthday.
- Thank you...
How do I look?
Very hot...shall I gobble you up?
Mango! My birthday gift to myself.
What did you get for me?
That's it?
How could I borrow money from you,
to get a gift for you?
It's my birthday!
I wasn't expecting
a diamond necklace,
you could have got me just a rose...
You get pocket money after all.
Open the door,
or else we'll break it down!
Happy Birthday to you...
Hi Wassup! Hey!
Open the gift ya...
Amazing!
Guys c'mon ya!
Go for it!
Open the gift ya...
It's awesome
Go get the candles!
Go get it!
Your cheque...it's bounced again.
The landlord's fuming dude.
You've got to arrange
for the rent today somehow.
Bro you help me out today.
I'll arrange the money by next week.
Dude you haven't returned
the last loan either.
I need cash badly,
please return my cash as well.
You know what, forget it...
just arrange for this month's rent.
And Mohit, bro,
do something about your job.
I'm working on it, I am.
What are you doing?
You're just busy
flying high in the air!
Come back to earth bro,
accept a job in a lower position.
Why should I?
I'm an MBA for God's sake,
top of my class.
And who got promoted, you or me?
I was, and because of that
promotion your job got saved.
So in return I should pay
your rent for the rest of my life?
lmmy
Get out!
You know what...you've started
enjoying being unemployed.
You want your money?
You'll get it...
Now just get lost!
I don't have fifteen thousand.
I spent a lot this month...
I got a new dress,
my birthday party,
your car EMI,
your credit card bill,
your phone bill,
your pocket money...
Awesome!
Means whenever
I ask you for money,
I'll have to listen
to this entire list?
If you had warned me
about the rent in advance,
I wouldn't have bought
the rock show tickets.
Rock show tickets!
Did I ask you to buy those tickets?
Mohit now don't do that...
- You don't do that ...
If you had told me earlier,
I'd have sacrificed this as well...
like all other things.
Sacrifice! What a sacrifice!
- Yes ... sacrifice!
You don't realize anything...
I haven't even bought a new pair
of sandals these last two months.
O god ... What a crisis!!!
What a crisis!!
Yes it is a crisis ...
Stuck on pizzas
and your oily omelet's..
I've gained two bloody kilos!
I work hard so that
I can enjoy my life,
but thanks to you,
leave alone malls and night-clubs,
I've even forgotten the
smell of multiplex pop-corn!
I don't want to waste my life
sitting in front of your television!
It's one rock show that I wanted
to go for and even for that...
you're creating such a scene!
Mayera, one rock show!
It's just a rock show!
You know what,
you should be given a Nobel Prize!
Somebody, please,
give her a Nobel Prize.
Any half sensible man would've
actually given me a prize!
Why prize,
I'll give you your money back.
Don't stress,
I'll settle everything!
Ok Mohit every single penny...
Of course! With interest!
- You are so disgusting ...
Yes, I'm the disgusting one.
You're Mother India!
Mohit stop the car ...
I said I'll return it.
I don't want to sit
in your dirty rotten car!
Stop the car!
Ok..
Out of my car now...
Get lost, bye...
and never sit in it again!
Moron!
Where to madam?
What do you want? Move ahead!
Hey rickshaw...rickshaw.
One two three four...
One two three four
One two...
I've got mail...
there is a vacancy...
I would like to welcome...
join company.
Yes! Yes! Yes! Oye yes yes!
Sir, it's a car not a cycle...
Latest model.
No dent, no scratch,
hasn't run even a thousand miles.
Your quotation is a shame for me...
Make an offer I can't refuse...
The car is in your garage...
as soon as the money is
in sir's pocket!
...Or else I can go to Mr. Bhalla.
Yes Sir
- Yes Mohit...
I've called to inform you,
an interview call has finally come.
It had to...the application
was filed so neatly.
Neatly means nothing...
My five page, mind-blowing
bio-data must have impressed them.
Anyway, reach home quickly.
We have to start preparing
for the interview.
No Sir, not now...
there's some crisis here...
Ok... if you can't come,
I'll come to your office..
No no...
You don't come here.
I'll do something
Good, reach by 5.
And look...thank you for all.
Ok then.
Yes papa...
Mayera come home early today...
Look, have I ever asked
you to come home early?
No, right!
But today please reach home by 6,
and no discussion on this.
Or I will never speak to you again.
Six means six. Bye bye bye.
Radha!
O radha
- Yes papaji
Order two chicken
from the meat shop...
and prepare the biryani spices....
Mohit and Mayera
are coming home for dinner...
Alright!
- And listen, make halwa as well.
Gursharan...You know
PC Jewelers right?
Can you get me a discount?
So meet me there!
At the South Ex show room...
in one hour...
I'll call you back.
Eighty eight thousand...
with detailed accounts, date-wise.
I've put in five thousand extra,
just in case I've made a mistake.
And if the mistake is of more
than five thousand, just email.
I'll you a draft.
Where is the damn accounts slip?
It's ok...
I'll make a fresh one...
I remember everything...
What impression will
my son-in-law have of me,
if I give him such a ring?
Show me a solid one,
not these flimsy things.
What are you doing madam,
Sehgal Sir is secretary
to Government of India IAS...
Show us something
worthy of his status.
Where is your owner, call him...
No no Sir, I'll show you...
Take a look at this...
Matching rings for
the bride and groom.
Yes, yes these are
solo diamonds right...
What are they called?
- Sir solitaire..
Solitaire. solitaire.
They are good.
This will cost you around
four and a half lakhs...
No...
Four and a half is too much...
Show us something reasonable.
No, do one thing...
please pack these.
Here!
Please check...
this includes the tickets
of your stupid rock show...
So I guess everything
is cleared between us.
All clear...
Rock show is stupid
because I wanted to go...
and to be a cry baby like
you and stay home is very clever.
I don't want to be clever like you,
I'm fine being stupid.
And you know what,
clever and stupid
shouldn't get married either.
Yes, as if I want to get married.
In any case I can't afford
the stupidity of love
and marriage anymore.
You know Gursharan
- Yes sir!
This boy that Mayera has chosen...
His market value may be less,
but his character is priceless...
In my humble opinion,
character is the only value sir.
Today when I got the interview mail,
I thought I've tested
this boy enough...
I should agree to their marriage...
Correct thinking sir.
But Mohit should never
know I was praising him,
how long does it take
to get conceited, huh?
Top secret sir.
Now even this expensive
ring seems reasonable for him...
perfect matching.
We are not made for each other.
Tsck!
Actually there isn't any
point in meeting again.
So I've not come to meet you,
I've just come to return the money.
Break-up.
In fact I was going to say it first.
Breakup!
- Fine,
you're first, I'm last...happy?
Fine then get lost.
You get lost
This is my office Mohit,
you get lost...
Your office, your money...
go to hell Mayera.
Why do a;; answers,
Seem unre;iab;e.
Nothing seems rea;,
On these crossroads
Except an imaginary indifference.
This is the entire
history of the company...
Please put away the
games and try to read it.
Why should I read about them,
are they taking my interview
or am I taking theirs?
When I had come to
ask for Mayera's hand,
I had done my complete
home-work on you...
so that I don't say anything
that will make you reject me.
Wow! You're very cool...
Ok, I'm leaving now
- Wait, wait...
I'll get you a beer...
- No Sir, I have to go to work...
Beer is just a cold drink
Please don't have a cold drink
before your interview.
Ok, do one thing..
you load the game,
I'll just come. Load the game...
Now where's this Mayera?
Must be on her way...
- It's six...
I had told her to come early...
How much longer can I delay Mohit...
Aah...The smell of the
halwa is irresistible...
The thing is son,
this is not a chilled beer,
it's a child beer...
Cheers!
- Papa I am home ...
We're here Mayera...
Where are you off to?
Mohit?!!!
What the hell ...
What are you doing in my house?
I...l...
- Hey, son of Romeo...
your Juliet is here...
Leave the window and come in...
Papa please...
- Shhh...quiet....nobody will speak,
Only I will speak now...
Radha!
- Radha is at home?
So where else will she be?
C'mon Mohit, show some enthusiasm...
Sit down both of you!
Congratulations brother...
Sister...
Yoohoo...Surprise...
Congratulations...
One for you and one for you
Take it, will you keep
me standing like this?
Tell me, do you like it?
How do you like it, the rings?
What?
Someone say something...
This is your probation's
report card...
you're not perfect,
but we'll make do...
Now before I change my mind,
please make each other
wear the rings...
What's wrong?
They're solitaires...
Don't like the design?
Ok, just wear them
now for ceremony...
Tomorrow you can go there
and choose your own rings.
Ok?
So who wears the ring first,
the boy or the girl?
Why are you laughing?
Papa...we are not getting married...
She is serious ...
It's over between us...all over..
Hey...sit, sit down!
So I simply played all this squash,
wasted my sweat,
made enquiries in
fifty departments...
And do you know how many
phone calls, photocopies,
plastic files I've spent
on...on this Mohit of your's?
Not mine.
Now I'm not going to
investigate any other boy...
Talk to each other, and resolve
whatever this fight is about...
Say sorry,
and exchange rings...come on...
Papa it's impossible.
There's a huge gap between us now.
Which can only be filled
with a lot of money.
Money that your daughter has,
but I don't...
Does anyone fight over money...
Did you borrow money from him?
Return it...
I don't have any money
for her to borrow...
I haven't got a salary
for three months...
and the fact is, I am unemployed..
I'm looking for a job.
You lost your airlines job?
Oh bloody!
You lost it then itself, right?
I knew it...I knew it...
You lied to me?
- Yes...
I lied to you...
So now, should I
make her wear the ring?
Like hell you will!
You've failed a 100%...
100% fail!
You've lied, you liar!
And you pretend to be Gandhi...
you are lying to Mayera yourself...
What lying?
I'm trying for a job,
he's helping me...
Was helping me...was!
You had promised me...
Sister, halwa...
Forget it Papa ...
Please get rid of
this job mania...ok?
Mohit gone... mania gone!
Driver, bring the car...
- Excuse me sir...
Come in Mayera.
Sir is the Dubai
position still open?
You've taken too long silly...
Dubai office has
already got someone.
Trust me I don't
like that moron one bit.
I wanted you there Mayera.
But he's joining next week,
if you can go before that...
Can you leave tonight?
The travel desk will
arrange the visa..
Absolutely sir
- Perfect!
I say go there, work for a week ...
do your magic ...
If you are able
to convince them there,
I'll get all the approvals here.
And once you get
the appointment in Dubai,
come back over
the weekend to shift base properly.
What say?
I say ... Thank you ...
thank you so much sir.
But for now,
just keep this to yourself...
you are going on
a regular assignment.
What about Mohit?
Mohit is history.
What's going on?
Hello sir...l'm Nawab Master...
the driving instructor...
I have a second hand
business as well...
just yesterday I sold
Mohit sir's car at a top price...
Call me if you have anything.
Mohit?! Dude You sold your car!
What's going on!?
Ok so all accounts
have been settled now...
Where are you going?
They're settled today,
they'll be unsettled tomorrow...
If I stay with you guys
any longer who knows,
I might begin to enjoy
being unemployed...
Mohit ... Mohit sorry.
I swear I'll never
read your newspaper...
I'll never watch Big Boss...
I'll pay for beer for
the entire month...I swear...
You can have my entire
Playboy collection!
The remote as well!
Mohit...
You coach your heart,
Reproach your heart,
Foo; it into submission.
;f it's not broken,
;t's trust is not taken,
Then why does it hurt so much...
Fa;se concessions...
Fake confessions...
;t hides a;; your mistakes...
;t foo;s others,
And condemns itse;f,
Looks for gain even in ;osses.
Stupidities...
Meaning;ess and point;ess ...
Need;ess and thought;ess...
Unnecessary stupidities...
Stupidities...
Meaning;ess and point;ess ...
Need;ess and thought;ess...
Unnecessary stupidities...
Mr. Chaddha
- Yes...
Hi Mr. Chaddha
- Hello.
I'm really sorry ...
All the positions have been taken...
Why don't you leave
your resume behind,
we'll get back to you.
No... thanks
Ok...all the best.
Your temper's sti;; high,
You show no improvement.
You fa;; on your face a;; a;ong.
Not a;; is f;awed,
Not a;; is ;ost,
Then why is your face so ;ong?
You spend your days cursing others..
Oh how stubborn you are!
Someone must stop you,
at ;east accost you
Ti;; when wi;; you foo; yourse;f?
Mohit, hi.
- Hi.
Meet Mohit ...
Our new counter manager ...
Hello sir
How are you doing?
- Hello
Hi there
- Welcome
Meaning;ess and point;ess ...
Need;ess and thought;ess...
Unnecessary stupidities...
Very hot...
shall I just gobble you up?
Stupidities...
Meaning;ess and point;ess ...
Need;ess and thought;ess...
Unnecessary stupidities...
Hey you foo;, its easy
To join these broken parts...
Don't fret, its not hard
To say you're sorry at ;ast.
Why are you faking,
Posturing and raving,
What wi;; you achieve from it?
Why open accounts...
Why weigh...
...what you ;ose and win?
Stupidities...
Meaning;ess and point;ess ...
Need;ess and thought;ess...
Unnecessary stupidities...
Stupidities...
Meaning;ess and point;ess ...
Need;ess and thought;ess...
Unnecessary stupidities...
Thank you sir...
Negi...who are those
couples at table 3 and 12?
They've been occupying those tables
for the last three hours...
Get them out!
- They're penniless lovers sir...
Where will they go
for their love talk?
If they go home,
parents will slap them...
If they go to a park,
cops will shoo them away...
They're sitting here
quietly cooing...let them...
Why get into the business of love...
when they're penniless!
Yes Sir, boss's orders...
I'll shoo these love-birds away...
Hey senior-most ...
First put that stick aside...
Give them a cappuccino each,
and tell them they won't
get anything for free after this!
If they want to sit here,
they'll have to spend...
Or else, out in an hour...
My love mantra touched
you as well, right?
Yes bro, I'm really touched...
Shall I give them
both a brownie as well?
Shall I throw you out?
You're something else...
try to be happy...
Hi..
Hey, you're back!
Sir this is Manju...
She'd gone to Rohtak
for her cousin's wedding...
This is our Mohit Sir...
Hello sir ...
- Hi Manju ...
Sir I'll just be back...
Sir Manju is my GF
I can see that.
Now I'll enjoy my work...
Sir
- Yeah?
Don't mind, but your
professional story is very sad...
But your love story
can be easily solved..
..by saying sorry to each other.
- Manju, by god!
Her mother calls
her 'Big-mouth Manju'...
I'm never going to
tell you anything now...
I'm sorry I told her sir...
Other than this,
your secret is a top secret...
It's her fault...
she should say sorry...why should I?
But Sir, just listen...
Just talk to her once and see...
Let's go Manju...
Sir has a very bad temper!
Hey let me just talk
to him for a second...
That liar!
Jobless...
...dependent on Mayera
for the last two months!
I should have sent him to jail!
Don't know why I'm
so confused about him...
Sir, the Government never
respected your goodness...
transfer upon transfer...
But God is watching Sir,
he saved you and our
Mayera at the last minute...
No more scope for confusion.
Tell madam to give me whatever
money is due for these rings...
Sir patience sir patience...
But I didn't understand one thing...
Once he had broken up with Mayera,
why did he go out
of his way to help you?
Logically speaking,
he shouldn't have...
I think it's a big conspiracy Sir...
In my humble opinion, pull
some strings and send him to jail...
Gursharan Singh!
What an opinion.
Sir your luck is very good,
gold prices have shot up...
You've made a profit
of thirty seven thousand,
five hundred and eighty rupees...
Thirty seven thousand...
Why did my luck
have to change today?
Bloody!
I don't want to sell...
thanks a lot for your assistance...
Sir
- Sir
You raised one question
and cleared the entire matter...
couldn't you have done this earlier?
I wouldn't have had to
bear such a big loss.
Sir what question did I raise sir?
He had made me a promise...
and how could he break his promise?
He came to help me
even after the break up...
Wow! Look at the character
of that guy...
How can I leave a guy
with such a fine character?
Sir anyone can get a character
certificate by paying extra money...
but the boy is jobless.
Yes he's jobless,
but he taught me that life
doesn't end but starts at sixty...
That duffer made me,
what is that, cool...
He made me cool!
He's an MBA,
sooner or later he'll get a job...
That's ok Sir... but..
the thinking of the boy
and girl doesn't match yours...
They are fighting...
Gursharan,
have Romeo and Juliet ever
come together without the villain?
No sir
- No!
This time as well the
villain will unite them.
Mayera!
- Where were you?
I've been trying your
phone for so long!
Give me the keys,
I need your passport...
Passport? Why?
What?
- Just hear me out...sit here...
What is this?
Our new house, in Dubai...
Our new house?
Yes papa.. It's a
4 bedroom apartment...
A kitchen that's bigger than
our living room, fully equipped.
Meet Mayera Sehgal papa...
new vice president
of the Dubai office...
Double the salary,
that too in Dirham...
See, I did what you wanted!
What?!
Now don't say you
don't want to go...
because you don't have a choice...
No silly...
I'm in shock, with happiness...
It's the best decision
of your life...
Here are the keys...
But we have to pack
up the house in two days,
if I don't join on Monday
the offer will be cancelled..
Don't worry, I'm there...
I'll do what's correct for you...
That Mohit, that useless Mohit...
Imagine if you'd
gotten married to him,
would you have been
able to move to Dubai?
Radha, did you get the cartons?
Yes...
Don't worry, we won't leave
without taking our revenge...
I have told Gursharan to
make a fake case against him
and send him to Tihar jail...
Papa are you mad?
First they will break his
bones with the Tihar sticks,
that'll really be breaking
Mr. Mohit up!
What fun!
You're just too much!
Call Gursharan Uncle right now...
Stop him, come on...
Will you feel bad
if that rogue is in pain?
If you love him so much,
why are you running away to Dubai?
I'll get out of your way...
Now you're getting confused,
should I go to Dubai or not...
To be or not to be...
Romeo and Juliet...
There's no confusion...
I just don't want any new problem
to come up and keep us behind...
Talk to Gursharan uncle...
Yes Gursharan
Tihar-plan cancelled...
Happy?
Hey Gursharan my friend...
nobody has to be sent to Tihar...
Now listen to me,
Mayera has taken both
our passports to Ajanta Travels
for the tickets and visa...
You have to set up something
at the travel agency so
that we don't get the visas...
Now you understand?
Yes, we shouldn't get the visas!
Good...
Yes!
Come on Mohit, answer the phone...
Oh hell!
Now how do I contact this duffer?
You sir...?
- Yes.
Sir...Mohit was just here...
I think he's gone
to the conference room...
Will you keep lying all your life,
to save your friend?
Not lying...
Where is he? Tell me the truth.
He's changed his number,
doesn't reply to emails...
I don't know Sir,
he's just disappeared...
Think!
There must be someone
who can tell us about him...
Think carefully,
the Home Secretary was my batch mate!
By God, what happened to
Mohit was very unfortunate...
I tried to tell him,
don't show off your automatic car,
who knows you may not
have even a cycle tomorrow!
He didn't listen to me...
But where is he?
Stop bro, stop...Sir over there...
Very good...Thank you Master.
Ok lmmy, thank you...
- Welcome sir.
Hey waiter!
Bloody good!
How can I help you sir?
Do you get a salary,
or are you on daily wages?
Which coffee sir?
Hmm, get me a Cappuccino...
and a cup of tea for you.
It's on me...
No thanks... One cappuccino please!
Anything else?
How about a brownie ...
Let me help increase your sales,
you must be getting
a commission huh?
Bring it out please.
Let the ;ove never be ;ess,
; wi;; take every other ;oss...
Let the ;ove never be ;ess...
Hey boy!
What shoddy service is this?
Clean the damn table!
Take it...
You can get your new
girlfriend peanuts with it...
And this time look for
someone who is of your status.
Why have you come here?
To tell you that Mayera
is moving to Dubai.
It hurts doesn't it?
How you both used to boast...
''We can eat love,
we can wear love''
''we can fill love in the
petrol tank and drive off...''
So where is all that love?
Now do you understand
the value of money?
As always,
Mayera is smarter than you..
She's taken a transfer to Dubai...
In a week's time Dubai will
make her forget the pain, and you...
You just keep selling
your tea coffee here...
You think you're very smart,
but you're just a big duffer!
Don't you understand
Mayera is spoilt...
She's gotten used
to the 5 Star life...
You should be happy
the marriage didn't happen,
she would have made you bankrupt!
See, as soon as you
lost your money,
that snob tossed you aside like
an insignificant fly!
You're calling your
own daughter a snob?
Why are you feeling bad?
What does she mean to you now?
Anyway, she's dumping
you and going...
that too in business class!
After this, don't ever let yourself
fall in love with a money-minded,
selfish, opportunist like Mayera...
Enough Mr. Sehgal!
This is too much..
You've said enough...
Now if you say even
one word against Mayera I'll...
You'll what? What will you do?
The Romeo passion doesn't
go well with empty pockets...
You flaunt your love
like you're some millionare
but you're just a bloody waiter!!
We're leaving for
the airport in about three hours...
understood?
If I see you within a five kilometer
radius of the airport...
remember, the Home Secretary
is my batch mate!
Excuse me!
Your photo will go
to the home department...
Then it will flash to every PCR van,
Black Cats,
NSG commandos, CRPF, RAW agents...
Don't you ever mess with us
and stay away from my daughter!
Bloody waiter!
She's moving to Dubai...
She could have atleast told me that!
Sir there's no point
in being sad right now...
Just go say sorry to ma'am,
and stop her from leaving.
How can I just go
and apologize to her?
She's the one who broke up first.
She'll have to say sorry first.
Sir it's not a race...
If you're going to let your
ego become as big as an airplane,
Ma'am will simply fly away!
And you'll be left wondering forever
Bloody waiter....
Sir, that old man
has insulted all of us...
You've to give it back to
that rotten fellow!
Yes Sir, steal Mayera away
from right under his nose...
That will be a fitting reply.
Are you done with the lecturing?
Enough of me and my life...
get back to work.
Sir please listen to me...
- I said get back to work!!
Hey! Stop right here...
Yes...Stop...
How much?
- Forty five sir...
Keep the change...
Where were you papa? Hurry up
and get ready or we will get late...
I'll just get ready...
Gursharan done?
- Ma'am please sign here...
No, not done sir.
Not done what?
- What done? Not done?
What? No nothing...
Go inside!
Ma'am your passports with
Dubai Visa ... and tickets.
Radha, you've latched
all the windows properly right?
Yes!
- And switched off the gas?
I have...
- Ok alright!
Give all your papers
to Gursharan uncle...
And come here to
clean up every Saturday,
otherwise I won't
come back to get you...
Sis, don't go please...
Why are you crying?
I'm coming back to get you, ok?
Please don't go sis...
- Stupid girl!
I will miss you a lot...
Ok now stop crying
and take all the bags out, ok?
Sir in my humble opinion ...
What do we do about the rings?
I've never abused
so much in my life...
I called my own daughter proud...
I tell you, these two
are more stubborn than me...
I don't know whether gold prices
are up or down now...
but sell them irrespective of
whether they fetch a profit or loss!
And deposit the
money in my account...
I guess this time too Romeo
and Juliet will have a tragic end.
Sir,
- What?
Sir, please come here...
- What's the matter?
Sir see!
- What?
Now let's make sure
he doesn't go free!
Gursharan pick up a weapon!
Wait Sir, I'm coming too...
- No, you wait here...
Sir that mad old man is dangerous...
I know, but after all
he is my father-in-law...
Careful sir ...
Brother Mohit
Beware!
Don't you dare take a single step,
or I'll handicap you...
Gursharan call the
Police Commissioner...
Yes Sir!
The Home Secretary...
- Yes, I know, he's your batch-mate.
But I don't want to talk to you...
Call Mayera... Call her...
Mayera, Mayera...
Mayera...
Why should Mayera come?
Who are you, just a waiter?
First earn some money,
have a bank balance...
My Mayera won't go with a loser...
She's come to her senses now,
you bloody penny-pincher!
Sir reality check...
You're behaving very,
very uncool right now Sir...
Insulting my waiter friends,
uncool...
Calling Mayera proud, uncool...
And your hundred year old
money-theory, that's uncool too...
If one followed your theory,
the poor would not be
allowed to love or live...
If there is love,
thirty rupees
and one cup of coffee...
is enough to be happy...
What if there's no money,
there's unlimited love...
Money or no money,
loves finds it's way...
Where there's love, there's a way...
She hates you...
And you must know,
we were going to pray
at the hanuman temple
on the way to the airport...
that you are never happy in life...
You bloody loser...
- Papa enough ...
What has Mohit done to you?
He agreed to the probation...
He lost all the matches with you...
He's the national level under-16
silver medalist in squash...
yet he lost all matches for you...
He helped you
with your job-hunting...
lied to me for you...
He calls you Osama, but you're
not less than a terrorist...
he kept tolerating you, for me...
The man who can do so much for me,
can also give his life for me...
Waiter or manager,
pauper or prince,
I love him...
Some sacrifices will
have to be made...
I won't get to go to rock shows,
dinner once a month,
shopping once a year...
Hey hey...l'm not going to
work at a coffee shop all my life...
Until you do...
We will still have fun...
Without you I don't
enjoy shopping at all,
whatever the credit card limit...
Because when you're not around,
there's nobody to say...
Very hot...shall I gobble you up!
Hey...no hanky-panky here...
all this after marriage...
What's going on dad?
Weren't you very happy
with our break-up?
Your generation always has to do
the opposite of what
the parents say...
It's always the case...
Papa you are crazy
If I had listed his good qualities
would you say sorry
and patch up with him? No!
I abused him only then
did you understand...
Hey, stupid!
You call me uncool, you bloody fool!
If you want to be my
son-in-law take my blessings...
Not like this, give me hug...
A good one...
Stupid fellow...
Come here!
Now give the rings...
Your wish means everything,
and mine means nothing...
Which wish?
Today is my interview...
I have to go there...
Rings can wait...
- Papa!
Let him go, otherwise
he will never leave us alone...
He won't be able
to take the pressure
of a private job at his age.
He's letting you
decide for yourself...
Let him do the same...
Dear in my humble opinion,
he's right...
Ok...fine guys.
So...how am I looking?
Don't you have a suit?
- Suit.
I got a new Safari suit made
for this, from Singh Tailors...
four pockets.
Suit and tie please!
- Oh bloody
Where are you taking me?
- Come on, come on...
Gursharan I am being kidnapped...
- C'mon!
Oh wait, you guys have
sandwiched me in between!
The sandwich needs a good tie!
Hello Unni sir ...
I love you too much...
I can't leave you and go to Dubai...
How crowded this place is...
come on guys...come on...
You'll shift out of this hole in
the wall after marriage, wont you?
Say sorry sir...I take offence...
Say sorry sir or no tie...
Sorry, bro sorry!
Please get me sober tie,
according to my age...
Young and dynamic sir.
Where are you going?
- He'll get something silly...
Ok, choose a good one...
I missed you.
- I know man, where were you...
Osama
- Crap!
Killer!
Sir don't show off in the interview,
that the home Secretary
is your batch mate...
It'll give a good impression...
you won't understand...
Papa, it doesn't make
a difference to anyone...
Really,
- Yeah!
I thought that's why
Mohit is scared of me...
You're not scared of me?
Hey duffer...
Don't scare anyone.
You're going for an interview,
not to pick a son-in-law...
I know ya... I'm your father
you are not my father.
Sehgal VK
- They're asking for your name...
not for your email ID!
- Vinod Kumar Sehgal...
VK Sehgal
- This way sir.
Sir your GF is top class...
I agree
Peter
Top class coffee for top class GF...
Sir, take one cup... and share
Idea!
Your financing skills,
and my marketing...
lets open a coffee shop..
I've understood one
thing from all this...
even if they have no money,
people don't stop drinking coffee...
Brilliant...and we will
call it One Cup Coffee...
No ya...
- Why not?!
Then people will drink only one cup!
Listen, I will keep the name...
The home Secretary
is my papa's batch-mate ok!
I'm going to gobble
this Home Secretary up...
Osama...
Oh no.. papa..
Don't worry its ok
Meet the new CEO
of the company Sehgal VK!
Oh my god that's amazing.
Wow that's so cool!
Sehgal Sir so proud of you.
Oh duffer, my son-in- law.