"They don't look like they're old
enough to get married, right?"
"Hey... has Pappachan's daughter
really turned 18?"
"What a throw and that too
with your tilted shoulder, ichaya!"
"Oh, wow! They've been married
only for four months, right?"
"He is Mr. Chacko's son after all...
Ha-ha-ha!"
"Just wait till I start crawling.
I'll turn your world upside down!"
"Oh, Eesho! Who wrecked this place?"
[EESHO = JESUS]
"It's Eesho indeed!"
"I am... Eesho... He-he-he!"
"Dad... I'll go forward...
Just pass it back to me..."
"Don't think you're better than me,
mone Dinesha..."
"Dad?"
"You have to bring either your father
or your mother for the PTA meeting,"
"not your sister."
"Sigh... This principal
is so funny... He-he-he..."
"This is not my sister.
She's my mother..."
"Happy 25th anniversary, darling..."
"You look so handsome
in this kurta, ichaya..."
"Do you two really have to flirt
right in front of me?"
As we all know,
this is the first time that a building
is being demolished through
a bomb explosion in Kerala.
There will be three sirens in total,
and the first two sirens
have blown already.
There will be one more siren.
As we're already aware,
1,312 perforations have been made
in this apartment building.
Explosive materials have been loaded
into all those perforations.
As the third siren blows,
the countdown will appear
on my right side.
I mean,
on the right side of the screen.
The third siren
has been sounded now.
The countdown has started!
Nine seconds to go.
Eight seconds...
Seven seconds...
Six more seconds to go.
Any moment now, this skyscraper
you see behind me will be demolished.
The explosion has happened.
The building is falling!
The building has... not... fallen!
Though the explosion happened,
the building has not fallen.
We need to find out what happened,
and the engineers are on their way.
Let's try asking them.
Sir! Sir! Sir! Sir!
Sir! Sir! Sir!
What happened? What happened?
We cannot give
a clear answer now.
But it's only because this builder
used top-quality TMT steel bars
that nothing has happened
to this building.
This is our technical team's
initial inference.
Well, now we know the reason.
Anyway, whom do we blame for this?
The state government, the police...
or the fire force,
or the local ruling body?
Whom do we blame for this chaos?
You can blame anyone!
But you cannot blame the engineers
who built this apartment.
Because they have used.
ISI 550D certified
strong and sturdy TMT steel bars!
Kattadi TMT steel bars!
The one that doesn't sway
with the wind!
Very, very strong!
Father,
how's our new advertisement?
Nice. It's really good.
It's a great concept.
The concept is mine.
- And you know Kurian, right?
- Which Kurian?
- Malieakal Kurian!
- Oh, yeah!
- His advertising company shot this.
- Is it?
Anyway, it's a really creative idea.
The idea is mine!
Whosever it is, it is quite catchy.
It will play in theatres
next week onwards.
The crowd is going to erupt.
Wait and watch, Father!
So, you must have spent
a lot of money on this, right?
Father, the Kattadi company
was founded by my father,
Kattadi Chacko.
So, we didn't really bother
about the money with this one.
Yes! You should never bother
about money for such things.
- I spent close to Rs. 25 lakh.
- Good, good.
Coffee.
Father.
I have come here to talk
about two things mainly.
The construction of our new chapel
is going on.
So, I'm expecting a fair donation
of both steel bars and cash!
Father, you know what?
My business is going
through a dull phase.
I'm doing this advertisement
to get it up and running.
John, it is for Eesho Mishiha.
[JESUS CHRIST]
One should never cut corners
when it comes to Him.
My dear Eesho,
what's with this look?
With your long hair
and goatee beard,
are you out to fool people?
Look at how you've turned out!
You don't need your family
or your people.
- Is this how you talk to Eesho?
- Of course!
Eesho is our only...
He might be the only one,
but he definitely needs
a whack once in a while.
- Him and his damn Bangalore style!
- Yeah!
Huh?
Bangalore style?
For Eesho?
Oh, God!
Oh, you were talking to him!
It is Dr. Samuel's
daughter's wedding today.
He will come wearing those ear-studs
and a tie-dyed shirt.
I am sure!
- Annamma!
- Yeah?
Can you get me a coffee?
Make it really frothy.
Hi, Father!
Eesho!
Eesho John Kattadi.
You haven't seen him, right?
How will you? He never comes
anywhere near the church.
He is my son.
Oh!
Praise be to the Lord!
What do you do, Eesho?
I'm working
for an advertising company.
Though I've been a priest
for so many years,
this is the first time
I'm seeing Eesho in person.
Awesome.
Mummy!
The phone has been ringing
for so long!
Where the hell is Dad?
Oh! Where else could he be?
He has gone in
for his usual exercise.
He has begun his exercise?
He will come out
only after an hour then.
Can you please come out?
If we don't leave
at least by now,
the function will be over
before we reach.
Just keep quiet!
There is a war going on in here!
You can fight the rest of it
in the morning.
Just come out!
Tough luck.
Oh, my God!
Huh?
What's with this outfit, girl?
It's a wedding reception!
Go, wear a sari.
What's wrong with this outfit?
I had told her.
But she won't listen.
Only if people see you
dressed in a sari
will you get proposals from
boys born in good families.
I'd rather stay single!
Just do as we say.
Dad, these are not cheap clothes!
This is Zara's top
and Tommy's jeans!
Why are you wearing
other people's clothes?
As if you don't have any?
Dad!
Aren't you ashamed to call yourself
an advertising professional?
These are two of the most
famous brands in the world!
Tommy Hilfiger and Zara.
Oh! Like that!
Then you do one thing.
Wear a nice, branded sari.
Do saris have brands?
Saris don't have brands?
But...
there was an ad shot by that guy
whose alliance we had
considered for you.
That was an ad
of a branded sari, right?
Yeah, what a great brand!
"Peedikapparambil Fancy Clothes,
Kulathuppuzha."
Why was I even born
in this family?
Forget the shop.
What's wrong with him?
He was a nice guy, right?
Dad...
I've told you many times.
If you want a good employee,
you should hire someone
and give him a good salary.
Don't think that you can get me
married to some loser
and make him work
under you for free.
Got it?
Well, what was wrong
with that advertisement?
Kattadi TMT steel bars!
The one that doesn't sway
with the wind!
Very, very strong!
- This is such a lousy ad, John!
- What?
If you show this in theatres here,
I'll stop coming to this city!
I'd rather work
as a bonded labourer in Bangalore.
I had asked you
to do an ad for me, right?
- You didn't do it.
- I gave you an idea, right?
Oh, yeah!
You gave me an idea!
What was that? Oh, yes!
- "Engineer's choice."
- Yes.
My dear son, Eesho,
you should understand something.
Our steel bars are not purchased
by engineers.
Our steel business
is with small-time contractors
and masons.
The commissions and margins
that we give them,
along with a steel bar that
can be bent and twisted as they wish,
are what keeps
this business running.
Oh! Why did you do this ad then?
I have done this ad to remind
certain others
that I am alive
and running such a business here.
No one is going to come running to
buy our steel bars seeing this ad.
That's an insult
to the entire advertising community.
Just think about it.
After waking up in the morning,
when we apply toothpaste
on the toothbrush,
what are we reminded of?
A toothpaste ad!
After that, we head
straight into the bathroom.
And there we have hair oil,
soap and shampoo.
All these worthless items are habits
created by
advertising professionals.
After all that, when we sit down
to have breakfast,
we buy everything from the batter
for idlis to the flour for puttu,
watching the advertisements
made by these professionals.
Our entire life is controlled
by advertising professionals.
Whatever you say,
I don't want an advertising guy.
Tell me why, Anna.
Well, advertising guys don't know
how to keep secrets.
What?
Sir, look here, please!
Look into the camera.
Smile, please!
- Cheers!
Cheers!
Doctor...
So you're all settled now.
Your only daughter's wedding
is over.
And your son-in-law is a doctor.
Now, he can hand over
his hospital to the two of them
and chill, having a couple
of pegs every evening.
Of course!
My dear John,
it's easier said than done.
My responsibilities
are only going to grow hereafter.
How is that?
My son-in-law has brought
a great business proposal.
A foreign investment group.
Our plan is
to start a chain called
SMT Group of Maternity Hospitals,
spread across four states.
Once we start that,
I'm going to be busier than ever.
As if he's the one birthing babies!
Well, Doctor...
my company will get the full
advertising contract for it, right?
For what?
You're going to open four
or five branches anyway.
You will definitely need us.
We did an awesome ad
for John's steel bars recently.
John, tell him about it.
It was great.
Really cool ad!
We're going to release it
in theatres next week.
We will sort it out.
Don't say that.
We've done everything for you,
right from your logo.
You must give this to us.
We'll see.
Now you eat.
Gosh!
You've grown up to be
a fine woman, dear.
You look so beautiful in a sari.
Shouldn't we get her married, Elsy?
She should feel so too, right?
She has no such thoughts
in her mind.
Don't you have anything else
to talk about?
You open your mouths
only to talk about marriage.
- Anna!
- Yes!
Well...
I...
I was calling my daughter.
Dear...
get me an ice cream.
Pickle will do for you!
- Hey! Stop it!
- Then?
He is borderline diabetic already.
Here you go, Uncle. You have this.
I'll get another one.
See! I got something
as soon as I wished for it.
He's smart.
Hey, Eesho!
Like I've always told you,
I have left a chair vacant for you
in my company, permanently.
Listen, John...
the creative director's chair
belongs to your son.
Uncle, we mostly work
for international technology
and fashion brands.
I don't really know
how to deal with
obituary columns
and toilet-cleaning lotions.
Is that supposed to be funny?
I'll go get some ice cream as well.
Oh!
Too high-flying for me, huh?
Fine!
When are you returning?
I'll leave tonight.
You're working
at Infosys there, right?
No. I moved to ITC now.
Oh!
Koramangala?
No.
- Electronic City.
- Ah!
I had wanted to call you
for something sometime back.
But I didn't have
your number then.
Ah! Really?
The two of you have been
in Bangalore all this while,
and you don't have
each other's numbers?
What if you have to call each other
for some emergency?
Give her your number.
I'll give it.
Then what are you waiting for?
Give it to her right away.
- 953933..
- Hey!
Say it slowly.
- 9539..
- Yeah.
33...
2222.
22, and then another 22.
Okay.
Hey!
I was thinking about Anna.
She has grown up into a beautiful
young lady, all of a sudden.
How pretty she looked in a sari.
- Ichaya...
- Yes?
Shall we get her married to him?
Great! That will be amazing!
Her father, Kurian...
was head over heels in love
with your mother for five years,
right from our high school days
till the end of college.
But she never even
acknowledged his presence.
And when he took his father...
to her house to ask for her hand,
what did your dad say?
Your dad called them
upstarts and kicked them out.
He must be carrying that grudge
in his mind even now.
Stop it, ichaya.
Those are all old stories.
Who keeps all that
in mind even now?
Is it because he doesn't have it
in his mind even now
that he named his only child
after you?
- Ichaya!
- Oh!
Now you two don't start fighting.
I don't dig that girl anyway.
What's wrong with her?
Oh! She's as tall as a pole,
and she keeps yapping non-stop.
On top of all that, her name. Anna!
You rascal!
What's wrong with that name?
Exactly this!
If I call the name "Anna,"
both you and her will respond.
Full confusion!
Oh, boy!
No way! He won't be right for her.
If we're thinking
of a guy like him,
Josootty is a much better option
any day, right?
He shot that sari ad
so wonderfully after all.
You're still holding on
to that sari?
Is this like that?
He's so dashing.
And that name.
- Eesho!
- Yeah, right!
His name is Eesho!
But his character is like Judas.
When I asked him about joining
our company, what did he say?
He called us
a toilet-cleaning company.
That's right, Dad.
He's rude to you
whenever he sees you.
- Yeah!
- Who does he think he is?
Some advertising genius!
Ask him to get lost!
- Of course!
- He is a little too arrogant.
I'll find an advertising guy
who's better than him
for my daughter.
Dad!
I just said that in a flow, dear.
Watch out.
It was raining.
That's why.
Okay. I'll manage that.
Okay.
Oh! James!
- Achaya!
- Where are you going?
I'm going to Bangalore.
I got transferred there.
I keep coming once
every two-three weeks.
- You've come to drop off Anna?
- Yes.
- Shall I get in?
- Okay.
Dear... take this.
- Dear...
- Okay, Dad. Bye.
Call me as soon as you reach.
I will.
Bye, bye.
[RADIO ANNOUNCEMENT IN KANNADA]
[IN TAMIL] Honey!
Has sir come back?
Yes, he is back.
He got back early
in the morning.
[IN MALAYALAM] It's Tuesday.
So?
It's your turn today.
Coffee.
Here you go!
The coffee is very nice!
You've gotten even better at this.
No way!
It's not because I got better.
You feel so because
you went home for two days
and had your mummy's lousy coffee.
Oh! Now start bickering
about my family!
Your acting was quite
over the top yesterday.
When it comes to acting,
you are always better.
You were so sycophantic!
Huh?
Well, why do you have always
have a bone to pick with my dad?
Why does your dad keep inviting me
to his lousy company
whenever he sees me?
What's your problem?
My mom's coffee is lousy,
my dad's company is lousy!
And you want to marry
their daughter?
Well, I never said anything
about marriage.
Get lost, you dog!
On our way back
after the wedding last night,
my mom hinted about you.
Huh?
What?
It was vaguely
like a marriage proposal.
Oh! And?
Oh! I said no to it immediately.
I can't even imagine
spending a lifetime with you.
Oh! Is that so?
Same pinch!
- Morning, Venkayyah!
- Good morning, sir.
Hi, sir! Good morning.
[IN TAMIL] How are you?
[IN TAMIL] I'm fine, dear.
Please give this key to the maid
when she comes.
The place is really dusty.
- Okay.
- So...
you had gone home
for a couple of days, right?
- Did you have fun?
- It was awesome!
Okay. See you.
[IN MALAYALAM] Shall we go?
Hey!
I wasn't joking.
Dad is quite serious about it.
About what?
Well, Dad has been
pushing me subtly.
Huh? For what?
To get married!
Oh, that!
I can hold on
for around one year easily.
But after that,
I may have to give in.
We have one year, right?
Why do we need to get stressed
about it already?
It's almost the same situation
in my house as well.
I think my mummy
is really fond of you.
Really? What did she say?
Well, she didn't say much.
Tell me what she said!
Nope! You don't take well
to flattery.
Now I really want to hear it!
- Tell me what it is.
- Calm down!
Just say it!
It's nothing.
When she saw you in a sari,
Mummy was really impressed.
You looked "beautiful," it seems.
Oh!
That's all?
Well, I'm beautiful,
whatever I wear.
- Get down.
- What?
Get down, beautiful.
We've reached.
We've reached?
Sorry.
I didn't notice
because I was wearing sunglasses.
I got it for a discount.
How's it?
- Awesome, right?
- Absolutely.
But if it was a helmet
that covered your whole face,
it would have been even better.
Lame joke.
It's Sathish's farewell party
in the evening.
If you come to my office,
we can have a couple of free drinks
and go home.
I'm not coming.
You ad agency intellectuals
are such boring company.
I'll take a cab. You have fun.
Okay.
See you.
♪ Walking in silently
You brought color into my life ♪
♪ You have engulfed my heart
As my better half ♪
♪ Oh, full moon, as the fog clears
Descend upon this earth ♪
♪ O golden moon that covers
My throbbing heart, please come ♪
♪ Let's fly all over the heaven
That we've built for ourselves ♪
♪ You fill up all my thoughts
Morning, noon and night, forever ♪
♪ My heart keeps skipping a beat
When I see your face every morning ♪
♪ O full moon, as the fog clears
Descend upon this earth ♪
♪ O golden moon that covers
My throbbing heart, please come ♪
♪ Let's fly all over the heaven
That we've built for ourselves ♪
♪ My life has gradually blended
Into yours ♪
♪ Haven't we become so close
That we can never part ways? ♪
♪ We do not need words
To understand each other ♪
♪ Even our eyes speak to each other
With a smile today ♪
♪ I have preserved
A thousand desires for you ♪
♪ O golden moon that covers
My throbbing heart, please come ♪
♪ Let's fly all over the heaven
That we've built for ourselves ♪
♪ You fill up all my thoughts
Morning, noon and night, forever ♪
♪ My heart keeps skipping a beat
When I see your face every morning ♪
♪ O full moon, as the fog clears
Descend upon this earth ♪
♪ O golden moon that covers
My throbbing heart, please come ♪
♪ Let's fly all over the heaven
That we've built for ourselves ♪
My jacket is inside.
Here you go!
- Bye, Eesho. That was so much fun!
- Bye!
- Bye! See you! Good night!
- See you!
- Bye-bye!
- Take care!
Eesho, get ready quickly.
It's already past 8:30 a.m.
I'll be really late.
Should I wait for you
or book a cab?
Hey, you!
What the hell
did you drink last night?
Susan?
- Where is Susan?
- What?
Err... sorry!
Anna...
What's the time, Anna?
It's a really bad time for you.
Huh?
Anna, there's really no way
to say this politely.
Your coffee,
as usual,
sucks!
Don't drink it
if you can't stand it.
Or bring someone else
who can make coffee like your mom.
That's a good idea.
Who can we bring?
There's one person.
Someone who took over
Sathish's position yesterday.
A stunning girl from Thiruvalla.
Susan. Susan Mathews.
How about her?
I'm serious.
What a personality!
Amazing sense of humour!
Superb reading habits too.
We shared such a terrific vibe!
She's a die-hard fan
of Orhan Pamuk as well.
See!
You don't even know who that is.
Great!
Who am I even talking to!
You do one thing then...
Go and stay with her.
For that,
she too has to agree, right?
Did you see my phone?
Did you see my phone, Anna?
I had clicked some great selfies
with her last night.
Forgot to send them to her.
Where did I keep it?
Foul!
That's a foul!
Checking my phone
behind my back!
Tsk-tsk!
I didn't expect this at all!
I wasn't checking it!
When I saw it here, I kept it aside
so that it doesn't fall.
See for yourself.
I haven't checked it.
Let it be.
Give me 20 minutes.
We'll leave.
No. I'll book a cab.
Hey, we can leave together.
No one has to take the trouble
of dropping me.
I was just joking.
Why do I care
if you check my phone?
She has a boyfriend.
She's just a new colleague
whom I can talk to.
That's all.
Do whatever you want!
Why are you saying
all this to me?
Who am I? Your wife?
Oh!
So, you do have this emotion
called possessiveness, huh?
- Hey, I was just..
- Let go of me!
Oh, no! Anna!
Blood!
Why do you have to do things
you're not cut out for
when you can't handle it?
How are you feeling now?
I'm... I'm okay, Doctor.
What is this, young man?
A few drops of blood
and you faint?
You may leave once the IV is done.
Okay?
That's just a small cut.
No need of stitches.
- Dressing will be enough.
- Okay.
- [IN KANNADA] Give her a tetanus shot.
- Okay, Doctor.
Okay?
Thanks.
Are you okay otherwise?
Yeah, Doctor. I'm fine.
Your eyes look pale.
Periods are regular, right?
Yeah. Periods are..
Congratulations!
Thank you.
For what?
8 weeks.
2 months.
What?
Anna is two months pregnant.
Well... err...
I...
Err... actually...
Doctor...
It was an accident.
Hey, that's all right.
This is how it happens
in most cases.
Just accept this as God's decision.
But...
We...
Actually, Doctor... we...
We are...
not so prepared.
Well, you can start now.
Ten months is not just the time
a baby needs to grow
in a mother's womb.
It is the time for the parents
to become prepared as well.
Well...
We...
Is there any way to avoid..
Eesho...
See...
the two of you are adults.
You are educated.
Eight out of ten people
who come here
come praying for a child
to be born somehow.
Think about it.
Take your time.
Make a wise decision.
Anna, I'm not prepared.
I'm not prepared at all.
Are you prepared?
No one is prepared, Eesho.
But is this how you react to it?
What else do you
expect me to do?
Will you be able to tell your family
that you're pregnant?
We are...
They don't even know
that we're in a relationship.
Eesho, whatever you're saying
is right.
But...
this is a human life!
I...
I have an urgent meeting to attend.
See, triple-layer protection,
dotted, ripped,
other patterns of your choice...
All these are the competitive
advantages of this product.
But how do we take the campaign
away from this?
How do we make it more personal?
More emotional?
Hello? Eesho?
Menon? Susan?
Come on, Mallu gang!
Give me an idea!
One wrong decision
can turn your life upside down.
One minor negligence
can thwart all your future plans.
You know, something on those lines.
What's up with him, man?
What do we do now?
I've been asking you that
all this while.
The decision is yours!
- You should tell me.
- Oh!
Really?
Now this problem is just mine?
This didn't happen
because of me alone.
Did I say that, Anna?
Is that what I meant?
Yes, Dad.
Where are you?
I...
I'm in my office.
An important meeting is going on.
What is it?
There will be buses or trains running
even after your meeting, right?
Board one of them.
You should be here
tomorrow morning.
What?
In the morning?
Dad, I just got here!
I called you because
you need to be here.
- John, tell me what the matter is.
- Don't say anything.
You should be here
tomorrow morning.
Did you tell anyone at home?
At whose home?
My home.
I'm not so cheap.
Did you say anything to anyone..
- Hey, Eesho!
- That's not what I meant!
Did you say anything at all
to your friends or someone?
As if this is something
I can brag about!
Ugh!
How come John is here
to pick me himself?
This is unusual.
What is it, John?
What happened?
I'll tell you.
I will tell you.
Annamma!
What happened?
John seems like a tough nut
to crack today.
You sit.
I'll bring coffee.
Tell me what happened.
Eesho!
Eesho...
how old do you think you are?
Why do you ask, John?
When I was your age,
you had flunked
your tenth grade once already.
So?
So, I believe that you are mature,
wise and old enough
to listen to something
I want to tell you.
Son...
your mother is pregnant.
WHAT?
Who did you say is pregnant?
Well...
she felt slightly dizzy
and exhausted yesterday,
and I took her to the hospital.
So, when we got some tests done,
it was our Samuel
who told us that...
she's pregnant.
Coffee.
So... how do we take this forward?
John, for one moment...
for just one moment...
couldn't you have
thought of my face?
You really think your face
is what I think of
when I sleep with my wife?
Did you think about the stature
and respect I have in this society?
What respect do you have
in this society?
This man!
Dad, what exactly were you thinking
of when you did this?
Is that a question you should
be asking your own father?
We have to meet the doctor
at 11 a.m. today.
You should also be with us.
Kattadi, did you ask me to rush
all the way here for this?
As an elder child,
do you prefer a brother or a sister?
I...
Out of the frying pan,
into the fire!
That's what is happening now!
So, it's been two months.
The heartbeat can be seen.
Everything looks normal.
I mean, we can't rule out
age-related complications.
There is a risk factor.
- We don't need this then!
- Huh?
If there's a risk,
then let's not go ahead with this.
No, no.
I didn't mean that.
No. We don't need
any unnecessary risks at all.
On those lines, going out
on the road is also risky, Eesho.
What I meant was that
you should be extra cautious.
That's all.
There's nothing to fear.
But a complication is
indeed a complication, Uncle.
That, too, at this age.
So, my opinion is that
we shouldn't..
Eesho.
Come with me.
Just a minute, Doctor. Come.
I'll be right back.
What is it, Annamma?
What happened?
This is a human life.
You too were...
in this womb for ten months.
It's just that
I can't see it now.
But this child is just like you
for me.
Hello?
John called me here
because there was
a slight confusion at home.
I'll tell you everything in person.
Where are you now?
I'm at home.
Why? You didn't go to the office?
No.
What happened?
I didn't go. That's all.
I...
Yesterday...
all of a sudden...
when I heard everything together...
I spoke like that
because I was confused.
Forget what I said.
We must figure out
our future plans, right?
We'll talk once I get back.
Okay?
Anna...
You're okay, right?
Yes.
I love you.
I love you too.
Hey!
What are you doing here,
talking on the phone?
Well, I had to make
a couple of office calls.
So that's how it is.
When so much is happening here,
you're worried about your office?
John, I have to go back
and take some decisions..
Where are you going?
You're not going anywhere.
-I have left certain things midway-
-Hey! Hey!
I have to go to Ahmedabad
to buy steel in two days.
I can entrust her only to you.
There are some very important..
Nothing is more important
than this, right?
You won't understand
what's happening there, John.
You're talking as if your wife
is pregnant over there.
When did I say that?
You needn't say anything.
You can leave after five days.
If you can't even do that,
then resign from your job.
As if I need your money
to buy steel bars!
Hey!
Raw spinach,
broccoli,
drumsticks...
Err... maybe not drumsticks.
Egg whites, bean sprouts...
Ah, here's sweet potato.
- Why do we need all this?
- These are all very important!
She needs a lot of proteins
and minerals during this time.
Only then will the newborn
be intelligent and wise.
I couldn't buy all this when
she was pregnant with my first child.
So, going all out this time!
Come, my firstborn.
Raw spinach,
sweet potato,
bean sprouts,
egg white
and...
then a few other things.
All these are very good apparently.
For what?
Well,
the first three months
are really crucial.
You should be really careful.
Who said so?
My dad!
Why did your dad say that?
My dad bought all this
for my mom today.
For what?
What would it be for?
How would I know?
Make a guess.
You're talking as if it's your mother
who's pregnant.
Correct!
What?
Stop it! Stop joking!
As if I'm at the age
where I can joke
about my mother being pregnant!
What do you mean?
I mean... why do you think
my dad asked me to rush here
all of a sudden?
Oh, Mom!
Not your mom! My mom!
- Eesho!
- Yeah?
Not you! I was calling Jesus!
- What do we do now?
- What can we do?
They are planning
to go ahead with it.
Not that! What about us?
I've called you
to discuss just that.
Shall we elope?
What?
I can't think of any other idea.
Eesho, this is not a joke.
What else do you want us to do?
I can't hold on like this
for too long.
- We should tell this at home somehow.
- Yes.
Tell this to your family.
Try to convince
your father somehow.
To my family?
I was talking about
telling your family!
Don't you know my father?
This is the perfect time
to tell my family, right?
That's exactly what I meant.
What?
Whatever you tell them now,
they won't be shocked beyond a point.
Everything is quite
messed up anyway, right?
Present it tactfully.
Uncle John must be feeling awkward
and embarrassed at this point of time.
Meanwhile, just tell him,
"Dad, I too had a slip-up,
just like you."
Present it like that.
- Will it work?
- Yes.
And one more thing.
Don't tell my family
about your mother.
Why?
Don't even think about us then!
Oh!
Got it.
All the best!
Thank you.
Hey! You will live a hundred years!
I was just thinking about you.
You will leave only after
seeing the end of me!
My darling son,
I wanted to ask you something.
Well, the matter is...
it's Reena's daughter's
baptism tomorrow.
We have to go to the church anyway
and to our ancestral house
soon after.
So, we cannot avoid
meeting my mother.
How do I present this to my mother?
What?
The fact that
your mother is pregnant.
I have never hidden anything
from my mother.
How do I tell her about this?
Can you give me an idea?
Me?
Why do you have to think so much?
- Why don't you just say it?
- No, no!
You won't get it.
Talking about pregnancy
to our own parents...
Ugh! It's really embarrassing!
True. I shouldn't have come.
- What?
- Why should we go there tomorrow?
But we are the child's godparents!
- Don't you..
- Hey!
Dad and son needn't rack
your brains so much.
Saying that you're going to
have a child at this age
might be a credit for you.
But I'm quite embarrassed about it.
You don't have to tell her all this.
So what?
What's wrong if I say it?
Oh!
Don't I know your mom by now?
The entire town will come to know
about this then.
When it's the right time,
I will tell her tactfully.
You don't say it
and ruin everything.
Correct! Mummy is correct!
You'll say everything
and create a scene,
and finally people will know
this and that,
and everything will be a mess!
- What everything?
- Who?
- What do you mean by everything?
- Well...
The baptism is tomorrow, right?
You will go there,
say this and that...
and just make a mess of everything.
Godfather, it seems. Isn't there
anyone else in this family?
Why?
Aren't we good enough?
I didn't mean..
For you to get married
and have a child,
we'll just have to keep
waiting forever!
When I got a chance,
I agreed to do it. That's all!
Hey, John!
If you keep hurling
these taunts at me, it feels...
Can't believe this guy
is my father!
Taunts?
What happened to him?
It's all one sloppy mess.
- Have some more.
- How's the food?
- All okay?
- It's nice.
Sister, some kallappam?
- No, thanks. I had it already.
- Have one more.
No, thanks.
Father, kallappam.
Come on, one more.
Oh, no!
John, hold this.
I'll bring some kallappam!
Hey! This is kallappam...
Shall I serve some beef?
No, thanks.
- Father, praise be to the Lord.
- Always and forever.
Sisters!
Aunty!
Kurian! Elsy!
Be seated.
Get something to eat.
Let me go wash my hands.
Go ahead.
What are you looking at?
Go inside.
- Kurian!
- Joji!
- Anna!
- John!
- Am I late?
- No, no!
I'll be right back.
Hello?
I don't understand this!
Why did your dad come here now?
Don't you dare bullshit me!
My dad came because
your family invited him.
I am trying to make both ends meet
somehow and in between that...
Dad is just a little tough
on the outside.
He's a softie inside.
If you behave affectionately
with my dad,
he will soften up.
This is your best chance!
Just soft-soap my dad today.
If that happens, we needn't be
so stressed thereafter.
Okay! Okay!
What do I tell her dad now?
What a time to crack jokes!
Oh, my God!
My back!
Ichaya, don't eat that.
I'll bring fresh pickle.
Hi, Uncle.
He did this deliberately.
No doubt about that!
He ruins my day
every chance he gets.
Stop it, ichaya.
Stop conjuring up things.
It must have been an accident.
Why do you always take his side?
- I...
- I'm not taking anyone's side.
Accident, it seems.
As if he's a child.
I shouldn't have come here.
What's happening?
Is it clean yet?
How?
It's doused in oil.
It's all wet and greasy!
What's the husband and wife
doing inside?
- What do I...
- Take a bath if you want.
Or you'll be smelling of pickle
for the whole day.
- I'll bring a shirt for you.
- Sure!
Yeah, right! Bathe me and bury me!
Bring a fresh soap and towel.
I'm talking to you!
Stop gaping and wash this!
- Hello?
- Hey!
Did you see my dad yet?
- Yup!
- Did you soft-soap him?
I am about to.
How's this?
How can he wear this, achaya?
It's too tight even for me.
Achaya, how is this?
Isn't it awesome?
I bought this from Pattaya.
It's really colourful
and quite loose too.
Yeah. Loose is better.
- Come.
- All of you, please look here.
Come here!
Smile, please!
Smile!
Okay!
Sister, pack this duck roast too.
That's okay. Let it be.
Why? Isn't it from your own house?
Now you don't have to go
back home and cook.
Oh! That's right.
I can't go back and toil now.
Hey!
Where's the sweet and sour
ginger pickle?
It was delicious!
I wanted to ask for some more.
- Is it over?
- No, sister.
It's here.
Ah!
How come you're so tempted
by sweet and sour ginger pickle?
The sweet and sour ginger pickle...
Its taste...
It's really good.
Is it? Give me some too.
Let me try it.
You're right. It's really good.
By the way, do one thing.
Go and ask your husband
to come to my room.
- Why, Mom?
- Well, well!
Why do I need your permission
to talk to my son?
Huh?
Just ask him to come, girl!
- Praise be to the Lord.
Hey! Your mom wants to see you.
Alone, in her room.
- What's the matter?
- I don't know.
What is it, Mom?
Did you call me?
On top of my cupboard,
you'll find my medicated oil.
Bring it here.
Must be because I've been
standing since morning;
My legs are killing me.
There's no better masseur than you.
Go.
Why not!
Oh, dear Lord!
When the people here massage me,
it's never warm or strong enough.
Gosh!
Yeah! Like that!
Press it tightly!
- Johnnykutty!
- Yes?
Look at me.
What is it, Mom?
Nothing.
Just wanted to see your face.
You're so good.
Really good.
Hey, look at me.
What is it, Mom?
What's that glow
on your wife's face?
Is it?
She has a glow?
I didn't think so.
But I did!
What's the matter?
To attend this function,
she had gone to a beauty salon.
Maybe that's why.
Really?
Well, so be it then.
- Johnnykutty!
- Yes?
Look at me.
What is it, Mom?
I have given birth
to eight children, including you!
Which beauty salon
did your wife go to?
Huh?
Mom, it's just...
How many months is it now?
Two.
When I gave birth to Nancy,
I was around the same age.
That means
there will be
age-related complications.
You should be careful.
Mom, I haven't really told this
to anyone.
You shouldn't.
Don't tell this to anyone now.
You know how our people are, right?
There will be rumors
and gossip all around.
It's not like the old times either.
I won't tell this to anyone.
You don't, either.
You never have time for me.
How come you have
so much time for her?
Mom, I'll just...
You are impossible.
Your dad was the same.
What?
Oh!
He couldn't keep
his hands off me either.
Mom, I'm going downstairs.
Close that bottle tightly.
Yeah, yeah.
Get going.
Hey!
What are you doing,
standing here?
Hey!
Do you know something?
- My mother is a sweetheart.
- Yes.
Mom caught us red-handed.
But she was so cool about it.
Our family's positive vibe
and our elders' attitude
are just awesome.
Since I had the medicated oil
in hand,
things went much smoother
than I expected.
In that case...
- I have something to tell you.
- Tell me.
Our family's positive vibe
and our elders' attitude
should apply even then.
Tell me, sweetheart.
Your dad is here to solve
any problem of yours!
Kattadi John is here! Tell me!
- Dad... I...
- You?
- I too had a slip-up like you.
- Yes, yes! Yes?
- Johnnykutty!
- Oops! It's Mom!
Hold this. You must tell me, okay?
I'll be right back.
John!
Here you go.
Enough, man!
You have stuffed in enough.
Come and get in, quickly.
Always talking
till the last moment.
I'm coming!
I have to drop you home
and reach the airport at 5 p.m.
There are no more direct flights
to Ahmedabad this week.
Oh! You're leaving?
Here you go.
This is for you.
What is it, Mom?
Sweet and sour ginger pickle!
- Didn't you say that you love it?
- Oh!
Mom is always partial
towards her elder daughter-in-law.
We're staying with you full time,
and we get nothing!
Not just ginger pickle,
I'll prepare whatever you want.
But, for that, your husband
should be capable enough.
Right, Johnnykutty?
Yeah! Come on, let's go!
- Get into the car, everyone.
- Bye.
- Joji!
- Careful with the jar!
Careful with the jar.
John.
I...
I need to tell you something.
John.
We've reached.
- Have we?
- Yeah.
I...
- I need to tell you something.
- There are a couple of things.
One, Annamma has to be taken
for a check-up tomorrow.
Don't make her exert too much.
You should give her the medicines
at the right time.
I'll do all that.
- But I need to tell you something.
- Just a minute.
Hello?
Rajeev!
- John...
- I was about to call you!
That's what I said.
I've kept the cheque ready.
You just have to give it.
Hold on with the next payment.
We'll meet once I'm back.
Hey!
- I need to tell you something.
- Oops. I forgot something.
The cheque is not at the office.
It's at home.
You should go
and give it to Rajeev.
- It is for Karim Sahib in Palakkad.
- I NEED TO TELL YOU SOMETHING!
What's with the anger?
If you want to say something,
say it.
Yeah.
You know... Anna?
Who? Your mother?
Not my mother, Anna.
Uncle Kurian's daughter, Anna.
Yes, Anna.
That Anna...
is pregnant.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Huh?
How?
If you ask me how...
Please come.
You didn't go, ichaya?
No.
Didn't you say that it was
a really important meeting?
When much more important things
are happening here,
how can I go?
I knew it.
What?
That you won't go,
leaving me in this condition.
Oh, yeah!
Didn't I tell you
that I'll be all right?
Will you say it...
or should I say it?
You say it, Dad.
Tell me what the matter is!
Well, you know...
Anna?
- Who?
- Kurian's daughter.
Yes! Anna.
Anna. She too is like you now.
Like me?
She's pregnant!
- Oh, Eesho!
- Yup! It's Eesho indeed!
Where are you hiding?
I had warned you.
What?
Not to name him after Eesho.
EESHO, THE SAVIOUR OF THIS HOME
You could have told me!
John told me about coming here
only at dawn today.
He booked flight tickets
immediately, and here we are!
I tried calling you so many times.
Eesho, didn't I tell you?
I was vomiting all night.
I went to sleep only at dawn.
So, I couldn't check my phone.
What's the point
in saying all this now?
Go and give it to him.
Me?
Then who? Me?
Come.
Uncle...
Coffee.
So, you know how to turn out
like normal humans too, huh?
Well, that photo was
clicked two years back...
So, it's been a while
since this sojourn began.
How come things
got so delayed then?
- The 10th month after I married your mom..
- Dad!
Well...
Just saying.
Sit down.
- No, thanks.
- I wasn't talking to you.
Sit down, dear. Come.
Uncle, aren't you
drinking the coffee?
No, no!
So, what's the plan?
How do we take this forward?
We must tell this
to Kurian anyway.
How do you think Kurian
will react to this?
You know how my dad is, right?
Yes, that's a problem indeed.
Back when we were in college,
some bus conductor misbehaved
with his younger sister.
And this fellow barged
into the Kottayam bus stand
and beat up all the conductors
there and made them vomit blood!
So, yeah!
It is a problem!
It is a problem indeed!
Well...
Dad...
Aren't you Uncle Kurian's
best friend?
I'm sure you can tactfully
present this to him.
Perfect news to present tactfully!
Aren't you happy that
I am living a peaceful life?
I'd like to stay alive at least
until I see my second child.
Uncle, I completely forgot about it.
Congrats.
Same to you. Same to you.
Well, what I'm trying
to say is that...
it will be a problem only if
we say this to him directly, right?
We'll come to your house
with a marriage proposal.
Well,
there are no other
complications, right?
The families know each other,
and we belong to the same parish.
We're very close too.
And if I ask something like this,
I believe Kurian just can't say no.
What do you think?
But, Uncle...
Dad is not very fond of Eesho.
Quite natural.
We can't blame your dad for that.
What is there to like in him?
Don't think any further.
Pack whatever you have to.
Let's catch the next flight
to Kerala.
I'll figure a way
to tell this to Kurian,
and come home to see the "bride."
And we'll conduct the wedding
as soon as possible.
Let's take the rest as it comes.
But, Uncle...
How can I go home now?
Why?
Well...
Whatever I eat now,
I keep vomiting it out.
If I go home, Mummy will definitely
figure something's wrong.
How do we do this then?
Do one thing.
Tell your mom that
you came by train and the vada
or tea you had in the train
upset your stomach.
Blame it on Indian Railways
for a couple of days.
By then, I will...
figure out a plan.
I'm going on a long leave.
- I'll be back only after a while.
- What's the long leave for?
Any good news?
What... what good news?
There's no good news.
I'm sure there is!
My wife told me
in the morning...
that Anna looks like
she could be carrying.
Good news should always be...
Anna! Congratulations!
Careful!
Hello.
Who is this?
Your elder brother?
My dad.
Oh, dad...
Dad?
He's your father?
Sir! Wow!
She's a gem of a girl.
It's been three years
since they got married.
My wife and I have been
praying to all the gods
to bless them with a child.
Oh, no.
We're happy now, sir.
Three years?
How many years
has it actually been?
Four.
Hey!
Come, dear.
Don't worry.
Everything will be all right.
I'm here for you.
We're all here for you.
Okay?
Get going.
I feel, if we don't start
operating things quickly,
everything will go kaput.
I'll call Mr. K
and meet him today itself.
And we'll take things forward
as we planned.
Mr. K?
Kurian!
Huh?
Oh!
- Hello?
- Hello. Where are you?
I am with Dr. Samuel.
What is it, John?
How about we catch up
this evening?
- Where?
- Err...
Let's meet at Hotel Hyatt.
Why not?
See you in the evening then.
- I'll call you. Bye!
- Okay.
It's John.
So, Kurian,
like I was saying,
I spoke to my son-in-law
about this.
The thing is...
it's a huge project.
We're planning to start this
in five cities,
including Kochi, Calicut, Chennai,
Hyderabad and Pune, in one go.
So, he thinks
it's safer to go
with some top agency
from Bombay or Bangalore
for this job.
He has budged a little bit
upon my insistence alone.
So, you can present
a concept, Kurian.
Only if it's really good,
he said the campaign is yours.
That's enough, Doctor.
You just have to give us a chance.
We'll present
the best concept to you.
One more thing.
Top agencies based
in Bombay and Delhi
will also present their concepts.
If you don't get the contract,
don't be upset with me.
Don't worry at all.
We'll bring a cracker of an idea.
Okay.
- Thanks, brother.
- Okay.
Well, well!
How come you decided to come,
just like that?
I thought I'll give you a surprise.
I'll be working from home
for two weeks.
Anyway, you're really lucky!
Why so, Elsy darling?
It's your favourite
on the menu today.
Boiled arums and sardine curry.
What is it?
What happened?
Well, I ate a vada
from the train in the morning.
It started since then.
Bad idea, I guess.
What's wrong with you?
Haven't I told you not to eat
anything from the train?
Say something, Kurian!
I agree.
She's old enough to be married.
And if it is to your family,
that makes me happier.
Nothing to be worried about.
Our families are really close
as well.
But, my dear John,
even God doesn't know what's on
the minds of kids these days.
The last time I spoke to her
about a proposal,
she was ready to eat me up!
She has been saying that
she doesn't want to get married
for many years now.
Dude, Annamma suggested this to me.
I thought it was a good idea,
and so I said this to you without
giving it too much of a thought.
- But..
- Hey.
Go home and discuss this
with your wife.
- Well, I..
- Ask Elsy.
If Elsy is okay with it,
try presenting it to Anna.
If she says no,
we'll forget this immediately.
John!
Don't think any further.
Let's have a couple of pegs
and get down to business.
Kiddo!
Two JDs. Make them large.
Okay, sir.
Tell me what happened!
There's nothing much to say.
I have presented
the matter to him.
But he wasn't exactly
jumping with joy.
Well, can't blame him, can we?
Why?
Did he say something?
He said nothing.
Then?
When he came to your house
to ask for your hand,
what did your father do?
He set the dog on him, right?
So, he won't be interested in getting
his daughter married to our family.
You can't blame him for that!
Yeah, right. As if he's keeping
all that in his mind.
And he won't be interested
in this guy either.
He keeps annoying Kurian
every chance he gets!
Hey, you!
After creating such a mess,
why do you have to keep getting on
his nerves every time you see him?
How would I have known
that things will turn out this way?
What?
Ichaya!
I'm not saying anything.
Anyway, I've convinced Kurian
to talk to his daughter about this.
She won't say no, right?
Guess that will be the end
of all problems.
Hey!
She won't say no, right?
Well, we can't say!
She has got two days
to think about this.
An entire lifetime with him
can be quite scary!
John, I'm like a dog
whose head got stuck in a pot.
But...
I had the same slip-up
as him, right?
See! See the attitude?
Why blame Kurian?
If I had a daughter, I won't get her
married to him.
Arrogant scoundrel!
- Ichaya!
- Okay, just "scoundrel" then.
I don't understand
what your problem is.
I think this is a good proposal.
Didn't I tell you
when I saw him that day
that he's smart and dashing?
Yeah, right!
As if he is the only one!
Elsy, I told you, right?
Should I keep repeating myself?
Well,
I don't understand
why you're vouching for him.
Aren't there other boys in town?
What are you saying?
Who else is there in our parish?
There are so many guys!
Name one.
What about Kalekkuzhi Jose's son?
Isn't he smart?
Like you said, he's dashing too.
Yeah, he's dashing indeed.
But I heard that
he's living together
with some girl in Bangalore.
What?
How did you know that?
I just have to sit here.
I have ears everywhere.
Fine.
There are other guys too.
I will bring a proposal.
- You watch!
- My dear ichaya,
I think this is a good alliance.
Just because that boy
cracked a joke,
should we reject
such a great alliance?
Ask her about this.
We have to proceed
only if she's okay, right?
Yeah, right!
What a thoughtful joke to make!
What did he say that day?
Toilet-cleaning company, right?
Elsy, no more discussions
about this.
He wants my daughter!
We need not ask her opinion on this.
She had said that day itself
that he's a little too arrogant!
I'm going to call John
and say no right away.
You won't understand!
Do whatever you want!
Hello?
Hello, Kurian?
Anna, hello.
John is taking a bath.
What's the news there?
Well, here...
We're making puttu for breakfast.
Is it? We're having puttu too.
Oh, really?
What about the matter
we discussed yesterday?
Huh?
Well, about our children?
John spoke to you yesterday, right?
Err..
Did you ask your daughter?
Err... No!
Elsy and I were discussing it.
I had told John
that you both will be
really happy to hear this.
Yes, yes, yes.
Anyway, I'll ask John
to call you once he's done.
Please call back
once you speak to your daughter.
Sure, sure.
What do I tell my wife now?
What happened?
Did you tell him?
Err... well...
When I gave it another thought...
let's ask her as well.
She's going to say no, for sure.
So, we'll have a reason
to tell them, right?
Isn't that what I told you earlier?
Who managed to get that
into your thick skull now?
- Well... I... err...
- Good morning!
Oh, Puttu again?
Ask her!
You ask her.
What are you two mumbling about?
What else?
It's about your marriage, as always.
Oh! There you go again!
How long will you do this?
What do you mean?
Do we have anyone else
to worry about?
Now you needn't rack
your brains over it.
You tell me, Dad!
What should I do?
Well,
you should agree to get married.
Okay! Agreed!
- Fine?
- Huh?
What do you mean?
I mean that I am ready
for a marriage.
Huh?
Now, tell me.
Which loser should I marry?
Err...
We have received a proposal.
But...
there is a problem.
Is this how you present something?
Well, what's the point
in hiding it?
What happened?
Well...
I don't know whether
you'll like the groom's profession.
Why?
He works in advertising.
Oh, well! I knew that you'll bring
only such proposals anyway.
What's the point in me
objecting to it now?
Advertising it is, then!
But...
didn't you say that advertising
guys can't keep secrets?
Well...
what you told me
that day was true, Dad.
Right from the toothbrush we use
to brush our teeth in the morning,
to the shampoo we use on our hair.
Even...
even this puttu flour.
They are all choices we make
from seeing ads.
So, I felt that
you had a point, Dad.
So, you no longer will
have problems from my side.
Well, profession is okay.
But...
when you know who the groom is,
I doubt whether you'll agree.
He...
is a little too arrogant.
Can you just say it?
Who's that?
My friend John's son, Eesho.
See! Didn't I tell you?
She felt nauseous as soon
as she heard his name!
My poor child!
You don't have to drop it
just because he's not to my liking.
Eesho it is, then.
But I have a condition.
What?
I don't want the wedding
immediately.
I need a week or two.
What?
A week or two?
Yeah! Even a week will do.
Wow! It's all Eesho's plan.
Huh?
Well, she didn't want
to get married at all.
Now she's saying that she wants
to get married in a week or two.
It's all Eesho's plan.
What else could it be?
Oh! That Eesho!
Sorry, Eesho.
Tell me what she said, Kurian.
I presented the matter
to my daughter.
Unlike what I thought,
she didn't have much of a problem.
But...
let me be frank, John.
The problem was never hers,
but mine!
Why is that?
Well...
my father struggled a lot to
establish this advertising company,
traveling by foot and on a cycle,
doing rounds of dead people's houses
to get obituary ads.
And I have raised it to this stature
to the best of my ability.
I have a wish that
this company should thrive
even after my death.
My daughter chose a different
career path in engineering and IT.
So, at least the one
who's marrying her
should be capable and interested
in keeping this company running.
I really can't have
two ways about that.
Kurian, you have a fair point.
I understand that.
Whatever our forefathers created
should not end up going to the dogs.
All of us think
on the same lines.
If this wedding happens,
the very next day, he will resign
his job in Bangalore
and join your company.
Thereafter, it will be him
managing your company.
But...
he too has to agree to it, right?
When Annamma gave birth to him,
I was 24 years old.
From then till now,
more than being a dad,
I've been an elder brother to him.
And even more than that,
I've been his best friend.
I will make him agree to this.
He will come.
This is Kattadi John's promise!
Are you sure?
Am I sure?
I am absolutely sure.
Then,
why don't you all come home soon
at your convenience?
It's not like we need
to ask anybody else now.
Why delay it?
We can come tomorrow!
- What?
- Yeah!
All of us will come there tomorrow.
Good deeds mustn't be kept pending.
So be it, then.
Uncle, coffee.
She made it herself.
I don't drink coffee
at 10:30 a.m., dear.
No, thanks.
I swear!
I'm sure you'll like the coffee.
Wow!
Has it been long
since you came home?
No, Aunty.
I came two days back.
Will you be here for a while?
Yes, I'll be working from home
for two weeks.
Eesho, you must have come
to attend the baptism, right?
Yes, Uncle.
And, I had some other work as well.
Where is your office
in Bangalore, son?
It's at a place
called Windsor Circle.
It's close to Brigade Road.
Okay, okay, okay.
So, do you stay near your office?
Around seven to eight kilometres
away from the office.
It's a place called Byappanahalli.
Are you staying alone,
or do you have
someone else with you?
- Yes.
- Huh?
- No... Yes... I do, right?
- No! No! Yes! Yes!
Yes, there is someone.
There is someone with him.
It's a Bengali.
Beng...
With such a long beard,
thick-framed glasses
and long hair.
It's the same person whom I met
when I came the last time, right?
Err... Yes!
He's a very creative person.
We can sense that
from his beard. Isn't it?
Yeah!
What can we say!
Bengalis are everywhere now.
But yeah, it's really hard to find
a place to stay in Bangalore.
I had sent her to...
You know, right?
Elsy's elder sister, the nun?
She's the mother superior
at Ursula convent in the Vatican.
I arranged for Anna's stay
at the convent in Bangalore,
using her influence.
The best part is that
the place has great discipline.
And of course
the prayers and devotion.
She has that too.
Not just that.
After a while, she didn't
want to leave that place.
When we kept telling her
about different marriage proposals,
she kept saying no.
We were scared whether
she'd end up being a nun.
This is such a relief.
So...
how do we take this forward?
Well... we fix the nearest date,
and conduct the wedding.
By "nearest" you mean?
I mean...
By next week
or the week after that.
What are you saying, John?
She's my only daughter!
And he's your only child too, right?
Shouldn't we invite
all our relatives and friends
and make this a grand celebration?
Yes, sure.
But, Kurian, the lent for Christmas
will start after two weeks.
It will be really late
after that.
If it is delayed too much,
things will grow and start showing,
isn't it?
Oh, no! We can't do that!
She is my younger brother
Kuttappayi's favourite niece.
He has said that he'll come
for her wedding from Philadelphia,
come what may!
So, we can't do it
until the lent is over.
But that's quite far away, right?
Not so much.
It's just two months, right?
Let's fix a date after that.
It's not like I have a problem.
But...
two months will be...
Two plus two...
What's wrong with that?
What do I say?
On her way from Bangalore,
she had a vada from the train.
It started since then.
Annamma ate a vada too?
Well...
if she sees someone
feeling nauseous,
she also feels nauseous.
- That's why.
- Oh!
How are you...
feeling now?
I'm okay, Aunty.
How are you feeling?
Annamma, you're not sick
or anything, right?
No.
I am fine.
I was saying that...
there are only 16 days left
for the lent to begin.
So, once the lent is over,
we'll conduct the wedding,
one week after Christmas.
But we'll only have
one and a half months altogether.
Isn't that too close a date?
Yeah, that's what I said.
Let's hand this over to someone.
Hand this over to someone?
The team that conducted
our Doctor's daughter's wedding?
Wasn't that an awesome function?
Yes, that was a great function.
It was conducted by
an event management company.
They will stay
until the wedding is over,
wash the plates
and remove the stage too.
We needn't be stressed
about anything.
That's nice.
That's really nice.
So, let's give it to them, right?
We'll do that.
Since I made a timely intervention,
everything went smoothly.
"Timely intervention."
You were really over the top, John.
Bengali with a beard, it seems.
Couldn't you think
of anything else?
I was scared
if you'd ruin everything
by going way overboard.
You heard that?
He's saying I ruined everything.
You heard him, right?
As if everything he did
was really decent.
Yes, I deserve to hear this.
Don't say anything, ichaya.
You were quite
over the top today.
You don't quite know how to act.
You're also supporting him, huh?
When you also went off
to vomit right behind her,
everything was going kaput.
Since I came up with a story
at the right time,
no one suspected anything.
Did they?
Did they suspect anything?
You tell me!
What did you say
you had from the train?
Lent for 25 days means...
altogether one and a half
months more.
How's it during the fourth month?
Will people be able to find out?
Don't you know that?
When I was four months
pregnant with him,
people used to ask me
whether my date was due.
But this guy...
is a big bull!
He was 4.25 kilos heavy
when he was born.
- 4.5 kilos!
- Oh, yeah! 4.5 kilos!
Will every child be like that?
There won't be any problem.
Let's give her a really tight sari
and make her wear a lot of gold
to hide the tummy.
People won't find out.
Yes, Anna?
Eesho, Mom found out.
But everything went smooth, right?
What went wrong after that?
Didn't I tell you already
that you were really over the top?
No... Can't be...
This is something else.
Hey!
Look!
Kurian is calling.
This will be an issue.
A huge issue!
- You answer the call.
- Me? I won't answer it.
Then?
Did I create this mess?
It's not like what you think.
This will be a huge issue!
Answer the call!
I won't answer it.
He's your best friend, right?
You answer the call!
Annamma, you answer it.
Here you go.
Ichaya, answer the call!
Come on!
- Hello?
- John.
Hello?
Where have you reached?
We're halfway through.
Kurian!
You should do one thing.
You should listen to me peacefully.
Don't say anything more.
You should come to town
police station tomorrow.
Kurian, please listen
to me peacefully.
We can't keep this for later.
We have only one
and a half months!
We should meet them
and fix everything immediately.
Just come near that police station
tomorrow and call me.
Their office is somewhere
near that station.
- Whose?
- Didn't I tell you earlier?
That event management company?
I had called them now.
We can meet them
if we go tomorrow.
We should finalise
everything tomorrow itself.
Them?
Well, Elsy is saying now
that we shouldn't delay it at all.
So, Elsy and Anna?
Yes. I asked them.
They are okay with it.
They are right next to me.
So, we'll meet tomorrow.
Okay?
See you tomorrow.
- John, you are..
- I'll hit you!
This is weird.
Something has happened
over there.
Something we don't know.
Wait a minute!
Until they left,
you were saying that your brother
has to come from America,
your nephew has to come
from Italy... and so on.
And as soon as they left,
you're saying that
we shouldn't delay it at all
and do it right away.
Make up your mind for once.
Well, if you're all in such a hurry,
why should I be the odd one out?
♪ Marriage is all hunky-dory
In the beginning ♪
♪ Life goes downhill thereafter ♪
♪ A cage for the green bird... ♪
If he comes to know about this,
I can't even imagine
what will happen.
Even when he kept saying no,
I was the one who compelled
him for this alliance the most.
Mummy!
Shut up!
I'll give you one tight slap!
If he figures this out
before the wedding,
he'll dig a grave outside our house
and bury the two of us there.
- Elsy!
- Yes!
Ichaya!
How many have you had?
It's just my sixth drink!
Sixth?
If not today, then when?
It's the day we fixed
our daughter's wedding!
That, too, to a groom
just like we wished for!
I mean,
a groom just like I wished for!
Do you know where he's working?
He works for a huge
multinational company.
We can't dream of hiring someone
from there for our company.
You should see the awards
he has won.
We can't even pronounce the names!
Well...
you were not so fond
of him initially, right?
I mean,
initially I thought that
he won't join our company.
Later, John promised me
that, the very next day
after the wedding,
Eesho will join our company.
You know what that means?
Our business will skyrocket!
Dr. Samuel had called
sometime back.
It's a business deal worth
around Rs. 25 crore.
If Eesho is with us,
we can win that deal easily.
Oh!
So, that's your big plan.
I just hope everything
goes according to plan.
Everything will.
Wait and watch.
- How about a drink?
- No.
I'm going to bed.
Okay!
Good night, sweetheart!
Yeah, yeah.
Done!
Anything, anytime, anywhere!
I am Happy.
We're also happy.
Sir, I was telling you my name.
I am Happy.
Happy Pinto.
Oh!
I mean... anything, anytime,
anywhere, we'll get it done.
If it's for a wedding,
you should bring
the bride and groom.
We can't provide that.
But your role ends there.
We'll get everything else done.
We'll start with
the wedding invites.
Everything will follow
one color theme.
The color of the sari, the suit,
counter and even the flowers...
Everything will have
the same color theme,
even the juice.
And then, the little kids,
elder sisters, younger sisters,
elder brothers,
younger brothers, aunties...
Why, even you will be
under our surveillance.
- Us?
- I mean, sir...
Everyone will dress according
to the dress code assigned by us.
- How's that?
- Oh! Like that!
And then, the food!
My mouth is watering
at the very thought of it.
Street food, South Indian,
North Indian, Arabic, Chinese,
Continental, Uganda!
Uganda?
Yes, Uganda.
It's the latest trend.
The chef will come from Kenya.
And then, the stage.
Houseboat, ship, train,
airport, secretariat,
Parliament, White House,
Beemapally...
Not Beemapally.
I mean, Taj Mahal.
I have 3D models of all these.
I can show them all.
I'll show you everything.
I have another item as well.
Shall I show it?
Call them.
Boys!
[IN HINDI] Give them a salute.
- Salute!
- [IN HINDI] Yes, sir!
Oh, my God!
It's okay.
It's only once in a while.
How's it?
What? The salute?
On the whole?
Isn't it quite overboard
on the whole?
We should go overboard, sir.
We should go way overboard!
Why else are you getting
your children married?
Isn't that so?
We brought them in a truck
from Jaipur.
They are our latest attraction.
We haven't used them yet.
There are eight people like them.
They will be building our stage.
Oops. Sorry.
I mean, they will be sprinkling
rose water on the stage.
I got confused.
[IN HINDI] Go! Go! Go inside!
- Go!
- Don't hit your head on the ceiling.
Bend down!
- Have food!
- Yes, sir!
They are high maintenance.
Quite expensive.
Please don't mind.
So, that was it about humans.
Now, let's get to the animals.
Horse, elephant, camel, zebra.
Which one do you want?
- Zebra?
- Yes.
- Who said zebra? Me?
- Yeah!
- Oops. We don't need zebras, sir.
Zebras might be
even more expensive.
Plus, we'll have to bring them
from Johannesburg.
Let's go with camels.
They can be arranged from Dubai.
We can get them
from Rajasthan too.
But they'll be skinny and ugly.
- Why do we need camels?
- Very simple.
The newly-weds will come
to the reception,
riding on a camel.
Riding and shaking like this
in slow motion.
Hell no! Nope, no camels.
They will... err... shake a lot.
We don't need that.
- No camels?
- No! No!
Let me think of options.
Cat, dog, duck, python...
What we need first...
is an invitation card.
Sheesh! Those are all
out of fashion, sir.
Pre-wedding shoots are popular now.
Pre?
Ah! I'll show you!
It's trending now.
They are really unique.
So interesting!
You'll die laughing
if you see them.
Check this out.
This is a photo where
they're lying in the marshlands.
Did you see all that sludge?
It's all original.
Look! The newly-weds rising up
from a 40-feet deep well.
If the rope breaks, they're done for.
We'll die laughing, seeing them.
Wow! This is a fire escape.
Fire escape?
Oh! We took so much risk
to shoot this, sir.
Are these people still alive?
Who?
They... Are they still alive?
Are they?
They... must be... right?
They are alive, sir.
They should be.
They haven't called me
after this, though.
Sometimes, it's like this...
Their payments are still pending.
Impressed?
Bye, bye!
Bye, bye, sir!
We don't have much time.
We need to start work immediately.
Good clients, right?
Both of them are filthy rich.
We should squeeze the last
penny out of them!
That's all good, but our camel plan
didn't work out.
I thought so too. They didn't buy
what I said about the camel.
It's not that. We had fed it
some biryani
during the inauguration
of Altaf's Mandi restaurant.
It hasn't had any food
after that.
Will anyone feed biryani to camels?
Aren't they vegetarians?
It's not that.
It's the climate here.
What's wrong with the climate?
The camels should be happy.
It's not as hot as Dubai here.
- But they prefer the heat.
- Yeah?
And yeah, one of them
is almost done for.
What do we do?
- Hello?
- Hello, sir?
- I am Happy.
- We are happy too.
I know, sir.
Sir, won't there be an engagement
before the wedding?
So, on the previous day..
I was just talking to the chef.
We can serve a special
Arabic item, sir.
- Camel biryani.
- Huh?
- Camel?
- Yes, sir. It's an awesome dish!
It's really good
Arabic biryani, sir.
Please save me, sir.
I mean, please trust me.
It will be really good.
Ah! Camel or whatever!
It's about the food, right?
No one should have any complaints.
Everything should be amazing.
- Okay sir. Thank you, sir.
- Okay.
- Safe journey.
- Thank you.
♪ On to the camel now!
This is it for you! ♪
♪ Bye-bye, big fella ♪
♪ Hiding from everyone
Without telling anyone ♪
♪ We speak to each other
Through our eyes ♪
♪ The day we've been waiting for
Will be here soon ♪
♪ Our lives
Will gradually turn colourful ♪
♪ To see you blushing
To tone down your anger ♪
♪ I'm always with you
Like a shadow ♪
♪ I shall be the shade
In your life ♪
♪ Never leaving your side ♪
♪ O faraway koel
O faraway koel ♪
♪ Shower me with dreams
All over this shore ♪
♪ O faraway koel
O faraway koel ♪
♪ When you are in grief
Turn to me for a smile ♪
♪ As you turn into my lullaby
Every night ♪
♪ When you are present
In every glance and word of mine ♪
♪ Even the passing breeze
Is humming your tune ♪
♪ I feel a change in myself
With each passing day ♪
♪ I shall be the eye
That guards you ♪
♪ I shall enter your nest
And share my heart with you ♪
♪ Come as an undisclosed dream ♪
♪ Never leaving my side ♪
♪ O faraway koel,
O faraway koel ♪
♪ Shower me with dreams
All over this shore ♪
♪ O faraway koel
O faraway koel ♪
♪ When you are in grief
Turn to me for a smile ♪
♪ O star that blossoms
At midnight's doorstep ♪
♪ Will the sun be late to rise? ♪
♪ Will the night go on further? ♪
♪ Is the dream that I see
In front of my eyes a reality? ♪
♪ O time, moving at a snail's pace ♪
♪ Can you please go faster? ♪
♪ I can't wait to join him ♪
♪ To quench my unending thirst ♪
♪ Like a half-written poem ♪
♪ You are far away from me ♪
♪ Is this a new kind of joy? ♪
♪ My habits are all long gone ♪
♪ Am I flying in the sky
Or on the ground? ♪
♪ Is this the illusion of love? ♪
♪ O faraway koel,
O faraway koel ♪
♪ Shower me with dreams
All over this shore ♪
♪ O faraway koel,
O faraway koel ♪
♪ When you are in grief
Turn to me for a smile ♪
♪ O faraway koel,
O faraway koel ♪
♪ Shower me with dreams
All over this shore ♪
♪ O faraway koel,
O faraway koel ♪
♪ When you are in grief
Turn to me for a smile ♪
So, Uncle...
This is our prototype.
We will modify our hospital
in Kochi first.
The work for that will begin
in one week.
These are the under-construction
designs in the other cities.
Impressive!
It will be really good.
So basically, Uncle...
For branding and
communication alone,
we've set aside Rs. 25-30 crore.
So, what we expect from you
is a clear idea on branding
and communication approach,
a marketing strategy,
and of course,
the new look of the brand.
I'll share the brief
with your team.
Kurian, as I told you,
I'll just be watching
from the gallery
because I don't have
any idea about all this.
So, my involvement
will also be limited.
In short, Cyril will be taking
all the decisions.
I will also be watching
the game from the gallery.
You've handed it over
to your son-in-law.
I have done the same.
The one presenting the concept
to your son-in-law
won't be me.
It will be my son-in-law.
- Who? Our...
- Exactly.
John's son, Eesho.
Uncle John's...
You mean Eesho Kattadi?
Really?
Then, we're sorted!
Eesho is one of the most sought-after
creative directors in India.
And if he's heading
the campaign,
I don't have to think
of another option.
I'm in!
Don't worry at all, Doctor.
We will rock this!
What are you saying, John?
You can't just make
promises like that!
I've come here on a leave
of three weeks.
Once I get back,
I have to go for a shoot in Prague.
What? You're going
to shoot a frog?
"Prague!"
It's a place.
It's a huge opportunity!
After that,
I'll get the salary I ask for
and a share in the company!
And you've gone ahead and promised
that I'll work in
this godforsaken place?
Eesho, you should
understand something.
After eight months,
you'll be the father of a child.
Once you have children,
you should be at home.
Do we need to make money
by gallivanting around the world?
Each person has his own interests!
Did you ask me even once
before giving him your word?
Oh! Is that so?
Did you ask me before...
doing all this?
What is it, ichaya?
What's the problem?
I'm trying to solve
all this somehow, and...
Let me tell you something.
He has agreed to this wedding
only because I made this promise.
I have given him my word.
I can't go back on it,
come what may.
You should go
and meet him tomorrow.
He has a huge project coming up.
You should do it for him.
And after the wedding,
you should settle down here.
You gave him your word, not me.
Kattadi John is a man of his word.
I can't go back on my word.
You needn't go back on your word.
I will talk to Anna.
You don't know Kurian well enough.
What will he do?
He won't eat me, right?
Every now and then, you keep saying
I don't know Kurian well enough.
As if I am...
Will the child in your womb
also turn out to be like this?
Don't think I can handle that!
Hello?
Sir, how about a falooda?
Huh? What?
Sir, shall we serve falooda
as a special dessert?
Lebanese falooda.
It's a special item.
It's really good
for digestion, sir.
Next morning,
the floodgates will open.
Is there any way I could get
one of those right now?
- Now?
- Yes.
- Now...
- Forget it! Fine!
Do whatever is necessary.
No one should have
any complaints.
No, sir. We'll make sure
that does not happen.
Thank you, sir.
Phew!
That sounded so tempting.
How did it go?
Oh, well, it did not.
Shall I do something?
Shall I prepare the concoction
that my sister suggested?
What concoction?
Twenty-five gooseberries dried
in moderate sunlight
along with rock salt
and turmeric powder.
She has given me a long list
of ingredients.
I have already dried
the gooseberries too.
If you drink one glass of that,
your constipation will be gone.
I'll drink whatever
you want me to drink.
I have to get so many things done
after this.
I'll bring it quickly then.
Hey! Where is she?
Seventeen...
Oops.
Listen, don't make it too tight
around my stomach.
Okay, okay.
- Just a minute.
- Okay.
Hey, note that down.
- Yes, Eesho.
- Anna...
I have to tell you something.
Eesho, you are always talking
about your job and career.
Have you ever thought about me?
I don't want to hear anything!
You have to hold on at least
until the wedding gets done.
Anna, please try to understand.
If you can't say it,
you don't have to.
I'll talk to your dad.
Do whatever you want.
Anna?
- Hello?
- Achaya, this is Jameskutty.
What is it, James?
I've called you to tell you
something urgently.
I'm in the middle of something
even more urgent.
Call me later.
No, Achaya.
This is an emergency.
Tell me, then.
Our Anna's groom?
Who?
The guy who's going to marry Anna?
Eesho?
Even if you asked me to or not,
it is my duty, right?
So, since I am in Bangalore,
I made an enquiry about him.
So?
He has a small set-up here.
- What do you mean?
- I mean,
he was living together with a girl,
here at Kammanahalli.
Moreover,
that girl who was with him
got pregnant too.
What are you saying?
Yes!
And your friend, Mr. John?
That guy's father?
I heard that he came here
personally to settle the issue,
and then packed the girl off.
Though it's a little late now,
I have told you what I had to.
Hey!
Is this the truth?
- Are you sure?
- I am sure, Achaya.
This is from a very reliable source.
How is it, Dad?
Wow! You look so pretty!
Look, ichaya.
It's really nice, right?
You don't need this dress anymore.
What happened?
It didn't work?
Ichaya, what is it? What happened?
Don't you get me started!
But that can't be!
I was told that one glass
of the concoction
will definitely work wonders.
Ask her to burn
that wedding dress.
This damn wedding
is not going to happen!
Oh, no!
What's he saying?
Answer the call, John.
It's Kurian.
I'll talk to him later.
Pick up and say something.
- John...
- Kurian...
I'll call you later, please.
I am at this shady place.
That's why.
What is this?
He's at a shady place, huh?
I'll show him
what being shady is like!
Please call after some time.
Ichaya...
Ichaya!
Ichaya, please wait.
At least tell me
where you're going!
Shucks!
- Hello?
- Eesho, where are you?
I've been calling you for so long!
I am at... err... this place.
What's the matter?
I want to see you right away.
This is not a place
you can come to.
Eesho, stop fooling around.
I need to meet you urgently.
Didn't I tell you?
You cannot come to this place.
You...
Are you drunk?
What if I am?
Oh! So you got drunk, called my dad
and created this mess, huh?
You know the shitstorm
you've caused now?
I haven't called your dad.
Neither did I tell him anything.
But I intend to, and I need
to have a drink before that.
I'm yet to talk to him.
Tell me where you are, you dog!
Aren't you John's driver?
Yes, sir.
John sir has come
to the hospital.
Why has he come to this hospital?
Where is John? John Kattadi?
Sir, he's in Samuel sir's cabin.
Twenty-five dried gooseberries,
20 petals of garlic,
15 green bird's eye chillies,
rock salt, ginger extract, lemon
extract, bananas and black cumin.
Add them to neem oil
and grind it properly.
Have this concoction
twice a day for two days.
Hey! Hey!
- Where's the toilet?
- The visitors' toilet is on the 7th.
- Where's the nearest one?
- The nearest one is nearby, sir.
Make way, please!
Oh, no!
Open, damn it!
Well, I said I was at this
shady place because...
Doctor, hey!
What I was saying earlier
was that.
Kurian needn't know about this
for the time being.
That's why I spoke like that
when he called me earlier.
But Eesho is going to marry
Kurian's daughter, right?
So, you will have to say it
at some point?
Well, if he learns about this
pregnancy in between all this,
everything will become complicated.
This is not your ordinary
pregnancy, right?
You needn't tell this
to anyone, Doctor.
I'm not going to tell anyone.
- Why should I tell anyone anyway?
- Exactly!
It's a little delicate now.
I'll tell him
once the wedding is over.
There won't be any problem then.
Okay.
As you wish.
- What do you want?
- Sir, I am Happy.
I'm not so happy.
Shall I tell you something
that will make you very happy then?
Yeah! Try your luck!
Considering your stature
and status,
you must be giving an expensive
surprise gift to your son-in-law,
apart from the dowry, right?
If you could inform us what that is,
we'd like to plan a small event
that matches it.
What's that gift, sir?
BMW? Benz?
If it's one of those luxury cars,
my aunt's son is a dealer
of such cars.
I can get a good commission...
Argh!
I mean, I can get you
a good discount, sir.
Your bloody auntie's discount!
Not for him! I'm on my way
to give a gift to his father first!
- Where?
- I'll call you after and tell you...
- Please do.
- ...what my gift to the groom will be!
- Okay, sir.
- Hang up and get lost!
Is there such a ceremony?
I didn't know that.
Hey! Don't waste time.
Note this down!
There's a ceremony
where the bride's father
gives a gift to the groom's father.
Okay. I know that.
Such unique ceremonies.
Very interesting.
Ichaya!
Gosh!
Why does this guy
keep following me?
Pull over.
The co-passenger is not wearing
a seat belt.
You'll have to pay a fine.
Sir, I was wearing the seat belt.
I swear!
I just took it off
when I saw you.
Sir, we don't have time.
It's the end of the month.
Come out with your documents.
Shucks!
Seat belt, damn it!
There's no cash in this?
Do you have any cash with you?
How will I have cash?
How about you?
No.
Such misers!
Sir!
Sir, I don't have cash.
Do you accept cards?
You own a Benz, sir.
Stop playing tricks,
pay a fine of Rs. 500
and get going.
So, you don't accept cards?
Huh?
Okay. Fine.
Such waste of time.
Ah!
I'll solve this right away!
Go, show the documents!
Sir, this is the father
of my son's fiancée.
Oh! Oh!
Kurian!
Oh!
Give me Rs. 500.
I was just thinking about you.
You can deduct this
from the dowry.
Let me go stuff this
in his mouth!
Here's the fine, sir.
Giving or accepting
dowry is a crime.
I can charge a case for that.
Sheesh!
I was just joking!
Okay! Let it be!
What is this, sir?
Kurian!
John.
Well, how come you're here?
I have to...
ask you something.
What is it, Kurian?
What happened?
Who was that Bengali
staying with Eesho?
- Kurian..
- Didn't you tell me that day
that it was a guy with
a long beard and thick glasses.
Have you seen him?
I... I was..
Hey!
Are you aware that there was a girl
staying with Eesho?
Kurian,
I was going to tell you that.
You needn't do a damn thing!
Did you know that she got pregnant?
Let me explain.
Your son gets a girl pregnant,
you sweep it under the carpet,
and you hope to marry him off
to my daughter?
- It's not like what you think.
- I don't need to hear a thing!
This is it!
I shouldn't see you
anywhere close to my daughter
or my house ever!
There's nothing between us anymore.
And the balance
of that Rs. 2,000!
Keep it as alms...
for quitting this alliance!
Here's the receipt
and the balance money.
So, we'll come and meet you
at your house at our convenience.
Why?
Well, from whatever I heard,
there's dowry, adultery, pregnancy,
molestation and cheating.
So, there will be
quite a number of cases!
I have your address.
I'll come and meet you
at your house.
Ichaya...
If we don't do something
immediately,
the situation will get
out of hand.
Call Eesho.
Ichaya!
I've been calling you for so long!
Where is Anna?
Anna has gone to meet Eesho.
To meet Eesho?
Where?
I didn't ask her that.
Call her right away!
- Ichaya, what's the matter?
- Call her, I say!
Tell me what the matter is!
Haven't I told you earlier itself
that only his name is Eesho.
His character is that of Judas!
He got a girl who was staying
with him pregnant,
and he wants to marry
our daughter!
Just call her!
Give it to me!
- Yes, Mummy.
- This is your dad.
- Where are you?
- I came to meet Eesho.
Where?
At Hotel Sheraton.
Huh?
At a hotel?
Where is he?
He's upstairs.
I'm going there now.
You're not going anywhere.
Stay where you are.
I'll be there right away.
Dad?
Hello?
- Why are you coming?
- I'm coming too!
He has called her to a hotel.
There are only a few days
left for the wedding.
And he has called my daughter
to a hotel!
My dear Anna,
believe me only if you can.
If I've said that
I haven't called him, I haven't!
I haven't said anything
to your dad either.
Why is my dad so angry then?
Well, that is...
Where's the rooftop bar?
It's at the rooftop, sir.
- Huh?
- At the rooftop.
Oh!
Ichaya!
Why are you driving so fast?
Didn't you understand
what I told you so far?
He shouldn't meet her,
come what may!
If he sees her,
he will brainwash her.
I thought he called my dad
and spoke about the job.
Didn't I tell you all this while
that I am innocent? I am innocent!
Innocent?
He is innocent, it seems.
- John, how about another drink?
- You!
His speech is mumbling already.
And he wants another drink!
Uncle, that's another problem.
Dad said he is coming here.
If he sees Eesho like this,
it will be an even bigger problem!
That's right.
Let's leave quickly.
I'll meet Kurian
and try to convince him somehow.
- Okay, bye!
- Come on!
Get up!
What's that for?
Keep it there.
Please!
Come!
Oh, no! Monster!
Stop there, you!
Stand here.
Kurian... let's talk.
Didn't I tell you that you don't
have to say a damn thing?
Anna...
come here.
Dad, I was...
Just come here, I said!
Dad!
You don't have to say anything.
I'll tell you everything.
They were cheating you,
all of them!
Kurian, you're not aware
of the whole picture.
Oh!
I'm not aware, huh?
I will ask him.
This is for you to hear too.
Was there a girl staying
with you in Bangalore?
There was.
Did she get pregnant?
It was an accident.
Was your dad aware of this?
I had to tell him.
You heard him, right?
You heard him too?
No further doubts, I presume?
- Kurian..
- Don't utter a word.
Come.
Uncle, all this ruckus
for such a silly thing?
- You bloody rascal!
- Ichaya!
- Oh, no!
- Kurian!
I won't spare him!
This must be silly for you!
But for me,
it's my daughter's life!
Dad, whatever you're saying
is true.
But these are all things
I'm aware of too!
What are you saying?
Yes, Dad.
But there's something
that you don't know.
I am the girl
who was staying with him.
I am three months pregnant now, Dad.
She is just...
making this up, right?
Ichaya...
I was going through so much
turmoil for so many days,
not knowing how to say this to you.
I wanted to tell this
to you somehow.
But I didn't know
how you would react to it.
Oh!
So, that's how it is!
Everyone knew everything.
I'm not needed here anymore.
All of you can do
whatever you want.
I am just a fool.
I was playing the fool.
You...
Weren't you my best friend?
- Sir, how about a brass band?
- Right now?
Sir, it's a new team.
I got them from Chennai.
This is their first programme.
It will also be their last.
I mean, it will be their best!
I know that you won't understand
whatever I say.
So I'll make you listen to them.
Start!
Stop!
How's it, sir?
Isn't it awesome?
- Nice.
- Thank you!
Oh, no! Blood!
Eesho! Oh, no!
Eesho!
Son!
Of course.
Sorry, Dad.
I just couldn't bring myself
to tell you.
Had you told this to me first,
what did you think
your father would do?
Hello?
Auntie, can you pass
the phone to Eesho?
This is Eesho.
Tell me.
Eesho,
I don't know what should be done
and how.
But if we are getting married,
wherever it may be,
my dad should bring me
to that church, holding my hands.
Happily.
If not, I don't want this marriage.
Anna?
Didn't you go to sleep yet?
When we were in college,
everyone knew that
Kurian was in love with your mom,
except your mom.
And finally, when the time came,
Kurian didn't express
his love to Annamma.
He expressed it
to Anakkallil Pappachan.
Your grandfather.
"You're not even worthy of cattle feed
from Anakkallil house."
That was what Pappachan
told Kurian's father then.
If we take that into account, when
we went there with this proposal,
Kurian shouldn't even have
allowed us into his premises.
I can understand all that, Dad.
- But..
- No!
You won't understand.
I remember a young Kurian
who came running to our bank
with Elsy's nuptial chain
when Anna was born.
That day, he didn't even agree
to take the money
without mortgaging
that chain there.
When you have children,
it's like starting your life
all over again.
All the habits and priorities
you had until then will change.
When a child is born,
a father and mother
are also born along with it.
Do you know how long
he would have dreamt of.
Anna's wedding day?
That wedding
and his daughter's life...
If today, he felt like he has
no role in either of them,
then we are at fault.
You are at fault.
You won't understand
the gravity of his pain now.
You will begin to understand it...
after seven or eight months.
Dad!
Is there any way out, Dad?
There is one.
I can show it to you,
but you will have to walk
that path alone.
Good morning, sir.
Sir, Dr. Samuel had called.
- Why?
- He said it's really late.
He was asking if we can make the
presentation, at least by tomorrow.
Call him and tell him
that we're not pitching this time.
But, sir, didn't we commit to it?
Hey!
I will throw this business
to the dogs!
To the dogs?
Sir!
I was going to tell you
that you have a visitor.
Just forgot...
Uncle,
I want to talk to you
regarding something serious.
I have nothing more to say
than what I did yesterday.
Nothing.
You may go, Eesho.
I am busy.
Didn't I tell you
not to allow visitors today?
When did you say that?
However busy you may be,
you should listen to this, Uncle.
During pregnancy,
the stress and anxiety
that the mother goes through
may cause physical
or mental disabilities
to the child that's yet to be born.
Many research reports
are coming out,
all over the world, about this.
What?
For example...
This is the most recent
research report
from World Health Organization.
The depression and anxiety
of a pregnant mother
can increase stress hormones,
and that can severely affect
the child in her womb,
according to these research reports.
So?
Well...
We can't blame anyone, right, Uncle?
Depression and stress have become
as common as a cold or a cough now.
Sometimes it may be
due to our lifestyle issues,
or due to the stress
at our workplaces.
If not any of those,
the minor arguments and fights
that occur in families,
stubbornness
or any such minor incident
can propel a person into depression.
But...
that?
Yes, Uncle.
When certain people are angry
or under extreme stress,
they might resort to violence.
But certain others
don't express any of this
to the outside world
and keep it all
within their minds.
But, Uncle, that...
That may lead to much more severe
health issues.
And what if they are pregnant?
Even the lives of the mother
and the child may be endangered
at the same time.
Eesho...
I didn't do it deliberately...
This is a research report
by the Central Child Welfare Board.
If the mental and physical health
of every unborn baby
has to be better,
the atmosphere around them...
I mean, the family atmosphere,
the social atmosphere...
There should be attempts
to improve all these as well, Uncle.
Well...
what do I...
Not just you, Uncle.
Each one of us.
Especially,
a hospital group
which specialises in maternity.
Huh?
Yes, Uncle.
When a child is born into a family,
it's not just a new baby
who's born there.
A new father and mother
are also born the same day.
SMT Group of Maternity Hospitals.
Not just for newborn babies,
but for newborn parents too.
This is awesome!
This will be amazing!
SMT Group of Maternity Hospitals.
Not just for newborn babies,
but for newborn parents too.
Kochi, Calicut, Chennai,
Hyderabad, Pune.
That's it. That's the...
end of our presentation.
Two, three!
Oh, no! Rain?
Stop smiling!
Not here! Sprinkle it there!
- Sprinkle it over there!
- Yes!
Who's at that table?
Hey! That table looks really empty.
Fill up the place.
Don't forget to give our cards
to people who leave after dinner.
- All the best.
- Thank you.
Hello?
Everyone, please pay attention.
Thank you for coming today.
Thank you!
Today is a very happy day for me!
- For us too, right?
- But...
I'm not just
a very happy father today.
I'm a very, very happy
future grandfather as well.
Well, I have no qualms
in saying this!
My daughter, Anna...
is three months pregnant.
How?
Three months?
In that case, I want to say
something too.
Okay. Tell me. Oops, sorry.
I know, buddy!
You want to say that the child's
father is your son, right?
It's not like
they haven't got that by now.
No! It's not that.
- I'll come there.
- Oh, no, ichaya!
Don't serve the ice cream, as yet.
Give it to me.
Hey!
Since Kurian has revealed
a surprise,
I guess it's my turn now.
I'm not just someone
who's going to be a grandfather today.
I am someone
who's going to be a father
all over again.
How is this possible for them?
Even my wife, Anna...
is three months pregnant,
just like her.
Wow!
Bro, when did this happen?
Somehow managed it in between
my busy schedule. Sorry!
That's awesome!
Dude!
Two baby showers!
Note it down!
Congratulations!
Okay. Serve the ice cream!
Come on!
Oh, no!
Who is Anna's husband?
Me!
Huh?
Cut!
♪ Are the wombs now empty? ♪
♪ Are they going to be
On the same path hereafter? ♪
♪ Are fresh smiles
Flapping their wings? ♪
♪ And the story is awesome! ♪
♪ Leave it...
Forget it, bro! ♪
♪ This is a game of destiny, bro! ♪
♪ With colours all over ♪
♪ Have a blast, bro ♪
♪ Are the wombs now empty? ♪
♪ Are they going to be
On the same path hereafter? ♪
♪ Are fresh smiles
Flapping their wings? ♪
♪ And the story is awesome! ♪
♪ Leave it...
Forget it, bro! ♪
♪ This is a game of destiny, bro! ♪
♪ With colours all over ♪
♪ Have a blast, bro ♪
♪ Bro Daddy! ♪
♪ Bro Daddy
Daddy Bro! ♪
Bro Daddy ♪
♪ Bro Daddy
Bro! ♪
Cut! Okay!