Priya, listen to me
Let go of me
You always do this,
it's always other women
I didn't mean to hurt you
Every time you say the same thing
You know how much I love you
Please, listen to me
I love you so much
Cut!
Kaira, good for you?
Guys we'll do one more
We got this shot right?
We are running out of time, we don't
have permission for the whole day...
Kaira has a nice idea,
we'll do one more
What's the point of finishing
on time if we don't get a good shot?
Look, no respect for producers
Especially these new
cameramen... sorry... women
Come on, hurry up, let's do this!
Fatima, we are going to change the guy
You want the other guy?
He's got to look a little sexy
Get the camera
Cut!
Got that?
Fantastic!
Superb execution!
Good shot
I shot it at 48 frames,
speed up the end if you like
I'm going to take a
plate of the building now
Saw the shot Raghuvendra?
That one expression of the girl
checking out the passing guy says so much
I wish I had met Kaira earlier, I
would have shot the whole film with her
I got that
It's a wrap guys! Thank you!
Told you, don't have to carry my bag
I'm so sorry
Your mom called on
my cellphone earlier...
you never pick up yours...
please call her back,
before you take off
I will, you enjoy your mini holiday
You could have enjoyed
Singapore with us...
but you wanted to
fly with someone else
Shut up
Go go
I tried to upgrade you, couldn't do it
Please
Hi guys what can I get for you?
Beer
- Coke
Just Coke?
I drink only on two occasions,
when I am in love and when I am not
Okay...
Cheers!
Kaira, everything okay?
As in we're good right?
What are you talking about,
what happened to us?
Cheers!
Raghuvendra, I want to
shoot an entire feature film...
enough of this patchwork
I mean I can't keep waiting
for other cameramen to fall ill...
no one will even know
that I've shot this scene
I want to shoot my own film
You will
Who wouldn't want to work
with a hot DOP like you?
Hot!
Is that my only talent, seriously?
Seriously
Don't talk to me
Of course you're talented...
You are shooting so many
ads...earning good money
Ads and all are fine
I want to shoot a film
You will, you will, soon
And you're so young, I mean...
you wear zero number
glasses to look older
Excuse me?
If actresses can be at their peak at
a young age then why not technicians?
Have you heard of the word 'Patience'?
No I haven't, tell me about 'Patience'
Pick up...
pick up the cook's call...
if you want I can
just go and come back
He is not a cook,
he is the owner of a restaurant
Not even a cook?
That shot was your idea right?
Girl with guy, checking out other guy?
Inspired from life?
Listen Kaira...
you take my seat, I'll take yours...
I can sit in Economy class,
no need to sacrifice
Your long legs won't
fit in there anyway
That is true
It is very true
Yes Mom, it was good
Can't talk now,
the plane is going to take off
Bye!
So...
can I come up?
I'm really tired
Dinner?
I'm busy, but I'll see you
Alka!
Didi! (Sister)
You've become so fat!
L-low was your flight'?
Your mother called 3 times
You are so sweet Alka
Thank you!
Do you want coffee
or shall I serve breakfast?
Later
Didi...
this guy is so cute
Was cute!
Was!
I don't find him cute anymore...
just take down his photo
I just put it all in perfect order
Now it's perfect
So then, how was your trip'?
It was good
Just good?
Okay, great
You look beautiful sweetheart
Sorry, I'll just...
No it's okay, go ahead
meet them I have to go pee anyway
Table for 4 please?
I'm sorry guys,
we have a strict dress code
No shorts and slippers please
Come on, it's his birthday
I'm sorry, wish I could
But she's wearing shorts!
It's okay for girls, I'm sorry guys
Just this once, only for you
Next time I'll come along
on shoot with you, as your caterer
What do you say?
I slept with Raghuvendra
I should go...
Sid...
I'm sorry
What are you doing!
It's all good!
It's okay, it's all good...
Hey look, Sid!
Shit! Where?
That's not Sid, Jackie
He looked so much like him...cute
Poor thing, nice guy he was
Really nice
Little too nice for you right?
Oh my God! This jacket!
It reminds me of school,
our 'Famous Five' gang
Was that the 8th or 9th grade?
10th grade, same one
See, I can have a long
term relationship too
Yes, with things
So are we things too?
Yes, you are a thing
Sorry
Have you gone blind in love?
Am I invisible?
We said sorry
Staring into her eyes!
They are a couple
'Oh my coochie coo'
'So sweet I love you'...
The same rubbish crap it's irritating
What are you doing?
Go to hell!
Stupid! Hate couples!
Are you guys here to help
me or to do a comedy show?
Both
Guys I have a deadline, I have
to show the director the costumes
Fine
Raunak do you need help?
Listen, I've to go,
I have my 'BD' appointment
What's this 'BU?
'Brain Doctor', my therapist
Oh 'BD'... Raunak you're
still going to that 'BU?
I have to
'Brain Doctor'?
Why are you seeing a therapist?
Are you mad?
Who isn't? Look at him
That's a cut, nice
Good for you Kaira?
Good for me
Rubbish I
can direct better than this!
Tell me something...
Why did you start
seeing your therapist?
So that you could
tell everyone you're gay?
No
So that I could tell myself, I'm gay
When is your flight to Goa?
Don't remind me I can't
believe I'm going to Goa
You're the first human
being who's saying this so sadly
It's Goa! Enjoy
Shut up
And yes it is sad...
Because I'm going on duty
Every 2-3 months
have to go show my face
Raghu?
Duty!
Yes mom, I'm coming tomorrow
What's with this food every time!
Make what you like,
don't ask me I'm busy
Mothers! Same standard
question every time...
'What will you eat' 'What to make'
Either she isn't my real
mother or she's had a memory loss
Kaira!
At least eat my food...
Only way to handle the torture...
I think this time I'll
work on my short film
Short film
The longest project of this century
That's so bitchy
It's true
l-low do you like my French food'?
Landlord? I'm not answering
I don't know about French
food but this dip is amazing
Full Indian spice, try it
The dip is from Kaira's fridge
I have made the puff pastries
Jackie, at last you made something
What do you mean, at last?
You film people think that
only you do important work...
and the rest of us are useless?
I have decided to work on myself
That's tough work
Do n, do it
What's wrong with you?
I'm not going to Goa
Guess what?
'Raghu' your friend called...
and I have to shoot
a music video here in 3 days
Now get ready
Okay'!
I have never seen anybody
so excited not going to Goa
No Goa
What happened to her?
It's not because of my food
Okay everybody,
just get away from the table
This food is contaminated
Hey Fats. . .you good?
Koko
Yes
Guess what?
What's up?
I'm pregnant!
What?
It wasn't Jackie's food
Oh my God Fatty! Congratulations!
I mean we're supposed
to be happy right?
I don't know...
I want to throw up right now
Should I go?
Yes please
No I'm just kidding
I'm just very excited
Are you pregnant too?
So I was working on a co-production
with this New York film company...
and it has come through
Thank you
Wow, you are going to be
shooting a feature in the US?
Yes
Tell me more...good script?
Superb
Are you going to be
filming 'in' New York?
You are going to
be filming in New York
As in 'we' are going
to be filming in New York
If you're not available
we'll get another camera person...
Oh my God...l will kill you!
Told you, not going to Goa is lucky
Lucky for you, unlucky for me...
I want to kill my husband...
You're sure right?
It's not because
you think I'm hot right?
Obviously... you think
it's because you're talented?
What's wrong with your head?
Why are you so complicated?
You're the best,
that's why you got the job...
Simple
Thank you, appreciate it
So let's break up
Oh my dear
Let's break up
Oh please say yes
You and I will never work out,
oh let me go
So let's break up
Oh my dear
Let's break up
Oh please say yes
You and I will never work out,
oh let me go
When I see
A beautiful girl
I get excited
Basically basically basically. ..
I 'm a rascal
It's a wrap!
Hi mommy, congratulations!
Fatima the fatty!
Cute guy
So many men in your life
Shut up
You'll also get to spend
time with Raghu also...
when you're in New York,
shooting for 3 months
Hello ladies, and one gent
Oh hello?
Oh sorry two gents
Can I steal Kaira for a minute?
Thief! Even we want to hear
What?
Even we want to hear!
What? I can't hear anything
Okay pose
Nice one
So I'm off to New York tonight
What?
Yes
The financiers want to meet urgently
Someone has to fly so that you can
OK go, fly...
Have a nice flight
That's it?
Have a nice flight?
What else do I say?
Say something
You pulled me here,
you say something
Firstly stop looking so hot
Tie your hair up
And behave yourself,
just for two weeks
Here you go, happy'
Very happy
l-low do I look'?
Lovely
So I had to talk to
you about something...
Do you want to hit the dance floor?
Hi Justin Bieber
We're just in the
middle of a conversation
Anyway, you were saying
I was saying that...
Gautam i...
Who?
Gautami Sharma will be
the line producer of the film...
OK, so?
The financiers have recommended her...
they think she is the
best person for this job
What are you trying to say?
Gautami and I, many years ago...
were in a relationship
Okay, it's a reunion! That's amazing
Reunion my foot...
It's going to be a
really awkward situation
I mean she was such a weird one...
I don't even feel like seeing her
I just want the job to go smoothly,
and I thought you should know
Cool, whatever
What Whatever'? Come here...
Anyway I've had someone else
on my mind for a while now
Look I think...
it's time that we got
serious about each other
I think it's time that you go
Do you want to miss your flight?
Kaira I'm serious, I'm not kidding
We really should...
We have a flight to catch...
It's late
Okay Okay)'
Go, it's okay, it's cool
Really?
You don't have anything to say?
No, that's it for now
Bye
What did I miss?
Shots!
So, let's break up
Oh my dear
Let's break up
Oh please say yes
You and I will never work out,
oh let me go
When I see
A beautiful girl
I get excited
Basically basically basically
I 'm a rascal
But you're no less baby
Somedays you're nice
Somedays you're crooked
Basically basically basically. ..
You're a rascal too
Koko, why don't you think
seriously about Raghuvendra?
He is so right for you...
This is why some
people should not drink
Why should she think
about Raghuvendra?
Is he the last man in the world?
Why shouldn't she consider him?
I will tell you point by point why
Raghuvendra is the perfect guy for Koko
Point no. 1...
And this is the most
important point in the world
He is good looking
Hardly two percent of people
in the world look good...
and if you have to spend
your life with somebody...
every morning you should
at least see a handsome face
Point no. 2...
He has a great sense of humor...
and more laughter means more sex
Where are you getting
this information?
Point no. 3...
He understands your profession
If you marry a software
engineer or a farmer...
what will you discuss at dinner?
Virus or cow dung?
Hello, my husband
is a software engineer
And we have many
interesting discussions
Like what?
Like a lot of things
And I'm sure farmers
are interesting too...
they can tell us
about organic vegetables
They can tell you
where to get cow's milk
Go, marry a farmer
Ganju, tell them I'm right
Yes, please give us
your male point of view
Guys, just shut up
This is all pointless
He's going to meet his
ex-girlfriend in New York
Ex-girlfriend! That's just great
Ex is an ex, that's in the past
Just punch her
No, the important question is...
are you his present?
William Faulkner once said...
"The past is never dead,
in fact it's not even the past"
What?
Your 'BD' taught you this?
Hey I want to go to this 'BD'
Raguu!
Take it take it...
No I don't need it
Stop acting pricey...
1 know you like Raguu
No, I don't
Take it, keep it, very tasty so yum
Yuck Jackie, so cheap
I love the taste of Raguu
Have you gone mad?
Limited offer, grab now
You've gone mad
Pasta!
No don 'I be so desperate,
let him call
New photo?
Yes, nice?
Eat quickly, it will get cold
Raguu Raguu Raguu. ..
Just crush the blacks
More...
See...
Let's Play
Much better see...
Yes, it's looking nice
Okay now pause and zoom in
Ganju! I told you to remind me at 3 PM
I had to take Fatty to the doctor
Fatty! I'm so sorry, I'm just leaving
No, you wait I 'm coming there,
to eat the canteen Veda Pav
My doctor's appointment got canceled
This landlord...
Hello...
What?
You are not going to believe this
Being single is now a crime!
What?
My landlord is kicking
me out of my apartment!
What?
I'm going to join the
ranks of homeless in Mumbai
And you want to know why?
Did I damage the apartment? No!
Did I forget to pay rent? No!
The building committee
just got together and decided...
that only married couples
and families can live there
ls that even legal?
This just happened?
Yes he just called!
I've been avoiding his calls for days
Gosh Fatty, I have to vacate
by the end of the month...
I don't know what to do
Damn these people
Mumbai, India's most
modern cosmopolitan city
Seriously
Listen, you know you can stay with me
That's not the point
In a way, thank God...
thank God I'm leaving this city
and this country for this project...
But seriously what thinking
No marriage means no home for women?
Why don't they make this law instead 'no
staying with your in-laws after marriage'?
Forget it
So, when is the New York shoot?
I don't know
I will know the exact
dates in a month...
when the man returns
The man has not called?
Raghuvendra has not called?
No
What 'hmm'?
Why you looking so suspicious?
Fatty? Tell me
He got engaged
He got engaged!
I'm sorry, who got engaged?
Raghuvendra
When?
Last week
Last week?
He was just here,
I mean, he just left...
I know...
Who told you? How do you know?
Ajay, that guy from production...
Just one second...
he's not even messaged...
Who told you?
Ajay, from production,
he went to New York with Raghuvendra
He got engaged?
I don't believe this to whom?
Just please, one second, how can he'?
Koko...
God! This is just getting worse
You okay?
It's just the chilli
You want to know to whom?
No
Okay playback
Sorry it slipped
Where do I go from here
Where do I hide
This half heart
How do I share?
We parted from myself
Pm separated from myself
This half heart
How do I settle?
Oh hurting heart
Oh Dying heart
Oh broken heart
What's your problem
Oh heart, just go to he“
Just go to he“, Oh heart
I don't believe this
Back to Goa, back to square one
It's just for 1 month...
then the New York shoot will start...
won't it?
I don't know...
Personal and professional...
always keep it separate
You always say this
When will you ever use this?
Such strange things you buy
Damn, I have to live
with my parents for a month
How am I going to do it?
Stay with me...
I'm also going to be in Goa
We'll do yoga together
Do yoga in your fancy holiday house...
I wish my parents would
buy me a villa in Goa
Guess what?
When I reach Goa, I have
to do a beautiful shoot for my dad
Uncle also joined the film business?
No Jackie...
he wants me to shoot a promotional
video for his friend's restaurant...
Who knows?
This could be the
turning point in my life
Are you my fault
Or your own mistake
Shamed heart
Please tell me so
What do we gain now
What do we lose now
Shamed heart
Crying is no use
Oh hurting heart
Oh Dying heart
Oh broken heart
What's your problem
Oh heart, just go to he“
So Koko
Have you met 'Salman Khan' yet?
Oh my God, 'Sallu'!
Is he so handsome in real life?
Does he actually have a 6 pack?
Or is that just how
it looks on screen'?
Tell me Koko, I'm dying to know
First of all,
I haven't met your 'Sallu'...
and if I ever meet him...
I'm not going to tell him...
'Take off your shirt
I want to see your 6 pack abs'
Exactly
Tell us about your ad with 'Dhoni'
One second dad
'Salman Khan'? Abs? Really?
Stop bugging her...
talk about the main topic
Yes Ashu,
she should be doing a proper job...
in an office...
something more respectable
That's when we can talk to
people seriously about marriage
Why will she do some other job?
She's done a cinematography
course in New York
She is brilliant at her
job and she's still young
She won't be young forever...
all the good boys will be taken
That's my biggest worry you know...
come baby...
So Kaira, tell me...
Are you a...
Are you a Lebanese?
It's not Lebanese', it is lesbian!
Yes, are you a Lesbian'?
Oh my God...
If I were, would that stop
you from talking about marriage?
Even if you are,
it won't make a difference...
all this gay stuff is
cool in the film industry
You're right...
from big stars to spot boys,
everyone's gay...
we call it 'Gollyvvood' now
Really?
Of course not!
Do you people even
listen to yourselves?
It's such rubbish
The film industry doesn't have more
gay people, it's just more accepting...
there must be many gay
people in your office too...
but sadly they have to hide the fact
So, are you?
A 'lesbo?
No, unfortunately not
So why don't you settle down?
We're just worried about you Koko
If you keep hanging
with these filmy men...
how will you find a nice boy'?
Filmy men are okay for checking
out abs, but not okay to marry?
How much junk you keep eating
I've made all this for you...
eat this
For me? Have you
ever seen me eat this?
I thought you like paneer...
you used to eat it...
that's why I keep
asking what you want...
anyway, dinner is put...
come baby, come...
You know Koko
getting married before 25...
can reduce the divorce rate by 50%
There is a 100% chance
of not getting a divorce...
...by not getting married
I'm going to stay with Jackie
Koko?
Pm addicted to pain
Even my tears, laugh at me
Why do I give myself new scars
Somebody save me from myself
What about the New York project...
What is this question,
'did you sleep well'?
If I say no what can you do?
I don't care what people think...
I'm not going to stay
with you for other people...
don't irritate me please
'Good morning' is it?
Now it's a 'good morning'...
If your night is not good...
how will your morning be good'?
I think I should
be a night watchman...
Should I take an
appointment with a doctor?
Who is that?
He moved here a few weeks ago,
to write...
Nice guy
Take an appointment with him
There she is, my talented daughter...
She shoots with all
'Bollywood' celebrities
Really?
I know this is a small job for you...
but this new restaurant
video is very important for us...
thank you so much for doing this
No, it's cool
Actually we should start,
the camera setup will take a while
Yes, she is very professional
During work, only work, nothing else
Dad!
Can we stop all these
useless formalities?
I need to get this done
I only have a day
Get the 24-70
Tried everything Ganju...
even sleeping pills, nothing works
Try 'Reiki'...
my grandmother also tried it
Shut up and setup
Remove all this,
what's all this rubbish...
I am sorry,
this can't be moved right now...
only after this session ends
What?
We have to wait? Then why call us?
Ma'am, the session is going on
Madness!
National Convention for
Mental Health Awareness...
it's a festival for therapists...
RaunaKs playground...should we go in?
Shut up and sit
Here?
Just sit
I've done a shot breakdown,
you want to see?
I'm sleeping
Dr. Chopra,
therapy, counseling, analysis...
so many big terms...
what do they actually mean?
A proper map can be drawn after defining
commonly accepted medical terms...
if your prob/em or illness
falls in those definitions...
your prognosis will
tell you your diagnosis
it will become clear whether you need
intensive therapy or counseling...
whether you need an
analyst or psychiatrist...
it's quite simple actually
It's very simple
What are they talking
how to understand?
Dr. Pereira, how does one decide which
type of doctor they should be going to?
A psychiatrist or a psychologist?
Each model has it's own
strengths and weaknesses. ..
Ah individual may find one approach
more appropriate than another...
depending on his
persona! preferences...
and the depth and severity
of the problem presented
If I hear another minute of this...
I'll go nuts
This question is for Dr. Khan
Dr. Khan, how do you know
if someone is crazy or normal?
What?
Take me for example...
many of you might
think that Pm crazy...
I've come for this formal
seminar in these torn jeans...
so, am I crazy?
Or maybe all I need is a good stylist
Crazy! Very scary word
Because here we still believe that...
a problem of the mind
is something to be ashamed of
If you have a problem with your body,
that's normal...
you can tell everyone...
'hey I'm in hospital...
with a kidney failure...
lung infection, jaundice'
But if it's a problem of the mind...
then the whole family goes silent...
hush hush hush...
as if the mind is not
even a part of the body
Don't laugh just yet...
the joke begins now
Here in Goa,
my parents used to tell everyone...
that I'm a gynecologist,
not a psychologist
Which means the doctor's
own family is ashamed...
to admit that their son is a therapist,
dealing with problems of the mind
Imagine my plight...
many of my pregnant relatives landed
up at the clinic for a free check up...
and you know what,
I delivered a few babies too...
for the extra pocket money
No, I'm just kidding
Dr. Jehangir Khan
Thank you
You'll close it please?
So I'm Jehangir Khan...
but you can call me '.Jug'
May I have a glass of water...
from that jug, Jug?
I'm sure you can
crack better jokes Kaira
May I call you Kaira?
I have only one name
So, how does this work?
I have no idea how that works...
you tell me
Can I lie down here?
Why, are you sleepy?
I'm not able to sleep
That's the reason I am here
Did you see a doctor?
Isn't that what I'm doing?
You mean the white coat,
stethoscope, pill-giving doctors...
I tried pills, they didn't work
That's why I'm here
Sometimes I use this to
knock my patients off to sleep
You're funny
But, you need to work on your jokes
So tell me
Any major change in your life?
I just moved from Mumbai to Goa...
is that a major change?
Yes that's a major change...and?
And nothing,
the moving out, the settling in...
Or the leaving, the unsettling?
No, that's not a problem for me...
I like to move,
not being in one place...
in fact I love to travel...
it's just this sleeping problem
So why did you move
from Mumbai to Goa'?
You know...
I came to Goa to be
with my best friend...
she's having issues with this guy...
who she really likes,
really 'liked'...
and she thought he liked her too...
but then he suddenly
got engaged to someone else
So your best friend, is she okay now?
I don't think so...
I don't think she is okay
I think her main problem
is her profession
She got this dream job,
which is linked to him...
his new fiance will
also be on this project
So how will she handle that?
I don't know
What if everything gets messed up?
I don't know what to advise her...
should she just deal with it?
It is her dream job after all
Sometimes I feel I should tell her -
'Grit your teeth and just do it...
you won't get another
opportunity like this'
And sometimes I feel I should say -
'Shut up! And say no!...
don't you have self respect?'
So I don't know what to tell her
So you are not able to sleep,
because you are up all night...
wondering whether to tell
your best friend to shut up or not?
My grandfather used
to tell me a story...
please narrate it to your best friend
My grandfather was a mountain-climber
Before any expedition,
he would be thoroughly prepared
Sadly, poor Pyarelalji
was not like this
Who Pyarelalji?
A very old friend of my grandfathers'
He was also a
mountain-climbing enthusiast...
whose life-long desire
was to climb the toughest peak...
Mt. Everest!
Finally one day, Pyarelalji
got the chance to climb Mt. Everest...
with a Chinese trekking
expedition group
Without thought or preparation,
he said yes and left
But the group was Chinese...
so they could speak only
in their own language...
no English Vinglish
So the trek began
As they slowly and
steadily climbed higher...
Pyarelalji paced ahead of
the group with much enthusiasm...
while the Chinese people kept waving
from behind and shouting in Chinese...
'Don't go ahead! hatahau hatahau!.
but Pyarelalji thought
they were cheering him oh...
and saying 'go ahead,
You can speak Chinese?
Can you?
No
Then this works
Don't laugh, listen
Suddenly, Pyarelalji saw a growling
snow leopard in front of him...
Pyarelal got scre“"
1 mean he got bloody scared
Now he started waving his hands
frantically and shouting 'Help, Help!'
But the Chinese people
thought he is just happy
So he kept crying for help,
and they kept waving back
Then?
Then the snow leopard
ate up poor Pyarelalji
What?
Yes he was hungry
You don't find many
people on Mt. Everest...
And the group kept shouting...
'don't go ahead'
What a strange story
No, it's not a strange story
Please tell your friend...
that sometimes we choose
the tough path only because...
we feel that to achieve
important things...
we have to take the tough path
We feel we need to punish ourselves...
but why?
Why not choose the easy way out?
What is so bad about it?
Especially when we are
unprepared for the tough path
Why climb mountains
when you are not ready to?
Excuse me
You will tell your
friend the story right?
It's important
Okay, I think...
My sleeping problem began...
when Raghuvendra got engaged
Raghuvendra?
The guy in my story?
Right, your friend's...
No, mine
At least I thought he was mine
We used to work together
Jack!
What are you doing here?
You don't answer my calls,
you moved here without telling me
Without telling you
Why would I tell you?
Who are you?
Actually I have one
thing to tell you...
I've made my decision
What decision?
Kaira, I have to talk to you...
Just shut up, one second
Listen to this story
This man wants to climb Mt. Everest...
but without any preparation
he leaves for Mt. Everest...
with Chinese companions...
and as he's about to fall...
the Chinese people don't understand...
obviously, because they are Chinese...
and they keep waving their flag...
and the man is stuck...
and then a tiger eats him up!
Got it?
The difficult option
is not the only option
We can choose the easy option
also because the easy option is easy
You know, forget it
It's too much for your small mind
It's a very deep thought
Are you talking about
working on the film?
I was talking about
NOT working on the film!
That's my decision
Okay, okay good
Good?
Yes I think that's the best...
You think?
Did you hear that?
I have already taken the
decision to not work on your film...
What do you mean by 'you think'?
I guess someone really
does need therapy...
You told him?
No Koko
Him?
Yes, she told me, so?
And anyway why do you need therapy?
What's the big tragedy in your life?
You didn't want to get serious,
didn't want to commit
So I don't understand,
what is the problem?
You don't understand?
- No!
Then get out
Oh God Kaira...
You really need to grow up
Good thing you've decided
not to work on my film...
I'm looking for mature
people to work with
What did I just say?
Get out right? Get out!
Bye, see you Jackie
I'm not mature enough to
handle your big fat project...
but mature enough to sleep with you?
Amazing! What a revelation
Kaira I came here to...
I don't want to do this, get out
What are you doing Kaira?
Just get out!
Koko, are you sure about this?
I know with all these
personal issues...
working with Raghu will be tough...
but this was your big break
Okay Jack
Sometimes we choose
a tough path just because...
we believe that to
achieve important things...
we have to choose the tough option
But sometimes you need
to choose the easier option...
because at that time that
is the best option for you
Right?
Especially when you are
not ready to face that tough path
Damn! Wish I had said
it right when he was here
You want some tea?
Tonight I'm going to sleep so well,
so well...
Very well!
I was at this construction site...
with all these construction workers...
all short and strange people
Suddenly, I lose my balance...
and I go falling down...
this big fall...
and land in muck
I think it was a gutter
All these workers are just staring,
but no one is helping...
I look up...
and I see my camera dangling...
and then suddenly out of nowhere...
this group of newly married women...
in saris, pal/us & bindis
all land up there...
and they start pointing
at me, laughing at me
Bam! I woke up
It was 4 am...
I went straight to the bathroom
and stood under the shower
Why shower?
I don't know
I felt dirty, I felt
like I needed to clean up
So this Raghuvendra,
he is tall and handsome?
That's your conclusion of my dream?
Just asking
You know what I felt...
I felt I am ugly, trashy, cheap, dirty
That's funny
What's funny?
I mean...
all this from a girl who is
the opposite of ugly, trashy or dirty
That's funny... not "ha-ha" funny
Okay'!
Oops!
What's With this?
It only creaks when you really like
someone, but can't do anything about it
Yes, Raghuvendra is tall and handsome
So you like tall people,
not short and strange
Maybe...Sid was also tall
So there's a Sid too?
Yes so?
So I mean you're a young
and beautiful woman...
you will have admirers
What do you mean?
What do you mean by admirers?
I mean you're a young
and beautiful woman...
you will have admirers
Admirers?
- Yes
You're trying to say
that there are lots of men!
That's what you're trying to say
No, what do you want me to say?
Why would I say that? No
That's what you are saying
You actually mean that I'm a fast girl, a cheap girl...
- No come on!
Fast dirty cheap...
...why use these words?
Isn't that what the world thinks?
If a girl has more than
one relationship then that's it!
Kaira...
have you ever bought a chair?
What?
A chair, kursi
have you ever bought one?
Yes
And did you just go into a
shop and buy the first chair you saw?
No
Exactly my point
We look at so many different
chairs until we find the right one
Some chairs may be comfortable
but look like shit...
others look nice but
are hard on the butt...
So the process starts,
chair after chair...
how many chairs we
check out before we find...
that one chair!
It doesn't creak with me
If we look for so many
options just to buy a chair...
then shouldn't we look at options...
when choosing a life partner?
So...dirty cheap fast...no
Smart clear fine...actually superfine!
Wait wait wait
So the women in my
dream who believe that...
marriage is the only
acceptable relationship...
I felt dirty because of them
See? You figured it out yourself...
you don't need anyone's help
But the dangling camera?
What does that mean?
Just like my future,
it's hanging in the air
Maybe you should sit on my chair...
and I should sit here from today
It's so cool
I wish the whole world could
hear about your chair theory
Why is it important for
the whole world to hear this?
No I just...
if they understand this chair theory
they will stop judging others...
and what a beautiful world it will be
No Kaira...
when you understand yourself well...
then what others think
of you doesn't matter
If you don't take charge
of your own life somebody else will
I pity those who don't shop for chairs
Kaira, will you go
back to your chair please?
Looked like you wanted
to take my chair home with you
And speaking of home,
I have homework for you
Homework?
Yes I'm very strict
with my homework assignments
Okay'!
I want you to chat
with your mom and dad
10 minutes with each please
Please, what will I say to them?
Time's up, see you next week
What! We have 20 seconds more
Hey you saw that?
What happened?
20 seconds happened
I don't like this buzzer
Homework Kaira
Hey, those are really
nice looking glasses...
Thanks
You're going to see Jug?
Yup, I have an appointment
Really?
You have problems too?
YUP
I am going to get my cycle repaired
Repairs cycles too?
Hi dad
Hi darling, when will you come home?
I'll come
You will be home before
Kiddo arrives right?
There's enough time for that,
of course I'll be there
Your mom is in high spirits...
full planning for the party
Obviously, her prince is arriving
Those restaurant guys
loved your film...
They said it was very well shot
Oh the hotel video
Close up of Prawn Balchao?
Anyway I'll call later
Okay'!
Bye
4 minutes!
Yes Koko, you called?
Yes, why didn't you pick up
- I was cleaning Kiddo's room...
I didn't have my phone
Okay but I'm busy now,
can't talk bye
Okay'!
Shift that!
'Talk to mom and dad
for 10 minutes'...is he mad!
Beach?
Are we having the session out here?
Why not? Problem?
No, but is it allowed?
Whose permission do I need?
I don't know,
but aren't there some rules?
Like privacy,
closed door, couch and all that?
There are rules
But one should know which
ones to break and which ones to not
Now people will know I am crazy
Who are these people
who keep following you?
Despite the mess, Goa is
the most beautiful place in India
I wish I could agree
Why? You don't like Goa?
I was born here
This is where my parents live,
how can I like it?
Did your homework?
Only half...
I managed to talk
to dad for 5 minutes...
okay 4 minutes,
but that's a record in itself
And your mom?
I tried, but she was busy
So you've only done a quarter
What did you chat with your dad?
About Kiddo, my brother...
he's studying at
the London University...
he's coming home soon, so
my parents are hosting a big party...
for his homecoming
When I got here nobody
even said 'welcome'
So you don't like Kiddo?
No no I love Kiddo, I really do
He's the only one
who can make me smile...
just by being there
When he was little,
I would read him his favorite comic...
you know Tinkle, have you read it?
Yes
Hunter Shambhu,
Kaafia the Crow & Supandi'...
So Supandi! was Kiddo's favourite...
So I would rep/ace Supandis
with Kiddo's name...
and read it to him
He loved hearing the story in my voice
Even today, he says it's
his best childhood memory
And your best childhood memory?
Come on, there must be something...
I don't know
What are your favourite childhood
memories?
My dad used to bring
me here every Sunday...
To play Kabaddi with the sea
Kabaddi with the sea?
Kabaddi kabaddi
Go back!
Just two more
Okay'!
I can do this all day long
It's important that parents create
happy memories for their children
Now I am a parent myself
So I'm hoping...
my son has at least
some happy memories...
to tell his therapist
He stays with his mom
In divorce cases kids
usually end up with the mother
I just regret not being
able to spend enough time with him
I remember Shaira...
my doll
My dad's birthday gift to me
When I used to live with my
grandparents, Shaira was with me
I never played with her,
just kept her close to me
At night,
I would hug her tightly and sleep
You were shy?
Yes
How did you know?
Shaira-Shy... I'm a genius, really
When I was little I was shy...
dad used to call me Kaira-Shaira
But now I'm fully Kaira
Kaira-Shaira, now fully Kaira
Yes
Are you sure?
Come on
Listen tell me...
why did you want me to talk
to Mom and Dad for 10 minutes?
Is there some Chinese
mountain story behind this?
Someday you'll have
to climb Mt. Everest right?
Where is Shaira?
Who Shaira?
My doll!
The one dad gave me
How come you thought
of that doll all of a sudden?
Do you know where she is or not?
She may be in the storeroom...
along with your and Kiddo's old things
What do you mean by maybe?
She must be there somewhere
How will I remember
after all these years?
Do you remember anything
at all about those years?
Taste this Bibik
What is Bibik now?
Bebinca! Kiddo's favourite
No I'm leaving
Pm making coconut laddoos for you...
your favourite...
see I remembered
You just want to make me fat!
Coconut laddoos!
I feel like breaking
a coconut on someone's head
No, no violence, do deep breathing
What memories will
parents leave behind?
When they can't remember
anything themselves?
Let's drink to Shaira, wherever she is
In my street
The moon that appears
That brings Eid with it
is that you?
My mom
Has made me a suit
Has shown me a dream
is it of you?
My heart is destroying
itself for someone
Who is it?
Ifs you
My heart is protecting
itself for someone
Who is it?
Ifs you
Who is that so far away
Who is that so close
Who is that so specie!
Ifs you
The one for whom
I'd break all other hearts
is it you?
The one for whom
Pd go on living
I 'd insure my loving
is it you?
The one who's presence
Makes all come alive
Who is it?
Ifs you
Who is that so far away
Who is that so close
Who is that so specie!
Ifs you
Who is in my verses?
Who is in my poetry?
Who is in my diary?
Ifs you
Hi!
Oh hello...
That was a beautiful song
You have a beautiful voice
You totally rocked it
If your audience is so rocking,
the song has to match up
I'm Jackie, this is Kaira
And you are?
Rumi
Rumi?
Girls night out?
Yes
They are the best nights
Hey, great song bro...
...you killed it!
Did I?
Killed who? We're all alive here
Girls night, don't mind, cheers
What a voice you have,
you should be singing in films
Why only films?
There are all kinds of music...
there is rock, pop, jazz, blues...
do you like blues?
Blues?
You seem more red to me...
What?
Vorresti fuggire con me?
That was Greek to me...
It's Italian actually
Does that mean that I'm
so deadly and gorgeous...
that you can't take your eyes off me?
Not at all
It means that I'm heading to a private
beach with some of my friends...
to play some music
Would you like to run away with me?
Not bad
Somebody seems to be
in a musical mood today
"My heart is destroying itself
for someone, who is it? It's you"
Excuse me?
"Last night! went
out to listen to a band"
“Which band was it,
where did you go where did you go?”
"The name of the band I don't know
I don't know. ..but singer! know"
So tell me more...
tell me more tell me more
We didn't talk, only music
What to tell?
So what was his name? Banjo?
Or the fellow was called Cello?
Rumi
- Wow!
My new kursi, my new chair
So, comfortable?
What?
New chair, comfortable?
Yes but it's a musical chair...
twenty four hours will
have to listen to music...
how to listen?
Why don't you tell him straight,
that you like dialogue too
How can you tell a musician
to stop the music and talk?
He'll think I'm a musical idiot...
have you ever felt like an idiot?
I've sat through a
three hour Italian Opera...
pretended it touched my heart...
when every minute was torture
I wanted to stand up on the chair
and scream even louder than them...
Pm an opera idiot!
Wow, okay
What would you do if you
were dating an opera singer?
I would say, 'Darling,
I will do anything for you...
but don't make me hear the opera'
Then end of story right?
She would dump you and run
Or after 6 months of suffering,
I would run away
If one is going to suffer,
the other person should at least know
What is the point
of suffering in silence?
See when...
I'm so sorry - It's okay
I will get a new one for you
I'll do it, don't touch it...
I think it's safer to have
our sessions outdoor
Go on, Rumi
I like people who smell nice
I hate smelly people
Really? Why'?
So you like smelly people?
Everyone has a different smell...
that's how people get
attracted to each other
Eeks! Who goes around smelling
people to get attracted?
Dogs
Ya dogs!
Ganju, we should record
our conversations...
they're true genius sometimes
Genius!
Yes please
"Genius is not one
who has all the answers...
genius is one who has the
patience to find every answer"
Deep
Which genius said this?
Dr. Jehangir Khan
Khan...khh
So does he smell nice?
Who?
There you go
Wait let it breathe...cheers
Listen to this bit
I love chocolate
Okay this bit
Wait one second
Pink Floyd's first album,
you have to get this
"I agree,
you're the most beautiful of all"
“§ agree,
you find a place in every heart”
You like strawberries?
“Yes you are a dream
your every move is a charm...”
"but, you're not one
to be wooed by praise"
Try some?
Can we just have the music off please!
I'm sorry, I just need some silence
Everything okay'?
I wrote this song for you
But it's okay,
silence is good sometimes...
there is beauty in silence too...
let's be silent
That's not silent
I'm sorry
Okay play your song
No forget my song...
let's talk about you
I want to know everything about you
Come, sit
Tell me about you
What was your first film about?
When did you decide
to be a camerawoman?
What's your journey?
You know, I haven't even
shot a selfie in my life
Isn't that funny?
So tell me...
I want to know about your dreams,
your inspirations, your aspirations...
I want to know everything about you
Huh?
What's going on?
Shall I put on some music?
Please
I've heard enough for a lifetime
So still suffering silently?
Or did you say it?
I yelled it
So he ran away?
No, he was very sweet actually
He stopped playing the song,
which he had composed for me...
and began asking about me
I felt guilty at first but...
Why are romantic
relationships so irritating?
With friends,
it's all so easy, it just flows...
you don't need to make such an effort
Who are the 5 people closest to you?
Your top 5?
Why?
There is an important study...
based on the size
of the human brain...
that shows that everyone has about
150 people in their whole universe
The next cut is the 50 who
you would invite home for dinner...
then 15 who you turn to
in times of need for comfort...
and the final cut is of 5
people who are your whole world...
your inner circle
Who are your 5?
Fatty, Kiddo, Jackie, Alka...
Raghuvendra, no
And I forgot to add...
these 5 people can
also change with time
That's true but these 4
people will always be on the list
Okay, so think of these 4 and tell me
How do you feel when
you are with them...
as compared to the changing 5th?
How, how do these
4 people make you feel?
Special, I feel special I feel...
important, I feel respected...
I feel happy and safe
So you don't feel safe
with your boyfriends?
No...
I feel safe but...
I don't know it's not that
With my friends...
I feel free, I feel like myself
Why safe?
When you start liking a guy...
What is your fear Kaira?
It's back in one piece
I believe broken things
can be put back together
How is the 'Brain Doctor' going?
Is he married or single?
Didi...
Hi Alka!
Look there
Didi...
how are you?
Rubbish
Why did you go to the doctor?
Are you okay?
I went to a 'Brain Doctor'
What happened to your brain?
Nothing, if you have an
emotional problem in your life...
a 'Brain Doctor' can help you solve it
Do such doctors exist?
Then everyone should go to them
Yes everyone should
I agree,
you're the most beautiful of all
§ agree, you find
a place in every heart
Yes, you're a dream,
your every move a charm
But, you're not one
to be wooed by praise...
Don't stop!
Come on, play the music
Heart...be silent
Don? beat so loud
Let her not see
you suffer
You will smile now at my state
But, you're not one
to be wooed by praise
Should I whisper in your ears
Or scream from mountain tops
It was good fun
We danced to Honey Singh
songs all night
What's happening?
Fatty!
I called you, why didn't you answer?
Hi Koks
Why are you both grinning like that?
Jackie is just telling
me about her new boyfriend
What?
Hello?
What new boyfriend?
How about telling me...
I'm right here, am I invisible?
You didn't even ask
Why do I have to ask?
Okay guys relax
How can you not tell me?
I know why, because it's
that weird guy at the bar right'?
See this is what you do
You're always judging my men
I'm not judging,
you called him weird yourself
That was then, now I like him
But you didn't tell
me that you like him
Because you never asked,
you're not around
How am I supposed to
know if you don't tell me?
You keep doing this
and blame me for everything
I am around!
Fatty where are you?
Great you also leave me
Good morning!
Good morning Jackie Chan
Anything special today?
Yes
Yo u
You're so special
Okay, I'm special
So you fix cycles too'?
I try
And if I can't fix them,
I recycle them
Recycle a cycle?
Kaira, you have to
crack better jokes please
So all that cycle
art in your room and...
Hey, hi by the way!
This boy was wearing those funky
looking glasses, you made all that?
Finally! You noticed
He's an artist
If you can't fix people
do you recycle them too'?
Bye Jug
Sorry about it
That's so mean
Yeah that's so mean, let's go
Why cycle today?
Just breaking the pattern
Yes, should break it
You must be going insane
listening to crazy people like me...
all day inside one room
Quite possible
Albert Einstein once said...
"An insane person is one who does
the same thing over and over again...
and expects different
results each time"
By the way, Rumi, it's over...
Why?
Can't do it...
it's too much
He doesn't fit in my...
I don't know...
I can't handle it it's too much
What's too much?
Too much
Wait wait, Lance Armstrong
Did Rumi do something wrong?
No we were just wrong
for each other...
Not this chair
Shiver! Only happens
when we feel cold...
or have a fever, or due to weather...
or sometimes people shiver
when they are scared...
I just want to be free...
free from all this
I also want you to be free...
free from your fears
Free!
Oh wow
Help me
Damn, our time's up
What?
Got to go! Sorry
Jug!
Get my glasses please
My darling boy, all good?
Yes all good
Kiddo! Spend some time with me now,
not fair...
Sorry, I was getting ready...
you know it's my party,
I have to look nice
You look nice
So are you part of this matchmaking?
Me?
Yes you
I have no clue but
I want to see the fun
Sweet boy Kiddo
And you,
is your best friend Jackie here?
Is she still single or...
Yes, she's still very
much single and so is Kaira
Please stop, it's starting to hurt
Kaira, come
I want to introduce
you to a young man
This is my niece, Kaira
Hi Kaira, Suresh
Suresh
Pleasure
Well I'll see you'll later then
Alright, cheers
Cheers
So you're a photographer right?
Cinematographer actually
One and the same thing
No, it's not the same thing
It's not?
- No
Okay'!
What do you do?
I'm a techie...
does that sound boring?
Fun
It's fun, then cheers
So, why should I be interested in you?
That was pretty direct right?
I can be interesting
if I meet an interesting girl...
it depends
Okay'!
See Kiddo, your favourite food
Thank you
What a sweet child Kiddo was,
never used to cry
Never left my side, always 'Mama Mama'
Well I figured 'Mama Mama'...
was a better way to get
what I wanted than to cry
How fast these kids grow up
I know
Look at Kiddo, he has achieved
so much at a young age
He has got a scholarship
for a higher degree...
then an internship with a big firm...
tell them the name
of the company, Kiddo
Dad, just stop it now
You will definitely be successful
You are doing the correct thing
You're not eating anything...
are you dieting again?
I don't feel like
Eat something
Fine, give it to me
Here have this
You remember Chanda,
Kiddo was such a gentle, quiet boy...
but Kaira, a real firecracker...
she's still the same
Firecracker yes,
you're absolutely right...
anger, tantrums and sulking,
most of all with me
You kids have no idea how
tough it is to be a parent...
and it's never ending
Once a parent always a parent
I agree
No holiday from this job, right Ashu?
All parents should be awarded
a President's Award
Huh?
I love the food
So end it then
Just end it
What?
The job of being a parent, just end it
You keep going on and on about
how 'tough' it is, so just end it
Who has forced you
to continue being parents?
Has anyone forced you to?
You didn't start the job well in
the first place so why continue it...
just put an end to it!
When kids need you the most
you happily leave them and go
and then complain
about their tantrums...
'Oh how angry she gets, makes faces'
It was your idea to
bring us into the world...
you treated us the way you wanted...
and then you blame
us for how we behave...
and you say it's 'tough'...
What do you mean by 'tough?
Tough my foot!
How could you just abandon me?
How could you just do that?
How could you both leave me and go?
And the only reason you took me back
was because I failed the 2nd grade...
yes, I failed the 2nd grade!
Shame Shame!
Dumb Kaira failed the second grade!
Such an embarrassment for you...
that you left everything
and came back to India?
And when I was finally happy
living with my grandparents,
you dragged me away from there too
You separated me even from them
Yes
President's Award just for that!
And I have a fire cracking
news for you!
Actually a bomb!
Are you ready?
I have begun therapy!
Yes! I am seeing a 'Brain Doctor'
So feel free to call me crazy, mad
Please say it to me
right now say it to my face
Say it!
I'm crazy! 'Kukoooo
'Kaira's gone mad!'
That's what you think...
that people like me are crazy
She is a bit emotional right now...
she is also out of work
Dad, she has enough work
She has chosen not to work right now
Kiddo, go get her
Don't worry
Make her understand that...
once your parents moved back,
she never failed in school again...
so they took the right decision
There are all kinds of failures...
and I am looking at a few right now
You okay?
I don't know
Were you happy as a child?
I only remember being
happy once you came home
See this
Where did you find that?
I was looking for
something from my past...
and found something from ours instead
You know...
As children, when we are sad,
our elders tell us not to cry
When we are angry,
they tell us 'give us a smile'
You know why?
Just to keep the peace at home
When we wanted to hate
they didn't allow us...
so now when we want to love...
we suddenly find our whole
emotional system is topsy-turvy...
it cannot function
Sadness, anger, hate...
we were not allowed
to express anything...
so now, how do we express love'?
It's okay to be angry sometimes,
even with parents...
It's good, it's healthy...
it's okay Kaira...
They left me at my grandparents' house
Mom told me this was like a vacation,
that I would join them soon
Dad's export business
in Goa had failed...
so he went to Africa, Middle East
looking for business opportunities...
mom went with him
In the beginning I was happy
staying with my grandparents...
in their big old house in Vasco
I would write a letter
to mom and dad every week...
sometimes even twice a week
At that age, 'writing'
meant drawing some pictures...
trying to write some big words...
but every letter ended
with the same question...
'When will you come back?'
I was 5 years old...
every week I would drop my letters
in the mailbox with my grandad...
then I would wait for a letter
wait for an answer to my question...
but it never came
When they called once a month,
they had some excuse each time...
something about 'an address change, no
post office close by, feeling unwell' etc etc
but I still kept writing
And my grandad would keep
walking me to the mailbox...
he always said that I will
get my answer some day soon
Then, a year later
mom visited me in Goa...
with my new baby brother, Kiddo
I was jealous
Because he got to be with
mom all the time, and not me
then mom said that I would be away
from them for 'just a little longer'
so I was still fine with it...
I remember asking my
mom if she got my last letter
she said that it was so beautiful that
she put it up on the refrigerator...
so that she could see it every day
I was so happy...
I ran to my room so I could
write another letter for her...
so I could see her get
happy in front of my own eyes
A scene I had imagined
in my head many times
So I took out my colours and paints...
drew a picture and
ran to show it to her
As I was about to enter the room I
heard my grandad shouting at my mom...
he was telling her that what
she was doing was not right...
how could she not respond
to my question, to my letters...
and then, I heard my mom reply...
"I can't give her false hope...
the truth is that we can't
take her back just yet...
not until the business is set up...
It is too tough to
handle two children...
and travel constantly blah blah
But everything just seemed to...
fade away...
It was a strange feeling...
like someone had grabbed
the TV remote from me...
and changed the channel from something
I loved to something horrid...
and then threw out the remote
I went back to my room,
tore up the letter...
l was 6...
took a decision as a 6 year old...
that I had nothing more to
say to them, nothing more to ask...
I didn't write a letter
ever again in my entire life
Never
My poor grandad kept
trying to get me to write...
but I knew I had nothing
to say to my parents...
or to anyone else...
I just became quiet
I shut down
Then a year later my mom said
that they were coming back for good...
dad's friend had a business
partnership for him in Goa itself
In all these years, dad couldn't
set up his business abroad
So imagine, all this for nothing
So they came back
But that year was the
most stressful for me...
I didn't want to be with them
I wanted to stay with my grandparents
They were separating me from them too
I threw tantrums...
cried a lot, troubled everyone
To top it all,
I failed the 2nd grade...
and that, not my 100 letters...
not the fact that I was their
daughter living away from them
But my failure made them
take me away from my grandparents...
and back with them finally
I'm sorry
If you don't cry wholeheartedly,
how will you laugh wholeheartedly?
It's okay...
I'm not much for rules...
but because of the rules...
I can't pop a champagne
bottle to celebrate this moment...
but we can do the next best thing
To letters, Kaira
Cheers!
Go easy...
To feel safe,
first the fears have to go
The fear of being abandoned,
of being left alone...
You have carried this
fear with you all your life...
this burden is falling on all your
relationships, especially on your love life
So you leave others
before they can leave you
You want to say bye
before they can say bye
Because you never want
to face that pain again
So, Kaira
Why not say bye to
this fear once and for all?
Why not say hi to life once again?
I am not saying that you
should forgive your parents...
or even to stop being angry...
you do as you wish
But I will say this...
try to look at them not in
the exalted status of parents...
but just as two regular people...
who make mistakes, like everyone else
As a child it is hard
to understand all this...
but now, as an adult...
you can at least try
Don't let the past blackmail your
present to ruin a beautiful future
When something touches your heart
Say hi to it...
When your heart is not in it
Say bye to it...
Let it come, let it come
Let it come into your heart
Say hi to happiness
Let it go, let it go
Let it go from your heart
Say bye bye to unhappiness...
Love you life
Love me life
Koko, I'm sorry
I'm sorry
Hello?
Hi Ma'am, I am calling from eBay,
are you happy with our services?
Yes why?
Please do continue shopping with us
Thank you
Sometimes hold my hand,
and walk with me
Sometimes leave my hand,
and let me go free
I 'm a little moody
You're a little crazy
What a pair we are
Let it come, let it come
Let it come into your heart
Say hi to happiness...
Let it go, let it go
Let it go from your heart
Say bye bye to unhappiness...
Love you life
Love me life
You are different...
you listen to me, you really listen
I wish I had someone
like you in my life...
Am I making sense?
Not at all,
but that will be 3000 rupees please
Where were you?
Just disappeared
I have to give proper
notice if I miss a session...
and you left me with one small note
'Sorry'... that's not fair
I know, life is unfair
Fine
Hide all your secrets
You know...
my issues with my
parents may get sorted...
but with men!
I am never going to find anyone
Tell me something
ls there such a thing
as a perfect relationship?
Like just one special relationship?
Kaira I think...
why just that one
special relationship?
I think one can have
many relationships in life...
different relationships
for different experiences...
like a musical relationship...
someone who shares
our interest in music...
or the lets-get-coffee-together
relationship...
perfect to have coffee with...
but not anything else...
Special gossip relationship...
with whom you can
have the perfect gossip
Or the special
intellectual relationship...
for all those perfect
bookish discussions...
So many different,
special relationships...
The romantic relationship
is just one of many
To expect a single relationship
to take on the burden of every need...
a bit unfair, right?
Never thought of it this way
I'm glad the camera is back
Me too
Jug, do you want to get
a cup of coffee or something?
No, our time's up
You won't bunk the next session right'?
It is the last week of our sessions...
how can I miss that?
So, done sulking with Goa?
No more sulking
What about your work?
Actually I got an offer
What?
A production company is interested
in funding my short film...
so I am thinking,
why not stay back here and shoot it
Since it's the final class,
have I passed?
This isn't school, to pass or fail
I wish there were teachers
like you in school
I'm no teacher
Okay not teacher but...
you know what I mean
We are all our own teachers
in the school of life
Okay, that got a bit heavy
Life is like a jigsaw puzzle
People like me can help
you find the missing pieces...
and put them back together...
but, only you can complete the puzzle
So now that this is over...
can we meet outside of this...
just as friends or something?
No this is not possible Kaira
And what if I tell you...
that I like you...
In fact...
Go on, I'm listening
In fact I really like you
That's it, said it
I really like you too
I really like you
I respect your feelings...
but my job here is done for now
As unconventional and friendly
as my methods may be...
I am still your therapist...
any other 'friendship' would be outside
the realm of my own professional ethics
The closeness that you may feel to me,
your 'BD'...
is very normal
This happens, it's common
So I'm common?
No, you are not common
You are different, special...
you are unique
You know Kaira
People feel all sorts
of strong emotions in here...
anger, hate, love
I shouldn't have said anything
No, you should have
It's really good
you said what you said
You expressed your
difficult feelings...
in a straightforward
and mature manner...
rather than letting them fester...
inside of you...
and we don't want that...
No
This Kaira, is huge progress
Okay but, tell me one thing
How can this be the last session?
No no...
No more stories?
So many new problems I will have...
Yes there will be many problems...
but now you know how to solve them
But I'll need help
I need you
Kaira...
when you see a pattern
emerging in life...
a habit,
then it's time to think about it
Genius is about knowing when to stop
Okay then
Baby Fatima, can't believe it
This is your godmother, Kokomaa
Battle after battle
Corporal Balthazar fought
in the Portuguese army for 14 years
Nobody knew that Corporal
Balthazar was not Balthazar...
but Dona Maria, a woman...
disguised as a man
This was the only way for a woman
to safeguard her life and dignity
For 14 years Dona Maria
fought two battles...
one on the battlefield,
and the other with herself...
with her fears
Finally, one day on the battlefield,
her true identity was revealed
As fate would have it...
in front of Captain Aphonso...
Captain Aphonso...
Commander of the fort and a doctor...
not only saved Dona Maria's life...
and nursed her wounds...
but made her fears disappear...
and freed her from the
ghost of Corporal Balthazar
For the first time...
Dona Maria had the courage
to face her true self
Finally she felt free, she felt alive
With her new found courage,
Dona Maria soon became Commander...
the first woman Commander
of the Portuguese army...
Now, Donna Maria fought
only one battle...
the one on the battlefield
Speech! Speech!
No speech, just shut up!
It was beautiful my darling
So proud of you
Beautiful film
Really?
Very impressed
People who make music with
the camera don't need musicians
I wrote a song for you,
want to listen?
Just kidding
I'm proud of you
You gave Kaira her first break right?
Yes
She could not have
done this without you
Actually if I was with her,
she couldn't have done this
Cheers!
To the longest project
of this century!
Cheers to my baby
Hi!
I was wondering...
Yes please tell me,
what were you wondering?
Would you be able to
live as a man for a few years?
Huh?
It's a really interesting concept,
your story
How did you come up with the idea?
What's your story?
Do you make films too?
No, I make furniture...
tables, sofas, chairs
Chairs?
Like Kursi chairs?
Chairs like Kursi
Kursi like chairs
Dear life,
I know we haven't been
in touch for a while...
So nothing
Just wanted to say hi
Kabaddi kabaddi. ..