Priya, listen to me.
- Just let go of me, okay?
Priya, listen to me.. - You always
do this, it's always other women.
I didn't mean to hurt you. Come on!
- You always just..
Every time, you say the same thing.
- You know how much I love you.
Please, listen to me.
I love you.
I love you so much.
Cut! Great shot!
Make-up, please!
- Get me some water.
Kaira, good for you?
Guys, we'll do one more.
We got this shot, right?
We are running out of time. We don't
have permission for the whole day.
Kaira has a nice idea, we'll do one more.
What's the point of finishing on time
if we don't get a good shot?
Look, no respect for producers.
Especially these new cameramen..
Sorry! I mean, women.
Come on, hurry up, let's do this!
Fatima, we are going to change the guy.
So, can you.. - Yes! Okay..
You want that guy? Darwin! Come here.
- Yeah. You have to do the look.
One second.
- He has to look more handsome.
Just turn around.
Pull your pants up, please, and go there.
Hand me the camera.
- Action!
Please.. - You always do this,
it's always other women.
I'm tired. - I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
I love you.
I love you so much, please!
Cut!
Got that?
- Fantastic!
Superb execution!
Good shot. - I shot it at 48 frames,
speed up the end if you like.
I'm going to take a plate
of the building now.
Did you see the shot, Raghuvendra?
That one expression of the girl
checking out the passing guy says so much.
I wish I had met Kaira earlier,
I would have shot the whole film with her.
I got that.
- It's a wrap, guys! Thank you!
Thank you, Nilin.
Thank you.
I told you,
you don't have to carry my bag. - Hey!
I'm so sorry.
Your mom called again on my cell phone.
You never pick up yours.
Please call her back before you take off.
- Yeah, I will..
You enjoy your mini-holiday.
You could have enjoyed Singapore with us
but you wanted to fly
with someone else. - Shut up!
Go, go!
I tried to upgrade you, couldn't do it.
Please!
Hi, guys. What can I get for you?
Beer.
- Soft drink.
Okay.
- Just soft drink?
I drink only on two occasions,
when I am in love and when I am not.
Okay.
Cheers!
Kaira.. Is everything okay?
As in, we're good, right?
What are you talking about?
What happened to us?
Cheers!
- Cheers!
Raghuvendra, I want to shoot
an entire feature film.
Enough of this patchwork.
I mean, I can't keep waiting
for other cameramen to fall ill.
No one will even know
that I've shot this scene.
I want to shoot my own film.
You will. Who wouldn't want to work
with a beautiful DOP like you?
Beautiful! Is that my only talent,
seriously? - Seriously.
Don't talk to me.
- Of course, you're talented.
You shoot so many ads, you earn
good money. - Ads and all are fine.
I want to shoot a film.
You will.. Soon!
And you're so young, I mean..
The only reason you wear glasses
is to look older.
Excuse me!
If actresses can be at their peak
at a young age then why not technicians?
Tell me.
- Have you heard of the word Patience?
No, I haven't.
Tell me about Patience.
Pick up.. Pick up the cook's call.
If you want I can
just go and come back.. - Okay.
Firstly, he is not a cook,
he is the owner of a restaurant.
Not even a cook?
Tell me something.
That shot was your idea, right?
Girl with guy, checking out other guy..
Inspired from life?
Passengers flying on SQ-422 to Mumbai..
Great!
- Listen, Kaira..
You take my seat, I'll sit on yours.
I can sit in Economy class,
you need not sacrifice.
Besides, your long legs
won't fit in there, anyway.
That is true.
- It is very true.
Yes, Mom. It was good.
Okay, sorry. I can't talk now,
the plane is going to take off. Bye..
There you go.
- Thank you.
So.. Can I come up?
I'm really tired.
- Dinner?
I'm busy tonight, but I'll see you.
See you!
- See you..
Alka!
- Ma'am..
You've put on so much weight.
Oh, stop it, ma'am.
How was your shoot?
- Rubbish!
Rubbish?
Ma'am, you..
Ma'am.
- Yes.
Your mother called three times.
You are so sweet, Alka.
- Thank you!
Do you want coffee
or shall I serve breakfast?
Later.
Ma'am..
Ma'am.
This guy is so cute.
Was!
- What?
He was cute.
I don't find him cute anymore.
Actually, remove his photo.
Just take it out.
Ma'am..
I had just put it all in perfect order.
Now it's perfect.
I love you.
And you must try our chef's special today.
I'm sure, you'll love it. - Thank you.
Danish.
- Yes, sir.
Danish, take good care of our guests.
And make sure they try our new wines.
Sure, sir. Just a moment..
- Have a good evening.
Enjoy yourself. All right?
- Same to you. Bye.
So then, how was your trip?
It was good.
Just good?
Okay, great.
You look beautiful, sweetheart.
Sid.
Hey, Tom!
- Hey, Sid.
How are you, buddy?
- Good. What's up?
Good to see you.
- Good to see you too.
How was the vacation?
- It was great. Fantastic!
London, right?
- Exactly. Yes.
Excellent. Your table is ready.
- Thank you.
I'm sorry, I was..
- No, it's okay.
Go ahead, meet them.
I have to use the restroom, anyway.
Just..
Table for four, please.
- I'm sorry, guys.
We have a strict dress code.
No shorts and slippers, please.
Come on, it's his birthday.
- I'm sorry, I wish I could.
It's my birthday. Come on, do something.
- But she's wearing shorts!
It's okay for girls. I'm sorry, guys.
- What is this.. Come on..
We really want to party, please.
- Do something..
Please..
Do something. Allow us.
- Please..
Okay, sure. Please.
- Oh, wow! Thanks!
Guys, I'm really hungry.
- Just this once, only for you.
Next time, I'll come along
on a shoot with you, as your caterer.
What do you say?
Hey..
I slept with Raghuvendra.
I should go. I should go..
Sid.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
What are you doing!
Stop! It's all good!
All good!
What are you doing?
Hey, look, Sid!
- Sid! Where?
That's not Sid, Jackie.
- No?
Oh! He looked so much like him!
Cute!
Poor thing! Nice guy he was!
Yeah, really nice!
Little too nice for you, right?
Okay. Let's go.
Oh, my God! This jacket!
It reminds me of school,
our Famous Five gang.
Was that the 8th or 9th grade?
Tenth grade. It's the same one.
See, I can have
a long-term relationship too.
Yes, with things.
So, are we things too?
Yes, you are a thing.
You're the most beautiful..
Oh, sorry!
Have you gone blind in love?
Am I invisible? - We said sorry.
Why is she yelling..
- Relax..
Staring into her eyes!
- They are a couple.
Oh, you're so cute!
So sweet! I love you..
The same rubbish! It's irritating.
- Hey! What are you doing?
To heck with them.
Stupid!
- Sorry.
I hate couples!
She's here..
- Pose!
Are you guys here to help me
or to do a comedy show?
Both. - Guys, I have a deadline. I have
to show the costumes to the director.
Fine. Look..
- Okay.
Raunak, do you need help?
- Okay, guys. Listen.
I've to go, I have my B-D appointment.
- What's this B-D?
Brain Doctor, my therapist.
Oh, B-D..
Raunak, you're still going to that B-D?
I have to. - Brain Doctor?
Why are you seeing a therapist?
Are you mad?
- Who isn't? Look at him.
Roll..
- Clap!
Trolley. Action!
Chocolaty!
- That's a cut. Nice!
Good for you, Kaira?
- Yes, good for me.
Okay, guys. Ten minutes' break.
Rubbish! I can direct better than this.
Tell me something..
Why did you start seeing your therapist?
So that you could tell everyone
that you're gay?
No.
So that I could tell myself that I'm gay.
When is your flight to Goa?
Don't remind me! I can't believe
I'm going to Goa. Seriously!
Seriously, you're the first human being
who's saying this so sadly.
Really!
- That's true.
It's Goa! Enjoy.
- Shut up.
And yes, it is sad.
Because I'm going on duty.
Every 2-3 months, I have to go.
Oh! Is it Raghu?
- It's duty!
Yes, Mom. I'm coming tomorrow.
What's with this food, every time!
Cook what you like, don't ask me.
Because I'm busy.
Mothers!
Standard question, every time..
What will you eat?
What should I make?
Either she isn't my real mother
or she's got Alzheimer's. - Kaira!
At least eat my food.
Only way to handle the torture..
I think, this time, I'll work
on my short film. - Short film!
Sorry.
- The longest project of this century.
That's so mean.
- It's true.
Okay. How do you like my French food?
Why is the landlord calling?
- I don't know about French food
but this dip is amazing!
Really?
- Full Indian spice, try it.
The dip is from Kaira's fridge. I've made
the puff pastries. - It looks quite nice.
Smile.
- Jackie, at last you made something.
What do you mean, at last?
You people from the film industry think
that only you do important work
and the rest of us are useless!
- Good point.
I have decided to work on myself.
- That's tough work.
Do it..
- Do it!
Hey, what..
- What's wrong with you?
I'm not going to Goa! Guess what!
Your friend, Raghu, called
and I have to shoot a music video here,
in three days!
We've to shoot a music video
in three days. Now, get ready! - Okay.
Come on, dance with me.
- I have never seen anybody so excited
upon not going to Goa.
- "No Goa!"
"No Goa! No Goa! No Goa!"
What happened to her?
It's not because of my food.
Okay, everybody, just get away
from the table. - It's not my food!
This food is contaminated.
Hey, Fatima. You're good? Yes?
- Kaira.
Guess what!
- What's up?
I am pregnant!
- What!
It wasn't Jackie's food.
Oh, my God, Fatty!
Congratulations!
I mean, we're supposed to be
happy, right? - I don't know..
I want to throw up right now.
I swear, I do.
- Fatty..
Hello.
- Hi.
Should I go?
- Yes, please.
Okay! - No! - No, I'm just kidding.
I'm just very excited.
Are you pregnant too?
- What..
So, I was working on a co-production
with this New York film company
and it has come through.
- That's amazing! Congratulations!
Thank you. - Wow, you are going
to be shooting a feature in the US?
Yes. Superb!
- Tell me more. Good script?
Are you going to be filming in New York?
You are going to be filming in New York.
As in, we are going
to be filming in New York.
If you're not available,
we'll get another camera person..
Oh, my God!
I will kill you!
Told you, not going to Goa is lucky.
Lucky for you, unlucky for me.
I want to kill my husband..
You're sure, right?
It's not because
you think I'm attractive, right?
Obviously.. You thought,
it's because you're talented?
You are so crazy!
Why are you so complicated?
You're the best, that's why
you got the job. Simple!
Thank you. Seriously!
Thank you.
All right.
- Brilliant.
Kanju, what is happening
with the haze machine over there?
Great boys.
More energy! Come on, guys.
"I don't know..
I don't know how to hide it!"
Okay, let's go for a take, guys.
And, music!
One, two, three, four..
"So, let's break up.
Oh, my darling!"
"Let's break up.
Oh, please agree to it!"
"You and I will never work out.
Oh, let it go!"
"So, let's break up!"
"Oh, my darling!"
"Let's break up!"
"Oh, please agree to it."
"You and I will never work out.
Oh, let it go!"
One, two, three, four!
"When I see"
"a beautiful girl"
"I get so excited!"
"Basically.."
"Basically, I'm a rascal!"
Cut!
- Got it.
It's a wrap!
Cheers!
Good.. Wow, congratulations!
- Thank you!
You will really be fat now!
Cute guy!
So many men in your life.
- Shut up!
You will get to spend time
with Raghu also
when you are in New York,
shooting for three months.
Hello, ladies, and one gentleman.
- Hi, Raghu!
Excuse me!
- Oh, sorry! Two gentlemen.
Can I steal Kaira for a minute?
Just for a minute, please! - No..
Thief! Even we want to hear.
- What?
Even we want to hear!
What? I can't hear anything.
- Even we want to hear!
One whisky on the rocks, please.
Yes. - So..
- Okay, pose.
Nice one!
- He's photo bombing again!
So, I'm off to New York tonight.
What?
- Yes.
The financiers want to meet urgently.
Someone has to fly so that you can.
Okay, go. Fly!
Have a nice flight.
That's it?
Have a nice flight?
What else should I say?
Say something.
You pulled me here, you say something.
Firstly, stop looking so attractive.
Tie your hair up.
And behave yourself, just for two weeks.
Here you go. Are you happy now?
Very happy.
- How do I look?
Lovely!
So, I had to talk to you
about something..
Hi..
Do you want to hit the dance floor?
Hello, mister.
- Hey..
We're just in the middle
of a conversation. - Sorry..
Yes..
- Okay!
Anyway, you were saying..
I was saying that..
Gautami..
- Who?
Gautami Sharma will be
the line producer of the film.
Okay. So?
The financiers have recommended her.
They think, she is the best person
for this job.
What are you trying to say?
- So..
Gautami and I, many years ago
were in a relationship.
Okay, it's a reunion!
That's amazing.
Okay, enjoy.
- Reunion, my foot!
It's going to be a really
awkward situation.
I-I mean, she was such a weird one!
I don't even feel like seeing her.
I just want the job to go smoothly,
that's it!
And I thought you should know.
- Yes.
Cool! Whatever..
What do you mean? Come here..
I have someone else
on my mind for a while now.
Look, I think it's..
It's time that we got serious
about each other.
I think it's time that you go.
Do you want to miss your flight?
Kaira, I'm serious. I'm not joking.
We really should..
Sir, we have a flight to catch..
- Yes..
Sir, it's late.
- Yes. Okay..
Go!
It's okay, go on.
It's fine.
- Really?
You don't have anything else to say?
No, that's it for now.
See you, bye.
Way to go!
What did I miss?
- Shots!
Shots! Shots!
"So, let's break up."
"Oh, my darling."
"Let's break up!"
"Oh, please agree to it."
"Things will never work out
between you and me. Oh, let it go!"
"When I see"
"a beautiful girl"
"I get so excited!"
"Basically.."
"Basically, I'm a rascal!"
"But you're no less, baby."
"Somedays, you're nice"
"and somedays, you're not."
"Basically.."
"Basically, you're a witch too!"
"So, let's break up."
"Oh, my darling!"
"Let's break up!"
"Oh, please agree to it."
"You and I will never work out.
Oh, let it go!"
"So, let's break up."
"Oh, my darling!"
"Let's break up!"
"Oh, please agree to it."
Koko, why don't you think
seriously about Raghuvendra?
He is the right guy for you.
This is why some people should not drink.
Why should she think about Raghuvendra?
Is he the last man in the world?
- Why shouldn't she consider him?
I will tell you point by point
why Raghuvendra
is the perfect guy for Koko. Okay?
Point number 1..
And this is the most important
point in the world, okay? - Tell, Jackie.
He is good looking. Come on!
Hardly two percent of people in the world
look good.
And if you have to spend
your life with somebody
you should at least see
a handsome face every morning.
Point number 2..
He has a great sense of humor.
More laughter means more intimacy!
Where are you getting
this information from? - Intimacy..
Point number 3..
He understands your profession, your job.
If you marry a software engineer
or a farmer
what will you discuss at dinner?
Virus or cow dung?
Excuse me!
My husband is a software engineer.
And we have many interesting discussions.
Okay? - Like what?
Like a lot of things!
- Like what?
And I'm sure, farmers are interesting too.
They can tell us about organic vegetables.
They can tell you how to milk a cow.
Go, marry a farmer.
Ganju, tell them that I'm right.
Yes, please give us
your male point-of-view.
Guys, just shut up!
This is all pointless
because he's going to meet
his ex-girlfriend
in New York.
So, just shut up!
Ex-girlfriend!
That's just great!
She is gone, that's in the past.
- Just punch her!
No, the important question here is..
Move your leg.
Are you his present? Now..
William Faulkner once said..
The past is never dead.
In fact, it's not even the past.
What?
- Did your therapist teach you that?
Hey, I want to go
to this therapist of his.
Raguu!
Okay, take it.
No, I don't need it.
Stop acting pricey!
I know, you like Raguu.
No, I don't.
Take it, keep it.
It's so tasty! So delicious!
Yuck, Jackie, so cheap!
I love the taste of Raguu.
Have you gone mad?
Limited offer, grab it now!
- Yes.
You've gone mad.
Pasta!
I shouldn't be so desperate.
I should wait for him to call.
Here is some water.
Ma'am, new photo?
Yes. It's nice, isn't it?
Eat quickly, or it will get cold.
Raguu! Raguu..
Just crush the blacks.
More. More.. More!
See..
- Yes!
More..
More.
Right here?
- Yes.
Yes, okay. Let's play.
Much better! See.. Much better.
- Yes..
It's looking nice.
- Yes, much better.
Okay. Now, pause and zoom in.
Darn! Ganju!
I told you to remind me at 3 p.m.
I had to take Fatima to the doctor.
Fatty! I'm so sorry..
I'm just leaving.
No, you wait. I'm coming there,
to eat Vada Pav at the canteen.
My doctor's appointment got cancelled.
This landlord..
Hello.
What!
You are not going to believe this.
Being single is now a crime!
- What?
My landlord is kicking me out
of my apartment! - What!
I'm going to join the ranks
of homeless in Mumbai.
And you want to know why?
Did I damage the apartment?
No!
Did I forget to pay rent?
The building committee
just got together and decided
that only married couples
and families can live there.
I mean, is that even legal?
- Oh, my God. This just happened?
Yes, he just called!
I had been avoiding his calls
all these days.
Fatty, I have to vacate the house
by the end of the month.
I don't know what to do!
- These people are unbelievable!
Mumbai, India's most modern,
cosmopolitan city.
Seriously!
Listen, I hope you know
that you can stay with me.
Yes, that's not the point.
In a way, thank God..
Thank God I'm leaving this city
and this country for this project.
But seriously, what thinking!
No marriage means no home for women?
I mean..
Why don't they make a law
that no one can stay
with in-laws after marriage?
Forget it.
So, when is the New York shoot?
I don't know.
I think I will know
the exact dates in a month
when the man returns.
The man has not called?
Raghuvendra has not called?
No.
- Okay.
What okay?
What?
Why do you look so suspicious?
Fatty? Tell me.
He got engaged.
- What?
I'm sorry, who got engaged?
Raghuvendra.
When?
Last week.
Last week?
He was just here,
I mean, he just left.. - I know..
Who told you? How do you know?
- Ajay, that guy from production..
Just one second.
Not even a message..
Who told you?
Ajay, from production,
he went to New York with Raghuvendra.
He got engaged?
I don't believe this! To whom?
- Koko..
Please, one second. How can he?
God! This is just getting worse.
How could he..
Are you okay?
- It's just the chili.
You want to know to whom?
No.
Okay, playback.
- Yes.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Sorry, it slipped.
"Where do I go from here?"
"Where do I hide?"
"How do I put my heart into something
when it is broken?"
"I've parted from myself."
"I'm separated from myself."
"How do I settle my broken heart?"
"Oh, my hurting heart!"
"Oh, my lying heart."
"Oh, my broken heart."
"What's your problem?"
"To heck with you, my heart!"
I don't believe this.
I'm going back to Goa.
Back to square one!
It's just for one month
then, the New York shoot will start.
Won't it?
- I don't know..
Personal and professional lives..
Always keep them separate.
You always say this.
When will you ever use this?
You buy such strange things.
Oh, gosh! I have to live
with my parents for a month.
How am I going to do it?
Stay with me in my house.
I'm also going to be in Goa.
We'll do Yoga together.
Do Yoga in your fancy holiday house.
I wish my parents
would buy me a villa in Goa.
Guess what?
When I reach Goa, I have to do
a beautiful shoot for my dad. - What?
Has he also joined the film business?
No, Jackie..
He wants me to shoot a promotional video
for his friend's restaurant.
But who knows? This could be
the turning point in my life.
"Is it my fault"
"or your own mistake?"
"Shamed heart"
"please tell me"
"what do we gain now"
"or what do we lose?"
"Shamed heart"
"crying over it will be worthless."
"Oh, my hurting heart!"
"Oh, my lying heart!"
"Oh, my broken heart!"
"What's your problem?"
"To heck with you, my heart!"
So, Koko..
Have you met Salman Khan yet?
Oh, my God, Sallu!
Is he as handsome in real life?
Does he actually have
those perfect set of abs?
Or is that just how it looks on screen?
Tell me, Koko, I'm dying to know!
First of all, I haven't met him.
And if I ever meet him,
I'm not going to tell him
Take off your shirt.
I want to see your perfect abs!
Exactly..
Forget about that.
Tell us about your ad with Dhoni.
One second, Dad.
Hello!
Salman Khan?
Abs? Really?
Stop bugging her
with all of your stupid talks. - Hey!
Talk about the important issue.
Yes, Ashu.
Firstly, she should be doing a proper job
in an office.
You know, something more respectable.
That's when we can seriously
talk to people about her marriage.
But why will she do some other job?
She's done a cinematography course
in New York.
She is brilliant at her job
and she's still young.
She won't be young forever.
All the good boys will be taken.
That's my biggest worry, you know..
- I know.
Come, dear.
- Come..
So, Kaira, tell me..
Are you a..
Are you a Lebanese?
- What?
It's not Lebanese.
It is lesbian! Lesbian!
Yes.. Are you a lesbian?
Oh, my God..
Well, if I were, would that stop you
from talking about my marriage?
Even if you are,
it won't make a difference.
Homosexuality is common
in the film industry.
You're right.
Be it stars or the spot boys,
everyone is gay.
It's the hub of homosexuals, you know!
Really?
Of course not!
Do you people even hear yourselves?
It's such rubbish!
That's what I want to tell you.
The film industry doesn't
have more homosexuals.
They're just more accepting.
There are as many homosexual people
in the world.
You might have a few in your office too.
But sadly, they have
to hide their true identity.
So..
Are you one?
A lesbian?
No, unfortunately not.
Then why don't you settle down?
We're just worried about you, Koko.
That's why..
If you keep spending time
with the guys from your industry
how will you find a nice boy?
Those guys are okay for checking out abs,
but not to marry?
How much more junk food
are you going to eat!
I've made all this for you.
Eat this!
For me? Have you ever seen me eat this?
Tell me.
I thought you like Paneer..
You used to eat it earlier, didn't you?
That's why I keep asking what you want.
You are the limit!
Anyway, dinner is served.
Come on. Let's get up.
Take your glasses. Come on.
- More drink?
No, thanks.
- Come, baby. Come..
You know, Koko
getting married before the age of 25
can reduce the divorce rate by 50 percent.
I know a 100 percent chance of no divorce.
Don't get married.
I'm leaving.
I'm going to stay with Jackie.
Koko..
"I'm addicted to pain."
"Even my tears laugh at me."
"Why do I keep punishing myself?"
"Somebody, save me from myself."
What about New York?
What about the New York project?
"Oh, my hurting heart."
"Oh, my lying heart."
"Oh, my broken heart."
"What's your problem?"
"To heck with you, my heart."
Why are you asking me if I slept well?
If I say no, what can you possibly do?
I don't care what people think.
I'm not going to stay with you
for other people.
Don't irritate me
early in the morning, please!
Good morning, is it?
Now it's a good morning.
If your night is not good
then how will your morning be good?
I think, I should be
a night security guard.
Should I take an appointment
with a doctor?
Who is that?
- He moved in here a few weeks ago.
To write something..
He's a writer, I guess.
Nice guy.
Take an appointment with him?
There she is, my talented daughter.
- Hi.
She shoots with all Bollywood celebrities.
That's wonderful.
I know this is a small job for you
but this new restaurant video
is very important for us.
Thank you so much for doing this.
- No, it's fine.
Actually, we should start.
The camera setup will take a while.
Yes, she is very professional, you know!
- Great!
During work, she focuses only on work.
Dad! Can we stop all these
useless formalities? - Wonderful..
I need to get this done.
I only have a day. Let's go. - Okay.
Get the 24-70 ready.
I have tried everything, Ganju. - Okay.
Even sleeping pills.. But nothing works.
Try Reiki. My grandmother also tried it.
Shut up and set up!
Remove all this.
What's all this rubbish!
I am sorry, sir.
This can't be moved right now.
Only after this session ends.
What! We have to wait?
Then why did you call us?
Ma'am, the session is going on.
Madness!
National Convention
for Mental Health Awareness.
It's a gathering of therapists.
It's Raunak's playground, isn't it?
Should we go in?
Shut up and sit.
Here?
- Just sit.
Thank you, Dr. Shah.
Ladies and gentlemen,
that concludes our final session
with our esteemed speakers today.
The floor is now open to questions.
I've done a shot breakdown,
you want to see? - I'm sleeping.
Dr. Chopra, therapy,
counseling, analysis..
So many big terms..
What do they actually mean?
A proper map can be drawn
after defining commonly accepted
medical terms.
If your problem or illness
falls in those definitions
your prognosis will tell you
your diagnosis.
It will then become clear whether
you need intensive therapy
or counseling.
Whether you need an analyst
or a psychiatrist.
It's quite simple, actually.
- It's very simple?
What are they talking?
I don't understand anything.
Hush! I'm sleepy. Keep quiet. - So,
how do we decide which type of doctor
we should go to?
A psychiatrist or a psychologist?
Each model has its own
strengths and weaknesses.
An individual may find one approach
more appropriate than the other
depending on his personal preferences
and the depth and severity
of the problem presented.
If I hear another minute of this
I'll go crazy!
This question is for Dr. Khan.
Dr. Khan, how do you know
if someone is crazy or normal?
What?
- Take me for example.
Many of you might think that I'm crazy.
Because I've come for this formal seminar
in torn jeans.
So, am I crazy? May be.
Or maybe, all I need is a good stylist.
Actually, crazy is a very scary word!
Because here, we still believe
that a problem of the mind
is something to be ashamed of.
If you have a problem
with your body, that's normal.
You know.. You can tell everyone.
Hey, guys! I'm in hospital!
With a kidney failure
lung infection, jaundice..
But if it's a problem of the mind
then the whole family goes silent.
Hush!
Then they start murmuring things
as if the mind is not even
a part of the body.
Don't laugh just yet.
The joke begins now.
Here in Goa, my parents
used to tell everyone
that I'm a gynecologist,
not a psychologist.
Which means, the doctor's
own family is ashamed
to admit that their son
is a therapist, a brain doctor.
Imagine my plight!
Many of my pregnant relatives
landed up at my clinic
for a free check-up.
And you know what?
I have delivered a few babies too
for the extra pocket money.
No..
I'm just kidding you.
Thank you, Mr. Khan.
- Thank you.
Dr. Jehangir Khan.
Thank you.
- Nice to meet you.
- It was a pleasure meeting you.
Very nice meeting you!
- Thank you.
Oh! Thank you.
Will you close it, please?
So, I'm Jehangir Khan.
But you can call me Jug.
May I have a glass of water?
- Yes, of course.
From that jug, Jug..
I'm sure you can crack
better jokes, Kaira.
May I call you Kaira?
- I have only one name.
So, how does this work?
I have no idea how this works.
You tell me.
Can I lie down here?
Are you sleepy?
- I'm not able to sleep since weeks.
That's the reason I am here.
Did you see a doctor?
Isn't that what I'm doing?
You mean, the white coat,
stethoscope, prescribing doctors..
I tried pills, they didn't work.
That's why I'm here.
Sometimes, I use this to knock
my patients off to sleep.
You're funny.
But you need to work on your jokes.
So, tell me.
Any major change in your life?
Or an issue?
I just moved from Mumbai to Goa, recently.
Is that a major change?
Yes, that's a major change. What else?
And.. Nothing.
The moving out, the settling in..
Or the leaving, the unsettling?
No?
- No, that's not a problem for me.
I like to move.
You know, not being in one place.
I like travelling.
In fact, I love to travel.
It's just this sleeping problem.
So, why did you move from Mumbai to Goa?
You know, I..
I came to Goa to be with my best friend.
I came to be with her. - Okay.
She's having issues with this guy.
And..
Basically, she really likes this guy..
I-I mean, she used to like him.
And she thought..
She thought, he liked her too
but then he suddenly
got engaged to someone else.
So, your best friend..
Is she okay now?
I don't.. I don't think so.
I don't think she is okay.
I think her main problem
is her profession.
She has this dream job
which is linked to him.
And that guy's fiancee
will also be on this project.
So, how will she be able
to handle all of that?
I don't know.
What if everything gets messed up?
I don't know what to advise her.
Should she just deal with it?
I mean, it is her dream job after all.
Sometimes, I feel I should tell her
Grit your teeth and just do it.
You won't get
another opportunity like this.
Just do it, no matter how difficult it is.
And sometimes I feel I should say,
Shut up! And say no!
Don't you have self-respect?
So, I don't know what to tell her.
So, you are not able to sleep
because you are up all night
wondering whether to tell your best friend
to shut up or not?
My grandfather used to tell me a story.
Please narrate it to your best friend.
My grandfather was a mountain climber.
Before any expedition,
he would be thoroughly prepared.
Sadly, poor Mr. Pyarelal
was not like that.
Who is Mr. Pyarelal?
A very old friend of my grandfather.
He was also
a mountain-climbing enthusiast
whose life-long desire
was to climb the toughest peak.
Mt. Everest! Directly..
Finally one day, Mr. Pyarelal got
the chance to climb Mt. Everest
with a Chinese trekking expedition group.
Without deliberation or preparation,
he said yes and left.
But the group was Chinese
so they could speak
only in their own language.
No English.
So, the trek began.
Slowly and steadily,
the group climbed higher.
But Mr. Pyarelal paced ahead.
He walked ahead of the group
while the Chinese kept waving
from behind and shouting in Chinese.
Don't go ahead!
Stop! Stop!
But Mr. Pyarelal thought
they were cheering him on and went ahead
while they kept asking him to come back.
You can speak Chinese?
Can you?
- No.
Then, this works.
Don't laugh, listen.
Suddenly, Mr. Pyarelal saw
a growling snow leopard
in front of him.
Mr. Pyarelal got extremely scared!
Now he started waving his hands
frantically and shouted for help.
But the Chinese thought,
he is just happy
because he was much ahead of them.
So, he kept crying for help
and the Chinese kept waving back.
Great..
Then?
Then, the snow leopard
ate up poor Mr. Pyarelal.
What!
- Yes, he was hungry.
You don't find many people
on Mt. Everest.
And the group kept shouting
Don't go ahead.
What a strange story!
- No..
It's not a strange story.
Please tell your friend
that sometimes, we choose
the tough path only because
we feel that to achieve important things
we have to take the tough path.
We feel, we need to punish ourselves.
But why?
Why not choose the easy way out?
What is so bad about it?
Especially, when we are unprepared
for the tough path.
Why climb mountains
when you are not ready for it?
Excuse me.
You will tell your friend
the story, right?
It's.. It's important.
Okay! I think..
My sleeping problem began
when Raghuvendra got engaged.
R-Raghuvendra?
The guy in my story.
- Right, your friend's..
No.. Mine.
At least, I thought he was mine.
Anyway..
Yes, we used to work together.
And when people work together..
Jack!
- Hi!
What are you doing here?
You don't answer my calls,
you moved here without telling me.
Without telling you?
Why would I tell you?
Who are you?
Actually, I have one thing to tell you.
I've made my decision.
W-What decision?
Kaira, I have to talk to you..
- Hush!
Just shut up, one second.
Listen to this story.
This man wanted to climb Mt. Everest.
But he leaves for the expedition
without any preparation.
He goes with Chinese companions
and when he's about to fall..
The Chinese don't understand!
Obviously, because they are Chinese.
And they keep waving their flag.
The man is stuck and then,
a tiger eats him up!
Got it?
The difficult option
is not the only option.
We can choose the easy option as well
because that would be easy.
You know.. Forget it.
It's too much for your small mind.
It's a very deep thought.
Are you talking about working on the film?
I was talking about
not working on the film!
That's my decision.
Okay. Okay, good.
- Good?
Yes, I think that's the best..
- You think?
Did you hear that?
You think?
I have already taken the decision
to not work on your film.
What do you mean by you think?
What do you mean by that?
I guess, someone really needs a therapy.
You told him?
- No, Koko..
Him?
- Yes, she told me! So what?
And anyway, why do you need therapy?
What's the big tragedy in your life?
You didn't want to get serious,
didn't want to commit.
So, I don't understand.
What is the problem?
You don't understand?
- No!
Then, get out!
Oh, God! Kaira..
You really need to grow up.
Good thing you've decided
not to work on my film.
I'm looking for mature people
to work with me.
What did I just say?
Get out, right?
Get out, okay!
Yes. You..
- Bye. See you, Jackie.
I'm not mature enough
to handle your big project
but mature enough
to sleep with you, right?
Amazing! What a revelation!
Kaira, I came here to..
- Just get out!
I don't want to do this, get out.
- I came here to..
What.. What are you doing, Kaira?
Kaira.. - Just get out!
Koko, are you sure about this?
I know, with all these personal issues
working with Raghu will be tough
but this was your big break.
Okay, Jack..
Sometimes, we choose
a tough path just because
we believe that to achieve
important things
we have to choose
the tough option, right?
But sometimes
you need to choose the easier option
because at that time,
that is the best option for you.
Right?
Especially, when you are not
ready to face that tough path.
Darn! I wish I had said it right
when he was here.
You want some tea?
Tonight, I'm going to sleep so well.
So well!
Very well!
I was at this construction site
with all these construction workers.
All short and strange people.
Suddenly, I lose my balance
and I go falling down.
Like.. One big fall!
And I land straight in muck.
I think, it was a gutter.
All these workers are just staring,
but no one is helping me.
I look up
and I see my camera dangling
and then suddenly, out of nowhere
this group of newly married women
in saris
who are all decked-up, come there.
They are looking at me,
they start pointing at me
and they're just laughing at me.
Bam! I woke up.
It was 4 a.m.
I went and stood under the shower.
Why shower?
I don't know.
I felt dirty,
I felt like I needed to clean up.
So, this Raghuvendra,
is he tall and handsome?
That's your conclusion of my dream?
Just asking.
You know what I felt?
I felt, I am ugly.
That I'm disgusting, cheap, dirty..
That's funny.
- What's funny?
I mean..
All this from a girl who is
the opposite of ugly,
disgusting or dirty.
That's funny. It's not
a hilarious joke, though. I mean..
Okay.
Oops!
What's with this?
It only creaks when you really like
someone, but can't do anything about it.
Yes, Raghuvendra is tall and handsome.
So, you like tall people,
not short and strange.
Maybe! Sid was also tall.
So, there's a Sid too?
Yes, so?
So, I mean, you're a young
and beautiful woman.
You must have admirers.
- What do you mean?
What do you mean by admirers?
I mean, you're a young
and beautiful woman.
You must surely have admirers.
- Admirers?
Yes. - You're trying to say
that there are lots of men!
That's what you're trying to say.
Just say it. - No..
What do you want me to say?
- That I am a terrible woman!
Why would I say that? No!
That's what you are saying.
You actually mean
that I'm a fast girl, a cheap girl.
No! Come on!
Fast, dirty, cheap..
Why are you using such words?
Why use these words? No..
- Isn't that what the world thinks?
No, come on! Seriously!
If a girl has more than
one relationship, then that's it.
That is what you are labeled.
Kaira.
Have you ever bought a chair?
What?
- A chair, have you ever bought one?
Yes.
And did you just go into a shop
and buy the first chair you saw?
No.
- Exactly my point!
We check and try so many different chairs
until we find the right one.
And yes, some chairs may be comfortable
but look terrible.
Others look nice, but doesn't
give you the comfort you expect!
So, the process starts..
Chair after chair and it goes on..
We check out so many chairs
before we find
that one chair!
That..
- It doesn't creak when I sit.
So, my point being
if we look for so many options
just to buy a chair
then shouldn't we look at options
when choosing a life partner?
So, dirty, cheap, fast.. No!
Smart, clear, fine..
Actually, super-fine!
Okay, wait..
So, those married women in my dream
who believe
that marriage is the only
acceptable relationship..
I felt dirty because of them.
See? You figured it out yourself.
You don't need anyone's help.
But my dangling camera?
What does that mean?
Just like my future,
it's hanging in the air.
Well, you know what?
You should sit on my chair.
And I should sit here from today.
It's so cool.
I wish the whole world could
hear about your chair theory.
At least they could know of it.
Why is it important
for the whole world to know this?
No, I just..
If they all understand this chair theory,
they will stop judging others
and what a beautiful world it will be!
No, Kaira.
When you understand yourself well
then what others think of you
doesn't matter.
Not at all.
If you don't take charge
of your own life,
then somebody else will!
I pity those who don't shop for chairs.
Kaira, will you go back
to your chair, please?
Come on.
- Okay..
Seemed like you wanted
to take my chair home with you.
And speaking of home, I remembered..
I have homework for you.
- Homework?
Yes, I'm very strict with my
homework assignments. - Okay.
I want you to chat with your parents.
- What!
At least 10 minutes with each, please.
Please, what will I talk about with them?
Time's up. See you next week.
What! We have 20 seconds more.
Hey, you saw that?
Here, look here.. Look..
What happened?
Twenty seconds happened!
I don't like this buzzer.
- Okay.
Homework, Kaira!
Yes!
Hey, those are really
nice looking glasses.
Thanks.
Are you going to see Jug?
Yes, I have an appointment.
Really?
You have problems too?
Yes.
I am going to repair my cycle.
He repairs cycles too?
Hi, Dad.
- Hi, darling.
When are you coming home?
- I'll come..
You will be home
before Kiddo arrives, right?
There's enough time for that.
Of course, I'll be there.
Your mom is in high spirits.
She's busy making preparations
for the party!
Obviously, since her prince is coming.
The restaurant management loved your film.
They said that it was very well shot.
Oh, the hotel video!
Close up of Prawn Balchao?
- Yes..
Anyway, I'll call later.
Okay, dear. Bye.
Bye.
Just four minutes.
Yes, Koko, you called?
Yes, why didn't you pick up?
- I was getting Kiddo's room cleaned.
Shift that!
Sorry, I didn't have my phone with me.
Okay, but I'm busy now.
I can't talk. So, bye..
Okay.
Shift that!
Talk to mom and dad for 10 minutes?
Is he crazy!
Beach?
Are we having the session out here today?
Why not! Any problem?
I don't have a problem.
But is it allowed?
Whose permission do I need?
I don't know, but aren't there some rules?
Like privacy, closed door,
couch and all that?
There are rules.
But one should know which ones
to break and which ones not to.
Now, people will know I am crazy.
Who are these people
who keep following you?
You know, despite the mess,
Goa is the most beautiful place in India.
I wish I could agree.
Why? You don't like Goa?
I was born here.
This is where my parents live.
How can I like it?
Did you do your homework?
Only half.
I managed to talk to dad
for only five minutes.
Okay, four minutes!
But that's a record in itself.
Wow! And what about your mom?
I tried, but she was busy.
So, you've only done a quarter.
Anyway, what did you talk about
with your dad?
About Kiddo, my brother.
He's studying in London University.
He's coming home soon,
so my parents are hosting a big party
for his homecoming.
When I got here, nobody even said welcome.
So, you don't like Kiddo?
No.. I love Kiddo. I really do!
He's the only one who can make me smile.
Just by being there
he makes me happy!
When he was little,
I read him his favorite comic.
You know Tinkle?
Have you read it?
Yes. Shikari Shambhu,
Kaalia, the Crow.. - Yes..
And Supandi..
- Supandi! Exactly!
Oh, God!
So, Supandi was Kiddo's favorite.
So, I would replace Supandi's name
with Kiddo's name
and read it to him.
He loved hearing the story in my voice.
Even today, he says
it's his best childhood memory.
What is your best childhood memory?
Come on, there must be something.
I don't know.
What are the best memories
of your childhood?
My dad used to bring me here every Sunday
to play kabaddi with the sea.
Kabaddi with the sea?
Come..
Kabaddi.. Kabaddi!
Go back!
- Okay..
Kabaddi.. Kabaddi!
Kabaddi.. Kabaddi..
- Kabaddi.. Kabaddi!
Kabaddi..
- Run!
Kabaddi.. Kabaddi!
Kabaddi..
- Come on!
Kabaddi.. Kabaddi!
- Kabaddi.. Kabaddi!
Kabaddi..
- Come on!
Kabaddi.. Just two more.
Okay.
- Just one second.
Come on, big one. Kabaddi!
- Kabaddi..
I can.. I can do this all day long!
It's important that parents create
happy memories for their children.
Now, I am a parent myself.
So, I'm hoping
that my son has
at least some good memories
to tell his therapist.
He stays with his mom.
In divorce cases, kids usually
end up with the mother.
I just regret
not being able to spend
enough time with him.
I remember Shyra.
My doll.
My dad's birthday gift to me.
When I was living with my grandparents,
Shyra was with me.
I never played with her
but just kept her close to me, you know..
At night
I would hug her tightly and sleep.
Were you shy?
Yes.
How did you know?
- You know..
Shyra starts with shy.
I-I'm a genius, really!
When I was little, I was shy.
Dad used to call me Kaira-Shyra.
But now, I'm fully Kaira.
Kaira-Shyra..
Now, fully Kaira..
Yes.
Are you sure?
Come on.
Listen.. Just a second.
Tell me something.
Why did you ask me to talk
to mom and dad for 10 minutes?
Is there some Chinese
mountain climbing story behind this?
Someday, you'll have
to climb Mt. Everest, right?
Where is Shyra?
Shyra who?
My doll!
The one dad gave me.
How come you thought of that doll
all of a sudden?
Do you know where she is or not?
She may be in the storeroom
along with your and Kiddo's old things.
What do you mean by may be?
She must be there somewhere.
How will I remember after all these years?
Do you remember anything at all
about those years?
Taste this Bibik.
What is Bibik now?
Bebinca! I just made it.
It's Kiddo's favorite.
No, I'm leaving.
I'm making Coconut Laddus for you.
Your favorite!
I remember.
You just want to make me fat!
Coconut Laddus!
I feel like breaking a coconut
on everyone's head.
No! No violence.
Do deep breathing.
What memories will parents
leave behind for us
when they can't remember
anything themselves?
Let's drink to Shyra, wherever she is.
"I can see the moon from my street."
"It's the one we celebrate with."
"Is that you?"
"My mom"
"has made me a suit"
"with the dream of finding
a beautiful woman."
"Is that you?"
"Who is it, for whom my heart
doesn't listen to me?"
"It's you."
"Who is it, for whom my heart
is protecting itself for someone?"
"It's you."
"Who is that so far away?"
"Who is that so close?"
"Who is that so special?"
"It's you."
"The one for whom"
"I'd break all other hearts."
"Is it you?"
"The one for whom"
"I'd go on living."
"I'd insure my love!"
"Is it you?"
"The one, who's presence
makes everything come alive."
"Who is it?"
"It's you."
"Who is that so far away?"
"Who is that so close?"
"Who is that so special?"
"It's you."
"Who is mentioned in my verses?"
"Who is in my poetry?"
"Who is in my diary?
"It's you."
Thank you..
Hi!
Oh, hello.
That was a beautiful song.
I mean, you have a beautiful voice.
Yes! You totally rocked it.
If your audience is so rocking,
the song has to match up.
I am Jackie and this is Kaira.
Hi, Jackie.
Hi, Kaira.
And you are?
Rumi.
Rumi?
- Rumi.
Okay.
- Girls night out?
Yes. They are the best nights.
- They are the best nights..
Hey, great song!
- Thanks!
You killed it!
- Did I?
Killed who? We're all alive here.
Girls night, don't mind.
Cheers!
You have a lovely voice!
- Thank you.
You should be singing in films.
Films! Why only in films?
I should sing everywhere.
There are all kinds of music.
There is rock, pop, jazz, blues..
Do you like blues?
Blues?
You seem more red to me.
What?
Vorresti fuggire con me?
That was Greek to me.
It's Italian, actually.
Does that mean that I'm
so beautiful and gorgeous
that you can't take your eyes off me?
Not at all.
It means that I'm
heading to a private beach
with some of my friends
to play some music.
Would you like to run away with me?
Not bad.
Wow!
Somebody seems to be
in a musical mood today.
"Who is it, for whom my heart
doesn't listen to me? It's you."
Excuse me?
"Last night, I went out
to listen to a band."
"Which band was it?
Where did you go?"
"The name of the band..
I don't know."
"But the singer, I know."
"So, tell me more..
Tell me more!"
We didn't talk, there was only music!
What do I tell?
- Yes.
So, what was his name? Banjo?
Or the fellow was called Cello?
Rumi.
- Wow!
He's new.. My new chair.
So, comfortable?
- What?
Is the new chair comfortable?
Yes, but it's a musical chair.
I will have to listen to music all day.
How to listen?
Well, why didn't you tell him straight
that you like dialogues too?
How can you ask a musician
to stop the music and talk?
He'll think, I'm an illiterate
when it comes to music.
Have you ever felt like an illiterate?
Yes.
I've sat through
a three-hour Italian opera.
I pretended as if it touched my heart
when every minute was a torture.
I wanted to stand up on the chair
and scream even louder than them
that I'm an illiterate
when it comes to opera.
Really.
- Wow, okay!
What would you do if you were
dating an opera singer?
I would tell her,
I will do anything for you
but don't make me hear the opera.
That would be the end.
She would dump you and run away.
After six months of suffering,
I would have, anyway, run away.
If one is going to suffer
the other person should at least know.
What is the point of suffering in silence?
There isn't any.
See, when you..
I'm so sorry.
- I-It's okay.
I will get a new one for you.
- I-I'll do it, don't touch it.
I'll fix it, all right?
- How much did it cost?
I think it's safer to have
our sessions outdoor.
Come on, tell me more about Rumi.
You know, I like people who smell nice.
I hate smelly people.
Really? Why?
So, you like smelly people?
Everyone has a different smell.
That's how people get
attracted to each other.
Yuck! Who goes around smelling people
to get attracted?
Dogs.
Dogs!
Yes, dogs!
Ganju, we should record our conversations.
You prove to be a genius sometimes.
Genius!
- Yes, please.
Genius is not one
who has all the answers.
Genius is one who has
the patience to find every answer.
Deep..
- Which genius said this?
Dr. Jehangir Khan.
Khan!
So, does he smell nice?
Who?
There you go.
Wait.. Let it breathe. Cheers!
Listen to this bit.
I love chocolate.
Okay, this bit.
Wait, one second.
Pink Floyd's first album,
you have to get this.
"I agree,
you're the most beautiful of all."
"I agree, you find a place.."
You like strawberries?
- "... in every heart."
"Yes, you are a dream.
Your every move is a charm."
"But.. You're not one
to be wooed by flattery."
Try some. - Can we just have
the music off, please!
"My heart.."
I'm sorry, I just need some silence.
It's okay.
"What if you see.."
Everything okay?
I wrote this song for you.
But it's okay, silence is good sometimes.
There is beauty in silence too.
Let's be silent.
Come here. I am sorry..
That's not silent.
I'm sorry.
Okay, play your song.
No, forget my song.
Let's talk about you.
I want to know everything about you.
What?
- Come, sit.
Tell me about yourself.
What was your first film about?
When did you decide to be a camerawoman?
What's your journey?
You know, I haven't even
shot a selfie in my life.
Isn't that funny?
So, tell me.
I want to know about your dreams
your inspirations, your aspirations..
I want to know everything about you.
You!
What?
- What?
What's going on?
Shall I put on some music?
Please!
I've heard enough for a lifetime.
So, still suffering silently?
Or did you say it?
I yelled it!
So, he ran away?
No, he was very sweet, actually.
He stopped playing the song
which apparently,
he had composed for me
and began asking about me.
I felt guilty at first but..
Why are romantic relationships
so irritating?
With friends, it's all so easy.
It just flows!
You don't need to make such an effort.
Who are the five people closest to you?
Your top five?
Why?
There is an important study
based on the size of the human brain
that shows that everyone has about
150 people in their whole life.
The next cut is the 50 who
you would invite home for dinner.
Then, 15 people who you turn to
during your good times and bad times.
And the final cut is of 5 people
who mean the world to you.
Your inner circle..
So..
Who are your five people?
Okay.
Fatty, Kiddo, Jackie, Alka..
Raghuvendra.. No!
And I forgot to add..
These five people
can also change with time.
That's true, but these four people
will always be on the list.
Okay, so think of these four and tell me
how do you feel when you are with them
as compared to the changing fifth person.
How.. How do these four people
make you feel?
Special! I feel special.
I feel important.
I feel respected.
I feel..
I feel happy and safe.
So, you don't feel safe
with your boyfriends?
It's not that.
I feel safe but..
I don't know..
I don't know. It's not that.
With my friends
I feel free, I feel like myself.
Why safe?
When you start liking a guy
what is your fear, Kaira?
It's back in one piece.
I believe, all broken things
can be put back together.
How is the therapist?
Is he married or single?
Ma'am. Here you go.
- Thank you, Alka.
Hi, Alka!
Look there.
- Hi!
Ma'am, how are you?
Rubbish!
Why did you go to the doctor?
Are you okay?
I went to a brain doctor.
What happened to your brain?
Nothing, if you have
an emotional problem in your life
then a brain doctor can help you solve it.
Do such doctors exist?
- Yes.
Then everyone should go to them.
Yes, everyone should.
"I agree,
you're the most beautiful of all!"
you find a place in every heart."
"Yes, you're a dream.
Your every move is a charm."
"But.. You're not one
to be wooed by flattery."
Please play! Don't stop!
Come on, play the music.
- Come on.. Play.
Hey, come on, play the music!
- Come on!
You were amazing! Don't stop.
Come on!
- That's like it!
"Be calm, my heart."
"Don't beat so loud."
"Let her not see"
"your restlessness."
"You will smile now at my state."
"But.. You're not one
to be wooed by flattery."
"Should I whisper in your ears"
"or scream from mountain tops?"
I'm telling you, it was good fun!
We danced to the latest songs all night!
What's happening?
Fatty!
I called you, why didn't you answer?
Hi, Koko.
Why are you both grinning like that?
Jackie is just telling me
about her new boyfriend.
What!
Excuse me! What new boyfriend?
How about telling me?
I'm right here. Am I invisible?
You didn't even ask.
- Why do I have to ask?
Okay, guys, relax! Please don't fight.
- How can you not tell me?
Oh, wait! I know why! Because it's
that weird guy from the bar, right?
See, this is what you do.
You're always judging my men.
- Girls!
I'm not judging, you called him weird.
- I want to..
That was then. Now I like him.
- Look how big I am.
Like a football. Hello.. - But you didn't
tell me that you like him.
Girls! - Because you never asked,
you're not around.
Fine! - How am I supposed to know
if you don't tell me?
How could you do this?
- You're supposed to be around.
You keep doing this
and blame me for everything.
I am around!
Fatty, where are you?
Great! You also leave me.
Good morning!
Good morning, Jackie!
Anything special today?
- Yes.
You! You're so special.
You're so special! Jackie..
- No.. My personal space!
Okay, I'm special.
So, you fix cycles too?
I try.
And if I can't fix them, I recycle them.
Recycle a cycle?
Kaira, you have to crack
better jokes, please.
So, all that cycle art
in your room and..
Hey! Hi, by the way!
- Hi.
This boy was wearing those funky
looking glasses, you made all that?
Finally, you noticed!
He's an artist.
- Yes.
If you can't fix people
then do you recycle them too?
Bye, Jug.
- Sorry about it.
That's so mean.
- Yes, that's so mean. Let's go.
Why cycle today?
Just breaking the pattern.
Yes, we should break it.
You must be going insane
listening to crazy people like me
all day inside one room.
- Quite possible!
Albert Einstein once said
An insane person is one who does
the same thing over and over again
and expects different results each time.
By the way.. It's over with Rumi.
I broke up with him.
Why?
No.. I can't do it!
It's too much.
He doesn't fit in my..
I don't know.
I can't handle it. It's too much.
What's too much?
- Too much!
Wait.. Lance Armstrong!
Did Rumi do something wrong?
No, we were just wrong for each other.
Not this chair.
Shiver! Only happens when we feel cold
or have a fever,
or due to the weather.
Sometimes people shiver
when they are scared.
I just want to be free.
Free from all this!
- Yes.
I also want you to be free!
Free from your fears!
- Yes!
Free! Free..
Oh, wow!
Help.. Help me.
Oh, no! Our time's up.
- What!
Got to go! Sorry!
Jug! Oh, my God!
Get my glasses, please.
Oh, God!
My darling boy, all good?
Yes, all good.
Kiddo! Spend some time
with me now, come on.
Sorry, I was getting ready.
You know, it's my party.
I have to look nice.
You look nice.
Listen. Are you also
a part of this matchmaking?
Me?
- Yes, you.
I have no clue
but I want to see the fun. - Dear..
Sweet boy Kiddo!
And you,
is your best friend, Jackie, here?
Is she still single or..
Yes, she's still very much single
and so is Kaira.
Sweet boy Kiddo!
Please stop, it's starting to hurt.
Kaira, come.. Come.
Bye. - Bye.
- Come on.
I want to introduce you
to a young man.
This is my niece, Kaira.
Hi, Kaira. I'm Suresh.
Suresh.
- Yes.
Pleasure.
Well, I'll see you all later.
- Alright, cheers, sir.
Cheers.
- Yeah.
So, you're a photographer, right?
Cinematographer, actually.
One and the same thing.
- No, it's not the same thing.
It's not? Okay.
- No!
What do you do?
I'm a techie.
Does that sound boring?
Fun.
- It's fun? Then, cheers!
So, what do you think..
Why should I be interested in you?
That was pretty direct, right?
But I can be interesting
if I meet an interesting girl.
It depends.
Okay..
- Yes.
Kiddo, your favorite food. Eat, dear.
- Thank you.
What a lovely child Kiddo was!
He never used to cry.
- Right!
Sweet boy!
He would never leave my side,
and always called out to me!
Well, I figured, calling out to you
was a better way to get
what I wanted, than to cry.
These kids grow up so fast!
- I know!
Look at Kiddo. He has achieved
so much at a young age!
He has got a scholarship
for a higher degree. - Is it?
Yes! Then, an internship with a big firm.
Tell them the name
of the company, Kiddo.
Dad, just stop it now.
You are doing the right thing!
You are doing the correct thing!
You're not eating anything.
Are you dieting again?
I don't feel like.
Eat something at least.
Fine, give it to me.
Here, have this.
You remember, Chanda?
Kiddo was such a gentle, quiet boy.
But Kaira, a real firecracker.
She's still the same.
Firecracker is the apt word for her.
Anger, tantrums and sulking,
most of all with me.
You kids have no idea
how tough it is to be a parent.
And it's never ending.
There is no end to it.
Once a parent, always a parent.
- I agree.
No holiday from this job.
Right, Ashu? - Yes!
All parents should be felicitated
with a national award.
What?
- I love the food.
Really? Nice.
So, end it then.
Just end it.
- What?
The job of being a parent!
Just end it.
You keep going on and on
about how tough it is. So, just end it.
Who has forced you
to continue being parents?
Has anyone forced you to?
You didn't start the job well
in the first place.
And now, I don't understand..
Why continue it?
Just end it. Put an end to it!
When kids need you the most,
you happily leave them and go.
And then complain about their tantrums
all your life.
Oh, how angry she gets, makes faces!
It was your idea
to bring us into the world. Correct?
You treated us the way you wanted.
And then you blame us for how we behave!
And you say, it's tough.
What do you mean by that?
Tough, my foot!
How could you just abandon me?
How could you just do that?
How could you do that?
How could you both leave me and go?
And the only reason you took me back
was because I failed the second grade.
Yes, I failed the second grade!
Oh, God! Shame..
Dumb Kaira failed the second grade!
It was such an embarrassment for you
that you left everything
and came back to India!
Just because I failed the second grade!
And when I was finally happy
living with my grandparents
you dragged me away
from there too.
You separated me even from them.
Yes!
National award just for that!
And I have a fire-cracking news for you!
Actually, a bomb!
Are you ready?
I have begun therapy!
Yes! I am seeing a brain doctor.
So, instead of calling me crazy or insane
behind my back
say it to me right now.
Say it on my face! Come on, say it!
I'm crazy!
Koko!
Kaira's gone mad!
Mad!
That's what you think..
That people like me are crazy.
Koko..
She is a bit emotional right now.
She is also out of work.
Dad, she has enough work.
She has chosen not to work right now.
Okay?
Kiddo, no..
Kiddo, go, get her.
- Don't worry, Mom.
Make her understand
that once her parents moved back,
she never failed in school again.
So, they took the right decision.
There are all kinds of failures in world
and I am looking at a few right now.
Are you okay?
I don't know.
Were you happy as a child?
I only remember being happy
once you came home.
See this.
Hey! Where did you find that?
I was looking for something from my past
and found something from ours instead.
You know..
As children, when we are sad,
our elders tell us not to cry.
When we are angry,
they tell us, Give us a smile!
You know why?
Just to keep the peace at home.
When we wanted to hate,
they didn't allow us.
Now, when we want to love
we suddenly find our whole
emotional system to be haywire.
It.. It cannot function.
Sadness, anger, hatred..
We were not allowed to express anything.
So now, how do we express love?
It's okay to be angry sometimes,
even with parents.
It's good, it's healthy.
It's.. It's okay, Kaira.
They left me at my grandparents' house.
Mom told me that I would join them soon.
Perhaps, dad's export business in Goa
had failed.
So he went to Africa,
Middle East and where not
looking for business opportunities.
Mom went with him.
In the beginning, I was happy
to stay with my grandparents
in their big old house in Vasco.
I would write a letter
to mom and dad every week.
Sometimes, even twice a week.
I didn't even know
how to write properly then.
I would draw some pictures, paint them
and try to write some big words.
But every letter ended
with the same question.
When will you come back?
I was five years old.
Every week, I would drop my letters
in the mailbox with my grandpa.
Then I would wait for a letter
in response.
I would wait for an answer to my question.
But it never came.
When they called once a month,
they had some excuse each time.
Something about an address change,
no post office close by
feeling unwell and so on..
But I still kept writing.
And my grandpa would keep
walking me to the mailbox.
He always said that I will
get my answer someday.
Then, a year later,
mom visited me in Goa
with my new baby brother, Kiddo.
I was jealous
because he got to be with mom
all the time, and not me.
Then mom said
that I would be away from them
for just a little longer.
So, I was still fine with it.
I remember asking my mom
if she got my last letter.
She said that it was so beautiful
that she put it up on the refrigerator
so that she could see it every day.
I was so happy!
I ran to my room so I could
write another letter for her
to see her smile in front of my own eyes.
I wanted to see her reaction,
her happiness, right away.
So, I took out my colors and paints
drew a picture
and ran to show it to her.
As I was about to enter the room,
I heard my grandpa shouting at my mom.
He was telling her that what
she was doing was not right.
How could she not respond
to my question, to my letters!
And then, I heard my mom reply.
I can't give her false hope.
False hope.
The truth is that we can't
take her back just yet.
Not until the business is set up..
It is too tough to handle two children
and travel constantly.
And she went on with the reasons.
And everything just seemed
to fade away.
Everything seemed unclear.
It was a strange feeling
like someone had grabbed
the TV remote from me
and changed the channel
from something I loved
to something horrid
and then, threw out the remote.
I went back to my room
and tore up the letter.
I was six years old.
I took a decision as a 6-year-old
that I had nothing more to say to them,
nothing more to ask.
I didn't write a letter
ever again in my life.
Never!
My poor grandpa kept trying
to get me to write
but I knew, I had nothing
to say to my parents
or to anyone else.
I just became quiet.
I shut down.
Then, a year later, my mom said
that they were coming back for good.
Dad's friend had offered him
a business partnership here, in Goa.
In all these years, dad couldn't
set up his business abroad.
So, imagine, all this for nothing!
So, they came back.
But that year
was the most stressful for me.
I didn't want to be with them.
I wanted to stay with my grandparents.
They were separating me from them too.
I threw tantrums
cried a lot, troubled everyone!
To top it all, I failed the second grade
and that.. Not my 100 letters
not the fact that I was their daughter
living away from them
but my failure made them
take me away from my grandparents
and back with them, finally.
I'm sorry.
If you don't cry wholeheartedly
how will you laugh wholeheartedly?
It's okay. Go on.
I'm not much for rules
but because of the rules
I can't pop a champagne bottle
to celebrate this moment
but we can do the next best thing.
We can do shots.
We can have water.
To letters, Kaira.
Cheers!
Go easy.
To feel safe, first the fears have to go.
The fear of being abandoned,
of being left alone.
You have carried this fear with you
all your life.
And the burden of that fear
is falling on all your relationships.
Especially on your love life.
So, you leave others
before they can leave you.
You want to say bye
before they can say bye.
Because you never want
to face that pain again.
So, Kaira..
Why not say goodbye to this fear
once and for all?
Why not say hello to life
once again?
You know..
I am not saying that you should
forgive your parents
or that you should
stop being angry with them.
You do as you wish.
But let me tell you that
you should try to look at them
not in the exalted status of parents
but just as two regular people
who make mistakes
like you and I, and everyone else.
As a child, it is hard
to understand all this
but now, as an adult
you can at least try.
Don't let the past blackmail your present
to ruin a beautiful future.
"When something touches your heart"
"welcome it."
"When your heart is not in it"
"say bye to it."
"Let it come, let it come."
"Let it come into your heart."
"Say hello to happiness."
"Let it go, let it go."
"Let it go from your heart."
"Say goodbye to all your fears."
"Love you, my life!"
"Love me, my life!"
Koko, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Bye.
Hello?
- Hi, ma'am.
I am calling from eBay.
Are you happy with our services?
Yes, why?
- Please do continue shopping with us.
Do let us know if you require
any further assistance.
"Sometimes, hold my hand"
"and walk with me."
"Sometimes, leave my hand"
"and let me go free."
"I'm a little moody."
"You're a little crazy."
"What a pair, we are!"
"Let it come, let it come."
"Let it come into your heart."
"Say hello to happiness."
"Let it go, let it go."
"Let it go from your heart."
"Say goodbye to all your fears."
"Love you, my life!"
"Love me, my life!"
You are different.
You are distinct.
You listen to me.
You really listen.
I wish I had someone like you in my life.
Am I making sense?
Not at all,
but that will be Rs. 3,000, please.
"Love you, my life!"
"Love me, my life!"
Where were you?
Just disappeared.
I have to give proper notice
if I miss a session
and you left me one small note.
Sorry. That's not fair!
I know, life is unfair.
Fine.
Hide all your secrets.
You know, my issues with my parents
may get sorted
but with men..
I don't know when that'll happen.
I am never going to find anyone.
Tell me something.
Is there such a thing
as a perfect relationship?
Like just one, special soul mate?
I don't know.
Kaira, I think
why just that one special soul mate?
I think one can have
many soul mates in life.
Different soul mates
for different experiences.
Like.. A special musical relation
with someone
who shares our interest in music.
Or the let's-get-coffee-together
soul mates.
Perfect to have coffee with
but not anything else.
No.
Special gossip soul mates
with whom you can have the perfect gossip.
Or the special intellectual soul mates
for all those perfect bookish discussions.
So many different, special soul mates.
So many kinds..
The romantic soul mate is just one of many.
I think, every relationship in life
has its own place.
Why put the burden on one person
to fulfill all your emotional needs?
It's a bit unfair, isn't it?
Never thought of it this way.
I'm glad the camera is back.
Me too.
Jug, do you want to get
a cup of coffee or something?
No, our time's up.
You won't bunk the next session, right?
It is the last week of our sessions.
How can I miss that?
So, done sulking with Goa?
No more sulking.
What about your work?
Actually, I got an offer.
What?
- Yes.
A production company is interested
in funding my short film.
So, I am thinking,
why not stay back here and shoot it?
Since it's the final class, have I passed?
This isn't school, to pass or fail.
I wish there were
teachers like you in school.
I'm no teacher.
Okay, not a proper teacher
but you know what I mean.
We are all our own teachers
in the school of life.
Okay, that was a bit too deep.
Life is like a jigsaw puzzle. You know,
the one we played when we were little.
People like me can help you
find the missing pieces
and put them in place.
But only you can complete the puzzle.
So..
Now that this is over
can we meet outside of this?
No..
- Just as friends or something?
No, this is not possible, Kaira.
And what if I tell you
that I like you.
In fact..
Go on, I'm listening.
In fact, I really like you.
That's it, I said it.
I really like you too.
I really like you.
I respect these feelings
but my job here is done for now.
As unconventional
and friendly, my methods maybe
I am still your therapist.
Any other relation with you
would be outside the boundaries
of my own professional ethics.
The closeness that you feel
towards me, your brain doctor
is very normal.
This.. This happens, it's common.
So, I am common?
- No.. You are not common.
You are different, special
and unique!
Really!
You know, Kaira,
people who come here
feel all sorts of strong emotions.
Be it anger, hate, love..
I shouldn't have said anything.
I just shouldn't have.
No.. You should have!
I-It's really good
that you said what you said. Really!
You expressed your difficult feelings
in a straightforward and mature manner
rather than letting them fester
inside of you.
And we don't want that.
No!
We don't want that.
This, Kaira, is huge progress.
Okay, but, tell me something.
How can this be the last session?
No..
- What?
I think..
- No more stories?
There will be so many more problems
in my life.
Yes, there will be many problems.
And you will have to solve
all those problems.
But now
you know how to solve them.
Here?
But I'll need help.
I need you.
Kaira
when you see a pattern emerging in life
or something becoming a habit,
then it's time to think over it.
Genius is about knowing when to stop.
Okay, then.
Baby Fatima.. Can't believe it!
This is your godmother, Koko!
Battle after battle
Corporal Balthazar fought
in the Portuguese army for 14 years.
Nobody knew that Corporal Balthazar
was not Balthazar
but Dona Maria, a woman
disguised as a man.
This was the only way for a woman
to safeguard her life and dignity.
For 14 years,
Dona Maria fought two battles.
One on the battlefield,
and the other with herself
with her fears.
Finally, one day on the battlefield,
her true identity was revealed.
As fate would have it
in front of Captain Aphonso.
Captain Aphonso
Commander of the fort and a doctor
not only saved Dona Maria's life
and nursed her wounds
but made her fears disappear
and freed her from the ghost
of Corporal Balthazar.
For the first time
Dona Maria had the courage
to face her true self.
Finally, she felt free.
She felt alive.
With her newfound courage,
Dona Maria soon
became Commander.
The first woman Commander
of the Portuguese army.
Now, Donna Maria fought only one battle.
The one on the battlefield,
not with herself!
Good, Kaira!
Amazing, dear! That was great!
Where is she?
- Kaira! Kaira! Kaira!
Kaira! Kaira!
Kaira..
- Kaira!
Speech! Speech!
- No speech, just shut up!
It was beautiful, my darling!
I'm so proud of you, dear.
Wonderful. Very good!
- Thank you.
Beautiful film.
Really?
- Very impressed!
People who make music with the camera
don't need musicians.
I wrote a song for you.
Do you want to hear it?
Just kidding!
I'm proud of you.
You gave Kaira her first break, right?
Yes. - She could not have
done this without you.
Actually, if I was with her,
she couldn't have done this.
Cheers! Cheers!
- Cheers.
To the longest project of this century!
Cheers to my baby! Cheers!
- Cheers!
Hi!
- Hi!
I was wondering..
Yes, please tell me,
what were you wondering?
Would you be able to live
as a man for a few years?
What?
The concept of your story
was really interesting.
How did you come up with the idea?
What's your story?
Do you make films too?
No, I make furniture.
Tables, sofas, chairs..
Chairs?
- Yeah.
Really? Chairs?
Yes, chairs.
Chairs!
Dear life..
I know, we haven't been
in touch for a while.
So, nothing..
Just wanted to say hi!
Kabaddi.. Kabaddi!
"When something touches your heart"
"welcome it."
"When your heart is not in it"
"say bye to it."
"Let it come, let it come.
Let it come into your heart."
"Say hello to happiness."
"Let it go, let it go.
Let it go from your heart."
"Say goodbye to all your fears."
"Love you, my life!"
"Love me, my life!"
"Sometimes, hold my hand"
"and walk with me."
"Sometimes, leave my hand"
"and let me go free."
"I'm a little moody."
"You're a little crazy."
"What a pair we are!"
"Let it come, let it come.
Let it come into your heart."
"Say hello to happiness."
"Let it go, let it go.
Let it go from your heart."
"Say goodbye to all your fears."