Fixed&Synced by bozxphd. Enjoy The Flick.
How many stars in the sky.
Have you ever tried to count it?
If you try to count it, then...
It's about 6,000 billion at least.
That too just in our galaxy.
And how many such
galaxies in all?
Scientists say maybe it
is two billion or more.
Therefore, what if in these
so many planets.
There's probably someone
somewhere in...
Some planet that's look
just like us.
And like us, who's trying
to go to the Moon and Mars...
They too searching
for us and come here...
Rajasthan - India.
The thing that was stolen
is for calling back the spaceship...
Without the remote control, he can
never go back to his home planet...
He does not know our language...
And he does not have
any friends here...
Alone, helpless, he thought
about just one thing...
Now, how can I go home?
Sorry, but I raise
my hand first.
Oh, sorry, but I ask first...
After that you came.
I'm a big fan of Raleigh
Rai Bachchan.
But I am a big fan
of Amitabh Bachchan.
I have read all the poems he's
written since 10 years...
From the age of five I memorized
all of his dialogue, that too without radio.
Who want this, final? -Give it to me,
he will not understand any poet.
100 Euros.
40 price, sell 100?
That too forged ticket? -Since
it took over 6 hours of queue.
Time is money.
You listen then...
No, no, you listen.
Ladies first...
Wait, what do you say
we split together?
First you hear poetry...
After free time, I see Amitabh sir...
Please...
That's a damn good idea!
10... 20... 30... 40
- 50... 6...
- 96
There are 96.
Small discount please. We're
from same country after all...
Motherland. Live! Bro...
Yes, long live... 100 Euros.
Can you lend 4 euro please?
You can take the watch
for that money.
Please Uncle, last ticket.
Its Full House already, you
won't get any tickets.
No Uncle, there's one Hero,
selling forged tickets.
Rascals...
People like him will tarnish
our country's name. -Right?
Boy, you stay here,
I'll get you tickets.
Thanks.
Uncle...
Who? -You ask who?
Where are my tickets?
Oh. Tickets?
100 Euro.
Bloody cheater...
You bastard, liar, shmucks...
Mind your language. -Mind
your language? To hell!
- Guards.
- Now go look inside... old man.
Come... come... come.
I'll take care of you.
- Go go go go.
- Cursing the girl.
Let me catch that old man...
Today, when...
What kind of generation...
Just give it up.
Never mind it...
How can I give up ...?
He's listening to good poem now
and I'm sitting here. -Give it up...
The past often hurt
out memories...
The future is waving its hand...
Come forward with me
toward it...
Me too write
a little here and there.
That's good. Tell
the rest of them.
No, cannot say the rest.
If you listen to the rest...
You'll end up proposing me.
- Are you crazy?
- No, really...
You really like Sir Rai
Bachchan...
Woman found him
in the morning...
He sang the words
of his poems...
By evening she married him.
- I've read it.
- Really?
What else?
Twelve waiting...
Just see...
Amitabh Bachchan.
Jaggu.
Jaggu...?
My name.
Papa put a long name to me...
Jhaggat Jhannani.
Everyone made fun
of that at the school.
- So I cut it short.
- Jaggu.
You live here?
No, Delhi. I'm hosting
a TV production here.
- And you?
- I'm Sarfaraz, study architecture here and doing part time job.
Here, at the Pakistan embassy.
Why Pakistan Embassy ...?
Because... I'm a Pakistani.
So, I cannot get a job
at Indian embassy right?
What happened ...?
No... nothing.
Pakistan mentioned...
And smile was gone ...?
Well then... God bless you.
Thanks.
Mom, Dad...
She's falling in love.
Fall in love?
He is so cute.
Come, show the picture.
What do the boy do? Not
a joint family, right ...?
Calm, I tell you everything.
First, What his name?
Sarfaraaz.
A Muslim?
Yes, Dad, study in architecture.
Family in Pakistan.
Pakistan... what Pakistan?
Mom... there's just
one Pakistan.
Over my dead body...
Do not disconnect. Do not move.
Hold on. I will be quick.
Lord, it will be
a catastrophe...
Please help.
I knew where Papa was going...
Ever since I'm a child, I saw Mr.Tapaswy
face... more than I saw my parents faces...
Bye Mom...
From school bag to home
bathroom wall, everywhere...
Mr.Tapaswi
is all over the place.
Good time for him to get lost.
Not protect the tooth.
Tapaswi has given father
a box of Gods.
For each task there's a god.
When Dad doing stock transaction,
he showed Lakshmi the computer screen.
While at treadmill, its
Hanuman he brought up.
Internet, Online,
blessing, all Mr.Tapaswi.
All these things
is because of Tapaswi.
Jaggu, come take blessing...
Why Jaggath Jhananni...
Why you want suicide...
Take down pencil.
And write... O Lord.
Please help...
Yes...
Alright...
God... what you say.
Look at the reality
Jaggath Jhandni.
This Pakistani youth.
Which name is Sarfaraaz...
He will lie to you.
Sarfaraaz will not cheat on me.
Boy, bear witness to history.
These people is not doing
anything but lies.
He will take advantage on you.
He'll use you
but will not marry you.
Jaggu come home immediately.
If one more night you're there,
our relationship is over.
Sahani, sir...
I'll talk with the children.
Child...
Press the delete button.
And get him off your system.
Hello...
What happened ...?
Do you love me?
Of course I do, why?...
Will you marry me?
Hello, but what happened ...?
Yes or no, Sarfaraaz?
- Yes... b... but...
- tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Tomorrow we will get married.
Mr.Tapaswi's prophecy is wrong.
I'll prove it.
Sir James Herrick and Miss Oprah
Brown, you are next
James isn't here yet.
Ah... talk to the Registrar.
Could you just hold this please...
Of Course.
This is for you...
- For me?
- Yeah.
Thanks.
It's a letter from Sarfaraaz.
We can't continue
because of our family...
Our countries, religions, people,
everything is different.
How can we be happy together?
We can't.
Do not try to contact me.
Sorry.
Where to go, young lady?
New Delhi.
New Delhi. Six months later...
I returned to my city...
But my father didn't
want me at home.
I join the news channel now.
Boss ordered to bring any dog.
He want to make it
a breaking news.
Haven't got any new news.
Sometimes had to make
up some news.
Disappeared.
Missing.
If found please contact PK.
That man, a good story.
You go to the office.
I'll come later.
Come quickly.
Excuse me.
Why do you give these out?
My case is not
solved yet with him.
He do not contact me
and hadn't been found.
My life has been destroyed.
Don't even know
what world he go to sit.
You got any idea where is he?
No.
Why are you wearing this helmet?
I've learnt one thing.
This yellow color, can
be seen from afar.
Despite huge traffic, one know
a taxi even from far.
- So?
- So God can find me from far.
Or else, how would He know
me from among the crowd?
Yes, to the left side.
OK, Perfect.
Background...
Jaggu, que.
Who said that animals
don't commit suicide.
This is Nikku.
Dr. Sweetie Singh's dog
from Ramesh Nagar, Delhi.
In the last month, it have
attempt suicide three times.
Try to jump off the roof,
ate sleeping pills,
And throw itself in fireplace.
Why did it do these things?
Is it have some mental illness?
Is Nikku...
Jaggu, what happened?
What's this shit, Nitu?
We hope to talk more with the millionaire,
but after the break.
Well done. Coffee?
Bring coffee here, someone...
Jerry.
- Oh no.
- What do you think? This dog have depression?
And psychotic disorder, schizophrenia
tension deficit hyperactive disorder.
Whatever it is,
why would I care?
Exactly!
Why would anyone care?
So why show this
stupid news to people?
So what you trying to say?
Come here, take this.
Look at this. Today,
I met someone.
Who gives these
pamphlets to people.
He's looking for God.
He found Him?
No.
Finding God, that's religion.
Found God, that's news.
If he found God then bring
him here, I'll put him on.
You know its company policy.
No news on religion and no
news on God. Finish.
What is wrong with you ...?
Where are the so called
fighter once before?
You wanna see the fighter.
Look here. Look at this.
There are three marks here. See?
They are not birthmarks.
Your father's friend,
that Tapaswi?
I have news program against him.
It's his devotees shoot my butt.
Yeah. Right in my bump.
From then on, I decided, if I want
to live in this country...
Then do not mess with religion.
That's it.
I have a show now. You can go.
Bye bye.
Welcome come back from the break,
we were talking about businessman...
Boss never give me the opportunity
to follow up this story...
But two weeks later, it
came back to my life story.
A thief... thief... thief.
Catch him. He steal
money from the box.
Hey... Where are you going?
Catch him.
Get away.
You idiot, dare
stealing from God?
Pandit... He is not a thief.
My purse fell through the box
when I want to give money in it.
He's helping me to get
it, that's all.
I'm telling the truth. Check it.
In the purse there's Rs 5,000.
You'll see.
Pandit... Those are mine.
Once, but when He
was named in your hands.
Now they are His.
Let them leave.
Hey...
What did you do there? I'm
taking my money back.
Payment has been taken, but didn't
do the work. -No, no wait.
I saw you begin to get some money,
and then you put some money back.
Rs200 for the register, I take that amount
from it and return the balance back in.
Before this, you wear
necklaces, rings, wasn't
you.? I reject it.
Now I won't wear it.
Then why are you wearing
these stickers?
Self-defense.
People always put Gods photo
in their wall, right?
So that someone would not kick it... I stick
it here. So that people won't hit me.
Nitu, where are you?
Come fetch me, I don't
have money to go home.
I'll tell you
what happened later.
There's a big temple
opposite that place.
Come quickly... Thanks... bye.
Take this. Keep it.
What's this? -For taxi,
so you can go home.
When I see somebody
couldn't go home.
I feel disheartened.
Listen. No more,
That's all I have.
No. I cannot take this.
Why? -You have to go
to your home too right?
And you don't have
any money too.
Even with money, I...
Still can't go home...
Why?
Where do you live?
Actually I...
Live in Bhauri...
But these days, the hotel
rent are high, you know...
So I have to Check
in at lock up.
Lock up?
As in the police lock up?
Yes, here in Delhi...
They give food for free - And you
want to check in there? Like a hotel?
Come, I'll show you.
Stay here.
Hey, look at this, idiot...
I'll take care of you.
Jaggu.
You sit behind.
I'll follow that car.
- Who's car ...?
- Our story.
Get your purse...
Need some money.
Hurry Nitu.
Thank you, bye.
Excuse me.
- Yes.
- I want to go into the lock up.
Why?
To meet that guy.
Lady, does this look
like a canteen to you?
Where you can eat and drink, have
fun with friends as you please?
This is lock up. Lock up.
Only someone who is faulty
is able to go in.
Ma'am, bribe is banned.
That's why I give it.
You can even be put in.
Oh please do it.
Thank you, Mr. Pandit.
Just an hour.
Hi.
I want to know your story.
Tell me.
What is it?
I'm a TV reporter.
This is my job.
Ask.
Whatever you want to ask.
So...
What's your name?
I don't have name.
All I know is everyone
call me PK, PK.
What's your job?
Ash toro naut...
(ASTRAUNAUT)
Astronaut?
Meaning, job which go
to the Moon?
Moon miner... do not work.
Not trustworthy.
OK... so what's your favorite
planet, then?
My planet. No, no,
beside Earth...?
No, I know this
planet's a beauty.
I said my own planet.
At night, that's up there.
I can see my home.
We're surprised when
we learned that...
There are another world,
people just like us.
So they sent me here,
for research purpose.
But when I just got here.
Someone snatched
my remote control.
And without remote control
I can't give signals to my home.
Without signals, no one can
come and take me home...
Hello... Listen.
What ...? Open the door please.
I want to go home.
Madam, that can be decide by party
from outside, not from inside.
Look I'm not a thief.
That's what thieves always said.
Where Mr. Pandit? Please call him.
Mr. Pandit went on patrol.
Mr. Pandit.
- Pandit.
- Hey thief, shut up. Or I'll give...
You think I'm crazy,
talking nonsense?
If not then what?
Your planet people talking like BHOJPURI
(LANGUAGE FROM Indian STATE BIHAR)?
Our world did not
have any language...
We all are talking with mind,
never arouse confusion.
But here, say something else
but meant something else.
One word but four meaning.
When saying something
good, it's like...
Everything is good, very good.
"Accha
(GOOD)" with big eyes...
When in wonder,
the tone is short...
"Your mother accident...
Really?"
When someone angry, the tone
sound even more high.
"Really? You want to teach me?
Really?"
When thinking, then
its long tone.
"Oh, that's it..."
You have to pay close attention.
Then one can understand
what they mean.
Because of so many confusion, I had
to learn it in full six hours.
Meaning you learned
all Bhojpuri language in just
six hours? -I can't touch
hands at that time.
Then I met one girl, I sit
together with her...
I hold her hands and transfer
all the language she has to me.
Do you have a laughing brain?
There's a limit
to everything you know.
Is your hands
is like a USB cable?
That can transfer files
from computer to another computer?
And your clothes ...?
Your world's also wearing jeans?
No no no... Our world's don't
wear any clothes.
First time I got here, I think
that people's here different from each other.
Our world different
by the skin, the skin here...
Some have shining bright
skin, some have black skin.
Some have coloured skin,
some have plain skin.
Some have a skinny skin
and some have hanging down skin.
Then one day I saw a car.
Dancing car.
Then I understood, that people's bodies
here is the same as my world.
The difference here
is that they all are wearing
something that fashion
over their body.
Now I can mix into the crowd.
But I don't know why all these
people are laughing at me.
After that, I understood
that men's clothes is
different and women's clothes
is different.
Day's clothes different
and night's clothes different.
Playing's clothes is different.
Eating's clothes is different.
Within my clothes I found
a kind of photo.
I slowly realize that this photo
is important to survive in this world.
That if I give this photo,
I can get food to eat.
So I started to collect
pictures of this old man.
What man...
Why do you give me these ...?
This for bookstore, man...
Yes... right... here
is your carrots.
Now I realize that this picture
is useful in one paper only.
The other papers, the photo
is useful for nothing.
Now the need for money and clothes
I will always get from the dancing car.
It is my bank, and it
is also my tailor.
There's one time, I got
a strange clothes...
Where I don't need to show
any picture or photo...
And the food comes
to me on its own.
Mr. take this.
I realized that if I want
to find my remote
control I have to learn
this world language.
Without language, no
work can be done here.
Just like the man that I want to tell
that his style has some defect in my opinion.
I have a feeling
that I've damaged his fashion.
Here, let me correct it
just the way it was.
I met him down the road.
Some rascals hit
him and runaway.
The mind's not good.
He didn't respond anything.
Maybe he is deaf?
Oii...!
He hear. But give no answers.
It looks like a firm's hit
in the head.
Its memory lost.
Memory gone.
Do you remember who hits you?
Remember car plate number?
Remember anything?
Something?
Let's go brother.
Come with me.
As long as your memory don't come
back to you you will be my guests.
They say to cure memory lost...
Go to where your memory lost...
And you can get it back.
I've seen it in film.
What's he talking... It's important
to understand now...
I need to hold his hand
and transfer his language to me.
The name of the car is...
Memory gone, and now can't
differentiate man from woman?
Hold on a sec.
Look at my driver's license.
Gender.
Male. Man. Human.
Rascal, Bastard.
If I want to go
back to my home...
I definitely have
to catch someone's hand.
Mate, I met colorful friend.
He is a strange man.
You've been hard for us boy.
Do not do it... so...
The boy has truly
become my guest...
I can understand
your pain, brother.
But don't openly hold hands.
Although it's a beautiful thing,
but it can be life threatening too.
You can wait no longer.
Come, come with me.
Here if you grasp anyone hands,
or legs, no one will kill you.
Come here, come on...
This is a good place.
Here they are very
nice and pretty.
Everyone inside was willing
to take my hand and take me home.
And then I've met a gentle girl...
Who has peace of mind.
Phuljaria.
Phuljaria, take him
to the honeymoon room.
Phuljaria was sitting
there with Patience.
In the meantime, I...
Over six hours...
Took her language into my body.
Pronunciation... X by J
I took everything
from her inside me.
First time, you useless...?
It's first step
before the start, or what...?
Yes.
Where are you come from?
I came from very far away.
You have not even heard
the name of it.
But you talk like us.
It's you who teach me...
SO I speak exactly
like you, sister.
Hey, This sister will show you your mother!
Go, get out from here.
Brother...
Brother. Wake up.
Get up brother.
Brother.
You're talking, brother.
I want your help, brother.
What magic did
Phuljaria do to you?
Come with me now.
This memory has a direct
connection to something.
This thing we must tell
the doctor, brother.
And you can be cured.
There is a very important job. Brother.
Please come with me, hurry.
Stop here. Stop here.
Brother...
That day, the chain
was taken from me here.
I want that chain, brother.
- Is it precious?
- Very much.
Listen brother.
The thief is from our village. But
the chain must have reach Delhi.
If you can trace where he sold
it, you can capture him.
So I have to go there, brother.
Where?
Delhi.
- Sir...
- What?
My remote control
has been stolen.
Are you drunk? Is finding
your remote TV a police job?
It's not a TV remote control.
Then what?
I cannot say that.
But it was fixed to a neck chain.
And it's worth much more.
Where did the theft happen?
At Mandawa.
It's stolen in Mandawa...
And you come to Delhi
to find it...?
But the thief must have
come to Delhi. So?
So where can I find the thief?
Hey weirdo. There
are two million people in this city...
Policeman is human. Not God.
Only God can help you.
Hold God's two legs.
He's the only one able to help you.
Only God know. How can we know?
God know where, get out.
Have faith in the God, son.
Who is this Bhagwan?
That can help me.
I see that everyone
mentioned his name.
After what I saw,
I was freaked out.
The people of this world...
Made Them as pictures...
They themselves made a place
for Him in one place.
There are even streets
in His house.
Hundreds of thousands
of people go to Him.
He solve everyone's problems
for a small amount of charges.
This kind of magic didn't
exist in my world.
I could not believe it. But I thought
I should try it once or twice.
Give me a God, brother.
Which one you want? This here is Rs.20...
50... 100... 500...
What's the difference
between Rs.20 and 500 ones?
Only the size, everything else is the same.
The Rs.20's will work too, right?
Ok, Rs.15 then...
O God, I am very hungry.
Give me something to eat.
I've become totally
out of control.
This God is working.
Now I can go to my home.
God, someone took
my remote control.
Please bring it back,
I want to go home.
Sir, is this God out of battery?
I just used it once,
then it broke.
What do you mean...? -I mean,
put a new battery in him.
It doesn't need any battery -Then
why this does not work...?
Is it a defect one? No,
I made it perfect.
Is it you who created this God?
Yes, from my hands.
Did you created God
or did God created you?
God created us all.
But we make only His sculptures.
Why create his sculptures?
So that we can pray to Him.
Tell Him about our joys
and sorrows.
There's been installed
a communication device?
How do we hear God say?
God does not need
any transmitter.
He hear directly.
If He hear directly, then
what's the need for sculpture?
What am I going to do
with this man...
Trying to end our business, huh?
What is Your problem?
My remote control has been stolen.
I asked God...
To tell me where it is.
Are you Peekay (PK AS IN DRUNK)?
What does that mean?
Bro, this small God cannot do
something big like that...
He can't capture the thief,
the legs is short.
Go inside the temple.
There is a big God.
Catch his feet.
He run very fast.
Give Him this nuts and some money to him.
Your job will be done.
That will be Rs.200.
Everyone was waiting for their turn
carrying nuts and money.
To make their work done.
Two hours later, it was my turn.
Oh God...
God. Give me back
my remote control.
B... Where is it?
Hurry, please.
Hold on, my remote
control's not received yet.
Sir. He's not getting the job
done, I already gave money.
You job will be done.
When will it be...?
Who can say when my son?
Your job will be done.
Move it. -But when
can I get my item?
Do not hold the queue, Go ahead.
What if someone else get my item?
Are you drunk? Hold on, ma'am.
What are you doing ...?
But where can I get my goods? -You
will find it in a mental hospital.
What? Paid money here,
and delivery at mental hospital?
Get this man out! Hey,
at least give me receipt.
Give me receipt so that I can ask
the man when can I get delivery?
Go on. Please go. But.
But my remote control.
I can't find my sandals.
Must be someone take it away.
Wear someone
else's sandals then.
That's what happen
at temples anyway.
Someone's take a full payment,
but never did the job.
Say his name.
Bhagwan (GOD) - say
the full name.
Don't know his full name.
Where'd he live?
There, in front of the temple.
You gave the money
to his own hand?
No, I put it in a box.
He said that your job will be done?
He does not speak.
- Why? He's mute?
- Maybe...
- Absolutely.
- Right...
Tell me his appearance.
He looks like this.
Just the size is large.
Come here... Come here...
Are you Peekay (PK AS IN DRUNK)?
(YOU'RE DRUNK?)
Err... Yes, but how do you all know that?
Am I blind?
20 years of police work. Just by seeing
I can tell who's drunk and who's not.
Mr. Singh, search him.
Give me his ID.
Dr. D'Mello.
Oh Dr. why did you drink so much
that you forgot your religion?
You've mistaken
between temple and church.
You go to your church.
To your own God.
Church...?
- Get out of here.
- But my item.
Beat it. Get out.
Because of you, God
have been crossed.
What?
Nailed? God?
- When?
- 2000 years ago.
For your sins.
But what did I do?
I came here only just now.
Are you PK?
- Yup.
- God is watching you. He's looking at your behavior.
Where?
Where? Where is He?
- What's in that cup?
- Wine.
Wine...
At that time, I understand
just the thing...
God have grown bored
with coconut water...
Now he's having fun with wine.
Now I will give wine.
So I started to collect money.
Some money I found
from the dancing car.
And some money,
from that gentleman.
Who stand at every bridge
everyday...
Who give me as much
money as I want.
Sir, is there any nearby God's house here?
Yes, just forward ahead.
Hold on.
What's in your hand - Wine.
For God. Where is He?
This madam looks very sad.
So I thought to know what happened,
I had to hold her hand.
How dare you disturbed
a widow, asshole.
How do you know this
madam is a widow? You
don't see she's wearing a white saree?
Asshole.
Is everything fine?
- I'm very sorry about the death of your husband.
- What? When?
How do I know when? You're
wearing a white clothes.
I'm getting married that's why I wear it.
No, all people wear it for death.
They wear black for death, stupid.
Tell him. Get out of here.
Are all three of you
husband's dead?
Hey, I'm still alive!
You...!
After a lot of chasing
I came to understand...
That this world don't
have just one God.
But there are so many Gods.
And each of these Gods
have different rules.
And each Gods open
their own company...
People have religion for them.
And each of these religion
have different manager.
In this world, everyone
have only one religion...
Meaning that they belong
only to one company.
And it's their company's God
which they worship, not of the others.
So, I'm a member
of which company then?
Which God should I pray to?
If I want to know about my remote
control, knowing this is very crucial.
What are you doing?
Where are the marks?
What marks?
Religion's marks.
How do I know which company
this kid belongs to?
Where's the God's mark, brother?
Security!
It's getting hard to find
out my religion.
Now I can do just one thing
I will worship every Gods
in every religion.
One of Them must
be the right One.
And will hear to what I want.
O God...
Where are you...?
Where are you... God...?
You have many names...
You have many faces...
There's so many ways
to find you...
I walked all the ways...
But you could not be found...
I cannot understand
what you want...
Where are you... God...?
I've had a mass confusion, God
I must have done
something wrong,
That makes you not heard me out.
Please tell me.
Show me the way.
Please...
I'm asking You, begging You...
I'll knelt down on my forehead
I've ring the bell for you.
I've speak
through loudspeaker too.
I've read Book of Gita...
Koran...
And verses of Bible.
Your different managers...
Is saying different thing
from the others...
One says to sacrifices
on Monday...
Another says to sacrifices
on Tuesday...
One says to pray
before the sunrise...
Another says to pray
after the sunset.
One says to worship cattle...
Another says to sacrifice it...
One says go to temples without any shoes,
another says go to church wearing boots.
This... who's right
and who's wrong.
I do not understand anything.
By mistake a came here...
I want to go home.
Whatever you say I will do.
Just. Send me home.
Please!
Say something.
Where are you hiding?
Please give me an answer.
Please...
Hey, why'd you lock it? Today,
I'll not let you leave.
Open the door,
it's my entry qeueu.
Shiva, destroyed the existing...
Don't fear anything.
Security!
Who are you? You
don't recognize me?
I'm PK.
(DRUNK)
Security.
Anyone out there? People come to drink
here. I hold a show in toilet?
Open the door.
First bring my remote control.
Which remote control?
My spaceship's remote control.
Spaceship?
Did you forget? How
many times I told you
I'm not from this world,
I came from faraway world.
This way you. You find
my remote control, then
I return to my home.
You understand, right?
Oh brother, leave me alone.
- I have small children.
- I know.
Your kids, They're not
so small anymore.
They can live alone at home. You give me
my remote control and then go to your family.
Lord save me.
Is there other God above you?
Where is He...?
Now presenting
the dance of Shiva.
The Fearless - Help me!
Help me...
Help me!
I'm at Himalayas mountain...
Remembering God.
Suddenly there's a light.
Great light of nowhere.
The small light was raised
pointed down to earth.
I looked at it.
Remember that God is about.
It quickly became a connection.
God. Pray to You...
What is this light?
In the cold winter it
make me feel warm.
God said.
This is from Shiva's. Take it...
And built a shrine.
This is only appearance
devotees,
All that pain out of.
Do you want to see it?
Shiva's part of drum.
Bola Bola Bam Bam.
Bola Bola Bam Bam thanks God...
Do not stop him, let him come.
Come on, son, come on...
Boy, not there. Come here.
Say what you want from here...
Bam Bam Bole. Thank God.
Where are you God?
Come on, on stage.
I want to thank you Lord.
He is here.
I met Him in toilet.
I request for my property, but He ran.
I thought He's running away...
But no, he took me here.
To my property, thank
God, Thank God.
This is not a piece of Shiva.
This one belongs to me. The
delivery mistakenly send it to you.
And your item may have
been send to someone else.
Just ask him. He's here. God
please come forward. Tell them.
Alright, I'll take
my property, ok?
Oh. It belongs to me.
Since when did you feel that you
came from another planet?
Listen...
You've to meet a psychiatrist,
mental doctor.
Now go ma'am.
- Rs.500 is able to give you so much punishment.
- Wait a minute.
This is my card.
There's my number...
If you like, I can fix
you for an appointment.
If you find time, call me, OK?
Thank you Mr. Pandit.
Do you think my story is a lie.
Then go proceed
with your suicide dog on TV.
Nikku...
That is your destiny.
Mr. Pandit, Mr. Pandit...
I want to go back
just two minutes.
What is going on these
going inside outside?
Do this, give me another Rs.500,
and take this man with you.
Nikku, The Suicide Dog...
When did I tell you about it?
You never did.
Then how do you know about it?
When you hold my hand.
Then I know...
You're doing a suicide
dog's story.
You were thinking, if this story went awry.
Now Nikku is your destiny...
Do not lie. I must have told you about it.
Tell the truth.
I'm not capable of lying. Lie used mouth,
and I only use mind to communicate.
Our world can just
holding hands...
- Give me your hand.
- No way.
Give it!
Help me, son, my wife
is critical...
Hospital has asked
for Rs.1000 to cure her.
Only Rs. 500 is not enough...
If you can give Rs.500 son, my wife can...
I'll give it.
Here - If you give me your address,
I'll send money back.
Uncle, money order will not
reach my home, you keep it.
Thanks son.
Uncle...
Take another Rs.100.
To give tip.
Boy, God bless you.
You prove it already.
You cannot read anyone's mind.
Don't you understand? That man
took the money by fooling you.
There is no hospital in this
neighborhood. I know.
He and his wife is taking
a meal at a five-star hotel.
Today, his wife's 75th birthday.
For 75 years he and his wife
never got to a five-star hotel.
He collected his pension
money little by little.
Then his wife ordered an ice cream,
the price had gone up a bit.
Then he came here
to ask for money.
Make up anything...?
Madam, I told you
our world don't lie.
The rest is up to you.
Wait, wait, hold on.
Give it with your hand.
Today's your birthday,
give happy opportunity...
I told you no one lies
in our world.
Have you told anyone...
Have you told anyone
that you an alien?
If I said I will be put in lab.
They will cut me inside out.
So why did you tell me?
Since I came here,
I only take people's money.
No one has given me money.
You're the first one given me by putting
in the box for charity in 5000.
I've a feeling that you're
a gentleman, the one I can trust.
I will find your remote
control, PK.
How's that?
Now I don't know yet.
But you definitely will go
back to your house.
That's my promise.
Why are you looking like that?
At you.
It's not everyday alien
come to my house.
So... in your world, they hear
everyone out of the way, like you?
The same. And
they all walks nude?
Don't you feel strange?
See that bird, sitting
there nude...
Is it feel strange?
If it'd wear clothes,
then it looks strange.
PK
I did not sleep
all night yesterday.
I was thinking how to get
your remote control.
Hello. Connect to Balbir
Singh, Room No. 4.
Wrong number.
Is this not a hospital?
Bro, you get a wrong number,
since yesterday I said that.
How did I get the wrong number?
I have save the phone number personally.
Okay, so what did you thought?
Hello. Connect to Balbir
Singh, Room No. 4.
Oh... you call late -why?
Balbir Singh died this morning.
What do you mean ...?
But how did the surgery
hemorrhage can die?
It's unfortunate.
But don't worry.
Let's write in death certificate
it's a heart attack.
So that family's reputation
will not be ashamed.
So come on, OK, take the body.
Ok - ok then bye.
How can you say that?
It's nothing, Now he'll go to hospital.
Think about it.
He'll see his friend is live
and how happy he will be.
He always call for wrong number, so
I'm having a little fun with him.
- Fun ...?
- PK I was joking
I understood. I saw the whole game.
They're kidding.
Mr. Tapaswi had called God...
He citing prayer and whatever...
But all his calls
is wrong number.
A person who answered
his call is joking with him.
Or else, how can he get
my remote control from Shiva?
It looks like...
Those who speak with God in this world have
a messed up telecommunications system.
Every call went
to the wrong number.
What do you mean?
I always thought...
Why God did not
answer my problem.
They say to scroll
down to get to him.
Tell me. We are all children
of God, right?
So which dad will tell
their children...
Scroll down to me
and everything will be done.
Have your dad ever told you that?
"Child, scroll
down to me if you want
to have a new outfit".
And there's giving
away milk too...
If the call go to the right
number, then what will God say?
What will He say?
He'll say, every day millions of hungry
children are on the road sleeping in Delhi.
Let them drink milk. Why
would I drink the milk?
I'm sure there's someone joking with us.
Like what you did just now.
PK think that Tapaswi
is an honourable man.
But I won't have him
confuse right now.
Because in my head,
there's a nonsense idea.
An idea that can bring
back PK's remote control.
- Who is this PK?
- Who? Where he come from? I know nothing of that.
But he can see this world
unlike any of us see this world.
- What does that mean?
- Means...
If he see you smoke, he'd call police
and tell someone's want to suicide.
Why? -Cause the cigarettes
packing has cancer picture.
What do you think?
War.
I would like PK to talk
I want him to talk
in a show on television.
Evaluate some values
in people's mind.
Jaggu, there's already three marks
on my right side butt...
Now you want the left side too so
that both sides are balanced, or what?
No Jerry, it's important
to put PK.
He will explain with love,
that everyone has call a wrong number.
Tapaswi can not imagine
how he would deal with this PK.
Jerry, Jerry.
He's sitting out there.
See him once.
I challenge you, you cannot
answer his questions. Trust me.
Sir, your cigarette fell just now.
Oh, thank you.
This is not mine.
Kamasutra, Strawberry flavor.
I hate strawberries! Ask others...
It's not mine.
Madam, is this yours?
How dare you?
- Just check your wallet. Maybe something's missing.
- Who are you? You rude.
Uncle, this is yours, then?
No, it's not.
PK it is his.
If you want to ask
anything, ask him.
Come in.
What is this?
Its condom.
What'd it do? To control
world population.
- How's that?
- Have to wear it.
While having sex.
You control world population
by wearing it? How?
It's not me wearing it.
Millions of people wear those things.
All of them get it from you?
Everybody's got those things.
I have two questions. Just ask PK...
ask him.
Why is that when people lost money
they all say "this is mine, this is mine".
But when condoms is lost, everyone say
"this is not mine, this is not mine".
Here, sex is a private matter.
How? -How can someone shout
that "today I will be having sex".
But then at marriage party...
There's crackers,
orchestra, dance...
It looks like to tell everybody
in the city, "today I'm having sex."
Why? What?
I do not have an answer
to your question.
But I do have a job for you.
Let's go, before this
guy change your mind.
Watch you back now Mr. Tapaswi,
Now it's my turn.
Mr. Tapaswi meet his followers here
everyday. They're talking about God.
We go in, listen
to his phone calls.
If you think that he is wrong,
then stop him immediately.
Make him understand
that he is calling the wrong number.
If I do that, will he return
my remote control?
If he understand that what you say then
he will understand that chain is a joke...
He'll return your remote control.
Yes, I'll make him understand.
My wife has paralyzed
for six months...
Doctors not able to do anything.
I want...
O God...
Praise to you...
Yes...
Do tell...
Where?
God it's your choice.
- Have you heard Prathan...?
- No.
It's in Himalayas.
Go there by train...
From there, take a bus...
To GANGTOK...
Then to Padyathra
(BY WALK)...
Stay for 8 days and pray...
At God's house.
Go with love. And
your job will be done.
Wrong number, this
is wrong number.
What is?
Wrong number.
Tapaswi, you spoke to God with a messed
up telecommunication technology.
Every call you make
is wrong number...
The one answering is a duplicate one...
He's joking with you...
What are you trying to say?
I'll make you understand...
We all God's children, right?
Yes, so what? -So, what'd you tell
your sick child if they ask your help?
Does you give him a cure?
Or tell him that...
Go 4000 km from this house...
There's one more house there...
Tell the one's in there
the same problem...
If he go to the real God, He
would say, Son, your wife is ill...
Go to someone else...
you're still alive...
If you're dead,
then come to me...
Now, you still alive aren't you?
Right?
I can prove it, someone
took a joke for you.
Tapaswi, please
call God again...
Ask Him if He can give
some guarantee to this cure...
Uncle, before you got written
guarantee, do not leave here.
Call Him now, let's see here...
Tapaswi's lunch
time has arrived...
Tapaswi, that duplicate God...
Has given my item to you...
It's a fraud...
Fraud. Fraud...
Until now, man don't even see
God or heard from Him...
What God tells us to do...
Has been conveyed
by His managers only...
PK has presented an important issue.
What is?
Is these Manager's voice
has reached the true God?
- No.
- He makes us understand that...
Is the calls made has
reached God, or a fraud?
- It's wrong numbers.
- So tell us PK, How can people react to this situation?
As long as the phone
line's not repaired...
Our problem will arise again and again...
We need to help each other.
PK tells important thing. As long as the Managers
can bring us to the right God...
We will not look to their aid.
We'll help each other.
PK says not to build
this temple.
He told us that chain belongs to him.
What is in your pocket?
Do you smoke?
- Yes.
- You do drink, right?
Yes, occasionally drink. You're a smoker.
Drink alcohol.
Knowing that both is poison.
The government gives permission.
Factory produced these poison.
The shops open sale these poison.
No one wants to question these.
But when I want to build in this
earth for the devotees of God...
Just want to build one temple...
Then why are these questions?
If you want to ask
question, go ask those...
Who try to stop
building the temple.
Who is this PK?
He's not Pervez Khan.
Not even Pasha Kaman too...
I ask you all...
If you want to ask, ask that PK.
What's his religion?
What's his religion, his sect?
Long time ago there's someone
wanted to destroy a temple.
Put our temples destroyed.
Today, someone else want
to do the same thing.
Yes, but...
Tapaswi, call your God now, you want
to know what's my religion, right?
But first, ask Him what is His
children's religion...
What the hell are you doing here?
Cal Him, ask Him. Ask Him...
I don't have to call God for this.
Even I can answer this.
This is Hindu, Christian, this
is Sikh, this one of the Jains,
And this girl
is from your nation...
Guys, please tell Tapaswi
your names now...
Hello, my name
is Sukhwinder Singh...
Assalamu alaikum, I'm
Abbas Ali Yaqub...
Hello, I'm Veer Jain.
Hi. I'm Christopher D. Souza.
I'm Jhaggat Jhandni Sahni.
Confused, right?
I have change
their appearance...
Religion's is always connect
to appearance, right?
I'll show you. Come here...
With all this
appearance, a Sikh.
Take off the turban,
becomes a Hindu.
Take off mustache,
then a Muslim.
This whole change was designed,
by that wrong number fake god.
If it's the right God, then it would be
marks on the body right? Show yours...
- Mine?
- Why turn back? Take off clothes, check it...
Why be shy?
Come on, removed all you clothes,
show your marks to Tapaswi...
Why be shy? Ok, I too
will take my clothes off.
Look at this.
Any marked, huh?
Is there?
Nothing right?
Have any sign?
And this too -Hey...
put this man out.
What is this, huh? I'm
going to prove it.
Goat cast eyes.
Jaggu.
Stop this program!
When you're 40 days born,
you got a name by Tapaswi.
The one who gave you name...
Can take it out/back too...
Dad, he gave me name
Jhaggat Jhandni...
Who want that kind of name...
You!
How much money you want, huh?
You're doing all this
for money, right?
No.
You'll go to hell... Haven't
you any fear of God?
Thank you, Father. Thank you.
I give the idea but you
understand the rest of it...
This game is about fear. That wrong number
case did not just make fun out of us.
He's taking our fear and exploit it too.
Do you understand?
PK Can you make my father
understand too?
Yeah. I can. I can prove it too.
Let's go.
I don't have time to spend
for this nonsense.
Dad, if this is nonsense,
I stop this program.
Father, This college is weird place.
Students here are all pretty scared.
Now I'm going to do business
about this fear. I'll show you.
Come.
This is the factory machine.
Invest some money.
And this is Unger...
Now wait. 15 minutes
to double investments.
Look. Look.
He's trapped.
Hot hot tea. Look
there, man selling tea.
He's making expensive investment. Green
tea, sugar, thermos, water, glass,
And here it's just stone
and a little red...
Hot tea, hot tea.
He have to call
for customer there...
And here, by itself,
long customer queue.
Come on, hurry,
others want it too...
There, they bow
down to the customer.
But here, the customer
bow down to it.
Look there. He has so much
fear, he plunged there.
That wrong number man is making a business.
Fear business...
He knows that those who scared
will go to temples.
You're pretty scared too.
Remove these.
Don't ever question religion.
It's about faith and believe.
If God want us to not
raise questions...
They said that if we reason with him,
He'll never give his miracle.
These religion's man, if they can't
answer, then they will beat us.
People become afraid,
and shut their mouths.
But now, we will not
shut up anymore.
Until now PK only ask one question,
but now, he'll ask thousands of questions.
So guys, take up your phones.
If you heard something wrong
number, record it on video.
We will broadcast
your recorded footages.
Pick up phones, and questions...
Baba, Baba...
One question Baba. If you can
make gold from your hand.
Why can't you end
the poverty in our country?
Answer please.
If you manage to make gold.
Why not aid us?
Answer.
Om... Om...
This is wrong number.
Jaggu come with me.
Come with me.
Just come.
I'm working. Come...
Whole country send
us wrong numbers.
You did a terrific job.
Look now.
He says, if we give the bull
grass, we can get a job.
Should I include this cow in my bio data,
and go from a company to a company?
Or should I write
a monster.com bio data.
This is wrong number. There is more.
There is more.
He's saying become Christian,
or else I'll go to hell.
If God wants me to become Christian,
I would born in a Christian family.
Now why the need to switch religion.
This, wrong number.
Everybody here wants
to go to school.
But they said, if we go
to schools, they'll shoot us.
How can our God
be so low that...
If these children learned, He'll be angry?
This is wrong number.
That is what is written
in our book.
He have for the whole
universe, a master plan.
- You have to accept it.
- Outside the temple, you sale this book for Rs.10.
It's written in page four.
Read it...
"And I will have a son".
Meaning that, buy
and read a Rs10 book...
And you can destroy
that master plan...
PK Your program has been quite popular.
SMS around the world is coming.
Look, another one.
What happened?
Father send me a short message.
He's ashamed of his daughter.
You know?
I was ten years old when...
First time I write a poem.
For my father.
Everyone says I look
like my mother...
Everyone is right.
But I'm my father's daughter...
When I finished
recite my poem...
Everyone clapped...
But then, there's whistles
from far...
When the applause end...
That one whistle
and clap doesn't end...
It was my dad.
He was so proud of me.
But the message he sent today...
Ashamed of you.
Your father's belief...
And this thing happened...
We will show him these
wrong number...
Again and again until he come
to his sense...
The day will never come PK.
Do not worry, get up.
Get up, you know
what our world do when we sad?
- What is it PK?
- Do it with me.
Batteries charge automatic.
What?
Copy me - PK.
What we are doing PK?
- Close your eyes.
- How can I copy you then?
Ok fine, open eyes...
Questions letter is more
than money in the money box...
Your pictures, books, medicines oil,
everything has stopped selling.
On Facebook and twitters also
millions of negative comments.
- Just this?
- This is the only one supported you.
The curses is in these ones.
Do something...
One more day and we can
be shut down...
Phone that man...
He got a lot of questions, huh?
I'll ask him one question.
- Hey Jaggu.
- What?
What happened?
Tapaswi wants to be in our show.
He wants to talk with PK.
That's awesome, PK will win.
It would be an amazing show.
You're prepare PK,
start advertising.
Do not forget...
"One more question"
6 o'clock Sunday afternoon.
Our boy has become a star.
Look, my bro's become a star.
He walked naked... naked...
I made him a star.
He sit in TV. And me?
What am I doing in this village.
I should be in there drinking with them...
A big star...
Became a star... heh...
PK, some Dheeru Singh
wants to speak.
- Brother...?
- Take that line...
- Brother.
- Oh, boy.
So... you became a star now?
- Where are you brother?
- Right now I'm in Mandawa.
I will come to you tomorrow.
And bring a present for you.
The one stole your item,
is here with me.
He sold your item at 40,000.
- Ask me to whom?
- To whom?
Tapaswi...
God said...
Shiva's drum broke down.
Take it...
Take it and built a shrine.
Because this is appearance...
Hello. What happened?
The one stole my remote...
- That thief got caught.
- What?
- Really?
- Brother said...
The thief sold he remote
to Tapaswi...
Then it's game
over for Tapaswi...
Take him home...
And tell Tapaswi to give
you that remote
control... Or else we show
this thief on TV...
Tapaswi got my remote control
on Himalaya's mountain...
This mean that Tapaswi a liar...
That means...
It's not a wrong number
duplicate God...
It's Tapaswi who got
it first hand...
Jaggu do you know of this?
Remember when you first told
me about the wrong numbers?
Tapaswi who calls God...
They all are wrong number.
I immediately realized
that you're misunderstanding.
But I did not explain your mess.
Because if you told that.
Tapaswi a liar, everybody
would have laughed at you.
People want something
new every day, PK.
This wrong number
you told people...
They are deeply touched
by its uniqueness.
Today they're with you PK.
This is the wrong number.
My plan worked, PK. Understand
that you got your remote control.
Friend...
You'll go to your home
tomorrow...
Gone...
We'll never meet again...
I'll feel lonely, friend...
I'll really miss you.
Will you stop me?
(FROM GOING)...
How can I stop you?
I'm serious.
I can work. I'll correct
everything.
I can settle down here...
You can find someone for me who can
spend time with me. Right?
I will marry her. Or what?
Who can marry you?
Why is that?
Your wife will be in trouble
to introduce you.
Meet my husband.
His name is PK
(DRUNK)
That's not my name. Everyone
call me that, nonsense.
- PK (DRUNK)
- I'll change my name.
Would you...
suggest my new name?
- Whatever name you like.
- Look.
The person's name
and his personality...
Have to be match.
Yes, you're right.
So... how is my personality?
Let me show a demo...
Kaka seriously said...
The difference
between name and face...
I do not want to hear poetry.
Say something else.
The name and image,
the difference...
Damn. How to make
her understand?
Get another name...
Get another face...
Fire has completely cooled...
That's very good... Here I have so
many cards and different names...
You choose any name. Look
inside and choose one you like...
Tandu Ram...
Another...
Tuttari Singh.
Sarfaraaz...
What happened? There
are more inside...
Jaggu What happened?
Nothing.
Hey brother...
One terrorist organization has claimed
responsibility for the attack.
They say this
is only one small example.
This is what happens
to those who attacked us.
We will defend our God.
Where are you going, PK?
The show. No, you
don't need to go.
It's important to go.
"One more question."
In this special program,
for all of you...
Where we bring together PK and...
Hold on...
Wait a bit.
Give me...
What is this thing?
God said that...
This is His broke down's drum...
But he said...
It belongs to him.
God said...
Build a temple.
And he said...
Don't make temple...
Who should we listen?
Is it God?
Or. This guy?
Wearing a yellow helmet,
and gave these out.
See this... look here...
First he said...
God is missing...
Then he called God a fraud...
Tomorrow he might say...
That God has died.
Boy, what do you want?
A world which doesn't have God?
Are you... so desperate...
To hurt people's feelings?
Some people do not
have bread to eat.
Some don't have roof to stay...
Those people don't even have
friend to talk to...
Everyday how many people kill
themselves, do you know?
Wrists cut, hang neck on fan...
why?
Because they do not have hope...
If God come forward...
Put tikka in forehead...
Put some thread
around their hand...
Giving them some hope to live...
So who are you to deny
this hope from them?
And if you...
Really want to snatch God
from those people's lives...
Tell me, what do you want
to give them instead?
You always said these wrong number.
Wrong number. Right?
So tell everyone here now,
what is the correct number...?
You're exactly right Tapaswi...
There's one time, when...
I too, could not
find food to eat.
I don't have home to stay.
I cried a lot.
I don't even have friends.
I only had one thing...
God...
Everyday I thought
tomorrow will be better...
God will show me some way out...
I agree...
That putting faith in God...
One can find hope...
The difficulties will go away... courage
will come. Will get strength...
But I have one question.
Which God should I believe in?
You all say that,
it's only one God.
I say, no...
There are two Gods...
One is the one who created
us all.
The other one is the one created
by people like you.
We know nothing about the God
who made us all.
But the God people
like you made...
Is exactly like you...
Liar. Pretend to act...
Giving false promises.
Meeting rich people sooner...
Letting the poor neglected...
Happy when get praised...
People are afraid
to even say word.
My right number is very simple.
The God who created us all...
Put faith in Him...
And the God people like you created...
The duplicate god...
Destroy it...
You talking about our God
and you'd think I will sit idle?
Boy, we will protect our God.
You can protect God ...?
You ...?
This world is very small...
This world is very small
compared to the whole universe.
And you... by sitting in this little world,
this little place, this little street...
Saying that you want to protect the God
who created all these universes?
He doesn't need
your protection...
He can protect Himself...
Today, one of my friends
died trying to help me...
I was left only his shoe.
Stop trying to defend God.
Or else in this world...
People will not
only leaving shoes.
One Muslim blasted bomb...
And one Hindu Guru...
Sitting here listening
to your speech.
Who's Hindu and who's Muslim...
Where are the marks...
show me...
This difference created
by you people, not God...
And this...
This world's dangerous
wrong number...
Is the most dangerous
Where people dies.
Torn each other apart.
This kind of wrong
number, you...
Lied to Jaggu's parent...
and separate her from Sarfaraaz...
What wrong number? -That
Sarfaraz will lie to her...
That Muslims are hypocrites,
who said that...?
So... he did deceived her.
It's not a lie.
Hold on. What is this ...?
- Look.
- You wait.
You're saying that...
The prophecy I said
about Sarfaraaz...
Is a lie?
Yes, that's what I said.
So prove it. Prove it
that my prophecy is a lie...
If you cannot prove it...
You've to touch my feet
and apologize...
And you must admit in front of everybody,
that you have launch a lie to me...
And if I can prove it?
Don't PK.
That, my son, is yours.
Conditions agreed...
Please focus the camera
on Jhagat Jhananni.
Jhaggat Jhandni... I hope that,
You would honestly
answer my questions.
In Belgium, you've been in love
with a Pakistani boy.
True? Or false?
Why would we discuss
about my personal life?
On Friday...
I told one of my prophecies
that...
This boy will betray you...
The next day,
You went to marriage
registrar office...
But the boy did not come.
True or false?
Yes, he didn't come, can
you please stop this?
Now...
You'll come to my feet?
Or I bring my feet to you...?
Sarfaraz did not betray you.
Let it go, PK. Please. No, tell
everyone what happened that day.
- Please PK.
- Only once.
For me.
I was in the marriage
registrar office...
I got a letter... Sarfaraaz
came to gave that letter?
No.
One little boy sent me that. -His
name written in that letter?
No.
Then how do you know
that Sarfaraz sent it?
It can be that...
That letter is for another girl?
There were no other girls there?
There's one right?
Who'd carried a cat?
She'd gave you that cat
to hold, right?
Did you recognize the boy
who sent you that letter?
- No.
- Did he recognized you?
- So how did he know...
To give you that letter?
Could it be that he forgot...
And gave that letter...
To anyone there?
He gave you that letter.
You read it.
Then you did not
call Sarfaraz...
Why would you assume
all this of Sarfaraz?
Because this Tapaswi...
Had given you
the wrong number...
That Muslims are all deceivers.
Sarfaraz didn't
deceived you, Jaggu.
What's going on here?
This cats and dogs.
I mean, you can tell any story...
And I'll just sit here listening
to whatever you talk?
Hold on. We'll know
the truth in this show...
Jaggu take out your phone.
Call Sarfaraz.
Jaggu Hurry,
"This number did not exist."
Another number? Friend,
college, something.
Come on Jaggu.
Belgian university. Right.
Hello.
Hello, I need to get in touch
with one of your grads student?
Sarfaraz Yusuf. Yeah, He
left for Pakistan last year.
Contact.
Has he left a number? Sorry, We're
not authorize to give out info.
Ma'am, this is really important.
Email us your
request so I can forward
it to student affairs.
Have a nice day dear.
Pakistan's number?
His home number? No.
Think, Jaggu think.
I have a part time job
at Pakistan Embassy.
He has a part time job
Nitu, call the Pakistan
Embassy, Belgium...
And put it on loudspeaker.
Salam... Pakistan Embassy.
Hello.
Is there a student
from Lahore working there?
Sarfaraz Yusuf?
Is your name Jaggu?
Hello, is your name Jaggu?
Yes, how do you know?
That call came.
That Delhi girl's call came.
Jaggu's call came.
Come on everyone.
India's call came, hurry come...
Ma'am,
Sarfaraz Yusuf call us
everyday, 9a.m, from Lahore.
And in all his call,
he asked only one thing...
Is there any call from India,
Jaggu's call for me?
We told him no, and he called
off the phone.
He make everyone crazy.
You hang in there,
I'll contact him.
Hello.
- Sarfaraz Yusuf?
- Yes, Salam...
From where are you talking?
From Lahore, why?
From where are you talking
right about this time?
I'm in my house, why?
Are there any chairs around you?
If there is, please sit down. You're
going to drop hearing this...
Oh sorry. I don't
understand what you said.
There's a call
from Delhi for you.
Now talk to her...
- Hello.
- Sarfaraz...
Jaggu...
Hello.
Hello, you're not Jaggu?
- You did came to the marriage registrar office?
- Yes I did.
But you're not there.
Why you didn't call me?
What to do?
I got your letter.
It was written, do not
try to contact me.
I knew your family
had pressured you.
But I don't know... Jaggu...
I've a feeling that...
You will try to call me...
I called you a lot Jaggu...
What to do?
I have your wrong number...
Just now a friend found
me the right number...
Thank you, son.
Please hold this...
PK, you're going to take a bag
full of batteries with you?
I can't find them there, no?
But what will you do
with so many batteries?
This tape
recording's sound, right?
I want to hear them, at my home.
What kind of sound?
That of everyone's in this
world...
Animals, music
and traffic noise.
You're gonna hear
the traffic noise?
If I miss this world. Then...
I will hear them all...
Hey Wait ...!
There's a second bag still...
PK, let it go...
How can I? It's all batteries
in there...
Listen...
You can listen to everyone
in your world?
Then they all walks nude?
What're you looking?
Something in my house?
You know?
I was ten years old.
When I first write a poem.
It is written for my father.
Everyone says I look
like my mother.
Everyone is right...
Poetry that is...
Ensuring sound a few big story.
You're so cute.
One more to a friend who...
No animal sound nor music...
Nothing of traffic sound...
Every tape was just my voice.
I got it.
I was...
What did you record in this, PK?
I told you. Animal,
music, traffic's sound...
When I recall of this Earth...
Then, I'll listen to the tape.
I'll wave my hand
to you from there...
Like this...
I see you from there,
when you'll come...
Get the time...
You didn't have my voice
in there, right?
Your voice...
There is...
You read your poetry, yes?
I have it.
Only one poetry?
Your love story maybe in it...
Which you waste
your time together...
He didn't look back even once...
Maybe he wants
to hide his tears...
He did learnt something...
He also taught something...
He learned to lie.
What did he taught...?
The true meaning of love...
That "love
is enough to let me go".
Just like when children come
to this world. Naked...
He too came naked.
Just like kids asking
many questions...
He also asked a lot
of questions.
Then one day...
He went away.
We are very far
from each other...
I think I was given a beautiful
gift...
Sarfaraz...
And my father.
As long as I live...
Every night I'll look
at the star...
Waving him...
I'm sure...
He'll do like this too...
I miss him.
One year later...
Brothers. We are one hour
to land on Earth.
Don't forget what I taught you.
Just 4 points.
First, walking nude
is prohibited on Earth...
Kissing and the likes,
People here do it secretly
and discreetly...
Beside that, peeing, pooping, beating,
all can do loud and openly...
Second, the big confusion
here is the language.
If you listen something like...
I love chickens, I love fish...
That doesn't mean
that they love that animals...
But it means that, they love eating
chickens, or eating fish for lunch.
What they think, what they say,
and what they mean.
We have to research about it...
Third, collect clothes
from the dancing car...
And hide your remote control
in your underwear...
Nobody will steal it if you
put it deep inside...
And fourth
the most important point.
If you ever meet with someone
saying he can contact God.
Do not research it... Just get
ready, and run at full speed.
Come bro. Don't be scared.
Come...
What are you staring at, huh?
- I have a question.
- What is it?
That last trip,
how many slap did you get?
What's these?
Self-defense. Really, Safety?
Yup.
- Ok, Come on...
- Go.
Where are you going?
Go here...
Hope it helped... >bozxphd
http://subscene.com/u/659433
Improved by: @Ivandrofly