Made by -- AWAL ELIXIR
Be sure to come to your wedding
Kanpour
Broadway cinema is proudly honored
Www.Bollycine.Info
How are you doing
Very well; come on, come on
Do you eat?
I am eating
Did you take a picture?
Image? I've had all my biographies
Watch the boat
Where to go eat a little
Turn off the gas
I took the rice bread
Well, Dai Jin --
Shocked girl, I got all the details
Good family
Mom said a lower grade
Get your own woman
All of your family is under your command
See you now
Is not that cute
Eve --
Yeah, a little bit pretty
Do not always make up
And we cook for him
19th
Not daddy! I am
I'm not hoping, Mrs. Shanti
Which you cook for cooking
Yeah why do you hope me?
I see
Contact my daughter with Sato
And tell me to see the girl on Sunday
Daddy's eyes
I see you can see the girl
Why did you sweat
You decide in ten minutes
What is the whole life with the same girl?
eh?
Yeah, and if you make a mistake
All your life is gone
So do not decide for ten minutes
How about --
We rent a Mercedes--Benz
Ride it and go
Check out lights, shields and everything
I say, you make that decision
I'm doing something
Check out my car lights and shields
I'll compare there
Ruthless choked woman;
shame on you
Your wife is yours
And is not mine?
Go daddy
See you
Han--
Do not boil me
Today is tuesday
Baptized eggs
Do not know, very pretty
I do not understand something; you are our own
Such a girl and we did not know
Give me my dad
Ok my mom
See what clothes you wear?
pink! That's what Aunt Goody brought to us
Truly see the earrings
Make sure you eat meat
Okay, Mommy Weared
I listened to the same last time
Mom see you
Say han
Talk to Baba for the last time
Maybe accept
I study so much bachelor's degree
I have a social science
I do not want to marry so soon
I'll read another one
Work and do something
Then I'll make a wedding with you
Talk to her for the last time, see
You do not know what you're saying
To send to Allah Abad University
I'm still pushing you back
Keep reading more
Truth talk to the true and polite boy
And do not gaze at your habit
Get a little bit of embarrassment
Mommy did not give me this embarrassment
Just now
Just as he is going to see
I'm going to see her
And if there is a great boy
And I say I do not want to be his wife
Dad give me by force?
My daughter arts, is there a problem?
What happened?
Why are you silent
Yes daddy
Do you like someone in the university?
Not daddy
So very empty!
Boyfriend has a office;
Government work; homes and their families;
Much higher than ours
We can not find a better connection
Do not get the manager and the state officer, did you understand?
Yes daddy
And yeah if you did not like it
Uncle you have found three more
Before the end of the year
It must be done, did you understand?
Yes daddy
So let your head down and down
Go see your boyfriend
What happened?
nothing
:A specialized translation of our artistic cultural media
Interpreters:Bingxa and Hajir
Satinder
Artistic --
Come on!
Do you eat anything?
Yeah
Waiter
What do you eat
Coffee
Coffee, two coffee meals with him
Something else Muffin Biscuit
Two coffee
Ok sir
Ask me what you want
I'm ready for the interview
Not an interview
Just as i came to see you
You've come to see me
You ask as much as you want
It's a truth to me, this way
How can you be half an hour
About the whole life decided?
In my opinion, it is not wise
Daddy said that a government employee?
Yeah, I'm your tax office
I'll be working next month
I just got hired
Tax office The Office of Bribery
You are cooking with bribery
Do you make progress
No, no, I do not mind bribing and taking
But our system is this
Blackjack bribes you
Not daddy i do not get
You can not refuse a bribe
Now you see I do not get
We will see --
I
Sir--
Thankful
you're welcome--
What are your expectations?
Are you from your future wife?
Wake up in the morning to make tea
And prepare breakfast
When i went to lunch
Like my mother's
It's been my father for many years
Let's go back to office and get ready
Massage your nap at night
I do not expect that at all
I just want a woman
That's the whole life of my friend
Just be careful about my parents
And respect them; that's enough
What are your expectations?
From your future husband?
Dad never want to work
I was always a student of my childhood
I just expect my husband
Let me work
Your education should not be erased
It's good to work
Otherwise, I'm pushing
And you have to take a bribe
I have another waiting, but it's a bit tricky
Tell you
I expect my husband
Every week I go to the cinema
Interested in cinema?
Very much--
So then every Sunday cinema
Sans late night
Really?
Yeah--
So what can we do now?
Pick a finger
this? I call home at night
And yes, I say a wedding
How much do you like me?
I do not have anything; everyone will treat you
Just your goddamn
Interested in someone else
I call my mom
Something to say?
Your face wears a lot
Thankful
What was Satynder's second finger?
.. that there
Aha! It's in place of the night
I just went to the bathroom
And I call them
That agrees to my wedding
Something to say?
Of course, if you do not get upset
Say, I've never heard of you
I'm not upset
Okord is not Akord
Han? I said the chords are?
We are married, we marry
Akuardo Bekhial
Okord
He is cord
I understand that I am learning
Husband, aunt, dear
come here
Yes--
Bravo
If you want to respect, leave it right
Do not play your role
Get back to your feet
come here
Be alive
How are your exercises
Good with your good prayers
Good prayer
Hello aunt john--
Your father is a dark man and a son of a transsexuals
(proverb)
Abbas and the ancestors of the dish and dishes
Now the boy wants to be an officer
Your son wants to do something
Support it
If he becomes a taxman
Seven generators are getting up
I will accept Dad next year
eh? Really?--
If I'm selling the store
How to study?
I need to focus on lessons
I set the focus of your guy
Come on, come on
Aunt John told me to act
Graduated last year
You must be the first person to take this exam
Am i going to do some meat?
! Ass!
These government jobs are not for girls
Do not make false suggestions
Honestly, this marriage is good
For the arts
So why are we going to go to Mr. Misrah?
Come on at 3 o'clock tomorrow
Han--
There are two bays here
Do not late
Your son--in--law will give you dinner and lunch
I'm not going to go anywhere
You are not you .. han
I talked with Mahish
Tomorrow is a few people from the Shukla family
OK
Shanti
Han--
I talked to Sato
We decided
Do not let the bride's family go
How to make a wedding?
What does that mean?
That means you can find a boyfriend
Do not you go
No more, han?
So how can it be without a jar
Did you make a wedding
Of your rights that did not gather anything
To find an officer's husband for a pony
This is the custom we did not make
Sato Wedding Whatever
Let's do it a little
Ponem wedding, which is two years away
Well, I'm going to double for another two years
Well, let it go
You ate the Shirton, it was cold
I told Mahish at 2:30
You do not say anything
One must have an account
Eat lactose and sleep
You and Abdai said one and two hundred
I say family and son are very good
If you want one and a half
We should not miss it
No, we can have 1200 of us
And that's why
You do not talk there
Two and a half million
No digits! Less than that
I'm going to be the groom?
Let's go
Wait to talk
Have we come
We have a small land
It's about 300--400 thousand sold
I saved a piece of art called Arti Bank
I take the rest of my loan from the bank
We want to merge with you
Why am i ashamed
How can you do that
.. This is an old drawing or otherwise
.. the moment of your spouse! I am
I'm talking
See my nephew is the only son of the family
And the only heir to this house
And now the state employee
You are tax office
And his groom is thirty years old
From college
what are you talking about?
So worth it to be something to say --
Yeah
.. I said that
.. We are joining ourselves. Otherwise
Sorry sir
No matter how my groom counted
If we make twice as many, then two million and a half do not
Mathieu is weak?
Han
Four million suggestions
Four million
Sato We love your daughter
Other than four million
We did not have a rupee
it's true
You said we were waiting for you
We waited for the next one to wait tonight
Where is your number boat?
Where is my phone?
Come on, groom, tonight next group
Four million
Let's go now
Do not talk too much
You have seen your literary and worldly readings
You know how powerful I am
I am responsible for urban development
But there is still a rupee for my bribe
You tell me how many your last album?
Not shockwave
.. I do not even have to
My son is telling you
Less than two and a half
This union is not possible;
Did you understand
One and eight hundred criticisms
Seventy sex
And this is our ultimate decision
My son and my sister also say that
We will not be less than this wedding
Let's go now
son in law
I agree with you
Your request will be executed
Why do you care?
Shanthi sweets
Now we're a family
Congratulations
You're just lying in front of me
'Your request is done'
Now 1300 Where do you add?
Rebellion does not make it any more
nowhere
I take a loan before retirement
And I'll give it away
At least my girlfriend with her loving husband
Marries
:Intagram and the official telegram of our media
@BollyCineOfficial
Something to say?
Like a ponytail
Do you go chowla
You have any color like Shahrukh Khani
Really?
Shahrokh mihra
Let's go
You're in the streets of Varanasi '
'So I wander all night in the middle of it
Characters like '
'And your eyes are like the Ganges
I'm off to sleep '
'And wake you up early in the morning
You're in the streets of Varanasi '
'So I wander all night in the middle of it
'Every Sunday, you see the cinema of the night with the film'
'It's a day to be your hero like movies.'
'Have fun, dance and be romantic with you'
'I'm glad to put you in your heart'
'That when I laugh at you,'
You're in the streets of Varanasi '
'So I wander all night in the middle of it
Something to say?
I've never lived as much now as I am
I'm not happy with you marrying you
me too
Can I eat coffee?
So where's the honeymoon?
Han
honey moon
I want to go to a cool place like a trash
We have to get involved
Okay, let's go
I also have a dream come true
What?
I once call with my husband
Come on
Eat wine and get drunk and cook
I never read, but you saw the movie
It seems to be very much
I saw that the hero gave the wine girl
And the whole thing is happening now
I want to do exactly that
And then if the husband is your best friend
Can you trust her no longer?
So what?
A moment
Pick one finger; this?
Biscay is eating
What is Biscay?
Viski is right
Yeah, we'll get the same
I feel like I'm not coming from now
What was the second finger?
Brandy
Brandy is not your brand
I will be completely foreign to you
You are coming home soon
English, fix it all
I'm tired of remembering them
What?
Really I said you brandy
Yeah satyndar
See you call me Sato
Those who love me
I call Sato
Come visit my beloved niece
Daie john
Where is the groom? --
O Baba! She's so busy
That's the wedding day
Now i am
Everything, everyday
Tell me I do not refuse
You will not find this anywhere else in the market
The boot has its own
Yeah, it's very nice to go to the body
Do not worry about it anymore
Other than the face, there is also a color
See this
No sister, if you give this shorts
And the boot is taking shape
Nilam?
No, no color is different --
sister?
what are you talking about?
There is more art
I'm going to take a little
An arte dumb stones
Which changes the size of the shoe
My wedding should be a pedicure
What's going on?
See, this is my bed
Mommy; my brother is shaking me
Mommy Take It
Aunt; I tell God
You wanna see your own modo
If Baba seeks us
You kill
I do not smoke
Lost son
Rounded round
Stope is not inside me
Daddy
Very delicious
Which one?
This is a very nice little thing --
Arty loves it too
The red is the girl's daughter
Our son does not wear red
Very good
Your husband is in the office
My husband is an engineer
Mine lysing master
And licking yours
Are you bored?
I'm talking to dad
Your husband knows
Do you smoke so much
I do not hide anything from it
And not from me
You do not hide anything from your husband
I do not hide
I just said to Sato
I want to drink wine with him to be drunk
Aha? You are ahead of me
Now what did Sato Khan say?
He is more excited than me
She has not yet been drinking wine
The boat .. Sato is so funny
I then learned a couple of two weddings
Which is the most important thing
What?
A lot of sex and a lot of money --
What are your sisters?
I say right again
! Wonderful timing!
It's as if without talking to you
Even her belly does not work
Oh Sister
Let me see what the speaker says
Do you speak speaker Is it crazy?
Daddy I know what he says
Put on speaker
You do not say anything
I'm not saying daddy
Hello
happy Birthday
Did you remember
Yes, all you say is
eh?
Well see you want to see
You got the temple there, and there's a room behind it
There we can see each other easily
I told you
Why are you in the room?
Do not think about the thought room
That wedding will be in your room
I did not see you for several days
I want to see you
Without you, breathing is hard
I'm coming
Okay, tomorrow morning
Hey Sato .. Elo
I love her, aunt of the romantic boy
Go along, you're cool
Well, your life is a guarantee of two
The life of marriage is great
This boy is constantly drowning
sister
And I'm thinking about it
But Arty is not something interesting
What
I am thinking of financially
Why?
Think about who she is
Invites the temple?
So much a five star hotel
There, he took a room and gazed at you
Do you want to call the temple to sound bells?
I do not know her but I have four before
The poor can not breathe without me
I'll give it oxygen
And I'll charge it until the wedding
But you remember something
Do not let it hit you
The boys are very bored
(Wat D?)
She is acting
And he doubts himself
I'm telling you
Mother's eye
happy Birthday
Morsi Sato Did you do all this for me !?
That is not something
Did you write something for me?
Poetry?
Yeah read
Joey, Maduroi, Diva Baharti
All of this is ZTEBOTI ARTI
Do you laugh
I do not smell very nice
My goal is you
The most beautiful Goddess initiative
Now I just want you
I love more than myself
Sato
how's it?
Very nice and very lovely
Thankful
This shape is very much up to you
What do you think
Why wear my face?
Were you wearing me?
Pn
Here is the flower
I .. I fell in love with you
Say i love you
It's all right
Ok i say
I love you
Turn you
Well, I love you
Tell me more
Tell me a little
I do not say
I'll give you a wedding
Ok, I'm asking for something?
ask
If you do not upset
Can i get your lips?
Lips! Can i kiss
Do you want a lipstick in the temple?
God is everywhere
eh? I would like to visit some place if I invited you
Maybe you did
A moment
I brought you something
happy Birthday
You're bribing me
To get my lip out?
I love you so much
Get it
Not a problem
Why do not you want now?
I do not want you
So get it over
Get it
Let it land
I keep it
Just take one
You get your Sato Lip
Then you doubt me
No I do not doubt
You are
Not to my mother's life
Now leave it for the wedding
I do not doubt
Just one day Sato, goodbye
Sato just waiting a bit
Tomorrow you see our wedding
'The sky was full of stars'
'When you shone like a moon inside me'
'I'll follow you and feel you'
'My friend lives in every breath'
'You are rising like dawn and dawn'
'I'm walking along with you; I am with you';
'I want to love you more than myself.'
'And I have vowed with my heart that I am with you; I am with you'
'I'll spend your night and night for you'
'When I sleep all night watching'
'You are somehow dissolved in my existence'
'It's the same without you in the middle of a bush.'
'I wish you the mirror'
'Okay, I'll see you inside.'
'I have also become your face'
'I want to love you more than myself.'
'I vowed with my heart to accompany me; I am with you'
'Love kites fly inside the chest'
'As if I was flying your scarf'
'I'm wet with you in the rain'
'When my hair is spread, I'll be your cloud.'
'My dark sea eyes are my dream sea'
'I stabbed and got lost inside them'
I want to love you more than myself. '
.. I vowed with my heart that
'I accompany me, I accompany me, I accompany me'
Dadash Shah Dummad
Shovel .. shovel
Did not you wait for two more minutes?
From tomorrow, he will be angry
See what do you do
Go again
Shout Mom CALLS;
View my name in the name of you
The other word is written in my life
Well, this is the life that I got for you
Why are you just in this life?
I love you every single life
Pick a finger
Right
I love you
What's the second one?
I love you very much so much
Heldy (drawing sandals) started?
Yea, you were trained
Did you beat
I got too yellow
Dadash, this sister of arts
And this brother
Welcome to our family
No, it is not necessary
You're coming
Sister .. Mommy Interior
Let's go back
how are you? --
Is not your husband my daughter?
You know your aunt
Engineers are busy
But it's a wedding day
Take my breakfast for breakfast
what are you doing?
My aunt I'm eating for the exam
that's good
I've done two times this time som--
Do not worry; you succeed
You just have to try a little bit
I just need your prayer
Thankful
Come on!
My baby is my baby
Last year we had gone
It is very high
Its a government, more
Its celebrations are high
Yes, exactly
Now Sato also has a government job
Ok not aunt Sato Worker
And Arty wants the wedding party to work
Good luck that allowed you
My husband's family who did not allow
Let's go
Who said?
Aunt .. Sato had told the arts
Sato is a kid
He says with excitement
Cover it too
I still choose
See my daughter
My soul
The brides of the Mishra family are not working
It's our custom, what do people say?
Who lives with the bride's money?
You are our brides in our house
They never work and do not
At least I'm not alive
And about government work
I am the president of this room
Take care of your bloodthirsty art
So think of a government job, han?
Mommy
My daughter is this money
Take my son some more!
! You did not eat anything
You are very attractive
Sato mummy behind the lane
Elo
I am very stressed
My stomach is a jerah
what happened?
I'm not talking about this
Send me a picture of the bridal dress
Some things must be ambiguous
I want to see you again
Surely you see
Today I was very handsome
Why wait anymore now?
Now we almost married
Stop him
I'm going to follow you
Bye
Do you beat me? Are you okay?
More money
I just had a phone call
You could not give me a try
Did you give pc
Is this a sister too?
Not telling me; are you crazy?
Your tone is over
Now tell me?
You accepted the arts
You can be an officer
The results are now
I saw online
Am I an officer?
My sister was accepted?
We have to celebrate
..I
All ten years of exam
I and two years old engineers are dismissed
And this is the first time this four times
I scored four nine points
What are you six, ladies?
Perfect Smith
Artish your mind
You own your own home
Red light car
And the knights say:'Yes, sir.'
Your book is so bad and so much
Respect that you can not tolerate
Now, yes, you say hello
Officer
Officer Shukla not ass
I'm artistic officer of Satynder Mishra
I do not believe it
My sister will be the officer
Sato is so good for me
Wedding is the happiest day of life
And for my dubbing celebration
Sister .. Yeah
Barat (Carnival of the groom) is coming
Hurry up ahead
Soon a moment
Come on here, daddy, my job is obligatory
Barat Torah --
Do not get angry please
Han groom still not
I knew where to go
..both it
Barat is coming
Put on your coat soon
Get an illusion
Listen to daddy
Please do not get angry
What is that
Tell me too soon
Artistic Examination Police
Accepted two steps
And he did not tell us
Have accepted the PSI exam
Yeah daddy
Online results now
Well, this is a very good news
Artistic
Barat is coming
Daddy did not listen to you
He can be an officer
From today, Artis is the bride of the family of Mishra
What does he do and what?
Mishra makes a decision
OK? Are you ready for the presenter?
Mommy make him look
We are making a big mistake
Barat Torah
He does not want to do an artistic work
We made a big mistake
By choosing this family
I say to Bob, nothing has happened
Your mom listen
Manjou will say nothing
Arroyo today is impossible to work
I can not be
.. I know you're angry, but once
Do not talk nonsense, otherwise my hand will rise
What do you do
This is our guest
Some other word
I say daddy ... why do not I say
Shut up
What do you want
Artis like me and my mom to cook
And great baby?
Do not try to be an officer once?
First time accepted
So talented
You're destroying your life
Why do not I say
Miss you and that mother
Girls are hiding in the houses
That's what you want for this nonsense
Stop this wedding?
Tell Mishra my daughter can be an officer
Console Wedding; Will I say this?
Yes, you cancel your wedding
She can marry later
But he can not be an officer
Her mother does not want to work
He always wanted to work
Bring this wedding
Manjoo is the crazy girl
Put it in front of my eyes
Otherwise I'll kill you
I'll be righteous then
The cruelty that you are having with the art of life
Shut up
I'm oppressing the arts?
See you married
Let your sister marry
Do not try to ruin it
Mom tell her
Silent
enough. Take the vehicle and go
Without you, we will hold an artistic wedding
Go
..Just once
Go from here
from your hand
My daughter is Vesta
:Intagram and the official telegram of our media
@BollyCineOfficial
What is your sister
come here--
I now sent a message to Sato
every thing is fine?
what happened?
Listen carefully, see what I say
Today we were going to the groom's house
I told your mother that she wanted an art worker
He completely rejected and said
Mishra's family bride does not work
How did you say that?
Sato told me
Yeah, I said you talk to Sato
Do you know what did you answer
Sato is baby and still covered
I buy it for you, do you mean this?
I was not the addressee, you were
I'm sure you're at home
Do not want to work
Forget about being an officer
Sato told me
What is Baba saying to Sato?
She can not speak in front of her mother
Now you decide what you are doing
My sister can not be a housewife
I want to marry Sato
But I want to do it
You told her the first appointment
He accepted
I can not have a house
.. I'm talking to Sato
Why do you like Satu Satu parrot?
That's my future husband
It's a secret
When the officer is 25
Like Sato, you work on your podium
I do not say that good son is very good
But even if he does not understand, he does not understand
What can i do
What can I do?
.. see me, father and mother .. it's yours
Husband, kid and three meals
That nobody knows
And respect the other side
Think of arts
Your future is calling
Check out the exam result Why did you come today?
Tomorrow I could come back
You could not do anything
You can run today
.. I call to my husband
She solves it
You go with him
I can not do this with Sato
Can you do it with you?
I and my city with you; you run away
Someone does not hear me here
run
You're all happy with the Baba and Sato officer
Artistic
What do you want my daughter
Daddy .. Sato
I solved it
Do you want to be an officer?
So run away
There is no other way
This community of this year
Keeping the boys on her head
But she does not value girls
And not a favorite life
They give them their own
That's when a girl gets the chance
Good luck, and life is happy
Make herself
All the seas of fire must be rejected and gone
Escape my daughter
run
Artist go to Barat
I have to go down so that no one understands or rises
I can not kill my dad
Artistic Dance Meditation
Just keep in mind that the guy says you're talking
You heard and ran away, go
Sister, what did Sato do?
I love you very much
Rejoin her love again
But this opportunity does not get any more
Go
I talk to her once
Not artistic; I did not say so
Do not talk to him. Let's go
If I understand why
The creditor also counts
Come on go
Barat Dam Valley
Make a dish
Mommy
Go ahead of the car on the back
Go to succeed
congratulations
Happy you too
Where is the arts?
Where is Arty?
She did not want to marry
Did not he want to, or did you not?
What do you do
Hands up your big girl?
Go away
Do not you? Do I crawl
Worship him
Do not touch it;
Why do you give it
Barat came
Say where have you gone
Where have you gone
I do not know Daddy, sorry
Send me a study
Send Allah Abad
Do not have a young girl's supply?
Why did you invite me?
Got rid of
Aunt Husband, why do you bother me?
Do you empty your sister?
I'm going to be two years old
The arts accepted
If it is to me
I choke them up
I'm burning myself
Stop
Spit on my face
What do we do now
Come on here
I understand your pain
Now is the hard time
But we must somehow break it out
See the people
Just think about it 1,800 million in cash
What did we get?
Tell me what to say
Excuse me
Our girl escaped
Put our money in your envelope
And deliver it, tell me this?
That's it! You do not understand Mahish if you listen
Our daughter escaped and did not give us a rupee
All the income of your life goes up
So how are you returning money?
Sister does not come back
We must return
Husbands allow me to manage this
Just keep them silent
Tea we get
First, what is the flow?
Why did you ask us here?
I'm really kidding
A great catastrophe came to our head
And so on your head
Bella
Yes--
What is the issue?
.. the thing is that art
what happened?
My son was not in his room
What was there?
Only this letter was there
See her
See you
When your daughter understood that
You've got two and a half million warriors
It is not decided to marry you
He left the wedding and went
Where have you gone
Where are we going from where are our son?
Call me to talk to her
Do not answer us
How do i say you talk
How about Jazz with satisfaction of both sides
Was determined
You were right
It is not a matter of joy; I know
Forgive me Sato
I have not told you to give it a try
Today came the conclusion and I accepted
I'm an officer
Allahabad sent a lesson
Maybe that's where you've been loved
Homage to family
And ran away; did you understand?
You are baking charcoal
And blush your face
.. You have to stop the ZebNet, or else
What are you doing, for example?
I do not have a job with you
Dear Mishra, you are literate
I will love you
Our daughter does not want to be married again
For this, we have one and eight hundred criticisms
Relax with us
And come back with respect with Baratton
This is a console wedding
How is console
Your girl escaped
Do you want money from us?
Embarrassed, huh?
We did not see a rupee
We will not return a rupee
Come on here
Are you crazy?
Do not think about it without giving money
Can you get it, did you understand?
Chando Kishawu
Come on, you
Put the gun on Mishra's head
One hundred and eight hundred to the last rial
If you do not lose ourselves
Someone does not leave here
Hey, take a sign
I'm going to daddy
hit it
I'm afraid of you?
Come on
Wash your cousin
And you do not read the bad guy with your own hands
Do not get out of here, did you understand?
A moment
what are you doing? --
Leave it
I'll get your money
But you do not have Dad and Daimim
I'm going
Go away
my son
Artistic
Did not you see the arts
No
Artistic
Where is the hi--art?
Whatever I call, I do not answer
where is it?
Take it with you
What is han sato
I'll tell you later
What have you done
Sato --
I'm sorry Sato
I would not have told you something
I had an officer exam
Today's results come true
I accepted
I'm going to be an officer
Sato
what happened?
Bobb
it `s nothing--
Do not cry
You do not cry
Save them
Where did you put Pula?
I want to bring them
Eight hundred spent a million
Take you and bring them with you
One million is not, everyone reads
We'll see them later
They do not accept
Where is this night coming from?
:A specialized translation of our artistic cultural media
Interpreters:Bingxa and Hajir
I left it for my pony wedding
It was you wearing my wedding
Damn it
That girl brought us life
He turned into hell and went
Eloh sister
Han! They're going now
Return all the money
Daddy good
Well, that's not; the uncle is sitting there
I'm one of my two days
To make things worse
Did you call Sato?
Several times, but according to your wishes
I did not answer
Sister some time to call her?
Yeah talk to him
Very sad
We just did the same mistake
His heart fail
I saw her
Keep the car
Where is it going
.. see you here
Husband
Daddy daddy
Do not die my son
I'm not so weak
I just felt a little nervous
Open the button
A moment
I do not want to go home
We were going to go home with the bride
What is going to go home now?
See your mother's tears?
Everyone is watching
.. 'see there'
... 'Professor Mishra, whose son's wedding'
Alright, my son went away
What do you say
Sato Vector
Please take it
We do not let them go
Do not worry, do not worry
5 years later
See in support of amateurs and planners
We opened a special window
Which does not require a double effort
So I hope you progress
And invest in our area
That's for you too
And it will be useful to us
Ask me if you have any questions
Nilam tell you a few times
Come straight to you
And I've told you many times
Here you are Rice
Look, I tried five times
I did not accept
But you were accepted the first time
I thank you for my art
I'm back
Today I'm busy with your blessing
Otherwise, I would teach you a school in Kanpur
Do you smoke, tea?
tea?--
Someone compliments us
Then you have to make it all
Two teas please
Truth, what's that
I heard you in the office right?
! Depends on what you heard
Do not go that way
You're just talking about the office
What?
What do you do
I did not look
You did not look
You walked
If you add the road, you will get low
Weight added
Sister's husband is always there
It gets angry
Yeah bad
Nilam rang
He said you are going to promote art
That is a very good news
Happy, my sister's husband
Yala Ranjn
Tea time
Han Tea Bring Sister
Be sad
I'll crush you all the time
You've made a lot of 5 years of arts
More just to make a husband
Our imagination is comfortable
stand up
Why?
what happened?
Shuffle soon
Lebastio Btkvn
what happened ?
The 5--year--old needle grabbed an artistic wedding
If it turns out you can move it a little
... from your hand
Counters --
Yaaa daoi, go away
Mom, why are you cheating?
Who am I cheating?
Impolite
You cheated
Snoo says you must have cheated
Dad, who am I cheating?
Well, it's time to go
Rip it over
O Baba in the middle of the game?
Your sister come
Come on
Hey niece
As if you were born to me ... Let's go
Yala
hit--
Manjoo is your turn
What are you guys prearti?
I want to go tomorrow
Miss Arty Shukla
You are temporarily suspended
To land 90 hectares behind the railway
To the company of Kukirja and the sons
You are charged with receiving 30 million
Bribe
Thank you all this year for me
Do you think that does it for me?
I do not mind my imagination
The topic is the findings of the research
Against you
And now special research has begun
And just the vice minister
Leadership research
You should see them tomorrow morning at 9 o'clock
Yes sir
Good Morning
Mrs. Arti Shukla, is it your name?
Sato
Hello .. you swear
Calling up with a small name?
What's your post
I
I am responsible for registering
how long is it?
Four years
You started from that first
To bribe
Do you like bribes?
Not right; you are a part of the system
So there's no problem getting bribed
it's true?
it's not like that
I said you are --
My Lord, I'm not guilty
I can explain
You do not need to explain something
Miss Arty Shukla
What you wanted to do
Now I want everything
And for the sin that you committed
You will achieve your action
..The prisoner and six years in prison
With feelings of guilt
If i be
I prove guilty
.. Sathyndar listen to me some time ago
Sir
Eve, brother of a four--year--old girl
And now in the right time
You took the case from the minister
What do you think?
Guilty
It does not matter to me
I just know for something
I know that guilty
I can do it
You're in this world if hell
I'm artistic about Shukla
Everything in the war and love is a prize
Love was over and the war began
Be happy
what happened?
Sweetie your sweets
Why happy What is the flow?
And see this
What is that
Now see it
Photo of this wizard
Why are you showing me?
what happened?
The lady was very honest
And was against jihaz
Escaped from the wedding
Now if he can escape
How about What's up
Imprisoned soon
Prison Why?
For bribes;
There was no ordinary bribe
30 million
Look around the corner
You will sweeten your mouth
Yes, it's sweet too
Okay, I'm eating ... your news was lekono
Sato is there
I tell him to be happy
Yeah say
Hi Mom
I have a very good news.
what happened?
Am i going to smile
Not even better
She was a Shukla girl
Who escaped from the wedding
Now she is caught up
Charged with receiving thirty million bribes
Directly goes prison
You are the lucky one
Get some news
Mom, I'll call you later
Bye
Okay, ok
Han ponem lady
Sato, how much he wanted
What did her bride escape?
I'll be without jesus
I'll marry you
Where are you going
Get Sato ... But do not worry
Listen to Mahish
She did not escape because of Jazz
She ran to be an officer
And 25 secretaries like Sato
Work on his part
You're in the form of secretaries like Sato
Spit does not matter
:Intagram and the official telegram of our media
@BollyCineOfficial
That poison you filled your heart '
'You will see
'My pain and fire, Oh, I'm gripping my stern'
'Now you see the result of selfishness'
'You rejected my love now, you will see my revenge'
'The answer to my love of selfishness'
'You did not have to betray me again.'
'You will see me hate me this morning and night'
'You rejected my love now, you will see my revenge'
'All the atrocities you have done with my mind'
'At last, God gave you the wrongdoings'
'The whole world will see you defeat in public'
'You rejected my love now, you will see my revenge'
All the house is upset
Now the officer wants to do anything
And wherever he wants to attack?
Guess what
Bring a glass
He has taken his case
It is not clear just come to take revenge from the arts?
Why do we fear when we have not done anything?
Because our force would not be her
The power of the other hand
She told her straight
He throws him in jail
You hurt you badly
Apparently work but personal revenge
He's gonna be
What is your sister saying?
Artistic
Why crying? --
All right
Drink water
Do something
Apologize for it
She loved you so much
Maybe for that very angry
Maybe you'll get it
I heard that I did not get a woman yet
Look outside of her office
Or invite some coffee
Do you sit by, I'll call them
Come on!
How are you
How can i help you
I see very sorry
for what?
Because of what I did with you
I still regret
Jazz was just an excuse
I had an exam
Do you drink tea?
Ashok ... Ashok
Yes sir
Take two tea
So what did you say?
I had given a test of the results of the day
A wedding came
I did not work
I also gave you a message
My sister said your family
I do not want to work
.. I do not know if I'm wrong
What is han
I know you've been cruel
Very hard
I want from my bottom
I apologize for you
I know why so much
I'm angry with you
But what should I do?
If you're so sorry
Why did not you try to see me?
How many times did you call that night?
I thought we loved each other
And now that the case is in my hands
Do you understand your mistake?
... and if I did not come here
I never thought about you ... no?
You were already pragmatic
You just became more beautiful now ... Han?
Arty Shukla officer
Very tempting and desirable
sorry?
Do you feel uninteresting?
Shukla officer? No?
So let's do something
Which you have come to
Do I get a duck Han
Satyndr .. Please do not talk like that
What?
Do not talk to me like this
Ok so tell you
How do you talk to me?
See yourself! You're seducing me
And I'm sorry
I'm ready to go ... do it
Satinder
.. Shukla, if you think
Seeing the face of beauty
I forget the frustration of my family
It's never so
And so you never forget
Satynder Please do not personalize the story
There is a person
It is very much
The gentry you gave me
I never remember
This is the biggest fight of my life
And really ... I'm not angry
I hate you
Now, get out of here
I'm sorry
out --
Herrerry
Mrs. Shukla; again wearing a ponytail
Stop me
I'm going to get you down
Hello tea
Put it on the table
Say han
Thank you for this archetype
And this is my own
Is this your own?
Yes --
And that cockroach builder?
He has a lot of businesses
With great politicians
And this is the land
To build the factory
And now you're on your own
And will come back soon
Has this deal been arranged?
Yes sir, I was a deal broker
My job is the same
The document was on the ground?
Yes sir, no document
How can you sell it?
Where is the land owner?
America gone
And it's clear that you do not have a number
Not sir
Address?
Something else! Where should I be?
I want to ask at 9 o'clock
It's now five o'clock
What did you eat
First of all I can go outside
I'll eat later
Do not let me swing
Take care
Bye
Listen, I'll call you again
Yes sir ... Yes, I talked to her
Tomorrow at nine o'clock in the morning and see it
Mrs. Tomorrow at 9 o'clock
I'm talking to her
I see what happens
Where is the photo?
We had gone to see the earth
Which was bought by Cokriya
You personally went and checked
Where is the earth and how much?
And then the hand of the state land
Did you call Kukriya?
No sir I did not really know
Who is this guy
Managing Director Mr. Kokriya
Mr. Siegel, you're sure
Buy lots of land
Yes
This land that has just bought its value
About 150 million. How many buys?
.. Actually, this was the flow
60 million
Yes
The land reached you 150 million sixty million
Then you got sixty direct benefits
Sixty
Thirty to Dadi to another Shukla Art
Is this your friend
Not sir
We only have a relationship
He also gave you a car
My friend bought me and my birthday
Gave me a gift
I sent it, I did not accept it
Still parked in my car park
I did not use it at all
Omsich
Yes sir
Have you ever brought a gift machine to you?
Never sacrifice
Never?
No
They're the officer
You are very special
Three days after your last birthday
This land is granted
Of course when you're in the system
Hard to dismiss, no?
Do you have any comments?
Your Excellency Cockerie Artisan
That's great
Do not ask for a land document
Is not that impossible?
This should be seen by your officers
That land government
I'm just a slave
The land document was correct
I bought it
Are you sure?
I'm pretty sure; never anymore
Do not bribe anyone
I think you're misunderstood
I ask you for advice?
Not sir
Is this what?
This girlfriend is a friend of art
Is not your friend
This is a great kind of people
How can i be my friend
Arty takes me with herself
I would go
Is your husband hacked?
Tutor
How much did you reach the two?
What is your earnings?
I just got my commission
Kakriya, I said that the government was doing
She does it
What is my fault in my midst?
You see, you have a picture
Chief Investigator
But if you accept my recommendation
Do not do this
Because you've got a chance
Deputy Minister of the Goodwill
Officer in charge of women
I'm not good at all. Repeat your hand
Sometimes the prime minister will see the next time
Sorry to tell them
I am going to eat i'm eating
Good evening lady
I am a primo singer
My lawyer from Allah Abad University
Lady, I know you from college
I was upstairs
How can i help you
Tell me how you are
Can i help you
Between you and the file officer
I trade
He'll get you out
.. for that little bit
I am the officer of your case
My Lord, I do not know him
Do you know him?
Is your friend
Yes sir
His prison is what he must have done
At least six years
what is your name?
Go to hell
So we'll take them all together
Come along
Take a paper
Write a letter to me
Hi Mom
Hello Dad
.. Shakla Army Research
Write
Shukla Artistic Research
It's fine
All evidence against
There is no hope of salvation
There is no hope
Tell my mom to be ready for charity
Ready to be good
Arbitrary imprisonment of Shukla
What did you write What is that What is that
I'm sure
.. Your honest husband
I write my name
Cut off
Slip out
Love is not easy
So imagine that the sea
And I want to drown it
No, I want to live inside
Have you made a personal babe?
Did you understand
Of course--
Listen to it this time
You never covenant with anyone
I would love more than my soul
That's it
This love and this is all brash
See here who came to see us?
I present this poem I have just said
To my able friend
..Lady
What was his name?
Mrs. Arty Shukla right?
Artistic Shukla
He is very famous; practicing
Your novelty about writing is your novelty
That bribe was thirty million
He is
How long do you come to prison, why are you with 30 million?
At least 200 million
!No? Thirty million is not what
This is the toilet of men
I can not do more than that
I tolerate torture
I'm choking, I do not breathe
What do you want from me
What do you want from you
I'm doing my job
You make the card
Are you abusing?
Am I abusing?
Yeah
Well, I learned from you--
You misused that time
Now it's my turn
I did not do that
What do you know about abuse?
What is that
I'm screaming now
And I say you're sexually abusive
.. The other is Satyrander Mi?ra, my case officer
I'm calling you illegitimate
That is the opportunism
Bring it down
No i do not say
Because I'm not like that
I was not and not
The results came
I did not understand Barat at the door
Your mother told my sister
I do not want to work, so what should I do?
Some time ago you talked to me
You trusted me
Satinder
I loved you
Did not you think about me for a moment?
Now you come to see the tears?
What are my tears?
What are my mother's tears?
I agree
But what should I do now? what do I do?
What can you not tolerate?
What did i get
Han
Did not you miss the pass?
But you once thought too
If I did not run away
Did not you have this shakat today?
what do you mean?
If you do not run away, you will not be able to sleep
And you were not an officer today
And you were still in the office
Did you think
Artistic Shukla
Today your truth turned out to be
You did not want to be an officer
Get married with a secretary
They were deductible to you, no?
I was younger, no?
I did not deserve you
I did not think so
Have you been chatting
You were riding a state machine
I was not right for you
Arty Shukla you were selfish on that day
You are here
I did not mean Satynder
.. my room
I'm talking to you
I'm not selfish
Do you want me to go to jail again?
Call the police now instead of tomorrow
I'm going today
At least from this daily torture
I'll be saved
I would not do it again, I accept that I got a bribe?
I will not do anything else
Call now
.. be honest!
What am i to be
You want to talk
Okay, let's talk
You do not know what to say
I'm talking calmly
I do not really get any more
I'm sorry. Today I got a lot of nerves
I said you would drink me
How did this cigar start from?
Then I went to the thrill --
I did not know what I was doing
But let's get those old stories
Choose one
Can I kiss you?
What? --
Is it a buss
I do not doubt you
No--
I do not kiss you
You're killing me; it's deep and fashionable
And then there, let's go there
We stayed at night together
Other, you have no problem
Do something
Do not you want
say
You know I was joking there
Not a joke right now --
Tonight the price of your imprisonment does not go away
come
I misunderstood you
What was your second finger?
Today is ten minutes, one more week
The result of the committee will be announced
The thirty million buckets that hit
Send me to
I am a part of the system
If I did not accept it, give me a boost
I did not take bribes
I do not have 30 million
Get it out of Cork
! Do not refuse! You know all the facts about him
See Shakla
You can not help this
No sister, do not say so
Satyndar is not kid! His work must be with thought and intention--
Now it's said thirty million bugs
Where are we going to go? --
See, I did not have the right to take that day
I'm not here
One day I sold my gold
To save the lives of my husband and brother
Now you know what to sell
And John saved her daughter
I will sell myself too
Thirty Million
It's your problem
Come on, lady
Mr. Kokriya is waiting for you
I'll solve it
Come on, lady
I had days thinking I did not see you
But I heard a lot of you
Mr., if I am accused
I lose my job
My parents die
I'm taking prison
You have to show yourself
And get the truth
The fact that everyone knows
Alexei is a naive role
Do not play in front of me
You have 30 crore money
I got a bribe? Is it 30 crore?
You did not tell your employees?
Everybody left alone?
I gave you a little bit of subjection
What do you say
I did not get any money from you
You must have one of your employees
I paid the money too
And now that you get caught up
Fall me down with you?
Eula Baba
.. I have seen a lot of officers, but you
Mrs. Shukla Case Investigation Officer
Just arrest him right now; yes, right now
It's not so much tougher
She's taking a revenge on her artistic work
We will try our last
Come on, I got everything
Go ahead it sooner
Trust in God --
Inshallah let them go
come
See you. I'm somewhere
That you wanted me to give it
Now the revenge is complete
happy Birthday
This is the best birthday party
Morsi
Sir
I wish I had never seen you
This document is our homepage
Please save yours
I wanted all the evidence
I will solve the problem
I want to get the Jouriary to get started
Come on --
A film where the answers are lucky
Where did I write something?
You are literally 30 million
And even the burqah is near and you want money again?
Now this stupid movie you started
Stop it all
Okay, I'll give you whatever you want
Just a file that is due to your ignorance
Began to close
Say something?
Not sir
I have nothing to say
Make every sentence you want
Mr. Kokriya, I'm not afraid of you
Even if you are imprisoned
I will not let you go
What does she say You said you traded
That's crazy!
I threatened to kill me
We need to do it
Draw it damn!
His former lover came to take revenge on him
Look like a hungry wolf
And in the end, we are hunting for it
This romantic series must be shut down
Kill it today
Can you explain Mr. Misrah?
Yes sir, I can
Mrs. Nilam Mamehma's husband and Rajai's dealer
Who has welded this deal
Are friends of childhood
State landless information
Mrs. Nilam is in charge of the office
And she gives her husband
Husband, she's going to remember Rajaj
He makes a hook piece for him
And it sells to several merchants at the same time
Are you sure you?
Mrs. Nilam misuses Artem's trust
And sign it on the document
For years, they are called Artish Shukla
Bribe and split between them
Cokria has given thirty million bribes
But Arty Shukla does not know at all
Because you never got the money
Are you Mrs. Nilam?
Thankful
Mrs. Mishra
Evidence is your claim
In the opinion of the Jury Board, Shukla is innocent
Arrest them
Yes sir
Sir
Today i found out when
It's an intruder
It's really the heart of Adam
Thankful
Thank you so much
You can get Satyndr Saddam
You can be from Monday
Come back
Sato
How is saxina
Thank you for accepting the case
John Artie
Do not hurt your hand
Thanks, you are not tired
Thank you sir
Well, I'm going to Kanpour
Then come back
An innocent art
See Sathyndar at home documents
Sent back
'I want to be with you'
'I will endure all the sadness with you'
'I'll talk you with words that I'm not going to do with everyone.'
'Well, you ... how good are you?'
'I want to be poor and Darwish love'
Where is the boss
Not yet --
Who is going
I do not know--
'I was careful thousands of times until I understood'
'You're running and I'm drinking'
'Loneliness where I can get there is yours'
'I realized for a hundred times that I accepted my story and your story.'
'When we get together, our communication becomes complete.'
'I want to see you again'
After all this happens
Anyone who thinks
If i was dying
I did not believe in love anymore
Your sister is upright
But I know Sato is still
I like too much
If he did not love, he would not hate so much
Who will be the officer and take revenge on me
Sato sister did not want to be an officer at all
The problem is just my brain
Do not fall in love with her
Now I make my mind silent
And I hear the sound of his heart
!listen! How much do you eat
I'm tired of daddy
I was rushed off by the officer
And you've been running my superiors
Stop tired
We have to stop somewhere else
I'm going to get away
leave me
Our way is different from the two
Our way is different
What is your goal?
Sato me down
I can not get faster than this
Come on!
Thank you sir
A moment
Do you bring me home?
Please, my car is ruined
Wash
Thankful
You get him home
Han Satyndar
Go
Where are you
It takes time to come
You got one of my two couriers
I came
I say you do not get me
But that does not mean
I can not eat whiskey
Wherever you are
I am in my place
Order me a drink
Come on, I'm drinking
You start
You are better than you
Miss Visky
Thank you ... crap ... it did not happen
There are some things
What are your goggles for me?
I'm attracted to not?
Please--
Mrs. your drink
Thankful--
I got a nice look
You are Tom Cruz Allah Abadi
Take a drink to the waiter
Art is on
One--only
..Husband
I want to take your hand
And you turn around
Please do not arrange
It's full of people here
Do you kiss me
One little one
Too much
Sato something to say?
Under the pretext of the case
I saw you again
Otherwise maybe forever
I would give you
Do you feel like you're upset?
I have not been there before
Let's go
Satyndar .. wait for Sato
I'm coming
Artistic .. Be careful
I'm looking for you very much
Something to say Sato
Satinder
Tell me
I think I'm in love with you
Say i love you
Han
I love you so much
I want to marry
Because I saved you from prison?
I saved you only from prison
I gave you too much time
I agree that my fault is ... Satinder
Reconcile again, please
Life is not strange?
My time is like divinities
I wanted to get it
I was thinking about you all day
What did you do
You escaped
.. you gotta And now you see
You know that day that my family's pride
I'm seeing breaking
I hated the word marriage from that day
And I'm not with you until the end of your life
I do not marry nobody
I understand it, thanks
The color of white love is not jealous. '
'And there is nothing inside of it
If you find one color too '
'The same white is everywhere, fire or sand
'It's the war you are your officer, I'll fight for you' '
'How good are you? How good are you?'
'I want poor love'
'I want to be with you'
'I will endure all sorrows with you'
I want to say '
'I can not beat others, I'll kill you
Danger
Yes sister--
Do not you have reason?
What did I do? --
What did you write this
Did not you know the name of the groom?
Do you want to be an officer with this mess?
Sharada writes to Shara
Go make it up
Time seems to be blowing
You do not understand at all
Yeah, you have a fair deal, God
That girl escaped
And he is sitting alone here
Do you swear
We die without seeing our grandsons?
He who has a husband
Do you want to play with your children?
This is why this game is played? Wonderful
Of course you're right! How many girls
Can you keep your house
You must have another wedding day
I do not say I do not care
I told him
My son, let me die, my grandmother
Yeah, my son, your mother is right
We want to be a grandchild
Do you have any questions for discussion?
This is very important to us
.. your love
Where are you now
On thursday
I'm going to the temple
how are you?
How are you? --
I am fine
I heard you're having a wedding
I thought my case study
Are not I finishing a wedding?
No, make sure
Your life
.. that .. shawl
I was thinking a few months ago
You told me you love me
And you want to be my wife
Yeah, I said, but you did not accept
Yeah, you're a pragmatic girl
You're doing right right now
So all my life is waiting for you?
No, of course not
But I'm glad I decided not to marry
Otherwise, a girl like you would get stuck
Like me that does not get at all
I'm just a donna
And I'm having a husband
are your family OK?
Yeah--
Shariah
This is my friend and I'm Satyndar
A very old friend
I know Kayha; in fact, he does everything
Told you about
And I want to thank you
I did not do anything
Thanks for the same
What if you married an artiste
What did I do?
is not it?
I'm coming back now
A moment
Sharad ... you turn on the car
If you do not mind saying something
say
Do not marry arts
Not reliable
What does that mean?
Do not get upset, but do not be sad
Just a few days ago
The scenes followed me
.. and now see
I'm telling you a friend
If you get married with this, you will be poor
Otherwise your life will be
Thank you so much
Come on!
no thanks
.. Yours
How dare you satynder
I am a tail?
Shard with me?
What do you want from me?
You do not marry me
Do not let the rest of you marry me
what do I do?
do you love me?
Of course I love you
How many times say
So you love me
And getting married to someone else?
Ok do not you
Han
Do you marry me?
You do not, because you do not allow me to
I decided to get married
Love is not obligatory for marriage
Love also arises after marriage
Come on tenth
I am not
Come on, I'm very happy
Make sure you come my wedding
Sato
Hurry shanti
Let's go
Take Mahish
See where you got to get started
It's going to be late
What's up here?
Where do you go
Let's go to my son's wedding
Artistic Wedding?
Han
Why do you die
My son, Shukla and his wife personally
Bringing a wedding card
Saying If We Wanna Bride
Do not go home
Must go my son
So what can you do?
Hey very pretty
Thankful--
I'm telling you to come
No, I'm not
I do not know why you are dying
:Intagram and the official telegram of our media
@BollyCineOfficial
Hello
Hello aunt; hi uncle--
Sato Very good you came
Arty now took you away from me
Have you come good
She went to the groom
Come on
Where do you go Sato?
Hi, groom Oh, sorry
Groom who is
Happy is sweetheart
You found a boyfriend for an arts
I saw her now
Daddy boy who has nothing
The family is very good
Jazz did not want to go
Oh really
Daejeon John, Hey Sato
Come to the bridegroom
Yeah introduce it
Come on again
Come on Sato
Hello aunt
Hi, my boyfriend is happy
son in law
Come to meet her
Future Artist Husband
I know him
Sorry, you advised me
But I did not accept it
I do not forgive you
I should not say that
In fact, it's a smell of jealousy
You arrived
I did not get my art
No one else's money, right?
See I'm so embarrassed
Do not be
Actually, thank you for me
Well, you got rid of it
Otherwise, today would not be my wife
Truly, with the ticket
Book for the honeymoon
So now let's get married
Let's go
Yeah let's go please
Where are you
Look at your left
Something to say?
Pain will make you look pretty much
You imagined
Wearing my face?
Is it really for me?
I love you
So fond of me?
Send me a picture of your bridal gown
How do i get
Quite like a bride
What am i doing
Forgive me, i love you so much
I'm not living without you
I proudly ruined everything
I love you
Something to say?
That same day for you
You escaped from the wedding
Escape with me today for our love
How to escape
Mom, Baba, Sharad and his family
I'm talking to everyone
I will give it
Do not marry
Just come with me
Let's go
What happened?
Pick a finger
I can not go with you
I can not be for myself again
Break the heart of my family
I'm not sorry about the art
Please arrange
If that day was wrong
Today i'm wrong too
You did not make a mistake
Please, sorry
You can not be anyone else
I love you art
what do I do?
Artistic
How did you come in?
Satinder please
We were talking
What do you do
Just leave us two minutes
No, what do you do?
Middle note
I'm talking
Please two minutes
Sharad please --
How did i lift up my hand
Get your gun on your head
The hero of the game ... Let's get the artistic
You stay here
:Presented by Bollywood Cinema Reference
Www. Bollycine.org
sit down
Mala Mobed Begin
Used to escape from the wedding
I took it and brought it
Begin to pray
Pasha .. Today I'm going to die
What do you do with Sato?
I say i love art
You do not mix
Are you crazy?
Somebody is coming forward
Listen satynder
Art is not mine
I do not want anyone to be
I shoot
What are you doing
Do not see what he is doing
Why do you play so bad?
What does that mean?
Grab my arms
It was not in the map
I was not your daddy with you
I was with Sato Groom
What?
what is this?
What did you imagine
I'm my deputy prime minister
Say to them
Artistic art of your hand
You are here right here
The gun shoots
Do you shoot my gun
Do not touch
Do you have any guns at a wedding?
Do not leave your sister's husband
I'm scared
Ridiculous
I say
what are you talking about? say
what are you talking about?
..Good
This is your wedding
You told us at least
You got involved with Sato
What did i do
I'm sorry I felt bad
He was having some hours
The lymph was red
I'm sorry
Get to know her
Artist's sister husband
And he is my sister's husband
Sorry sister husband
Not so much for me
And artistic effort
Thank you so much
Thank you daddy
But I liked it
You played very well
So, give me three things (the turban of the bridegroom)
Three sisters sister
Where did the priest go?
Sound it soon
Call him
Be happy, my son
:A specialized translation of our artistic cultural media
Interpreters:Bingxa and Hajir
The most complete archive of cinema and television in India
Www. Bollycine.org
'I'll donate a ring for my ring and three bracelets of gold'
'First make a modicay, then take me home'
(The cost of seeing the bride's face)
'I'll donate a ring for my ring and three bracelets of gold'
'First make a modicay, then take me home'
I am not a damn it.
'See how I blossom
'You must see my face.'
'My Pillow is Pendant'
'High one, dear!'
'Your palm is hanging'
An outsider and shawl who '
'The method has gone down
Bollywood goes to my instrument '
'So take care of yourself
'The beauty of the clean boys is crazy'
'Your face is unmatched'
'Katrina and Karina have a lot'
'You are not in this country a property like you'
'When you want a charity'
'My heart beat goes up'
'Come ahead of you, dear, show your face.'
'I'm drunk without drinking'
'Look dear, look awesome,'
Make people shame '
'There is something like that
'Look dear, look awesome,'
Make people shame '
'There is something like that
'It's not your intention, it's bad news too.'
'Different and cautious'
'Shit, how do we go?'
'That's the way it's going to go'
'My Pillow is Pendant'
'High one, dear!'
'Your palm is hanging'
Copyright Awal Elixir