SHAADI MEIN ZAROOR AANA
Surely come to the wedding
KANPUR
How are you brother in law?
Very Good..very good
Come..come
Food? I will also eat
Did you bring the photo?
Photo? I've brought the complete biodata,
sister look
Where are you creeping in?
Go..go..First turn off the gas
-Please bring the paratta
-Yes uncle
Its Shukla ji's girl,
I've got all the details
And she's from good family
Mom used to say,"If you bring a girl,
bring from a lower status than us"
All of the house and family
will be under control, you see!
Isn't she beautiful ?
Ye..ah more beautiful, than expected
I hope she doesn't sits there doing
the makeup and I cook for her
No, no we are there know
You'll cook and feed your daughter in law,
I've less hope on that from you, Shanti ji
Yeah, why would you've any hope from me?
Show me
Daughter, you call Sattu
And tell him to see the girl on Sunday
Yes Papa
Tell me one thing, whenever meeting a girl
why do you sweat?
In ten minutes meeting
how can any one decide that,
I want to marry and spend my
whole life with this girl
Ok
And if the decision is wrong
Your whole life is gone
-So don't decide in ten minutes
-Then?
Lets book an expensive Mercedes,
get in it and go
Headlights, bumper check
everything properly
I'm saying, you'll make the right decision
Lets do one thing
I'll check the headlights, bumper,
all of your car and send it back
Shut up; Insolent
Shame on you, she'll be your sister in law
Your girl, my sister in law
and my girl ?
-Ok listen
-Yes
Don't boil eggs for me,
Today is tuesday
Friend, your eggs are defintely getting
boiled, She looks very beautiful..
I don't understand one thing; A girl
like this in Kanpur and I did not know?
Give me
Yes mom..I'll go there
Listen. Which clothes did you wear?
The pink one, which Guddy Aunt gave me
And listen wear matching earrings
Yes Mom. I've put them,
Last time also i wore the same
-Ok Mom, Listen
-Yes..tell
Talk to dad for one last time,
Maybe he'll accept
I studied so much and topped in MA
I don't want to marry so soon
I want to study some more, get a job,
become someone
And then I'll marry whoever you say
Talk to him for the last time and see
You know, he don't listen to anyone
I'm still hearing for sending
you to Allahabad to do MA
Now forget about studying further
And listen, talk to the boy properly
And as it is your habit, dont laugh
Be a little shy..in between
Mom I can't be shy and all
I'm telling now itself
Just as he's coming to see me
I'm going to see him
And if the boy is great
And If I say I don't want to marry
Will Dad force me to marry?
Aarthi dear, is there a problem?
What happened?
Why silent?
Yes Dad
Do you like any boy in the university?
No Dad
You are a fool! The boy is educated,
He is a clerk in the collectorate
Government work, a good home,
Much higher family status than ours
We cant find a good proposal like this
for you again and again
You are not going to get any IAS or PCS,
Did you understand?
Yes Dad
And yeah if you don't like this boy also
Jogi Uncle have found three more boys
Before the end of this year
You will be married, did you understand?
Yes Dad
So be quiet and go see the boy
What happened?
Nothing
-Satyendr
-Aarti
Please sit...
Will you have something?
Yeah, I
Waiter
What will you have?
Coffee
Coffee, Two coffee..something with it?
Pastry..No..Biscuit..No
-Two coffee
-Ok sir
Ask..what you wanted to know,
I'm ready for the interview
No..its not an interview
Just as I've come to see you,
You've come to see me
You can also ask whatever you want to know?
To tell the truth..I feel all this so weird
How can anyone decide about the whole life,
in half an hour?
I also feel awkward
Dad said that you are in a government job?
Yes, I'm a Clerk in the Excise Department
I'll join from next month,
I just got hired
Excise Department
People of Bribery
Do you want to take bribe and progress?
No..no, I don't believe
in giving and taking bribe
But our system is like that if you
don't accept, Still they will give you
No..no I won't accept
No..You won't be able to refuse
-You will see I won't take
-We will see
-I..
-Sir
-Thank you
-Welcome
What are your expectations from your wife?
Wake up early and make tea for me,
When I go for bath, make breakfast
Prepare lunch box for the office
Like my mom has been doing
for my dad all these years
When return from the office,
get ready and look beautiful
Massage my leg at night..
I don't expect these at all
I just want a life partner
who will be my friend forever
Just who takes care of my parents
And respect them, that's enough
What are your expectations
from your future husband?
Dad never gave me permission to work
I was always a topper since childhood
I expect that my husband
Give me permission to do a job
You studied a lot, your
education should not be wasted
It's good if you've a job,
we'll have double income
Then I won't have to take bribe
I have one more expectation,
but it's a difficult one
You just tell me
I expect my husband to take me to
see cinema every week
-You love cinemas?
-Soo much
Then every Sunday we will watch
evening show in Sangam Talkies
-Promise ?
-Promise..
So now what?
Choose a finger
This ? I'll call parents in the evening
And say yes for the wedding
Did you like me that much?
Me...Anyone would have liked you..
Unless you like someone else?
I'll also call my aunt in the evening
Can I say something?
You look really pretty in pink
Thank you
Satyendr...what was the second finger?
That inside you...
O that ! Instead of evening
I'll go to the bathroom now itself
And call them to tell I want to marry
Can I say something if you won't get upset?
Say it, I'll never get
upset about anything you say
It's not Aakward..
It's is Awkward.
Haa? Did I say Aakward?
Ok..Leave it..Anyway we are getting
married, Now nothing will be aakward
Awkward
Aww..Aww
Aw...kward...Kbard
Not Kbard...Awkward
Ok..I understood
I'll learn it slowly
Uncle..Greetings
-Come here
-Yes
Excellent..
If you want to respect, Do it right
Don't act
Come, touch again
Haa..come here
Blessings!
Now tell.. How is the preparation
of your competition going on?
Going good...with your blessings
-What'll blessings do?
-Greetings Aunt.
Father is dying in darkness
and son is power house
I'm hungry....Come..come
Ancestors died selling utensils
And son wants to be an officer
If your son wants to do something
then support him, dear
Once he becomes a magistrate or collector
Your seven generations will be improved
-Dad, next year I will clear 100%
-O..really?
If I'm busy selling utensils at the store,
How will I study?
I need to focus a little know
Son, I'll set your focus
You come home
Aunt, I told Aarti to attempt it
Last year she topped in MA
She'll definitely top PCS
Should I do one attempt on your face?
These IAS, PCS are not for girls
Don't give wrong suggestions to sisters
That proposal is very good for Aarti
So brother in law,
when are we going to Misrah ji's home?
-They've called there tomorrow at 3 o'clock
-Hmm
Stand here at sharp 2 o'clock
Don't be late
Brother in law, you make my arrangement,
I won't go anywhere
You'll not change..right?
I talked to Mahish Tomorrow few people
will come from Shukla ji's family
OK
-Shanti
-Hmm
I talked to Sattu
We both decided that
We won't take dowry
If we wont take dowry,
How will the wedding happen?
What do you mean by that?
Means will you be able to find Poonam,
A family who doesn't take dowry
No...right?
How can the wedding take
place without dowry?
We can't save much from your job,
to find an officer's proposal for Poonam
and we didn't create this custom
Whatever will come in Sattu's Wedding,
We will fix and give it to Poonam
Poonam's wedding is after two years
Well, Dowry will be twice after two years
Ok, leave it
You drink the milk, it is getting cold
I told Mahish, he'll come at 2:30
You won't say anything
Someone should be there to talk sensibly
Drink the milk and sleep
You and sister had already thought upto 12,
I'm saying, as boy and family are very good
If it's extended till 15 also,
We shouldn't lose this proposal
No, we can only afford 12 and,
We'll do it in 12
You don't talk there
25 lakhs
Is there 25 lakhs now a days? No, my nephew
can't get married...in lesser than this
Shall we go brother in law?
Let's go
Wait..Let me talk
We have come here to talk know
Mishra ji, we have a small plot in Kanpur
It will be sold in 3 or 4 lakhs
Some we have saved in Aarti's name,
Rest I'll take personal loan from the bank
We want this weddding to happen
Why are you embarrassing me?
Give what you wish..its a custom, which
is followed since ages or else we would...
Brother in law..just a minute
I'm here know...I'll talk
See..my nephew is the only son
And the only heir of this house
And now he has a government job,
In excise department
And here my brother in law is a professor,
In the university for 30 years
-What are you..
-So they have the standard to ask...right?
Yeah
When we get the money we wish,
Then we'll agree for this wedding else no..
Sorry sir
No matter how much you make us count,
If we double the amount also
it doesn't make 25 lakhs
Is your maths weak Jogi gi?
What?
-We've 40 lakhs offer....40 lakhs
-Oho..
It's because our Sattu liked your daughter
Otherwise we won't have taken,
a rupee less than 40 lakhs
It's true
You said so we stopped and waited for you
Otherwise tonight we would
have finalised another party
Sister where is their number?
Where is my phone?
Come on brother in law, in the evening
another party is coming, with 40 lakhs
Let's go now
I told you don't talk too much
Mishra ji you're wise and
you've seen the world
You can understand the
capability of a man like me
I'm definitely in a BDO's post
But for me till today a single
rupee of bribe is immoral
You please, tell what
is your final wish?
Shukla ji I am...
Shukla ji we can understand your capability
This wedding can't be
possilbe in less than 25 lakhs
Do you understand?
18 is cash, 7 lakhs worth goods
And this is our final decision
My brother in law and my
sister also thinks the same,
This wedding can't be
possible in less than this
Now can we go....? Brother in law
Mishra ji...I accept it,
I'll respect your wish
Why're you folding hands?
Shanthi ji give sweets..
Now we're a family
Congratulations..
You're cleverness and
attitude only works on me
Mishra ji I'll respect your wish
Now from where will you
bring the extra 13 lakhs
We won't get a good boy in
less than this..anywhere
Before retirement I'll take
loan and repay it slowly
At least my daughter will get a home
she likes, Thinking that....I said yes
Can I say something?
In pink you look like Juhi Chawla
In every color you look like Shahrukh Khan
Really?
Shahrukh Mishra
Let's go
You be the streets of Varanasi
So I can wander till night in you
You talk like the savoury chaat
Your eyes are like the Ganges
I'll sleep near to it
And In the morning wake up in you
You be the streets of Varanasi
So I can wander till night in you
Every Sunday, in Sangam Talkies
we'll watch movie, The night show
Like in movies, there will be a day
When I'll be your hero
Every Sunday, in Sangam Talkies
we'll watch movie, The night show
Like in movies, there is a day
When I'll be your hero
Entertain you, dance and
Romance only with you
I'll stay in your heart like happiness
So when you smile, my reflection is seen
You be the streets of Varanasi
So I can wander till night in you
Can I say something?
I was never so happy in my life,
As happy as I'm now by marrying you
Me too
Shall I drink coffee from your cup?
So where will we go for the honeymoon?
Haa?
For honeymoon?
I want to go to a cold place...like Masoori
We should go to Masoori
Okay, We'll go
I also have a secret wish
What?
With my husband once I want to....
Yes
I want to get drunk
I never drank, but I saw in the movies
and it seems to be so much fun
I saw how hero makes heroine drink,
And he too gets drunk
Then they have so much fun
I want to do exactly the same
And if husband is your best friend
You can trust him...Right?
Absolutely..
Secret..
Choose one finger..this ?
-We'll drink Bhiskey
-What?
We'll drink Bhiskey
What is Bhiskey?
It's whiskey
Yeah, we'll drink that
I feel intoxicated now itself
What was the second finger?
Barandy
It is not barandy...It is brandy
Staying with you, I'll become a foreigner
You do one thing..come home soon
Fix everyone's English
I'm tired of teaching them
What?
Really, did I say barandy?
Yes Satyendr
See, you call me Sattu
Those who love me, call me Sattu
See who's here...my beloved niece
-Uncle..
-Where is your husband?
O Dad..He is so busy
He'll come on the wedding day
Now I am here
Any work, Anytime
Tell me I'll never do it
You'll not find this
anywhere else in the market
-The bra is already attached in it
-Yes,its already attached
This is very petty..Its fitting is
excellent Sir, these can be worn together
There are colors other
than these, look
No sister...this is beautiful
If she've decide,she'll buy
bra and panties in pink color
-Neelam
-No, that you can but in any color
It won't be needed
Sister? you say whatever you please?
How much more time...?
I'm feeling ticklish...
Aarti will rub and change
the size of your shoes
Its my wedding you have to do pedicure
What's going on? let's see..
Now this whole bed is mine
Brother is hitting me...Mommy
Mommy let's take this
Aunty, promise by God you wear it..
You'll look exactly like Madhubala
If Dad sees us, he'll kill us
You also have one
I don't smoke, sister
Ranjan
Round...round...stop
No not from my plate
Dad...
It's very delicious
-Which one?
-Lets finalize this red one
Aarti loves it too
Dear, Red color is for girls
My son won't wear red
Excellent..
Your husband is a clerk and
Mine is a junior engineer
Mine is expert in licking
And yours will make you lick
Sister...
I meant the sole
Does brother in law
know, you smoke so much?
I don't hide anything from him..Aarti
And he doesn't hide from me
We're best friends and You also
don't hide anything from your husband
No..I won't hide
I already told Sattu
That I want to get drunk
with him during honeymoon
Aha? You are two steps ahead of me
And what did Sattu Sir say?
He is more excited than me
He has never drank in his life
Sister...He is so cute
Aarti...I've learned two things from
wedding Which is the most important
-What sister?
-A lot of sex and a lot of money
Sister...You talk anything
I'm saying the right thing
What a timing! He is amazing..
It feels like without talking to you
He can't even go to loo
Chee.. Sister
Put it in speaker, let me hear what he says
Speaker? in front of you...
Am I crazy?
I know what he would say,
You put on speaker dear..
You won't say anything..ok?
I won't say anything
Hi
Happy Birthday
You remember?
Yes, I remember everything about you
Is it?
Well...Listen wife, I want to meet you
In the temple at the main
bus station,
Tomorrow meet me there,
there's a room behind it
There we can meet each other easily
I'll give you...
Why will we meet in a room?
You don't misunderstand by the word 'room'
Everything will happen at
home only after marriage
I didn't see you for many days
I just want to see you
Without you, its even difficult to breathe
I'll not come
Ok, tomorrow evening 4 o'clock
Hey Sattu...hello
I love him, what a romantic boy
Move...Move
Well, from 2 things one is set in your life
Your sex life will be great
This boy will always be on you
Sister...
-And now I'm imagining it also
-Chee..sister
But Aarti there is one problem..
What?
In the matter of money,
I think he is a miser
Why?
You think about this... Do anyone
call his would be wife to the temple?
There are so many five star hotels
He could 've boooked a room there,
And gazed at you
What'll he do in temple?
Make you ring the bells
I don't know about all that,
but I'll reach there before 4o'clock
Poor thing can't even
breathe without me...know?
I'll be the oxygen
And fix it up until the wedding
But you remember one thing
Don't let him touch you
You know boys are bastards
First he'll do something,
Then he'll doubt your character
I'm telling you
Yes...My lord
Happy Birthday to you
Thank you Sattu..You did all this for me?
This is nothing.. I wrote
something for you, Shall I read?
Poetry?
Yes, shall I read?
Juhi, Madhuri, Divya Bharati
You are beautiful than them, My Aarti
You're laughing? Is it bad?
No..Its lovely...Pls read
You're my destination, You're my dream
You're God's most beautiful idea
Now my only intention is to,
love you more than myself
Sattu. How's it?
Very...very..very lovely
Thankyou
This rose....pink color suits you so much
What do you think..
Why did I wear pink color?
O....For me?
For what else?
There are flower petals
I'm in love with you
Shall I say 'I love you'
It is your choice
Ok I'll say
I love you
Now your turn
I also love you
Say it....say it know
Its so small, say it
I won't say, I'll say everything
after the wedding only
Ok then, I wanted to ask you something?
Please ask
If you won't feel bad?
Shall I kiss?
Shall I kiss u..
Will you kiss in the temple?
God is everywhere
Right ji....If you invited me to
a five star, Maybe I would have
One moment
I brought you something
Happy Birthday
Are you bribing me?
Bribing to kiss me?
I love you so much
Then do it
No...no leave it
Why, now you don't feel like it?
No, I feel...
Then do it please
Shall I?
Shall I keep it down?
I'll keep it
Only once
Move....you'll kiss and then doubt me
No, I won't doubt
No, You would
Mother Promise...I won't
Now everything, after the wedding
I won't doubt
Its just one day Sattu, Bye
Sattu just wait for a bit
Tomorrow we'll meet at our wedding
The sky is bright with many stars
When you shine like a moon in me
I'll be so near to you,
that I'll be your feeling
Dear, come I'll live in your every breath
You set like evening and rise like dawn
I'm walking by your shadow,
I'm with you...I'm with you
Now my only intention is,
to love you more than myself
I promise by my heart,
I am with you...I am with you
I'll spend my day and night for you
When you sleep, I'll watch you all night
You are so much dissolved in me
That if I walk in the crowd
without you, I'll feel lonely
In any mirror I look
I only see you
I also became your face
Now my only intention is,
to love you more than myself
I promise by my heart,
I am with you...I am with you
Your love kites fly in my chest
I fly in the wind and be your veil
I'm soaked with you in your rain
When your hair is spread,
I'll be your cloud.'
Your dark eyes are my sea of dream
I got down and lost in them
Now my only intention is, to love you
more than myself, I promise by my heart
I'm with you, I'm with you, I'm with you
Brother...Bride groom
Wake up, wake up
Can't you wake me up after two minutes?
Tomorrow onwards, when sister
in law will wake you up,
Lets see what you'll do?
Go from here
-Get up mom is calling
-Coming
See, my mehendi...in your name
Now your name is written in my life
Well, I'm yours in this life
Why only in this life?
I'm yours in every single life
Choose a finger
Right one
Its 'I love you'
What's the second one?
I love you very very very much
Did Haldi(ceremony) start?
Yes, we were waiting you
Did you apply?
Yes, Brother is full yellow in color
Brother, this is Aarti's
sister and this brother
Welcome to the family
No..no, don't touch feet
You're looking nice
Sister...Mom is inside
Ranjan ji..
How are you?
Didn't your husband come dear?
Aunty, you know how busy
junior engineers are
But he'll come on the wedding day
-Dear bring the breakfast
-Yes mom
And Ranjan, what are you doing?
Aunty I'm preparing for PCS exam
That's good
I've attempted two times
and this is the third time
Don't worry, you can do it, You
just have to try a bit more..
I just need your blessings
Thankyou
Eat...eat
My Sister in law's son is an RTO in Indore
Last year we went there
It is a high status
Government job has its own grandness
Yes, exactly
Now our Sattu also has a government job
Its Ok know Aunty, Sattu
has a government job
And Aarti also want to
work after the wedding
She is very lucky Aunty that you allowed,
My husband's family did not allow me
Allowed? Who said so?
Aunty, Sattu and Aarti talked about it
Dear Sattu is a kid,
He will say anything in excitement
I buy his underwear till now
See Abha dear
The brides of Mishra family don't work
It's our tradition, what will people say?
We live with daughter in law's money?
Till today daughter in law of our
family didn't work, And they never will
At least not until I'm alive
And about government job,
I am the goverment of this house
When Aarti comes and
take care of this house,
Let her think this as a
government job, right?
-Mommy
-Give
Dear, this is for daughter in law
Eat, son
You didn't eat anything
You are looking very cute
Sattu...here Aarti sister in law
Hello
I am very nervous
I'm feeling very weird
What happened?
I'm here...don't worry
Listen...Send me your photo in bridal dress
There should be some suspense know..Sattu
Please send..I want to see you
Surely you'll see,
Today I'm looking very hot
Why suspense anymore?
Now we are almost married
Stop it brother
I'm coming to take you
Bye
Shall I beat you? Are you out of your mind?
You are a fool
I was just talking in the phone
You could have told me
you wrote PCS mains exam
What is there to talk about it?
There's nothing to tell...are you crazy?
If it's all done..
Can I talk?
Aarti you cleared the PCS main exam,
You can be an officer
Your results came just now,
I saw online
Me...an officer?
Sister, I passed
Party!
People try for ten years and,
they don't get selected
Me and Ranjan are trying for
two years and we fail everytime
And this girl hit a four in the first try
I hit a sixer not four
Not sixer Madam...
You scored a century
Aarti think, you'll have your
own mansion, Car with blue lights
And the servants saying "Yes Maam"
A big job in UP state, your
own office in Sachivalaya
And So much respect
that you can't even bear
Now, you'll be told
"Yes Maam", Officer Shukla
Not Officer Shukla...fool
I'll be Officer Aarti Satyendra Mishra
I can't even believe it
Sister, I'll be an officer
Sattu is so lucky for me
Wedding is the happiest day of everyone's
life and it's double celebration for me
Sister....
Baraat (Groom's family) will come now
Hurry up...keep it near the gate
-Dad, one minute
-What is it?
-They are coming
-I want to talk an important thing
Do not get angry...please listen
Ok, Your husband mustn't have arrived.
I knew it...Where did he reach?
-Dad it's...
-Listen
Baraat is coming
Put on your coat soon
You also get ready
Dad listen,
Please don't get angry
What happened?
Tell me quickly...there's no time
Aarti wrote the pre exam
of PCS and she passed
Then wrote the main exam and passed
in it also. She didn't tell us, dad
She passed the PCS exam
Yes Dad
Online results came
Well, this is a very good news
Aarti is ready....right?
Baraat is coming
Dad, You're not listening..,she has cleared
PCS main exams. She can be an officer
From today, Aarti is Mishra
family's daughter in law
What will she do or not do,
Will be Mishra ji's decision. Ok?
Are you ready to welcome them?
Mom...tell him,
We are making a big mistake
They will arrive soon
Aarti's mother in law won't let her do job
By getting her married to this family,
We are making a big mistake
By telling your Dad also,
Nothing will happen
Mom at least you listen
Manju tell her to be quiet and go inside
Today its the wedding day,
Don't make me do something wrong
Dad...I know you're angry,
but think once with cool...
Don't talk nonsense,
otherwise my hand will rise
What are you doing?
She is our guest
If you say one more word....
I'll say Dad, why shouldn't I say ?
Be silent please..
What do you want?
Do you want Aarti to do cooking, like
me and mom and look after babies?
Shouldn't she try once to be an officer?
She passed the mains in the first attempt
She is very talented,
Why are you destroying her life?
Why shouldn't I say ?
Because of people like
you and her mother in law
Girls are sitting inside the house
What do you want me to do?
Hear your nonsense and stop the wedding
Shall I tell Mishra ji that my
daughter can be an officer..
So I want to stop this wedding
Yes Dad, stop the wedding
She can marry later,
But she can't be an officer afterwards
Her mother in law said she
won't allow her to work
She always wanted to do a job, Dad
Please stop this wedding
-Abha quiet..
-Manju, this girl is crazy
Take her away from me,
Otherwise I'll kill her
Something wrong will happen
You are doing wrong Dad,
with Aarti's life
Abha, Be quiet
-Am I doing wrong to Aarti's life?
-No, she didn't mean that
Listen carefully dear, you're married
Let your sister get married
Don't try to be chief of
this house, understand?
Mom please explain it to him once
Enough!
Enough. Pack your bags and go
We will complete the
wedding without you, Go
Dad just once
Go from here
What are you doing? Dear wait..
-What happened sister?
-You come here
Just now I sent a message to Sattu
Is every thing fine?
What happened?
Listen carefully, to what I say
Today morning I went to your in law's house
I told your mother in law that,
Aarti wanted to do a job after marriage
She completely rejected it
And said Daughter in law of
Mishra family does not work
How can she say that?
Sattu himself told me
Yes, I said you talked to Sattu about it
Did you know what she said?
Sattu is kid and she still buy his
underwear. Do you know what this means?
She didn't say this to me,
She wanted you, to know
That you definitely can't
do job when you are there
Forget about PCS
But Sattu told me
What will happen with Sattu's words?
He can't speak a word in front of his
mother. Now you decide, what do you want?
Sister...I can't be a housewife
I want to marry Sattu
But in our first meeting itself
I told him I wanted to work
And he accepted
I can't be a housewife
I will talk to Sattu once...
Why are you saying
Sattu...Sattu like a parrot?
He is going to be my husband
He is a clerk
When you become an officer,
25 clerks like Sattu will work under you
I'm not saying that he is a bad guy.
He is very good..
But even if he wants to, he
can't understand this, Aarti
What will I do now?
What will I do....means?
Look at me, father in law,
mother in law, husband, children
And three meals of the day,
which nobody cares
And on other side..respect, freedom and
your self earned living. Think of it, Aarti
Your future is calling you
Think of it...why did
your results come today?
It could've come tomorrow,
after your marriage
You could have done nothing but
now you can. Go from here, just go
I'll call my husband
He'll handle everything
You go to Varanasi with him
I can't do this to Sattu
Can you do it to yourself?
I and my husband
are with you, you go
Nobody will listen to
you Go from here...
Dear, you first become an officer,
Dad, Sattu...everybody will give in.
Aarti
What do you want, dear?
Dad, Sattu
That I'll take care
Do you want to be an officer?
Then go away
There is no other way, dear
The society is like this,
Value their boys more
But don't value their girls
And doesn't give them the life they want
That's why whenever a girl gets the chance
She must keep her head high
and live life on her terms
She should cross all the sea of fire and go
Go dear, Go
Aarti, leave now, Baraat is at the door
I have to go down so that
no one suspects and come
I can't do this sister,
Dad will kill me
Aarti, Uncle said he'll take
care of everything..right?
Just keep in mind that Uncle will say,
That you heard about dowry and ran away
Sister, what wrong did Sattu do?
He loves me very much
You will get love again in life
But this opportunity won't come again,
Go..
Can I talk to him once please..?
Only once..
No Aarti...Not now,
and don't talk to him until I say
If they come to know why you ran away
They'll put all the blame on you
Come now
Abhaa, Baraat came
Come, Let's welcome them
Mom
Brother in law is waiting at the back
You go now..
Go, go.
Good luck
Congratulations
To you too
Where is Aarti?
I'm asking you something
She didn't want to marry, Dad
She didn't want to, or
you didn't want her to?
What are you doing?
Beating your married daughter?
Go from here,
Go away
If not beat her...what should I do?
Worship her?
Please don't hit her...why
are you hitting her ?
Baraat is here
Tell me where did she go?
She must have told you..
I do not know Dad, sorry Dad
Educate her more
Send Allahabad to study
You can't even look after a young girl?
Why did you invite her?
It's because of her...
Uncle, why are you scolding sister?
I didn't pass till now
At least Aarti has passed
If I can, I would have choked them
And burn myself
Don't say so...
She has disgraced us..
What will we do now?
Come here
I can understand your pain
It is a hard time, But we
must somehow break it out
See don't think of the world
Just think about the 18 lakh cash, we gave.
What will happen to it?
Now you tell me what to say
Sorry Mishra ji, we made a mistake
Forgive me, our daughter ran away
Put our money in an envelope
and give it back, Like this?
That's it Sir!
You don't understand
Once Mahesh hears our daughter
ran, he won't give us a rupee back
All the savings of your life will go
So how will we get the money?
Sister it won't,
We must get it out
Brother in law, I'm begging you,
let me handle this from here
Just keep quiet in front of them
We will drink tea later
First, tell us what's the matter?
Why did you call us here?
Mishra ji, the thing is
there's a big problem
For us and for you also
-Problem?
-Yes
Jogi ji, What is the issue?
The thing is that, Aarti
What happened?
Son, when we checked,
she wasn't in her room
Not there....means?
There was only this letter
Take it
You look
When our daughter came to know that,
You've asked 25 lakhs as dowry
She decided not to get married
She left the wedding and went
Where did she go?
Dear, how do we know where she went?
Let me to talk to her
She isn't answering our calls,
How do we make her talk to you
Shukla ji, how's it possible
Everything was fixed with
the consent of both sides
You are right
I know it's not the matter of dowry
I'm sorry, Sattu
I haven't told you one
thing, I attended PCS exam
Today it's result
came and I passed in it
I'll be an officer
She went to study in Allahabad
Maybe she had an affair there
The girl ran away, disgracing the family
Did you understand?
Buy lots of charcoal and put
it on your faces, understood?
-Put a brake on your tongue, Mahesh
-Or else
What will I do?
I don't want to talk to you
Look Mishra ji, you are educated
I am folding hands and requesting you
Now our daughter doesn't want
to be related to your family
So, return our 18 lakhs, in peace
And go back with respect
This wedding is canceled
Is this train ticket? wedding canceled?
Your girl ran away
and you want money from us?
Shame on you, Is it a joke?
We will not return you a rupee
We'll not return a single rupee
You come, let's go
Are you crazy?
Don't think about leaving
without returning the money
What will you do?
Chandu, Keshav
Come here
Hey Ranjan, Take the gun
You'll shoot, then shoot us..
18 lakhs, until I don't
count each and every rupee
You aren't going anywhere,
Shoot him
I'll shoot Dad
Shoot
I'm not afraid of you
Come...shoot
Mishra ji...sit silently
And till you don't
return it with your hands
You're not going anywhere,
did you understand?
One minute, what are you doing dear?
Leave it
I'll get your money
But my Dad and Uncle shouldn't be harmed
I'll take and come
Aarti
Did you see Aarti?
No
Aarti
Sister, where is Aarti?
I called her many times, she
isn't answering. Where is she?
Take everyone with you and go home
What?
What happened Sattu?
I'll tell you later
-What happened brother?
-Sattu
I'm sorry Sato
I haven't told you one thing
I attended PCS exam
Today it's result came and I passed in it
I'll be an officer
Sattu
What happened?
-Dad...Uncle
-Nothing
Nothing Mom...Don't cry
Save them
Where did you put the money?
I've to give it to them
8 lakhs has been spent, 10 lakhs is there,
you take it and bring them with you
That's not enough, they want the full cash
We'll give them later
They won't agree
At this time from where
will we bring the money?
I kept it for Poonam's wedding
I wore this in my wedding
That girl will be cursed,
She made our life hell and went
Hello sister
Yes, they just went
They returned Dad all the money
Is Dad fine?
No, But uncle is sitting with him
I'll stay here for two days,
Until things get better
Did Sattu call you?
Yes, many times, but you
said so, I didn't answer
Sister, can I call him once please?
Yes, talk to him once. He is very sad
We made one mistake
His heart broke
I saw him
Stop the car
Where is he going?
Sattu see..
Brother in law
Dad, Dad
I won't die, son
I'm not so weak
I was not feeling fine
Open the button
Stop, one minute
I don't feel like going home
We were to go with the bride, right?
What will do at home?
See your mother's tears?
Everyone will be watching us
See it's..
Jugal Kishore Mishra,
whose son's wedding...
It's very embarrassing, dear
What are you saying?
Satyendra
Please take it
We won't leave them
Don't worry, don't worry
5 years later
In support of builders and developers,
We started a single window program
With which you won't have
to do double effort
So I hope you would invest in our area
This will be beneficial for you and for us
Ask me, if you have any questions
Neelam, how many times did I tell you,
Don't knock. Come in, straight
And I've told you many times,
Here you are Senior and I'm Junior
Look, I tried PCS exam five times,
But I did not succeed
But you passed in the first attempt
Aarti, I'm very thankful to you
Today I've a job because of you
Otherwise, I would be
teaching in a school in Kanpur
-Shut up...will you drink tea?
-Tea?
Compliments with tea...That's nice
Two teas please
I heard something from the office.
Is it true?
It depends on what you heard
Now don't act
The whole office is talking about one thing
What?
What are you doing? I didn't look
You didn't look
You were peeping
If you peep too much, you will fall off
You've put on weight
When brother in law is loosing..
He gets violent
Yes naughty
Dad, Neelam called
She said maybe Aarti will get a promotion
That's a very good news
Congratulations brother in law
Come Ranjan
It's tea time
Tea's here...Bring it here Sister
Keep it there, Ranjan
I'm very grateful to God
Aarti made a lot of progress in 5 years
Now if her marriage gets fixed,
I'll be at peace
Stand up
Why?
What happened?
Turn around..turn
Wipe your sari
What happened ?
Her needle is stuck at
Aarti's marriage for 5 years
I thought if I find it,
I'll move it a little
I'll give you one
Yes Uncle, play
Mom, why are you cheating?
When did I cheat?
-She cheated
-You cheated
If Sonu is saying then
you must have cheated
Dad, did I ever cheat?
-Sometimes you do cheat
-Tell him to go
Ranjan, you take him from here
Oh, you in the middle of the game...
Sister you come
Come Manju
Come, Uncle's nephew
I think you were born for me, Let's go
Manju it's your turn
Abha, when are you going to Aarti's place?
I'm thinking to go, day after tomorrow
Miss Aarti Shukla,
You're temporarily suspended from your job
For transferring the 90 acres of land,
behind the Barabanki railway
To the name of Kukareja and sons
You are charged, for
taking bribe of 3 crores
Sir you've known me all these years
Do you think...I can
do something like this?
Aarti..It's not about,
what I think is right or wrong?
Point is that,Yesterday in department
enquiry also, Everything was against you
And now official enquiry has begun,
which ADM finance is assisting
And DM sir has himself started this enquiry
They have asked you to go
tomorrow morning at 9 o'clock
Yes sir
Good Morning Sir
Miss Aarti Shukla, is that your name?
Sattu
Are you calling a senior
IAS officer by his name?
What's your post?
I am the sub-registrar
How many years?
Four years
You are just born and already
started taking bribes?
Do you want to progress taking bribes?
No but it's Ok, you are part of the system
So there's no problem in getting bribed
Right?
-It's not like that,
-Did I ask you to sit?
Sir, I'm innocent,
I can explain
You don't have to explain anything,
Aarti Shukla
You've done, what you wanted to do
Now I'll do,what I've to do
And for the mistake that you committed,
You'll surely get the punishment
Job suspension and six years of jail
When found guilty..
When or If?
When I declare you guilty
Satyendr, Please listen to me once
Sir
Hats off to you, Brother in law
You were watching her for 4 years
Now at the right time, requested minister
and took the case under your control
What do you think?
Is she guilty?
It doesn't matter to me
I just know she is guilty for one thing
And I will punish her for that
There are many hell in this world
I'll send this Aarti Shukla there
Everything is fair in love and war,
Priyansh. Love is over, Now war begans
Be happy
What happened?
Eat sweets
Why are you so happy...What is the news?
See this
What is it?
Just see it
Why are you showing me her photo?
What happened?
Madam was being very dignified,
and was against dowry
Ran away from the wedding
Now lets see how she'll escape
Why..what happened?
Soon she'll be imprisoned
Prison...Why?
For bribery
Not a small bribe,
3 crores
She'll be fully stuck...
You sweeten your mouth brother in law
Yes, we should eat sweets
Okay, I'm eating. It's Lucknow's news,
Sattu is also there
I tell him. He'll be happy
Yes tell him
-Greetings Mom
-I have a very good news.
What happened?
Am I going to be an uncle
No..better than that
The Shukla ji's good girl,
Who ran from the wedding
Now she is caught,
Charged for taking 3 crore as bribe
She'll go straight to prison
You are also in lucknow,
Ask about it
Mom, I'll call you later
Greetings
Ok
Hey Poonam ji
How much did Sattu ask that his
bride ran from the wedding?
I'll marry you without dowry.
What do you say?
Hey..Where are you going?
Hey Sato, Don't get upset, friend
Listen Mahesh,
She didn't go because of dowry
She went to become a PCS officer
And 25 clerks like Sattu will work for her
She doesn't care for people like Sattu
What you filled in my heart,
You will see that poison
You'll suffer my pain,
The Havoc of my curse
Now you'll see the result
of your selfishness
You rejected my love,
You will now see my revenge
The answer to my love was cruelty,
You gave this meaning
You weren't forced,
But still you betrayed me
You will see my hatred,
Morning and night
You rejected my love,
You will now see my revenge
You've done all this atrocities,
Keeping something in mind
At last, God gave you punishment,
For your wrong doings
The whole world will see
your defeat in public
You rejected my love,
You will now see my revenge
You've done nothing, still he
broke the whole house
Now he became IAS so will he do anything...
And he'll raid wherever he wants?
-Bindu
-Yes sister
Bring a glass
He has taken this case purposely
Is it not clear, he has come
to take revenge from her?
Why would we be afraid when
Aarti has done nothing?
Because we can't do anything
Every power is in his hands,
He told her that he'll send her to jail
You are badly trapped
Showing professionally but,
He's taking personal revenge
Sister, now you tell
what she should do?
Aarti, Why are you crying?
Everything will be alright
Drink water,
Aarti, You do one thing
Apologize to him
He loved you so much,
Maybe he's very angry because of that
Maybe he'll forgive you,
I heard that he didn't marry yet
You meet him somewhere outside the office
Or invite him for coffee
Maam sit, I'll call Sir
How are you?
How can I help you?
Listen I'm really sorry
For what?
For what I did to you
I still regret
Dowry was just an excuse,
I had written PCS exam.
Will you drink tea?
Ashok....Ashok
Yes sir
Bring two cups of tea
So what were you saying?
I had written PCS exam and
result came on our wedding day
I was confused,
I send you a message also
My sister said your family,
won't allow me to work
And I didn't think what's right or wrong?
Yes
I know I've been cruel to you, I hurt you
I want to apologize to you from my heart
I understand why you are so angry with me
But what will I do now?
If you were so sorry,
Why didn't you try to meet me?
How many times did I call you that night?
I thought we loved each other
And now when your case is in my hands,
You realized your mistake?
And if I didn't come here
You would have never
thought about me, right?
You were practical then, and you are
practical now but you have become more hot.
Officer Aarti Shukla,
Very tempting, desirable
Excuse me?
Are you feeling awkward?
You've come looking so beautiful
that Himalaya will also melt, Right?
So let's do the thing
for which you came here
Shall I shut the door quickly?
Satyendr, Please don't talk like this
What ?
Stop talking to me this way
Ok then tell me,
How should I talk to you?
Look at yourself ! Have you
come here to seduce me
Come on, I'm ready.....come
Satyendr
Listen Miss Aarti Shukla, if you
think after seeing your beautiful face
I'll forget the disgrace
of me and my family
It would never happen
And you also should never forget this
Please don't make this personal, Satyendr
It is personal
Its very personal
This betrayal of your's, I'll never forget
This is the biggest fight of my life
And yes, I'm not angry
I hate you
Now, get the hell out of here
-Satyendr
-Get out
-I'm sorry
-Get out, move
Miss Shukla, from now on
Don't wear pink and come in front of me
It feels disgusting, Go
Sir tea
Put it on the table
Yes say
Sir this is Aarti Shukla's father's pass
book and this is her personal pass book
-Is this personal?
-Yes
And that builder Kukareja?
Sir, He has a lot of businesses
And connection with great politicians
He bought this land to
build a factory there,
He is in London now,
And he'll be back by next week
Who arranged this deal?
Yes, I did it.
Sir this is my job
Did they have the documents of the land?
Yes sir, without documents
How can anyone sell the land?
And where is the owner?
Shifted to America...
Yes sir
And it's clear that you
don't have the number
No sir
Any Address?
Here! Where else would I be?
I came at 9 o'clock
It's five o'clock now
Did you eat anything?
No, only if I go outside know..
I'm not allowed to move
Take care,
Bye
Ok Listen, I'll call you back
Yes sir, I talked to her
Tomorrow at about 9 o'clock in
the morning and I'll meet them
Madam Tomorrow 9 o'clock
I'll talk and see what happens
Where were the photos taken?
Sir, this is when we
went to visit the site,
The same plot which Mr. Kukareja bought
You physically went and checked,
Where is the land and how much is it?
And then on purpose transfered the
government land, To the name of Kukareja
No sir, I really didn't know
Who is this guy?
This is Mr. Kukareja's CEO
Mr. Saigal, you must
have bought lots of land
Yes
This land which you all
bought, its market value
Is about 15 crores. For
how much did you buy?
Actually Sir, the thing is that..
6 crores
Yes
15 crores worth land in 6 crores
Then you got direct profit of 6 crores
Six
3 crores you gave to Aarti Shukla, right?
Is this your friend?
No Sir
I only know him professionally
He also gifted you a car
Sir, he bought it in my name
and gifted me on my birthday
I sent it back, But he didn't accept it
Sir, Its still parked in my car park
I did not use it at all
Umesh
Yes sir
Have anyone gifted you a car?
No Sir, Never
Never?
No Sir
They're also officers.
You are very special
This land was registered, three
days after your last birthday
Of course, when you're in the system,
It's hard to say no
You believe so, right?
Kukareja ji, you are
such a big industrialist
Yes Sir
You didn't verify the documents,
It's impossible
Only your officers would've known that,
Its government property
I'm just guided by the documents
The documents of the land was correct,
So I bought it
Are you sure?
I'm pretty sure Satyendr,
Aarti won't take bribe from anyone
I think you had a confusion
Did I ask you for advice Mrs.Neelam Gupta?
No sir
Who is this?
Sir,This is Aarti's friend
Not your's ?
How can big people like these my friends?
It's that Aarti used to take me to
the parties, So I would go with her
What does your husband do?
Sir, He is  a school teacher
How much do you both earn together?
What would I earn in this, Sir?
I just get my commission
Kukareja Sir said that she 'll
handle the things in government
Sir, What is my fault in this?
Look it's your right, Aarti
The Investigation Officer can be changed
If you want to, But in my opinion.
Don't do it
Because as far as I know,
DM is a good guy
The other officer who'll
come instead,
Don't have a good reputation regarding
women. So I leave it to you
Let's meet CM sir and then
we'll decide what to do
Listen. Tell Sir, I'll eat and come
Good Afternoon Maam, Pramod Singh
BA LLB Allahabad University
Maam, I know you from college
I was your senior
How can i help you?
Maam, Tell me how can i help you?
Whoever is your Investigation Officer,
I'll make deal with him
He'll prove you innocent,
But for that you've to...
I am her Investigation
Officer, Make the deal
Sir, I don't know him
-Do you know her?
-Yes Sir
-Is she your friend?
-Yes
She'll surely go to prison,
Atleast for six years
What is your name?
Pramod, Sir
So I'll send you both together,
To keep company
Take it
Write a letter for me
Greetings Mom and Dad
Aarti Shukla's Enquiry
Write
Aarti Shukla's Enquiry is going well
All the evidence is against her
There is no hope of being saved
No, hope
Tell Mom to get ready
to make offering to God
Ready to, make offering to God
Aarti Shukla will surely go to prison
What did you write?
What is it?
It's sure, Full stop
Your's Obedient Son
I'll write the name
You can go
Go and sit outside
Love isn't easy
Just understand that,
It's a sea of fire and you drown in it
No, I want to turn to ashes in it
You made a one yourself ?
-Did you understand?
-Of course
Listen to this, Priyansh
Don't you ever promise anyone,
That you'll love them more than yourself
This is it
This love and all is nonsense
-I want to talk to you
-Look who've come to see me
I dedicate the poem I just said,
To my able friend
Miss
What was her name?
Miss Aarti Shukla right?
Dedicate to Aarti Shukla
She is very famous, a very practical girl
She is the talk of the town
She was in the newspaper also
The bribery news of 3 crores, know
She is the one
Now if you had to go to prison,
Then why three?
At least she should have
taken 10 or 20 crores, right?
What happens in 3 crores now a days?
This is Men's washroom
I can't tolerate this
torture anymore, Satyendr
I'm choking, I can't breathe
What do you want from me?
What would I want from you?
I'm doing my job
Are you doing your job,
Or using this oppurtunity for your gain?
Am I using the oppurtunity?
-Yes
-Well, I learned it from you
You did it that time, now I'm doing it
I didn't use oppurtunity
for my gain, Satyendr
You know how to misuse an oppurtunity?
How is it?
If I scream now,
And I tell that you're molesting me
Satyendr Mishra IAS, my
investigating officer
Is asking me favours
That's called opportunism
Go and tell
No, I won't say
Because I'm not like that
Not then and not now, Satyendr
When results came, Baraat was at the door
I was confused
Your mother told my sister, She would
never allow me to work, so what would I do?
So you should have talked to me
You should have trusted me for once
How
I loved you. Didn't you think once,
about me for these 5 years?
Now, are you showing me tears?
What about my pain?
And what about my parent's tears?
I agree, But what should I do now?
What can't you tolerate?
That I left you
Haa, You couldn't tolerate the rejection
But for once did you think that,
If I hadn't run away
You wouldn't have been
in this position today?
What do you mean?
If I didn't run away,
you won't have this fire
in your heart and you
won't be an officer today
And you would still be a clerk, right?
Did you ever think about it?
Aarti Shukla, today the truth came out
You wanted to be an officer and had
problem being married to a clerk
You feel embarrassed by that, right?
I was a lower class man?
I didn't deserve you, know
You aren't understanding me,
what happened to you?
You wanted to ride in blue lighted cars,
And I was not of your standard
Aarti Shukla you were always selfish
that's not what I meant, Satynder
I'm talking to you
I'm not selfish
Do you want to send me to prison?
Ok then send
Call the police, I'll go
Send me now instead of tomorrow
At least I'll escape
from this daily torture
I can't do it anymore,
I'll accept that I took bribe
I can't do it anymore
You call now itself
Calm down, please listen
What calm down?
You want to talk
Okay, let's talk
You don't know how to talk, Satyendr
I'll talk calmly
I can't really tolerate
I'm sorry, I got very angry today
I thought you would kill me today
-When did you start smoking?
-After you left, I was feeling insane
Didn't know what to do, Leave it
Those are old stories...
Choose a finger?
-If you won't feel bad, Can we kiss?
-What?
One kiss
-I won't doubt your character
-No, Satyendr
No, I won't kiss you, you'll kiss me
It should be deep and passionate
And then that's a five star hotel,
lets go there to spend the night together
And in five star, you won't
have a problem to do anything
You said it, remember?
-You know it was a joke
-This is not a joke
Tonight is the price for your freedom
Come on
I misunderstood you
Won't you ask,
What was the second finger?
Today is 10th, in one week. The result
of the committee will be announced
Send me the 3 crores you have, Bribe
I am part of the system now,
If I refuse, still give it to me
I didn't take the bribe,
I don't have 3 crores
Ask Kukareja, He won't refuse you
You know a lot of facts about him, right?
Look Shukla ji
We can't help you in this
No sister, don't say so
Satyndar is not a kid
He know how to do his work
Now if its 3 crores, you've to give it.
From where will we bring 3 crores?
Look, we couldn't talk
then and we won't talk now
Once I sold my ornaments,
to save the lives of my husband and brother
Now you see what you can
sell to save your daughter
If I sell myself also,
I can't get 3 crores
It's your problem
Come Maam,
Kukareja ji is waiting for you
Ok I'll do it
Come Madam
I was thinking for days that I have never
seen you, But I heard a lot about you
Mr. Kukareja, if I am proven guilty
in this enquiry, I'll lose my job
My parents house will be sold
I'll go to prison
You have to come and say the truth
Everyone knows the truth
Don't act so naive in front of me
You have taken 3 crores
Did I take bribe? 3 crores?
Didn't you give it to
anyone in the department?
Did you take it
all for yourself?
You should have given a little
bit to your subordinates
What are you saying?
I didn't take any money from you
Someone from your department
must have told this?
Now I lost my respect
and money because of you
And now that you are caught so
You want to take me down with you?
Wow, Madam
I have seen a lot of officers, but not...
Miss Aarti Shukla is trying to
manipulate the Investigation
Arrest her right away
Yes, right away
We can't be disgraced more than this
He's taking revenge for each and everything
Lets try one last time
Take this, I kept everything in it
Go fast and save Aarti
Don't cry
Pray to God that they let Aarti free
Come Jogi
See. I'm here where you wanted me to be
Now your revenge is done, right?
Happy Birthday
This night is the best
birthday gift in my life
Thank you
Sir
I wish I had never met you
These are the documents of our house
Please save our Aarti
I'd like to present all the
necessary proof and evidences
that we'll need to
reach a conclusion
On Miss Aarti Shukla's case
I'd like to seek permission
of the hon'ble Jury to proceed
-Please proceed
-Thank you, Sir
I want everyone to watch
this video carefully
Is it written on my forehead?
You'r well educated, You
took the complete 3 crores
And came here again for money?
Okay, I'll give you whatever you want
Just close the case that
started because of your ignorance
Do you want to say something?
No Sir
I have nothing to say
I'll accept your punishment
Mr.Kukareja, I'm not afraid of you
If I go to the prison,
I won't let you escape
What is this? You said she came to
settle this.. I think she's crazy!
She threatened to send me to prison,
We should do something about her
Kill her
Her old lover came to take revenge..
He is behind her like a hungry lion
And we will the prey to her foolishness
We have to stop their love story drama
Kill her today
Can you explain Mr. Mishra?
Yes sir, I can explain
Mrs. Neelam Gupta's husband
is a school teacher,
And broker Rakesh
Yadav who welded this deal
Is her husband's childhood friend
The information of the land,
which is unused for years
Mrs. Neelam takes it from the
office and give to her husband
Which her husband forwards
to broker Rakesh Yadav
Then Rakesh makes false documents,
And sells it to different business men
Right Mr. Yadav?
Mrs. Neelam misuses Aarti's trust,
And gets the documents signed
For years, they have been
taking bribe,
in Aarthi Shukla's name and then
split it between them
Mr. Kukareja surely gave 3 crores,
But Aarti Shukla doesn't even know about it
Because the money never reached her
Right Mrs. Neelam?
Thankyou
The accused, please stand up
Thank you Mr.Mishra
The evidence is conclusive
The Jury is of the opinion that,
Miss. Aarti Shukla is not guilty
Arrest them
Yes sir
Sir
Today I understood Sir,
When someone close to us betrays
The heart really breaks
Thank you, Thank you so much
You can call me Satyendr
You can join from Monday
Sattu
Saxena ji, How are you?
Sir, You saved Aarti by
sending her to the police station
Very nice of you
Pramod ji, Good Job
Thank you sir
OK, I'm going to Kanpur
I'll see you, when I'm back
Aarti is innocent
Listen, Satyendr sent all
the documents of the house
I want to be with you forever
I want to bear all the sadness with you
What I can't say to the whole world,
I want to say it to you
You are so good !
How are you "so good"?
I want to become a crazy lover in your love
You are so good !
How are you "so good"?
I want to become a crazy lover
-Where is Sir?
-He didn't come here yet
-When will he come?
-I don't know
I took thousands of precautions and
understood,
You are river and I'm the water
You are the only path in which I can flow
After understanding a
hundred times, I realized
I'm the chapter of your story
Only when we join together,
We will reach the conclusion
Once again, one more time
I just want to see you
After all that has happened
Anybody would be effected, Aarti
If I was in Sattu's place,
I also won't believe in love anymore
Sister, you are right
But I feel, Sattu still loves me very much
If he didn't love me so much,
He won't have the hatred, to
be an officer and take revenge
Sister, Sattu never wanted to be an officer
The problem is that his
brain has told his heart,
Don't fall in love with her
Now I'll make his mind silent
And I'll make him hear
the sound of his heart
Sattu! Listen, how much will we run?
I'm tired of it
I ran and became a PCS officer
And you became IAS officer
Stop it, I'm tired
We have to stop somewhere, right?
I'm going to run away
from you, Aarti Shukla
Stop following me, our paths are different
What if our paths are different,
Goal is the same..right?
Sattu, slow down
I can't run that fast
Here OK
Thank you sir
One second
Can you drop me home?
Please, my car has break down
Sit
Thankyou
Drop her at home
Haa, Satyendr
Go
Where are you
I'll take time to reach
Till then you drink 1 or 2 pegs
I came
I know that you won't marry me
But that doesn't mean
we can't drink whiskey
Now wherever you are,
That's my Masoori
Order me a drink
Ok leave it, I'll start from your drink
It's ladies first, right?
Maam, Whiskey on the rocks
Thank you, It's sour
Nothing happened?
Something is happening
Your specs are coming in between?
May I wear?
-I'm looking cute, know?
-Please
-Maam, your drink
-Thank you
You know, something more is happening
You are Allahabad's Tom Cruise
Waiter, Bring one more drink
-Ok, I think
-Only one
Husband
I want to hold your hand
And wander in the mountains of Masoori
Please, don't joke Aarti
There are people here, please behave
Shall I kiss you?
One, little one
-She has drank too much
-Aarti
Sattu, Can I say something?
I'm thankful to God for making us meet,
Under the pretext of the case
Otherwise I would have lost you forever
Sir, why do you look upset?
No, I was upset before, not anymore
Let's go
Satyendr, Sattu wait I'm coming
Aarti, Be careful
I was looking for you everywhere
Can I say something Sattu?
Satyendr....Satyendr
Can I?
I think I'm in love with you
Shall I say I love you?
Haa?
I love you so much
I want to marry you
Is it because I didn't send you to prison?
I only got you out of prison now,
I got you out of my heart long back
I agree that it was my fault, Satyendr
Please agree
Life is so strange
There was a time when I
crazily wanted to marry you
I think about you all day,
And what did you do?
-You ran away...
-Sattu
-Remember, and now see?
You know the day I saw my family's disgrace
From that day I hate the word marriage
And In my life, I don't want to marry you,
Or anybody else
You understand that, thank you
The color of white love, my beloved
There's no deceit, no cheating,
no discrimination, my beloved
You are equal to a hundred colors together,
Fire has turned into ashes, my beloved
The war for which you are honoured,
I'm a soldier in that war, my beloved
You are so good !
How are you "so good"?
I want to become a crazy lover in your love
I want to be with you forever
I want to bear all the sadness with you
What I can't say to the whole world,
I want to say it to you
I want to say it only to you
-Ranjan
-Yes sister
FEW MONTHS LATER
-Are you out of your mind?
-What did I do?
What is this spelling?
Don't you know the name of brother in law?
And you wanted to do PCS, right?
He wrote Sharada for Sharad
Go, print it correct
Time goes by so fast
Look, how is God doing justice?
That girl betrayed
And he is sitting here unmarried
Have you promised yourself that,
we'll die without seeing our grandchildren?
Now that girl is getting married,
Do you want to play with her children?
Why will he play with her children?
Of course you're right
How long could Shukla ji,
keep the girl unmarried?
She have to get married some day
I am not refusing her to marry,
I'm telling him
Son, Let me be a grandmother before I die
Yes Son, your mother is right
We want grandchildren
Don't you have any other topic to discuss?
This is a very important topic for us
......your marriage
Now where are you going?
It's tuesday, I'm going to the temple
-How are you?
-I'm fine. How are you?
I am fine
I heard that you're getting married
I thought my enquiry was over
Shouldn't I marry?
No, please. Do it
It's your life
The, shawl
No, I was thinking a few
months back you were saying
You love me and you want to be my wife
Yes, I said, but you refused
Yeah, you're a practical girl
You always do the right
thing, at the right time
Should I wait for you all my life?
No, of course not
But I'm glad that I decided not to marry
Otherwise, I would get
stuck with a girl like you
Not a girl like me...
I'm one unique piece
And now I'm also getting married
-Is everybody at home fine?
-Yeah
Sharad
This is Sharad, my fiancee
This is Satyendr, my old friend
I know who he is, in fact, she
told me everything about you
And I want to thank you
I didn't do anything
Thankyou, is for doing nothing
What if you married Aarti?
What would I do?
Right...Aarti?
Just a minute, I'll come now
Sharad
You bring the car
If you don't mind, can I say something?
Say
Don't marry Aarti, She can't be trusted
What do you mean?
See don't mind but she is not stable
Just a few days ago,
She was following me crazily to get married
And now see
See as a friend, I'm telling you
If you marry her, you will be ruined
Otherwise it's your life,
your call....man to man
Thank you for this advice also
Here, take the offering
-No, thanks
-Satyendr, you
How dare you Satyendr Mishra?
Am I unstable?
Will Sharad's life be
ruined if he marry me?
What do you want from me?
You don't want to marry me
You won't let me marry someone else
What should I do?
Do you love me?
Of course, I love you
How many times should I say, I love you
So you love me and you
are marrying someone else?
Ok I won't marry him, will you marry me?
Will you marry me?
You won't, because your
ego is not allowing you
I decided to get married
Love is not necessary for marriage
Love can happen after marriage also
Come, on 10th for the marrige
I won't come
Please come, I'll feel good
Surely come to the wedding
Sattu
Hurry up Shanti ji
Let's go, We have to
take Mahesh also on the way
Call the driver and
ask where did he reach?
We are getting late
What's going on?
Where are you all going?
We are going to the wedding, dear
Aarti's wedding?
Yes
Why are you going?
Son, Shukla ji and his wife
personally brought the card
They pleaded that if we don't go,
They won't give away the bride
We must go, son
So what,  don't go know
-Hey, you are looking beautiful
-Thank you
I would say that you also come
Please, I won't come for sure
and I don't know why you are going
-Greetings
-Greetings Aunty and Uncle
Greetings
Sattu, Its very good that you have come,
Aarti just asked about you
It's good that you came
-Come on, Groom is here
-Come on
Where did you go Sattu?
Hi, groom
Oh, sorry, Groom is there
Congratulations Jogi
You found a nice boy for Aarti
I just talked to him
Boy is very nice and
The family is also very good
They didn't have any demands
O good
Uncle, Hey Sattu
Come let's meet brother in law
Yeah, introduce him
Come on..
Come, Sattu
Greetings Aunt
Greetings dear, Be happy
Brother in law
Come...This is Aarti's would be Husband
I know him
Sorry, you advised me
but I didn't accept it
I'm Sorry
I should not have done that
In fact, I felt the smell
of jealousy from your words
Like if Aarti isn't mine,
She shouldn't be anyone else'....right?
Listen I'm too embarrassed, really.
No..no..don't be
Actually, I'm grateful
It's good that you let her go
Otherwise, today she wouldn't be with me
And Dad booked the
honeymoon ticket to Masoori
So now let's go. It's time for the rituals
Let's go
Yeah, excuse me
Come
Where are you?
Look at your left
Can I say something?
You look very pretty in pink
What do you think..
Why did I wear pink color?
O, for me?
I'm in love with you
Did you like me so much?
Send me your photo in bridal dress
How do I look?
Just like my bride
What have I done, Aarti? I'm really sorry
I love you so much
I'll not be able to live without you
I ruined everything in my ego
I love you
Can I say something?
Last time you ran away from the marriage
Today also go away from here, for our love
How will I go? Mom, Dad,
Sharad and his family
I'll talk to everyone
I will make them agree
Don't marry
You just come with me
Let's go
What happened?
Choose a finger
I can't go with you, Satyendr
I can't break the heart of my family,
or anybody's family again
No,no..Aarti
I'm really sorry Please
If I was wrong that day,
then I'm wrong today also
You were not wrong, Aarti
Please, I'm really sorry
You can't be anyone else'
Aarti, I love you
-What will I do?
-Aarti
-How did he come in?
-Satyendr please
Can we talk for two minutes?
No, What are you doing?
You just leave us
No, what are you doing?
I said, I'm talking
-Two minutes please
-Sharad please
-Why did he hit me?
Get your gun
Put it on his head
-He is being a Hero, Come Aarti
-You stay here
Sit down, Pandit ji begin..
She has made it a habit of running
away from marriages I brought her here
You begin
No, Sattu
I'll kill him today
What are you doing, Sattu?
I said I love Aarti, Don't you understand?
Are you crazy?
If anyone come forward...
Listen Satyendr
If Aarti is not mine
I don't want her to be anyone's
I'll shoot
What are you doing?
Don't you see what he is doing?
Why are you doing so much over acting?
What is he doing, man?
He is holding the gun,
this was not in the plan
Brother in law, I'm not talking to you
I was talking to Sattu brother in law
What?
What is this?
What did you all think?
Only you know planning and drama
I'm a DM
Tell them
Aarti is gone, you stay here
It is a gun
It will blow
-Will you show me gun?
-Sir
-Will you shoot me?
-Please don't hit, sir
-You take out the gun in every wedding?
-Sir, it's hurting
Calling me...Brother in law,
You are making fun of me
I'll say...I'll say
-What will you say?
-Will you listen......yes what?
This is your wedding itself
You could have at least told me,
that you planned with Sattu
Sister, What to do he hit me so much?
See, my face is red
I'm really sorry
Meet him
He is Aarti's brother in law
And yours too
Sorry brother in law
But seriously, you all did
this much for me and Aarti
Thank you so much
Thank you Dad
-Take the gun away..
-But You all acted very well
So, give me my turban
Give it, Brother in law
Where did the priest go?
Call him
Always be happy, my son
THANK YOU