Come in.
What was so urgent?
Inder, get some water.
You could have come in the morning?
Shahid...
By showing me injustice, He taught me to love justice.
What does it mean?
I don't understand English well.
By showing me injustice..
..God taught me about justice.
By inflicting pain and suffering..
..he gave me the courage to fight.
He taught me to help the helpless
A criminal has no religion.
Eventually both the killer and his victim are human.
Right?
Did I say too much?
Never forget this
(Voice on walkie-talkie) Come in. Kill "those" bastards.
I haven't had any sleep. Kill the bastards.
Mother, where's my shirt?
It's right there
I can't find it
look carefully, son
Press it like this and take it out this way.
Done that.
Where you going?
Shahid, where are you going?
Coming.
Shahid, where are you going son?
Coming mother
Where is Shahid?
Shahid?
Open up. It's Shahid.
Brother Shahid...
Mother, open the door.
Brother.
Open up. It's Shahid.
I think it's Shahid.
Open the door, brother.
Please let me in.
Mother, it is Shahid.
Get out of the way.
Why did you go out?
Why did he go out?
Everything's been set ablaze.
They are killing women, children..
They will destroy everything.
Are you alright?
Okay. Be quiet.
"Without any care, the colour has started to drain away"
"Rather than living like a slave..."
"I feel detached and dismayed"
"I can't express my condition"
"I'll get sacrificed surely"
"Life seems to have gotten angry with me"
"My heart-beats are now like smoke"
"I don't see any solution..."
"...nor do I see a direction, to head towards my destination."
"Allah o Akbar."
Kill him. Slit his throat.
Kill him.
"Allah o Akbar."
Shahid, stop.
Shahid.
"Love has slipped away"
"There isn't any care remaining"
"My heart just remains a assembly of thoughts."
Mother, Shahid is back
Shahid, what took you so long son?
We've been waiting
What about your exams?
Are you prepared, son?
Come on, freshen up. - Let me talk to him.
He just returned from our village let him freshen up first.
Let him rest for a while. He has returned after a long time.
Shut up!
I haven't told them where you were.
Shahid, switch off the lights. I can't sleep.
Shahid, switch off the lights.
Just a minute.
Switch it off.
Did we ask you to stay this long in the village?
Quiet. I have work in the morning.
Now study.
I can't even sleep peacefully now.
Shahid, what is this? Switch off the light.
He's switching on the light.
Shut up all of you. Go to sleep. Stop creating a ruckus.
Shahid, switch off the light.
Just a little while longer. - Shahid, do it now.
Ask him to turn off the light.
Where are your manners?
I am going out.
Go to sleep!
Driving me insane.
Just shut up and come with us. - I've done nothing sir. Honestly
My son has done nothing, sir. He has a job.
What do you need to know from him?
We just want to question him.
Get out of the way
Shahid, they are taking your brother away.
Who the hell are you now?
Shahid, move aside.
You are Shahid?
Leave that guy. Take this one in. He is our man.
He hasn't done anything wrong.
Get in the fucking car!
Shahid.
What are you staring at?
Come on let's go home.
Tell me now motherfucker.
Sit straight and stop crying.
3 terrorists. You don't recognize them?
Him?
Did a cat get your tongue?
Don't you recognize him?
I've done nothing, sir. I swear.
We found your phone number..
..in his fucking diary.
How does he have your number?
Why not ask him, sir. I've done nothing.
You thick skinned pig!
Tell me.
I swear I've done nothing sir
I really don't know.
Please, I haven't done anything.
Sir.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, I am Arif.
Sit down, why are you standing?
Thank you, sir.
Sir, actually I wanted a meeting
With whom? - With Shahid. My brother
Stand up.
Can't you hear me? Stand up.
He is no longer your brother.
He's now an enemy of the country.
Do you know what the anti-terrorism act is?
Sir, I went to Arthur Road jail.
Where have you come from?
Where do you live?
Sir, Bombay.
It's almost 6.
Take the next train to Bombay.
Come back in another 6 months
6 months? I've been coming everyday..
.. for several weeks without an answer.
Are you doing us a favor by coming here?
We didn't tell your brother to join the terrorists.
Sir, he is not a terrorist...
Don't show off by speaking in English.
Why are you swearing at me?
I'm trying to be respectful.
All I want is to meet my brother
Just get the fuck out of here Get out now!
What do you mean get out?
Get the fuck out of here.
Listen brother.
Sign here
Take my advice and you will be let off lightly
Or you may be stuck here forever.
Here.
Sign here.
Believe me.
I'm not your enemy, brother.
This is your only chance. Sign it
How is Shahid?
He is fine, mother
Do they still trouble him?
No.
Do they still torture him?
He is absolutely fine.
Tell me.
Keep moving.
Come on.
Hurry up...quickly.
Keep moving ahead. We're already behind schedule.
Keep moving.
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
What happened?
Can't you hold on to your fast for even 30 days?
What kind of Muslims are you?
Eating like gluttons when you should be fasting..
..and you call yourselves Muslim
Stop staring. Stuff your faces!
Greetings
I'm Omar Sheikh
I know. I've heard about you
What's your name?
Shahid
You are really quiet...
I'm sorry about the other day
I tend to lose it during the Ramzan.
Firstly, you're starving...
..and then you see your brethren hog before you
What can they do? The jail doesn't
allow them to follow the Ramzan routine
Do you play chess?
I do.
So then let's play.
When? Now? - Then when?
Let's go. Come.
I'm getting out of here
But your term is much longer?
They will do anything to get me out of here
Hijack a plane, take people hostage, anything
For whom? You or Masood?
Come with me.
Look at me.
Look at me, Shahid.
What?
What do you think? Will you ever get out of this place?
When?
Tell me, when? - No idea.
No idea?
Arif, stop visiting me
You are wasting your time
What do you mean?
It's pointless.
It's a waste of time.
I'm trying to get you out, Shahid
I grow weak every time I see you.
I won't survive this if you come again.
Don't come back again
Take care
So the 'Jihadi' likes to read?
What was that?
Come again, what did you say?
What do you know about me?
Birds of the same feather, flock together..
What flock?
The ones you play football with.
They are my friends.
They are nobody's friends..
They are smart people.
First, they will give you a political lecture.
Then they will use you.
They believe they're far superior to you.
I'm aware of Omar's oratory skills
He speaks well.
So what if he speaks well?
Omar knows Kabul has more than just horses.
This is a bad book.
Meaning?
It's simple. Gather all the asses around
and you automatically end up as their leader.
How are you such an expert?
Because I know the story of one such ass.
Who?
Me.
Greetings, sir.
Bless you.
This is Dr. Saxena.
A professor at Punjab University
Now let me introduce him.
He's a great guy.
He is Gulam Nabi War
He is opening a civil services institute in Kashmir
Especially for the poor
I am helping him with his project
If you want to change the system...
...be a part of it.
Sir.
War's father owned a carpet factory
But all businessmen had to pay a protection tax to the terrorists
War refused to pay once and they had him framed.
And now he's serving time.
He is quite a short-tempered man.
His father died two months ago.
How can they just throw people in jail without reason?
How far have you studied, Shahid?
I was preparing for my college's second year exam...
Shahid, you should study further
Sir, welcome.
Tired?
No, no..
Hello.
What?
I want to study
So what's stopping you?
The warden won't let me
I will talk to the warden
Now what's the problem?
Nothing, just..
Money?
I don't want to ask my family
I will pay your fees
No...
Fine. Sacrifice your education
for your silly self-respect
No. It's not that.
I will return the money
That's what I am saying.
Return it when you can
Yes. I will - This isn't charity. It's a loan
There is a condition
You have to stop meeting Omar and his donkeys
But I don't know anyone here
Why? You don't know us?
I do...
Ok, meet them on Sunday
Over a game of chess, only!
Don't get brainwashed
Nah.
You're too smart for them
Why don't you join the game?
No. Go ahead enjoy yourself
Thank you.
He is a bright kid
No matter which country's history
you are reading..
..there's one thing you should understand clearly.
It is not only about wars, conquests and battlefields.
It's much more than that
In fact, while studying history...
Beat the Mogul Empire, And banished them out of the empire.
And take over.
Within 5 years time...
...this man turned out to be the most remarkable king of India.
Sher Shah Suri.
You guessed it right.
Understanding of the final aspects of life.
Are very deep.
Just see how simply he says...
...the way he looked before and after...
...and time for...
It's amazing.
How simply, how honestly...
...and how precisely.
He has put a thought...
...that we all understand
But nobody has had the words to... Express...
It's only Percy...
No, no...
No, please.
Take it.
Dr. Saxena always says..
...that it's difficult to swim against the tide
But if you manage to do it...
You may find a shore that nobody has ever seen
Make the most of this time, my friend
Study hard
You won't even realize how time will fly
Just study
I maybe leaving this jail,
but I'm still with you
I'll see you again
Thank you
It is obvious that principles of natural justice have been..
violated in the State v/s Shahid Azmi case.
Shahid is hereby honorably acquitted..
and the court apologizes to Shahid and his family..
for the inconvenience caused.
It takes time, but it works
Indian Judicial.
It works.
Stop here.
This is home now. How is it?
We are on the first floor
It's made of concrete.
Come on.
Mother, the door bell
Answer it
Khalid.
He is all grown up now.
Mother, the milkman is here
Coming
Chandu, can't make yoghurt from the milk these days
How are you?
I'm okay.
Where do you roam around all day?
Where do you go?
Looking for jobs.
Job? He wants to do a job
Study. No comprises on study.
Brother, I want to study law
I've filled the form.
Why are you getting involved with the law again?
This is what I want to do
If you want to study, then study
You can't study and work simultaneously
Do one thing at a time
Mother, I will manage
Mother. Yes.
Mother, my first salary.
You keep it son.
You will need it.
I have enough. - No mother, keep it.
Do well, my son.
Bless you.
What's for dinner?
What do you want?
Will you make Biryani?
Okay.
Is Arif home?
Yes.
I've got a job
With lawyer Maqbool Menon
Good
I would have to leave the job that I'm doing..
So?
..but they will pay less.
How much?
Rupees 1200 only
How will we manage?
No worries, I have a plan
Please sign on the first and last paper.
Excuse me. Yes.
I have a meeting with Mr. Menon
What time?
4 pm.
Please take a seat
Mr. Galaadari, how long have you been working here?
7-8 years?
The judge will throw this file on your face.
And all of you handle civil cases, right?
Just like civil cases..
..that rot for years in old dusty cupboards..
..your brains too have begun to rot.
Look at this pencil
Blunt and small like all of you
Nobody ever bothers to sharpen it!
Your English is pathetic
How can you be practicing in High Court?
You guys deserve to be in the Lower Courts
Get out of here!
Where can I meet Gaffar?
Gaffar.
I have come from Menon's office
Where is Menon?
He's busy
Who are you?
I'm Shahid
So?
He can't come. He has sent me instead
Do you know who you are talking to?
Yes, I know
You have stolen 20 cars from Bombay.
While stealing your last car, you also assaulted the owner.
He has lost an eye
Now whatever you have to say, tell me
Can we sit and talk?
I will speak to Menon, you go
Abdul, remember his face.
Maryam? - Yes
I'm Shahid, from Menon's office
Tell me
You have a hearing next week
So you are here for the fees?
No...
Sir asked me to...
I have seen enough lawyers
More than you can imagine
I could not arrange the fees
I can part with a percentage after selling my property
Sir wanted the money before the hearing
Please leave then
But...
I said, leave...
I can talk to him if you want...If you need..
No sorry, I don't need any help.
Please. Leave. No.
How do we make money, Shahid.
Cases
Gaffar?
I met him, he's lying
I know
First he needs to trust you...
..then you will begin to trust him
It takes time
I know sir, but...
Police is right. he is guilty
I know
Then why are we defending him?
Because he is a client
It's an open and shut case. If we know he is guilty, then..
You want me to teach you law again?
What do we do first?
We collect the facts..
..then we manipulate and present it the way we want
The more you waste your time on these books..
Son, you will lose all cases that you fight
And witnesses?
Huh?
What witnesses?
Witnesses are all hostile now
All in the palm of my hand
What is this?
Sir, please appoint someone else for this case.
You came to my office begging for work
"I want to fight criminal cases!"
Nobody cherry picks cases in my office
Get out
What's happening at your end?
The world chases only money
I did not become a lawyer for money
I'm thinking of starting my own practice
There is a little cost involved, but not that much
I already have two loans to repay
Okay, I'll apply for another loan
Don't worry, start your practice.
When do you want to start?
I'll get the license tomorrow.
Oh! So you applied already?
Hello, Maryam!
Maryam! This is Shahid, remember? from Menon's office
Oh no, not for that
I have started my own practice
Yes.
Have you hired another lawyer?
How do we manage the house expenses?
Please don't cry
Shahid?
I'm Maryam
Please wait
Don't worry, case is in your favor
Okay. Okay.
Please come
Sorry to keep you waiting
Tea or water?
Nothing, thank you
Inder!
Go get some water
And get some tea as well
Property dispute case, right?
Yes
Please tell me a little about your case
My step mother has challenged my father's will in the court
My father had left me a house in Mumbai
She is now claiming it
Your step mother?
Have some water. - Thank you.
Is this the file?
Yes.
I don't have anything else apart from this house
Don't worry
This is your house and it will remain yours
Right?
And your fees?
It's ok. Not that important
You must tell me
Whatever you feel is right
There is a thing in our lawyer's code of ethics
What?
First we win the property from your enemies..
..and then keep it for ourselves
Then you will have to hire another lawyer to reclaim the property from us.
I've never heard of this before.. - It was a joke
Sorry, bad joke.
Shahid.
Phone.
Yes, mother.
I'm in office.
Yes, I am coming.
Greetings.
He is Zaheer's child.
He hasn't seen his father yet.
Go to uncle.
What's his name?
Asgar.
You're going to meet your father soon.
So be it.
Partition has caused loss to many.
Especially Muslims.
We're suffering in India..
..Pakistan and in Bangladesh too.
Yes, we all are suffering due to mistakes done by few.
What to do?
Well, remember I told you about Zaheer.
The one who was accused of Ghatkopar blasts? - Yes.
He's a software engineer.
He's completely innocent.
Did you meet his family?
Yes, I've done all the research from my side.
He's completely innocent.
I'm sure that we will win this case.
God willing.
Your fees?
Don't worry about that.
Only for official needs.
Yes, that we will give.
I was asking because..
..our finances come through donations.
During the month of Ramzan..
..we visit people's homes.
And the donation given to us by them are then used..
..to run the 'Jamaat', so I hope you understand.
No, don't you worry about the fees.
Zaheer, tell me everything you know
Don't try to lie or hide anything from me
If I find out later that you did...
I will drop your case
Tell me everything.
I have done nothing wrong
I just made a small mistake
I gave my laptop.. - I know that
It's been over 18 months
I'm beaten up everyday
Everyday I'm treated like a fleabag
No value for human rights here
You visited my house..
Do you think I am a terrorist?
Public Prosecutor, you can continue.
Zaheer This laptop...
Whose laptop is this?
Tell us whose laptop it is..
Who is the owner?
It's mine
Your laptop?
Who did you give it to?
Reply quickly!
To my friend
So you didn't know what your friend was using the laptop for?
No, I didn't know
You gave him your laptop..
But you didn't know what he was doing with it?
Prosecution is trying to lead my client..
..when he has said that he does not know
How can he not know? He said That he gave it to his friend
Your honor, the laptop was being used to send letters..
..for a banned organization
This is all unsubstantiated
The laptop was with his friend when they found the videos.
This does not have to be proved
Why not?
Please... you're doing contempt of Court.
What was inside the laptop..
..patronizing Jihad, Gujarat riot videos, inciting messages
It was not my client's, But of his friend who used it
It was his friend who used.. - If the prosecution..
..the laptop for all this - ..is saying the same thing
..then what is the case about?
Please, you are a senior
Do you want to ask something else?
No.
Thank you.
Thanks.
You...please continue.
Zaheer you gave the laptop to your friend?
Your honor, may I?
Please. - Thank you.
You gave the laptop to your friend, Enamul?
Yes.
Why?
His computer had crashed and he needed it
You have a computer repair shop too
Why did you not repair it instead of giving your laptop?
He needed a computer urgently
If he needed a computer he could have gone to a cyber cafe
Laptop is not a cycle that can be given to anyone who asks for it.
They are childhood friends
They are childhood friends - How long have you known each other?
since we were about 5 years old
Since they were 5 years old...
How can he not know? They have known each other since they were 5!
If a childhood friend asks for your camera..
..pen or mobile won't you give it to him?
I will, but I will know what he might do with it
They're bound to do everything together.
Mr. More, you are a senior lawyer, please sit down
Your honour, you have been asking me to stay quiet..
..just because I'm a senior
This is a contempt of Court.
Please... - This is...
A childhood friend comes to my house..
..and asks if he can stay in my house for two three days
Will I not let him stay in my house?
If he keeps a bomb in my house how will I know?
If the bomb is found in your house..
..then evidence is against both of you
You're just as guilty.
For a minor error of judgment my client has been languishing in jail
You were just leading the friendship issue.
Don't you know your childhood friend inside out?
I just remembered something...
Where's the need to get angry?
You are not making any sense..
Tell me one thing, wouldn't you know your friend?
Especially if you had known him since you were 5?
I understand.. I have childhood friends too..
Show me what's in it? - Nothing.
I can see a sandwich, give me some.
Give it.
Mr. Prosecutor, I hope you realize...
...you're on a slippery ground.
Police is investigating. it takes time
For the last 1.5 years they have been investigating
Please finish your investigation soon
And now we request bail. - Bail denied.
My client is ready to give an undertaking..
..that he will not leave the city
Next hearing 24th.
Please reconsider. No.
What good's an undertaking?
Witnesses can turn hostile
He can kill someone or get killed.
Don't worry the verdict will be in our favour
I don't understand the verbiage you use inside the court room
I don't know if it's in our favor or not
A lot of people don't understand it
But I am telling you.
The judgment should be out soon
It will be in our favor
In a month?
Maximum of three months
Ok
Are you in a hurry?
Just wanted to sell the property and go back to Delhi
Why? - I want to start a school there and teach children
You can open a school here..
.. there are kids here too who want to study
They also need good teachers
You want me to stay here?
It's not like that?
Are you married?
Because I'm your lawyer and I should know everything about you
Is the judge going to ask this question?
No, I'm asking
I'm not married
It's ok, don't answer
But are you married?
You ask too many questions
That's my profession
Hello
Maryam?
Who is this Maryam? This is Ramanathan.
Ramanathan.
So, you started your practice without telling me
It's not even started
By the way, who is this Maryam?
Just a client
Tell me.
Client.
Hello.
Yes, speaking
Drop Zaheer's case immediately.
Who's this?
Your father!
Drop the case, you motherfucker..
..or you will be sorry that you were born.
Where are you calling from?
Doesn't matter where.
Next time I won't call you.
I'll kill you.
A gangster threatened me.
What?
Over the phone
Why?
Don't know, they were saying..
..that you have to step back from Maryam's case
My case? - Do you have any relatives like that?
I don't know anybody like that
No
But somebody did threaten me
They want me to back out from another case
What do I do?
What does your family say?
I haven't told them
And you're telling me.
Why?
Please tell me what to do?
Okay.
I think you should not back down
Why?
Because you're right and they are not.
Yeah!
I knew you were going to say that
Really? How?
Because, I think the same
New evidence submitted in the court..
..has the confession statements from Altaf Ahmed Imran Qureshi.
The police charge sheet states that Zaheer..
..was involved with them in the conspiracy.
Their statements clearly states that..
..they just knew Zaheer and he was not a part of the plan.
Prosecution.
We are waiting for the external affairs ministry..
..until they confirm that the mobile number is not Zaheer's..
..we can't corroborate the other evidence in court..
How much time will it take?
Ministry of external affairs, time frame is difficult to ascertain
Your honor, we request bail.
Bail denied. Please reconsider.
Noted
This is between ministries this might take a lot of time
He is a father who hasn't seen his child since its birth
Bail denied. We request...
Mr. Council...
Evidence is against... - Please approach the bench.
Mr. Shahid.
Sometimes you have to let go.
Your honor, with all due respect... All I am saying is...
They don't have any proof against my client.
They are deliberately delaying the verdict, while my client suffers.
What we are doing is completely legitimate, how can you say that?
We are following the procedure.
I am not saying that they are not within their rights..
..when you arrest someone under the act, at least have a timeframe..
..you can't keep an innocent behind bars for 10 years like this.
Police is well within it's right.. - It's not about the police...
After 15 years even if you free someone, what's the point?
This law is national necessity, Mr. Shahid.
I know...I know.
Sir, delaying justice is denying justice
We're here to serve the law.
I am not questioning the law, sir.. Please.
All I am saying is... - Mr. Shahid.
Just look at him... - Please, you can go now.
Both of you.
Next hearing.
Mr. Ahmad Sheikh and Apurva.
Hello, brother Aslam
I have an important favor to ask
You have a link in the UAE external affairs ministry, right?
I have to get a fax to the Indian Ministry
Please get this done
Somebody will bless you for the rest of his life
Bail denied for the 9th time
When they have nothing all they can do is delay things
How much time do you think?
A month, maybe more. I don't know
You can see that I am trying
You heard the judge telling prosecution that day
"You are on slippery ground"
Our case is strong Zaheer
All they talk about is the Gujarat riots video
What about history channel videos, educational videos?
Mom and dad's pictures.
It's their case and they will show what they want, the way they want.
What did I say earlier?
It takes time but...
It will happen.
This is from the external affairs ministry..
..and it's been confirmed by Dubai Ministry.
And it states that, the mobile number's..
..registered user which the prosecution keeps talking about..
.. as vital evidence belonged to Khwaja Yunus and not my client.
It's all there. Prosecution. Yes, sir.
I am not aware of this
And under the Indian Evidence act, this evidence is not admissible.
This is primary evidence. Prosecution has been waiting for this
We haven't had time to review it.
You were saying that the mobile number had come from Dubai.
Here is your confirmation
Does not matter whether it comes from Dubai,Kuwait or Iraq
It has just arrived and we need time.
Prosecutor, if you have to directly say anything please do..
..or I am moving ahead
There's a similar case, you can have a look.
We need some time.
The Dubai ministry has confirmed that the number is not my client's.
It can be any ministry, how does it matter?
Prosecution, every case has its own facets
It is relevant under the Indian Evidence Act 1872..
and I will admit this evidence
Thank you so much, your honor.
But we need some time to cross-examine' No, thank you.
Thank you very much. Next hearing, 4th of August.
4th August. Thank you. Excuse me.
Next hearing.
Thank you, brother Shahid.
How long will they keep saying bail denied.
Someday they will have to say 'not guilty'.
Have you tried the 'Biryani' here?
No
It's very good
Really? then I will have to try it
Do you want to try it? - Now?
Not now - We can go for dinner today, tomorrow, whenever you want
Tomorrow?
Tomorrow? - Yes.
Not today?
No, I'm busy today
I know you are very busy
Now that I've won the case because of you
I've got a lot to do!
Without you I would've been visiting one lawyer's office to another.
Oh! One minute
It's just a small token.
I will pay you the rest after selling my property.
I can't take this, please take it back
But this is for you I will take it when I need it
This is just a part payment - That's why I am not taking it!
I will take it when I need it
Ok
I'll call you back in a bit.
Maryam, I want to marry you
What?
I want to marry you
I really like you.
I know it's not the right place to propose but...
You do know that I am a divorcee
And that I have a child
Yeah, I know. So?
So?
Maryam, I want to marry you
Excuse me. Bill please.
What happened?
Your fees..
Maryam. Coffee bill.
Maryam.
Kid, look after my bag.
What happened?
Why is everyone awake?
We were waiting for you
If I would have known I would have informed you
Who is that girl?
Which girl?
You don't know?
Brother, we know everything
Who is she?
There is no one
The same girl with you on the beach
Khalid told us.
Speak up. Who is she?
Maryam
Your success has gone to your head
Why do you go to her house?
Let me ask, who is she?
Why do you go?
Say.
She is my wife
I told you that he is having a scene!
Stop talking like a ruffian
Why are we hearing this from others?
Why didn't you tell us?
Do we mean nothing to you?
I was about to tell you
But then I was scared..
..then she wanted to leave so...
It's ok mother, a bride will only help you
She is a nice girl
Are you happy?
If you keep glaring at me what can I say?
Yes.
I want to meet her
Maryam
So early? All ok? No work?
I won't care even if I have to die, if I am allowed to be your love slave
Get ready, quick.
Wear this. - Mother wants to meet you.
Mother.
You told her?
Yes
Now go quickly get dressed
Shahid.
What's this?
What?
Burqa?
Yes
You want me to wear it?
Have you ever seen me wearing a burqa?
Just for today
Did you ask me? - Just for today please
Please.
Am I not looking good?
You look beautiful
Please, go.
Did you tell them about Sameer?
I will
I just told them about you
After some time I'll tell them about Sameer.
Give me some time.
But right now we don't have time. Stop arguing with me
I am going to make you wear this
Tariq, Arif and the informer - Khalid
He smokes a lot
I quit a long time back
Weren't you smoking the other day?
Tariq, wasn't he with Rahul that day?
No, that wasn't me - Mother
He got the most beating when he was a kid.
Mother, this is Maryam
Greetings.
How are you?
I am good
Please sit
I have asked Khalid to look for a bigger house
Not necessary
He will stay with me
I was also thinking about this...
It's up to you, son
I did not decide your marriage
How can I decide where you will live?
I'll get some tea
I'll get it. Sit.
Arif, I have to get somewhere
It's ready - We will get late
If you have to leave then go ahead
Ok, mother, I'll leave.
I'll drop her on the way
Ok.
Why did you have to say it today?
You were meeting her for the first time
I don't want any compromise with my son
What kind of compromise?
He won't get a decent upbringing in that home..
..neither will he be able to concentrate on his studies.
Look at me! Even I cannot live like this.
Even we grew up and studied in that home.
Maryam.
We will take another house
But in the same colony
Will that do?
Okay.
Maryam.
Let's go out for dinner today?
Yes, of course. Let's celebrate.
Let's do something
Will you come along?
Come on.
I'll just finish my tea and come.
I have just filed a petition for it
We must get this lake cleaned up
This has to be done.
What happened?
Are you angry with me?
What do I say?
Your life is settled now that you are married
And as usual I'll look after the family
Shahid, I'm really tired
You asked me to think about my life, didn't you?
When should I think about myself?
It's not like that.
Then how is it? How?
Don't worry, it's not a problem..
And if you have any problems, come to me
I will help you.
Brother Arif.
Prosecution.
Your honor, prosecution maintains that Zaheer Shaikh...
..should remain behind bars
Defense wants us to see his face, the face of his new born
Yes, we should
But let's not forget the faces of the blast victims..
..and their family members too..
Your honor...
This case is going on under the State Terrorism Act..
..he is a prime suspect and this is not a small matter
This is a question of National Security...
..this man should remain behind bars.
We should give our agencies more time for investigation
Zaheer Shaikh can be a very dangerous man.
That's all. Thanks.
Defense.
Zaheer has been in jail for the last 2.5 years
His bail plea has been rejected over 10 times
The police have been unable..
..to get any substantial evidence against him in this period.
Prosecution always mentions about ongoing investigations..
..without proving anything Zaheer has been labeled a terrorist.
Not only by them, but the world too..
..without any concrete proof
He is Zaheer's father.
He lost his job of 30 years in a minute
Why?
Because, police arrested his son for being a suspected terrorist
Is prosecution of the opinion that Islam and liberalism can't be one?
Or is Zaheer punished because his name is Zaheer?
Not Matthew, Donald, Suresh or More.
Is he still in jail just because of his name?
If the investigation drags along for 10 years..
..will Zaheer languish like this for 10 years?
After 10 years even if he is acquitted what will he do?
Who will give him a job?
He will be known as a terrorist for the rest of his life.
Prosecution says he is a dangerous man.
Why is he dangerous?
What has he done?
Because he made a wrong choice in giving his laptop to a friend?
Many innocents have lost their lives in the blasts...
I sympathize with them completely
But then you can't penalize an innocent man for that.
I request the court to deliver its verdict today
It's already been delayed a lot.
Prosecution has no valid reason to detain Zaheer any more
For the last 2.5 years Zaheer has been in jail because of this act
The court admits that the common man at times..
..faces great hardship because of it
But Defence...
This act is very important..
..for the safety of this country
Prosecution has not provided the court with any concrete evidence..
..which proves that Zaheer Shaikh is guilty
Therefore, this court in State Vs. Zaheer Shaikh..
..gives Zaheer Sheikh an honorable discharge, not guilty
Journalists will be outside just give simple answers
How do you feel?
I'm still dazed
Despite being innocent you were in jail for so many months.
Your thoughts?
No.
Do you want the state to apologize to you?
Apology sounds good. But here it won't work
Why?
When you haven't seen your only child since he was born
What is the point of an apology?
Mr. Shahid, your comments?
Terrorism is a reality that the whole world is facing right now
I am dead against it.
But then you can't put an innocent man behind bars..
..just because he has no means to defend himself
I am not saying that, all those arrested by the police are innocent
What about those...
..who lose precious years of their lives imprisoned for no reason.
I am against that.
Are you going to file a defamatory case?
Where were all of you till today?
I don't want to do anything - No more questions please...thanks
Brother Shahid.
He wanted to thank you.
Come inside. Please come inside.
Have some tea.
I already did
Have some more.
(Voice on News Channels) The blast took place..
at the most important landmark of Mumbai..
..Gateway of India
Seven blasts in seven locations...
I am so sorry.
Is Sameer asleep?
So sorry, got held up
(Voice on News Channels) 26/11 Attacks on Mumbai Landmarks..
Mumbai will not be the same city it used to be.
There are more than 100 deaths reported.
That female American officer
She felt me up all night
While my hands were tied
She showed me pornography
And then..
..touched her menstrual blood...
My God will never forgive me
They won't let me out of here
Hello.
Do you think you're Gandhi?
Jihaadi's Gandhi.
Who is this?
You fight for Jihaadis, asshole.
Obviously, only a terrorist can empathize with another.
Bloody traitor.
You're very patriotic?
You want to kill me?
You'll die on the streets like a dog, motherfucker.
Go ahead kill me.
I won't become a traitor because you say so
I know what you did in Kashmir.
I know it all. I know what you did in jail too.
People should know too.
Do what you have to and so will I.
You can threaten me as much as you like
You will die like a dog, motherfucker.
Kill me
Police has found some kind of a map..
..from the terrorist's dead body.
And they started hunting for the accused in different jails..
..and caught Faheem Khan.
His only fault was when he was arrested..
..he also had a map.
Why will Zaheer make a map for the terrorist?
Why will he make such a mistake?
Especially when he is in jail?
They should at least think before arresting someone.
It's an open and shut case.
It looks a little precarious.
You're confident and sure of it?
Of course I am. Otherwise I wouldn't have asked you.
If we don't defend him they will hang an innocent man.
And what about the phone calls you were getting...
..did you find out who's behind them?
No, I don't know. - Didn't the police help?
No, I've stopped thinking about it.
I'm really concerned about your well being.
Take care of yourself.
I'm fine. I'll be okay.
Public Prosecutor.
Faheem Khan is accused of providing maps to terrorists...
..for the target locations of the 26/11 attacks on Mumbai
That attack had a devastating impact on all of us
Not just public places, the common man feels unsafe at home too
Our laws deem death penalty as the most severe punishment
But my request to the court today is that..
..Faheem and his ilk are awarded a penalty..
..that is even more severe than death..
..so that nobody ever dares to commit such a heinous crime again.
That's all your honor.
Defense.
These terror attacks have claimed many innocent lives
Many people have lost their near and dear ones
This is very tragic
All of us watched these disturbing images on TV for over 3 days
These images will remain forever etched in our conscience
The total death toll in this attack is 164
164 innocent people lost their lives
And if what the prosecution wants..
..without any corroborative evidence
If that happens...
Then this toll will rise to 165..
..and the 165th innocent man will be Faheem Khan.
Why does it always happen that anything of this magnitude..
..attracts imprisonment for an ordinary man.
And the case lingers on..
..while the real culprits might be celebrating somewhere far away..
..drinking in AC rooms and planning future attacks
Why can't the Police ever reach them?
Why do they almost always never end up standing here?
Why do we always see a helpless man standing here
One who does not have the ability to fight back
Prosecution does not have any evidence to prove that Faheem is guilty
But we have strong reasons to believe..
..that forget death penalty or anything more severe
He should not be here at all
Thank you.
Please tell the court your name
Swapnil Mazgaonkar
What do you do?
I run a computer institute in Jogeshwari
In Jogeshwari? - Yes.
Do you know this man?
Yes, he studied at my institute
What name do you know him by?
Sahil Pavaskar
When does a person need to change his identity?
When he is depressed or is running from his past - I object.
But in this case..
She is raking up his past.
This case is about 26/11. Not about my client's past.
Sir every case is about someone's past.
Sir, defense is just trying to obstruct me.
This point is baseless.
Defense, objection over-ruled.
Thank you, sir.
In 2007 Faheem Khan came to Mumbai..
..to survey terrorist target locations
He first made a fake passport
Took admission in a computer institute..
And then rented an apartment in Lamington road
My client has been living in the apartment for the last two years
If someone moves to Mumbai he will have to live somewhere
Your honour, all the rental documents..
..have been submitted to the court.
Prosecution was living on rent till 2 years ago. Is she also a terrorist?
Where I live is not the point!
Don't be personal. Come to the point.
It's a case of creation of perfect alibi.
That's my point. Thank you.
What is your name?
Swapnil Mazgaonkar
And your institute is in Jogeshwari?
Yes
How many students in your institute?
175.
175? Exact?
Exact - Very nice.
So you must know all students well?
Yes - You must know them by their names
Yes - Excellent
Can you tell me the name of the boy in the blue shirt?
What is the point of this silly game?
As someone who studied in his institute
If he can recognize my client
Why can't he recognize other faces?
Your honor, it's a very important point.
Tell me, what's his name?
Go on tell me if you know - This way, it's difficult
You know his name? Yes or no?
Just simply say 'no' if you don't know
Sir, he's forcing him..
I am just asking him.
Yes or no? No.
No. Okay no. Thank you your honor.
What is the minimum qualification for your institute?
12th grade pass
12th.
You collect the marksheet for students?
Yes. - They must be in your records?
Yes - So, what did you say his name was again?
Sahil Pavaskar
Then you should.. You should have it in your records, right?
Say it. Aloud
I do - You do?
I do
Do you have written exams in your institute?
Your students must use paper for the exams
What's this got to do with the use of paper?
The court's time is being wasted
All institutions use paper for examinations
Maybe the prosecution isn't aware that technology isn't aware
Examinations can be conducted on the internet too.
Our country still uses paper extensively.
The prosecution's entire case is dependent on handwriting.
I suggest we have the handwriting analyzed by forensic experts.
Because their entire case is dependent on handwriting.
Mr. Mazgaonkar - Yes, sir?
Do you have the important documents the defense needs?
Yes.
Deposit them in court
Thank you, your honor.
Were there any phone calls? - No.
Come, Mitali - My name is Parangama
Yes
Why do you only fight cases for terrorists?
This is your question?
Isn't it true then?
No. Absolutely not
Then what is the truth?
Mitali, do you really believe that the police...
Sir, my name is Parangama
Yes, Parangama
Do you honestly believe that the police are always right?
In that case we wouldn't need the judicial system?
The police would arrest you and that's that.
I don't expect you to know the truth,
but atleast the pursuit has to be for the truth
..or are you also like the others,
who do not care for the common man.
But you are not a common man.
Why do you say that? I even fight cases for the common man
The ones who can't afford lawyer's fees
Those who don't have the means to afford a fair trial.
I fight for them
Not the terrorists
Does that mean you do it to stay in the limelight?
This is your second question?
Sir...
This is actually my 4th question
Show me...
Please have some tea
Sorry. This interview is over
Actually, these questions were written by my senior
Then tell your senior to try and find the truth
Tell her to go beyond the questions and try to find some answers too
I know, sir, but still...
Why did you decide to become a lawyer?
How are you my child?
I'm good.
Are you fine?
How is your mother?
She's good
Good.
She got second rank in her class.
Tell your father
I stood 2nd
Well done my child
Don't trouble your mother. Ok?
Be good okay.
Your father will be with you soon
Do you know Nooruddin?
Yes
They are calling him as a witness
We never got along in Dubai
Mr. Nooruddin, how long have you known him?
He was with me in Dubai
What did you do in Dubai?
I was a driver. He was a mechanic
Did you ever feel that he was connected with terrorists?
He met strange people, that I know
They would talk for hours
What does he mean by strange?
I am not being allowed to question the witness
I want the witness to define "strange"
He is obstructing my questioning
Thank you your honor.
Strange means that they were hard to understand
Their facial expressions were weird
Did you know them?
No. I did not even understand the language
But they used to talk strange and in Arabic
I only understood Hindi
When did you see him last?
In Nepal
Why had you gone there?
I had gone on a vacation with my wife and children
Where did you see him first?
I was near my hotel and he passed me by
He looked at me and ignored me as if I was a stranger
He ignored you in Nepal, why?
I don't know, ask him. Please tell her why you ignored me
What happened after that?
After three four days he came to my hotel in panic
I ordered food. His phone rang
His phone kept ringing incessantly
He was carrying papers..
..which slipped out of his hand and fell on the floor
Did you see those papers? - Yes, I did
What was in them?
Green, blue, white papers maps. A lot of stuff - Maps, too?
Yes - Like this?
Yes
Police claims, that you did see him handing over maps to terrorists
Yes, I had seen him. He used to move around with a bundle of maps
Where did you see him?
In Nepal
These are the same maps used by terrorists..
..to orchestrate the biggest terror attack in Mumbai.
That's all your honor.
Thank you. Your witness.
Thank you.
The map looked like this?
A little bigger
A little bigger?
Like this?
Yes
These maps are available on Google
Why would any organization rely on a handmade map..
..when a more accurate map is available on internet?
We don't know if a terrorist organization can stage an attack..
..of such a magnitude with maps provided on internet or not..
..but it looks like Mr. Shahid is an authority on this.
What are you trying to say?
You have spent a lot of time with terrorist organizations, haven't you?
Are you accusing me? - No, I am not.
Are you accusing me? - I'm just stating certain facts.
Am I on trial? You're not on trial.
Am I on trial? Who's on trial. - I'm just stating certain facts.
Am I on trail or Faheem Khan's on trial.
I can sue her for this but I won't.
Shahid sir. Your honor, she's accusing me.
She's accusing me. I can sue her, but I won't.
What are you implying?
Am I on trial?
Even in Jail you had links with the terrorists inside..
Because this case is about Faheem Khan. Not me!
You have spent a lot of time in jail
You also had links with the terrorists inside
Nothing was proven.
So, are you inferring that you have to be a terrorist if you are in jail?
I didn't say that - This way even King Shivaji..
..and Bhagat Singh can be labeled terrorists
So, now you are comparing yourself..
..with King Shivaji and Bhagat Singh
No, I'm not comparing..
All I am saying is that she's accusing me your honor.
Prosecution, please sit down
I can sue her for this, I won't.
Is she saying I am a terrorist? What are you saying?
I've some questions your honor.
Yeah, please.
Water?
Mr. Nooruddin, did you go to Nepal on your own expense?
No, my friend Balwant Thakur paid for the trip
So, your friend Balwant Thakur paid for the trip - Yes
How did you go to Nepal? Flight? Train? How?
We took a taxi to the station, then a train.
And from the station on a taxi to the hotel
What was the name of the train?
I don't know, I travel to so many places that I don't remember
He does not know the name of the train.
No problem. Which month did you go there?
February, 14th February - When did you return?
No problem, if you don't remember
What is the currency of Nepal? Surely you shopped there?
My wife handles money
You did not spend any money?
Where did you stay? - Hotel
How was it? - Good
Food was good? Did you get good service?
What was the name of the hotel?
The name of the hotel. Nepal's currency. Name of train.
What is the point of asking all this?
Can I come to the point?
Public prosecutor, please take a seat
Thank you.
Nooruddin does not know which train he travelled in..
..when he returned, what is the currency of Nepal..
..or which hotel he stayed in.
But he definitely knows that..
..the papers he saw on the hotel floor was a map..
..and that map was for targets in Mumbai
Your honor, all I am saying is... we can't trust the witness, he's lying.
Thank you.
You should pay heed to your friends, Shahid
You can't just take off in the court?
What happened?
You don't care right?
Let me call your wife there is no other way you will listen
Please don't
Why shouldn't I when you say you don't care?
Are you crazy? she is already upset
Come here you son of a bitch..
You dare speak ill about our leaders?
Keep your hands off me
Keep my hands off? You dare to speak about King Shivaji?
Do it. Do it.
Are you alright?
I'm coming.
Yes?
Who is it? - Where is that Shahid?
He does not live here
I told you he does not live here anymore
Where does he stay?
I don't know. Don't have his address
Who are you?
I will tell him myself
Let me make a call
No calls...
I will call him myself
Go and do your work
Go on and do your work
Shahid does not live here anymore
Then where does he live? - Why are you going inside?
Please tell me your name. I will tell him - By when will he come?
I don't know sometimes he comes, sometimes he doesn't.
Please tell me your name and I will tell him
Where is he staying now?
I don't have the address
Ok
I will come back
Let's go
They are asking me to back off from the case
Someone came to the house yesterday, looking for me.
No, I won't get Police protection. I know for sure
Is the food ready?
Who came to your mother's house?
Nobody
Why are you scared then?
I'm not scared
Do you think I'm a fool?
Who does not understand anything?
You look rattled
You are not even going to the office
What has happened?
Will you say something?
Threat calls again
You received calls the day before too. Right?
Did you call the police?
I've asked Ram to draft a letter
But I know it will result in nothing
Don't worry though. Let's eat
I want you to drop the case
Drop this case
I can't! You know that
And why should I?
I don't know how or why
You have to decide, that's it.
Maryam.
What should I decide?
I am telling you for the last time you have to drop this case
I am not going to drop out. That's it
Now we are not going to talk about it
You'll get us killed Shahid.
Are you mad?
One second
Do you think I'm not concerned about you
Will I get you killed? What kind of bullshit is this?
This is our life. Not some joke
I'm not used to living like this and i won't
I don't have any patience left for this
What about the people that I am fighting for?
Where will they go?
To police? Or where?
They depend on me
Yes, they have nobody..
..and we have the whole world at our feet?
Your family means nothing to you
Sameer and I have no place in your life?
You've lost your mind
You are overreacting
Listen to me...
Don't touch me.
You said..
You said that I should not back down
Didn't you say that?
In the restaurant many years ago do you remember you said that?
I did - And now?
We were not married then
Don't try to play God
First you decide what do I do?
Maryam,
I'm sorry.
Let's eat
He's been sick for a week. Do you know?
Did you take him to the doctor?
Why didn't you?
Why did you not take him to the doctor?
Let's go to the doctor
Maryam.
What are you doing?
Have you gone completely mad?
Put everything back inside
What are you doing?
Shahid. - What are you doing?
I will sort everything out. I promise
What will you sort out?
You can sort out nothing
I love you
I did not give him medicines, did not take him to the doctor
What were you doing?
I did not know. I am sorry
Don't touch me
Shahid.
Don't touch me.
Please don't do this.
Please.
Prosecution has provided the court with two important pieces of evidence
These are the trousers of the slain terrorist
Prosecution! Good morning
Can you tell the color of these trousers?
Can you tell?
No?
The original color of the trouser is dark green
But now you can see.
It's completely soaked in blood
And your honor.
This map which according to the prosecution ...
..Faheem Khan had given to the terrorists
Absolutely clean.
Not even a single drop of blood.
Very nicely creased.
The map remained in the trousers for three days..
..then how can this be without any blood stains?
How is it possible?
It's very simple
This map has been planted
Objection. Defense is trying to over-simplify the case, sir.
The case is simple, your honor. It's common sense.
Prosecution's case lacks any logic
Prosecutor.
Defense has a valid point.
Please sit down. Thank you, your honor.
Who is the reporter?
Which page?
One second.
Yes, got it.
I'll call you after reading it.
Bye.
An article is published in the newspaper, on me.
Reformed Radical.
I mean, I was never a terrorist or a radical.
Why do they write all this bullshit about me?
And how can they reform me?
What do you want, Shahid?
Why can't they leave me alone?
They will force you like this, to live in your past.
It's up to you.
You have to start off with a new beginning every day.
Move ahead and just live for a bright future.
You sound so sensible when you are far away.
I was quite sensible, even before.
You hate me, right?
I don't want to live a complicated life, Shahid.
I'm coming to bring you back soon.
No.
I don't want you to come.
Please, Maryam.
I need you.
Everybody against me. Please.
Hello.
All I'm saying is that you need to come at 8 and eat..
..and then get enough rest
Hello
Ask them to come in the morning
Ok! I'll be there. Wait
I'll be back in two minutes - First eat
Get the bread ready. I will be back by then
The meal's ready.
Come in
What was so urgent?
Inder, get some water
You could have come in the morning?
Shahid?
Shahid!
By showing me injustice, God taught me about justice
By inflicting pain suffering, He gave me the courage to fight
He taught me to help the helpless
A criminal knows no religion
Eventually both the killer and his victim are human
Your honor.
My summation is the same as my friend..
..Late Advocate Shahid Azmi
Your honor.
Prosecution has provided no credible evidence so far..
..which can prove beyond doubt that Faheem Khan is guilty
On the contrary...
..most of the evidence presented..
..reiterates Faheem Khan's innocence
When police arrests a common man in a terrorism case
Whether he is guilty or not.
The world already makes It's own judgment..
..for the rest of his life he is maligned...
Your honor.
Once again our Judiciary has been burdened with the responsibility..
..to correct a grave mistake committed by police and society..
..and to save an innocent man from getting wrongly persecuted
Justice is also due to the man..
..who always defended the defenseless..
..and lost his life, fighting for the cause.
That's all your honor. Thank you.
"Without any care, the colour has started to drain away"
"I feel detached and dismayed"
"I can't express my condition"
"I'll get sacrificed surely"
"Life seems to have gotten angry with me"
"My heart-beats are now like smoke"
"I don't see ..."
"...any solution..."
"...nor do I see a direction,
"...to head towards my destination."
"Love has slipped away"
"There isn't any care remaining"
"My heart just remains a assembly of thoughts"
"No whereabouts... About the destination or direction."
"I've reduced to ashes."
"Without any care, the colour has started to drain away"
"I feel detached and dismayed"
"I can't express my condition"
"I'll get sacrificed surely"
"Life seems to have gotten angry with me"
"My heart-beats are now like smoke"
"I don't see ..."
"...any solution..."
"...nor do I see a direction,
"...to head towards my destination."