DDRTorrents.com
Subtitle prepared by CDRiPD Team.
Shamitabh, Shamitabh, Shamitabh, Shamitabh, !
A new commer has taken bollywood by suprise.
Javed sir please, Javed sir
Its the begining of the strom
Such a stom that comes once or twice every
30-40years.
But when it comes, it changes the direction of
the wind.
In opening weekend itself it make Rs 61 crore alone.
A new superstar has born in bollywood.
Leave 6 packs, he doesn't have a 1 pack body. No height,
and ordinary to look at.
What has he got to make him the hottest thing today?
See, your question itself has the answer.
If he had everything, then what difference would it be.
Ekta madam, You are a
All I know is this industry has benifited from
Shamitab!
Few days back, know one knew him his name
Today, everyone has only one word to say,
Mr Sunil
Shamitab Rocks!
Mr Boney, Mr Boney!
When seeing the 1st scene of the movie, i told my wife,
This boy will set the stage on fire.
What a voice! What intensity!
Namaskar! I am Shamitabh speaking.
You are all welcomed here.
You all have been searching for me, and I have been
waiting for all here.
Its seems this time my voiceis trying to create problems.
Hi! Hello! & Namaskar! Wishing a good day.
Thanking you for liking Lifebouy so much.
An artist is just a medium. A directors thought,
and a writers word, to be put across to the public.
Generally, Directors dont go to gym, writer doesnt
shave. And a camera doesn't like it.
Thanks
Or else an artist like me, would never get
any work.
Ladies and gentlemens. The creater of Lifebouy.
Namaskar!
If you had wanted, you could have got any big star,
then why bring in a new face?
Every big star, at 1st is a new face.
One more question sir. Shamitabh sir. Shamitabh sir.
Sir, Sir!
Have you got your news?
What news sir?
That within 3 days of the release. The queen of England has
presnted me a Knighthood.
What!
Sir Anthony Hoppkins, Sir Richard Attenborough,
Sir Elton John.
We call them sir. I am far away from getting Knighthood.
Then why are you all calling me Sir?
Sir
Sir one question... Yes
Sir... Sorry... You had been kept away from the promotion
of the film. Why?
My director and producers say. The thing that comes free
is not valued.
Spending money and watching on screen.
The fun is all diffrent in it..
Sir, Sir!
Mumbai is the capital of film industry, and of
Maharashtra also.
Then why did it take a Marathi person so
much time to become a superstar... May I.
Go as the film industry. Why were the so late
in searching me?
Go ask the world, why were the late in listening to my voice?
Go ask my dreams, why it so long to become a
reality?
After that... After than
So children tell me, who this is?
Mohandas Karamchand Gandhi.
Who is Gandhi ji? Father of the nation.
Yes.
What did we get because of him?
Our Independence.
Danish... What are you doing?
If you cant speak, that doesnt mean you would
be left alone. Write on board and convey. Get up.
No one will give the answer.
Who was Gandhi ji's wife?
Kasturba Gandhi... No answers please!
Rohini Hatangadi
Not coming to school. Watching movies day night
Got no father, and cant speak, out of pitty
got you admitted to the school.
Thought, atleast you will learn something by atleast listening.
What will become by watching movies? Hero?
Really... You will become a hero?
Then show your Herism.
You didn't learn anything from the teacher.
Lets see what you learned from movies.
What?... The age of silent movies is past now.
Whats the scene?
Look at him. Hero asking for the script.
Ok, your mother is dead. Do action.
What.. What is he saying?
You have killed my mother... Sir.
Sir... You have killed my mother.
Is he mad? What is he saying?
Go back, I am asking you to stop.
I am telling you to stop.
Hey, hey, leave him, leave him...
Leave him
Sir. I won't let you live.
How will you become a hero?
Hey, you can shake the whole world without saying.
But which heroine will work with a
hero of you size.. Tell Me?
Nothing has happend to me. I will keep coming
here, and you keep giving me medicines.
Why?.. Because, if I don't act as if I am sick. He
will run away to  Mumbai. To become an actor.
This time I have to really give you medicines.
You are getting really sick.
You need to take rest, how many more days
will you work
If stop working, then he will take responsibility.
Then his dream to go Mumbai will be dashed.
No.. No.
Catch him.
One questions sir... Shamitabh... Shamitabh
You are from a small city, and your story is classic.
Rags to riches.
From, one roti a meal, to almost a no roti diet.
No their is no such story. As soon as came to Mumbai
I checked into a 5 star hotel. Hotel's name is MH 04 7789
What is it?.. Come to see the shooting?
What are you doing at the film city.
Raj Kumar Hirani, Sajay Leela Bansali...
Ok.
You have come here to become a Actor?
Meet Rohit Shetty... Meet Karan Johar..
But you are not allowed to meet them here. Got it.
Go meet them at their house... Hold it.
Go... Go away... Go away brother.
Deepak... Yes Sir... Whatis this?..
I think suitcase could be a prop
Move it. Also put my bag in the car.
Pack up.
You are not from film celebrity family. And have
no connections. Then how did you get the role?
A person whose fate is 5.2 inchs, and 51kgs.
What more connections does he need?
What were you doing in the vanity?
Whom did you ask and go?
How did you go in? Can you speak or not?
Lets take to production... Call security... How did
you come here?
Hand him over to studio people.
Hey, bro.. bro.. bro.. 1min, 1min..
What happend?
He went into the vanity... Hello! How are you?
What were you doing in the vanity van?
What are you looking at... Beat him up.
1 min.. 1 min.. What?
What? He is dumb!
You want to become an actor?...
Mad.
Here.
Do you know anyone here?
Villan shot at a very young girl, you saw.
Then ran away and reach police station.. Thats it.
Thats the scene.
Hey, Hello! Come here
All good.. What happend? Camera?
Ok. Ready?
Action.
Where is the sound?... Sir..
We can do voice dub.
So much intensity on his face.
Akshara... I am making a film, and not running
a NGO. How will we shoot with him?
How will the other actors perform with him?
What will they hear? What cue they would pick up?
How ill they react? We have no time for all this.
Sorry... Sir.
No.. It didn't happen.
What can I do ya? I am just an AD... Assistant.
Not a director.
Ok... Lets go.. When I make my film.
Then for sure you are my hero.
Lets go.. Lets go.. I can't do anything friend.
Hey, dont cry... Please... Get up.. Please.
He said no
What can I do? I can't do anything. Calm down.
Calm Down......
Hey, lets go! Please!... Oh Shit!
Enough! Enough!
Hello! Yes.. Hello Dad.
I am just bringing some one to the hospital.
He is ok.
He can't speak, and wants to be a hero!
What will happen to our country withot Cinema?
Where did he come from?.. I don't know Dad..
Anyways.
Igatpuri to Mumabi.
Sir.. Sir.. You are very talened, but have you ever
in your dreams thought you get such sucess.
I had gone with talent, I would have kept dreaming till now.
I had more belif in the thing i want, than talent.
All I wanted was to become an Actor.
When we start wanting more, Then you get it on day.
Hey Pandey! Whats up?... Hey Kumar what are you
doing in Finland for so many days?
I thought I will added a conference for one day.
Then escape on some Scandanavian cruise.
But for the 1st time in 30yrs. But the medical conclave
was so interesting, that I couldn't move.
And interesting.. Listen I heard something absolutely
mindblowing
I am about to visit thier research center......
Gone back home? I wish I could help him.
You may be able help him.
Hey, sisters where has he gone?
He's gone.
Hero.. You wouldn't have a passport?
You also turn in 48 frames.
You were born to be a hero man..
Welcome.. Dr Kumar.
This is worlds most advanced voice research center..
Good morning!
Technolgy can help speech impaired people.
Now you will see that.. This way.
Clearly his vocal cords are totally paralysed.
Its a simple procedure
One micro voice processor, will be implanted around your neck.
Below your moth.
In the begining, you may feel unconfortable.
Then it will be fine.
What's your name?
Danish... Danish.
What I have is something like a mobile phone blutooth device.
Where ever you are in 400 metre radius, even if its
sound proof, or mobile proof area.
People talking to you, and all sound from around
you, can be heard by me.
And whatever I say, you can hear if from
me clear without any outside disturbances.
And the same sound would be received by the voice
processor implanted in you.
And that voice processor has got a motion sensor.
When you move your lips. Motion sensor will detect it.
And that voice, that your voice processor has received
will come out of your mouth, through...
a high fidelity speaker... and very clear.
Today I can give you a live voice.
Chill.. By listening to voice.. syncing lip
movment is an art.
Chill.. With voice, syncing lips is an art.
If dont want to speak, while listening to voice,
dont open your mouth. Just shut up.
And, if you dont speak for some time, the voice
stored in your processor is automatically erased.
Now all you need is a good voice. Someone with whom you
can work out a good understanding.
My friend hero.. You got Talent.. Technology..
Tantrum.. But who has got your voice, my friend.
I have. I have a bottle.. a glass.. Water.. Thirst
Sancks.. Chicken..
But who has my liquor, my friend?
People have become fan of your voice.
Do you feel your voice was reason of your success?
No.. No..
I look good. Why?
My face should give you a inferiority complex.
You people from media can make a person feel
his hatred between his face and voice.
We have spoken a lot now.. Its time to party.
My throat has gone dry.
Hey, hello. I am going to urinate, so don't open your mouth.
Or you will change the meaning of no. 1
in bollywood.
Who is got my liquor, my friend?
Can we talk to you for 2 minutes?
Get some tea at my table.
Both you boys want to drink tea?
3 tea please... Ok
Do you bury dead bodies here?
No, I don't have licence for it.
There... Is my landlord... Who makes a person
from land to reach his lord.
I am his paying guest.
In Mumbai, where do you get a house for Rs. 500
a month, with such big garden?
Don't you get scared here?
Where people die, people get scared.
No dies in a cemetery.
Scared and dead come here.
You shoudbe scared outside.. outside.
Can we not sit some where else?
Why what is the problem sitting here?
Oh nothing, but its someones grave.
Are you dumb?
What is this?
What?
The thing we are going to tell you,
it is .
So before yo listen, you have to sign the agreement
that you are.. 1 minute.. 1 minute.
You want to talk to me... Yes... And to listen to
you talking I have to sign an agreement!... Yes
Did you understant anything?
Ok I dont want listen to anything.. No Listen..
No sign..
What the hell are you doing!
Wants to become an Actor.. If he becomes a
superstar, this is for safety.
Your vocie from his mooth sonds good?
This voice will sound good, even from a dogs mouth.
Sign over.. Now say..
The thing you have in your ears, is in his ears too.
Who ever talks to him, you can hear.
And when you reply, it will be heard from his voice...
(speaking a dialogue)
What happend?
Technolgy does't like the dialogue from
Mughal-E-Azam
No chance at all.
(Speaking a dialogue)
What happend?
Technolgy does't like the dialogue from
Mughal-E-Azam
No chance at all.
Jahanpanah.. You voice is coming from inside him...
Looks like he has eaten your mobile phone.
So, what is you name?
Amithabh.
Mr Amitabh Sinha... So Mr Amitabh.
Would like to become his voice?
What is your weight?.. 54.
59.
The weight of my voice is more than that.
Thats the beauty, heavy voice on your body is normal.
But it will stand out on his body, and people will
become fan of your voice.
40 years earlier.. I had come to Mumbai to
become a hero... What?
To become a hero.
Studio to studio. Studio to studio.
No only studio, even radio rejected me.
Because of this voice.
For heroes role.. I looked like a villan.
My voice was too soft for a villans role.
Here had is voice, and this voice made me a zero.
And with that voice, and your face you
want to be a hero.
For now he is its a charity case, but whatever he
earns, you will gwt a share of it.
5%
OK. 7%.
10%.. Last final offer.
Ok 15%.. Come on.. Thats...
Don't throw peanuts at me.. Don't throw peanuts at me..
I am watching a movie.. a movie.. Like..
Like the people from the big movie industry.
Because of this voice they threw me out.
And I am making the same big people from the
industry into a CA.
I like it.. I like it..
Akshara.
Sir, what is the story?
Are both tring to make a movie own your own?
No.. No.. This is a test.
We need something to show to the people.
Come here..
What is it?.. A small scene
The name is Lifebouy.. Work is..
Is this a scene or a soap?
Her directors, next films story, the hero beats up the
dirt(corrupted people), to clean up the country.
Yesterday I was taking bath with Lifebouy soap.
I had an Idea. Even so soap helps clean the dirt.
Then why not have a hero with name Lifebouy...
Lifebouy.. A boy who gives the country a new life.
Will beat him.. And walk away in slow motion...
A sound track will play.
(Singing lifebuoy jingle)
Now we have to make such an audtion..
Seeing which our director.
..who wants to cast Hrithik and Ranveer would
delete their numbers from his phone itself!
Can you hear his voice?.. If you were to reduce your
Drinking.. Concentrate.. Then anyone can hear him.
1 minute.. Ahh!
You will have to go a little aback.
Or the voice would sound twice.
Hello.. Hello.. Name is Lifebouy.
Work is to protcect  the country, and increasing its strength.
Hey, now because of your face I will
have to soften my voice?
Hello.. Hello.. Name is Lifebouy.
Work is to protect the country, and increasing its strength.
Hey you.. Have you come to take a stroll in the garden?
Subtitle.. Subtitle.. Now because of your voice,
do I have show only one expression my whole life time?
This can't be done.. He doesn't need a voice,
but needs a different face..
Have I seen you before.. It wont match..
His face and my voice.
Name is Lifebouy. Name is Lifebouy.
Work is to protect the country, and increasing its strength.
Now he is learning some acting.. Or else..
Name is Lifebouy. Work is to protect the country.
(repeats the dialogue)
Jahanpanah.. He's good.. Now days in films..
Actors talk in such casual manner. Isn't it?
No, the before act was also good.
Sir I have shot something, according to your concept.
Just for fun sir... Show me?
Isn't this that dumb guy?.. No sir.. He's a very
big actor. He was testing me by acting dumb.
Is it?
What an actor.
And Lifebouy.
What an Idea.. It your idea itself sir..
No.. No.. What is the interpretation.
Actually bang on title for my film...
I want to meet this..
This Danish... Hi. Hi. Danish..
Hey get the test... Ahh.
Read, Read, take it slow.. Come here..
Is thec amera set up ready?
Yes sir. Its ready.
After sucking out people blood, you health
has worsened.
Now we have to get a role for you as well.
But at 1st we will have to get some closthes for you.
Why? From the time I have seen you in only
one black T shirt.
Yes.. For you a role.. What role?
When the shooting is going on. How would be close by
withouting creating a doubt on others around to give voice over.
Manager.
But manager will have to talk to
other people. If the manager and
star talking in same voice, the
whole film intustry will be shaken.
And who all will be around the star?
Vallet! We call peons, vallet here
Perfect role.. Name.. Think!
Robert?
Stop the car.Stop!
Those big film industry people, for my this voice.
They pushed you and threw you out.
And I made those big people to act up as a CA
by using my voice.
Cant you even do this much?
Whisky.. Black.
Here.
You have money? So pay.
You need to control on yor drinking.
Am I drinking?
- I never drink inside the cemetery.
- But you drink inside your 500 ruppee bunglow.
Well thats outside the are of cemetery.
I respect the dead,not the living.
If whisky drinking is stopped, my liver
will have a heart attack due to shock.
So no whisky, is very risky
Akshara.. I am removing Danish
from this film.
Danish, I have thought about it a lot.
I know Danish, you will be very hurt.
I am sorry.
Its all for the success film.
We have change it.
You .. Will have to change your name.
(Laughing)
What did you think, its only you who knows
acting.
This is not good for our strength
I dont have a problem with all these. But my producers
belive in numerolgy
But, name Danish isn't as strong, as you
voice is.
He is correct.. Amitabh..Power..
Danish.. Is week.
Hey kiddo, We are thinking a name for you,
What do you want?
SHAMITABH...
Yes.. Shamitab!
You only used SH. From your name. Why?
I have come here on  behalf of BMC,
Brihanmumbai Municipal Corporation.
We got information that,4 homeless girls..
Hey what are you doing here. You are in frame. Move!
Oh, sorry madam.
(background soundtrack playing)
I have come here on  behalf of BMC,
Brihanmumbai Municipal Corporation.
We got information that,4 homeless dogs, are bothering
people here.
The number of injection you get after a dog bite.
That many bullets I will inject into you.
Enough, this is thought I am scared of..  In this world
we can kill a human, but not an animal.
Cruelty to animal case would be made, and I
would be put into jail.. So thats why..
We.. Don't kill homeless dogs.
They are caught with
nets, put into van.
Taken to hospital, then sterilised, and left back
on streets.
So that one day, they die in peace.
Then you can die too!
(background soundtrack playing)
I forgot to get dog catching net today!
The peon.
You are great Jahanpanah. End title.
And that Danish.
Introducing Shamitabh
I wonted to make fool out of other people.
But I made a fool of myself.
A peon.
I can feel the sadness in your heart,
Jahanpanah.
Scotch... me..
Water.
Mixing.
How to get high...
Is there such water.
That gives you high without whisky... Is there?
Is there?
And whisky gets you high without water.
Whisky.
Water.
Needs whisky.
Whisky doesn't need anything.
Setting! These people has set the awards!
Because of their reach in industry!
Keep it down.
Aamir Khan does it right, boycott such events.
They are all frauds!
This is all done to increase the TRP, they calls stars
to give out awards. Its all game of money.
Till the time people see such awards show, it willl keep
going on! Bloddy corruption!
If a movie is made on Anna Hazzare. For him too,
they will have to buy an award!
You were the best heroine.
Real.
But.. You won't get any award.
Because real heroes are not given any award.
Bandra's increasing population.
You sacrafized your 1 BHK flat and you
came here to settle undergound.
You are the real hero.
But you want get any award.
No one will understand.
Only a person who makes scarifice, can understood
other person who gave scarifices themselves.
You can hear right?
When people clap for you then... Lord
It can be heard in paradise.
Upstairs.
You are also dumb.
But you understand... you understand... you understand.
Bewani Sir... Its a very good script...
But.
Clint Eastwood.. Has already made this.. Fantastic film.
In the line of fire.
We have the rights for it sir..
Hey u dumba** who gave you rights?
Sir, I am getting the action director of
Mission Impossible.
Why don't you launch yor son in this film?
He looks like a star... Thank you sir.
Actualy in Lifebou, was an action film, but in this
film it should be different.. I want to do romantic.
I want do films, which releases in such festival.
But for this role....
I can decide, what I role I can do!
I can think for myself.And what I think
will happen. Just say what I want!
I can hear my own vocie.
Even I should like the script.
Even I have to do acting.
I am also an artist.
Shamitabh.. I am also Shamitabh.
When are we starting with the film..
Shamitabh.
Finish it before I come back.
I have done lots of here and there.
I have to write now.
You are doing it right.
The world
and your co-superstars.
You like the script, but he doesn't?
If you are finding it hard to keep one star happy.
Then how to convince to stars for just one role.
You want to become super duper star! Then what about others.
They also have teir ambitions!
Even I want to make a film.
Will you do my film?
Ofcourse, you will do.. I hav done
so much favour for you.
You have to atleast live till time you do my film...
After that who cares.
I know we will have to do confidentiality agreement
signed him also.
People look thin blacks.
I have gone a little fat?
Don't look at me like that.
I won't fall for your intoxicated eyes, like
your other others fan do.
You like a monkey.
But I don't even have time enough to continue this
scene, with my eyes closed.
Concentrate on you work, and let me also do so.
I am an Artist!
You should be ashamed.
Your name is also copied from hollywood.
I should rather say inspired.
What fate, what fate I have got.
Couldn't even think of an original name for himself.
How will he make a original film then? Huh?
I am saying it too fast.. I will say it slow.
When..
Because of my audio, that video works.
How can you call it a picture then?
No.. Its something to think about.
Because of my audio, that video works.
How can you call it a picture then?
Mixture.
Call picture, mixture then.
Like bollywood, make furniture out of wood!
Yes this.
What kind of rhyming have you done?
I am going now.
Sir has got his new vanity van.
Its nice ri?ght
Sir, your shot is ready now.
You like the script, you do it..
I am leaving.
Even after me saying no, how did you
dare to say yes for the film?
Without me, what are you?
You said yes by SMS.
Now do the film by sending SMS.
With out my voice you are..
Finished.. Finished.
If I am finished, then your voice is also finished.
I will have to save this shit film for getting flopped.
You should get married to me..
You should get married to me.. Why?
Because your parents don't love you.
But Why?.. What is your name?
Why you don't know.. Geeta.
Oh Geeta, if your parents had loved you.
They wouldn't have kept your name as Geeta.
Why? Whats wrong with name Geeta?
If you love somebody, you will face deep struggle
for his love.
Finding a good name is a struggle.
And your parents didn't struggle.
And gave you a very common name Geeta.
1st name that comes to our mind is Geeta.
1000's have the same name Geeta.
Probably the nursing home you were born was
named Geeta.
What kind of parent have you got Geeta.
So lazy to find a good name for thier own daughter!
I will call with love as 'Ta"
I will marry you Ta,
And go tell your parents, Tata!
Why are you saying thank you?
He is talking about the
dialogue delivery, not
about your facial acting!
Such a big star. He gets the make up done
by me with full trust.
Also drops his servant, by his own car.
But the old chap is mad, He keeps talking to himself.
He keeps saying things.
Please shut the AC.
What is this?
Its an injection... No No, injection
No.. No.. Doctor.
Nothing will happen.
Today he spoke for the 1st time.
No.. No.. I am alright.
I will go home, take bath, and come back for shooting.
No sir, today voice is a bit low.
I can come.. No.. No.. Don't bother..
You take rest.. I will shoot some other scene.
You just rest, don't worry.
See the love for your voice.
I am hungry,  get me something to eat.
This water is too hot, how to cool it?
Oh, burned!
What are you doing?
Jahanpanah, How are you?
Arrrh
I have an idea sir.Once your voice gets clear.
I want be the 1st director to record a song in your voice sir.
Sir, one song in your voice. Sir it will be sensational.
Will do it. Will do anything for you.
Sir. Thank you so much sir.
Arrrh, Arrrh, Why are yo taking too much tension.
At the most people listening to your song,
will throw shoes or slippers at you. Thats it.
You got me the injection!
Akshara? Even I am not able to get through to her
Maybe network problem in
Sikkim, why does she have to
go toSikkim to write script.
I really dont understand.
Singing
Song note is too high I think.
I have forgotten the words of the song.
What.. Why?
You got me an injection!
So now I will sing!
I have rehearsing for over a week, You sent me the CD.
Then whats with this one line and piddly!
Piddly, English words sir.. Meaning short inquisitional things.
Sir, in comparison to love, every thing is piddly.
And now day we need a hook line aswell.
If I do more rehearsal, my voice will get piddly.
(Singing)
In every partnership, one partners talent
Its alway little more than the other partner.
You used a short piddly word, you turned
it to a fantastic idea, sir.
If you really love me, then find me
a toilet.
Why do they call you Robert?
Your name on passport is Amitabh Sinha.
People call me Robert with love.
If peon and star talk in same voice then people
will think of the peon as the star.
Wear and here.
When things end at your age, and things begin at my age.
In your age, for getting things done, you need my help.
At my time, you wouldn't have even started.
You have spoiled my song...
Why did you spoil my song?
Did I beg you to do this song for you?
Did I beg you to do this movie?
You were the beggar, and I am the donator.
To save you, to save your superstar image .
I didn't have any inclining to listen to this song in my voice.
Only this song could have saved your stupid film!
You are so jelaous of my voice, that you
are ready to get the film flopped?
You are the 1st begger, who is
jealous of his donator!
Is bollywood changing from running around trees,
to running around loo's?
What a brilliantoriginal idea.
For years we have been seeing, heroine in chiffon
sarees, running around the snow in Alps.
Nobody would have thought in cold, even her bladder
getting burst!
You are a non-smoker. You are such a huge youth icon.
If you campagin for us, it will make a huge difference.
Why do youth start smoking? Usually for the image.
To show off.
Stylke should be thier, then whats the use
being youthfull.
Lets give them another style..
Meaning?
As a kid have tasted a candy, the one in shape of ciggarate?
Called you to London, for a speech?
Us?
But I will be the one to do the talking.
Giving a speech, taking all the claps meant for me.
How did this place come here again?
How did I reach from there to here again?
You know, you are the real actor.
You will understand.
Sorry my friend.
I forgot get the net?
He escaped.
When yo have a hand,
leg and face..
A Camera, Bike, super banground
music,then anyone can become an actor.
Sorry my friend, I forgot to get the net.
This is acting.
No hand, no leg, no trolley, no bike..
Only voice.
Whisky is love.
And water is everywhere.
This is real acting.. You show it to me..
Come.. Hey come here!
Why are you stuck there?
Come down here.
Do you want me to come and get you down?
What the hell, he thinks he is a VIP.
That I have to get you personally.
Get down you!
I will get this from up there.. Be steady.
Common baby, get down from there.
What happend is done.
It wont happen again.
I am very ashamed of him.
But is my servant
For what ever that happend...
I am asking all you media people.
All citizens of India.. The whole population of London.
The whole world.
I want to say is, I am not a bit ashamed!
What sir? Why such Insults?
Are you in your senses.
(abusing)
For you say A to Z abuses at me, you will need me.
And you are ashamed of me.
How could you dare, be ashamed of me?
Giving me a cheque of 10 million
ruppee, doesn't give you any
right to be ashamed of me. I
dont need a job from you!
Bar closed, you won't get any whisky!
Go drink water!
To speak to media, to tell people,
you will need a voice, you fool.
Where will you get it from? Order online from Amazon?
He is your voice, without him you are nothing.
Swallow your ego, lets go and ask for
forgivness.
My script is ready.
In a movie, its the hero who talks.
There is no melodrama.
Its independence day today.
The cemetery is closed.
Take the body some where else.
Amitabh... Don't touch me.
Hey, listen.
No, Stop.. Stop.
After touching a corpse, you should take bath,
before touching someone.
To lift a corpse, you need a shoulder.
Shoulder.
And when the shoulder feels pity for the corpse,
and has been crarying the cropes away..
And if the corpse thinks of its pyre as a its throne.
And if the corpse thinks he is the king.
And the shoulder its servant.
Treats the servant, as if he ashamed of him.
Then its the responsibility of the shoulder, to bring the corpse down and remind it thats its a corpse.
Without the shoulder, the corpse will decay lying in the street.
And.. even a hungry street dogs would be ashamed
of touching the corpse.
I want to tell the whole world, that I am not
even a bit ashamed.
What does he think of himself?
No my friend, there must be something wrong.
Sir its out of sync, the voice doesnt sync with the lip movment.
There is no technical error. Everything else is in sync.
See.. Something is wrong.
All of sudden, holiday in Finland.
What is he doing in Finland?
You want act a speech impaired person?
How will you talk to the director?
How will you talk to the Writer?
You are going talk for my film?
What will I do?
How will make my film?
Should I forget about it?
No way, why should I make a film
on your idea?
Do you think that, drunkard would return?
After hearning the news about the new film?
Means, I am screwed!
In world of monkeys, is there a shortage of female monkeys?
Is it?
Are your days going so bad?
That you are not able to get any sexy actress?
So why not take a chance on a weak director?
So that she could forget her only dream,
and only see your thousands of dream?
Boy and Girl, both can't speak?
Yes.. Trying.. But thats different and long back..
In movie Burfi.
No. We mudo this. Fantastic it will be.
I want to speak to him now. Sir he doesn't want to speak,
so he is learning sign language.
He wants to feel the quietness within him.
Every actor in the industry should do this.
For heroine role he wants someone, who cant speak in real life.
Fantastic Choice.
We have to do a lot of planning,
Atleast now open your mouth.
Sir, till the time film doesn't end,
he won't speak.
Won't speak till the end?
.. Till the end?
Bet?
For sure..
by the end of the 1st if you dont come up to me
and say I have another idea.
If you don't, then I will stop making films.
I.. Will.. Stop.. Making.. Films.
Jahanpanah, here is hot hot biryani for you.
What happend?
Jahanpanah.
What is this happening?
Without sim card, how is the mobile working?
Keep my table reserved.
Don't give it anyone else.
Where are you going?
If water can grow without whisky.
Then imagine, the high whisky can give without water.
Hey I want make a movie with Shamitabh.
But he is on high with the sucess he has got.
Dad, speak to Rabir
Please get me a sweet lime juice please.. Ok Sir.
What will the poor producer do?
In the whole industry, there are only 4 heros.
Why only counting 4? Dont
you see the big star
their drinking sweet
lime and sitting there.
Love is such a useless thing. For which...
Love is such a useless thing,
even after giving it all your
precious time, in return you dont
even get a second hand watch.
The voice is just like Shamitabh..
But has more power than him.
And this voice on my 6foot 3inch son,
will set him on fire.
Voice is like Shamitabh.
But the bass is stronger.
Such a waste..
I like this script a lot.
Bhiwani sir, stop him.
If he leaves, we are doomed.
Sir please. For me.
Can't you see.. You fool.
Thappad, is name of new film made by famous
producer Mr Keshav Bhiwani.
In which he is launching his own son Armaan.
Sir, please tell about your film?
My film would be a action packed masala film.
Ok..
Launch your son, he look like a star.
Common talk my friend.
What my mom didn't give when I was a Kid.
As a youth what a girl didn't give.
In such films you cant have deadly dance numbers.
It should be released in all theatre.
And It will be awesome movie.
If you slap it before the release,
Then what splaps will be there to see in the movie?
Meaning..
The biggest slap for the movie is the voice of your son.
Why are you hiting it for free?
Save it for the friday in the theatre.
There will be claps, evryday and latter.
Play the song.
We should promote this film with full dignity.
I need a full page article on daily basis.
Watch out for Armaan.
No stupid promotions, Shamitabh wont come
for the cookery show.
Sir, Shamitabh's movie is very hot.
Don't clash with his movie.
No.. December 4,We will relese our film.
Sir, we have heard that you want talk until,
the release of your film by 4th December?
The subject line of the picture is very sensitive...
Talking in sign language?
You people from media can create difference between
a persons voice and face.
The controversial superstar Shamitabh's
new film Ishhhhhhq, is releasing today.
worldwide in 3500 screens.
Todays 2nd release is from famous producer
Keshav Bhimani's film Thappad!
Visit DDRTorrents.com
How did you like Ishhhhhq, the movie?
Its a classy movie, but not like Lifebouy.
How did you like the
movie Thappad!?
Over a dead body, there is a
loud voice.Its a scary movie.
Shamitab is good, but without voice
its not the same Shamitabh.
By coppying Shamitabh's voice, anyone can't
become Shamitabh.
It was a time waste.
It will be soon released on Kindle.
The rise and fall of Shamitabh.
If you want to stop this book.
You will have to write something new.
And ther is only one way for it.
He is also a flop..
The drunkard will be back.
If you call him.
In life, you didn't think of the end?
Don't be so selfish, Take a damm break.
Think about me!
Do something for me atleast!
Madam, Jahanpanahs phone, only has 2 numbers, one is yours
and other is of Shamitabh sir.
For past 3 days, he's been
drinking a lot, Jahanpanah.
Its 1st time I am feeling scared.What
if something happens to him.
I will have to use this very hands.
Is there water?
Before burrying the corpse.
Its given a bath.
Give him a bottle of water.
No water.. Whisky.. Whisky.
Open a whisky
There is no need for water.
He is water, and himself whisky.
So he doesn't like water.
It is his big philosophy.
You fool! Look here.
Look here.. What is this?
43% Alcohol, rest 57% is water!
Whisky is made with water.
Without water there is no whisky
If you were in such ego, you should have read its label atleast.
You should never send a bigger back empty handed.
Go.. Get up..
No...!!
I.. dont need help getting up.
So say.
Speak.. speak.
I forgot.. You fool can't speak.
What?
You fallen now.
Fallen.. before I could.
What were you before me?
Zero.
What? What? Say?
You were a zero before me.
And after also zero.
Only in between, a hero.
Because behind that zero was a hero.. Hero!
What are your age?
97 Years
Both your ages added, you should have 97years
of knowledge in between.
Nor would anyone have knowledge about it like you.
Move it, of I will beat you up.
And burry you here only.
Stop.. Stop.. Where are you going?
Please sir 5 minutes here...
Sit down.
And now kids.
Now will learn the ABCD of life.
If you dont pay attention, you would get a kick from me.
No one can live alone.
If you want to grow, you have to stay together.
You know very well. A person who things he
can get things done and grow on his own.
How far can a person go all alone?
If you don't help each other,
You guys go into hiding.
If you don't act intelligent,
then both would become a joke.
Film also would be in black?
Or would there be any colours?
The title is good.
Stop, where are you going?
Is this Shamitabh's house, I have a meeting
with him.. You need permission.. I have Permission.
I know that.. You.
are my director, and I am yor actor.
I also want to be father of your kids.
You come into the wrong industry.
here in casting couch, actors need to sleep
with directors.
Not director with actors.
What will I get to see?
Your tail?
Visit DDRTorrents.com
What do we do?
What if he says the truth during the film launh?
I want to tell the truth to the world.. What?
Akshara's flim is getting started.
and you want to tell the truth?
very bad idea.
Truth.. Is worlds biggest idea.
If you say the truth. Then people who disclose
the thruth on ur behalf would go quiet.
Yes.. I am dumb.. This my voice.
The technology that brings it together.. And thats done.
What can anyone do after that?
If you the truth. The fear is lost.
By sayin the truth, shock value increases.
Shamitabh is dumb.
Superstar Shamitabh is dumb.
By saying the truth, emotions would flow.
One dumb person.. With his passion.
And left behind is handicap, and reached the heights of success.
And one more advantage on the side.
That more dumb people will make use of this technology.
And Shamitabh being the brand ambassador, will be an advantage.
The biggest advantage of telling the truth.
Tsunami of emotions will fill the theatre.
People will open their eyes, and see Shamitabh's performance.
Every ears would be hearing hero
Shamitabh's dialogue.
And for this dumb guy,people would be play a touching
background music, in teir hearts.
People will whistle and cry at the same time.
Visit DDRTorrents.com
If say the truth, I wont ever be drinking alcohol.
You are going to divorce me.
You so intelligent.
Wearing such ugly T-shirt, for your super star launch.
Full focus would be on yor T-shirt.
I will have to say a interesting history of this T-shirt.
Shirt is your way to get people take attention off me.
I understood.
I wish I was dumb too.
When a normal person grows big in strature,
he only becomes big.
But when a handicp person becomes big in strature.
He becomes a legend.
Even if I say the truth, like everytime.
Its again a advantage for you.
Is it my sister in law's love message for you?
She could have easily come with us,but she wanted to be thier 4 hours before.
to check mike,and see if every thing is in order.
Or else how would these females stay calm.
Thinking the lyrics.
I have not becme Javed Akhatar yet.
It would be hard to get the voice back.
Without my voice you are finished.
If I am finished, then your voice too is finished.
Love is a film.
Passion is a film.
Pain is a film.
Medicine is a film.
A praise is a film.
A Salute to the film.
Visit DDRTorrents.com.
Subtitle prepared by CDRiPD Team.