(Chants)
Move..
Move!
Stop!
'That's Mr. Sharma.'
This wedding cannot take place.
'He too is one of
the fathers in Delhi..'
'..whose daughter's
heart beat for Veer.'
'Like others, Mr. Sharma too is eagerly
waiting for Veer to get married.'
'So that,
he too can find some peace of mind.'
What happened?
Channi eloped with Veerey.
Damn!
You are in your bed..
And not at a wedding hall.
Channi is making parathas
(flatbread) in the kitchen.
Really?
- Tell me something?
- Yeah?
Why are you so worried about Veerey?
Why do you keep cursing him?
He is such a nice boy.
He is a gem of a person, this Veer.
(Traffic)
'Prabhu Arora.'
'A businessman.'
'He has more money than he can count.'
'But he is such a miser that
even his money yearns to be spent.'
I have already added sugar.
You don't need to add more.
- And I have made it so you don't have to..
- Listen..
You don't need to add sugar
when you make it, darling.
Enough of romance.
Your blood sugar level is high.
- Come on, let's eat breakfast.
- Coming.
- Tolaram..
- Yes, ma'am?
- Is the tea ready?
- Yes.
Did you add sugar?
Yes.. no.
No, I didn't.
'He has just one problem, his son..'
'Veer.'
'He keeps giving away
millions as charity..'
'And keeps giving his
father shocks in small doses.'
Listen, Veerey shenanigans
tend to hurt in such a way..
..that you cannot
even complain about them.
What happened?
Tell me..
What did he do?
He spent 270,000 on two dentures.
- 270,000?
- Yes.
- On two dentures?
Did he break someone jaw?
Tell me.
What are you doing?
I asked you something.
It's not so.
Then?
There's Trilok Nagar
behind the Hanuman, right?
Hmm.
There is a juice stall over there, right?
That uncle with moustaches
and his short wife..
The one who speaks like a parrot.
She met Veerey one day.
She was missing a few teeth.
She told him:
"Son, I wish to eat walnuts."
So, your generous soon
took her to City Hospital.
Do you know what she told him?
"We want imported teeth."
So, he got her imported teeth.
135,000 for one.
270,000 for two.
He did a good deed.
Even if only for a few days,
she will at least food that she likes.
Right?
Darling, what will she eat?
She has got a new pair
of teeth worth 270,000.
Now she calls him every day..
"Send over some walnuts.
I wish to eat walnuts."
Now they want him to arrange
for walnuts as well. Amazing.
Listen..
Sorry, my phone.
If you come across any
of his shenanigans, do inform me..
I cannot digest food
until I hear about one.
No matter what you say,
my Veerey is the heart of Delhi.
'You guessed it right. That's
the guy we are talking about, Veer.'
'Problem?
What problem?'
'That's the problem..
He doesn't have any problem.'
(Cell Phone Ringing)
'So, he keeps solve
problems of the world.'
'What?'
'You just saw his mobile phone.
Once you have a look at him..'
Veerey, I've got a tip.
- A few are planning to rob an ATM van.
- When?
11:30 am.
Four men.
They will pass through CP.
'Awesome.'
(Tyres screeching)
Step on it!
Okay.
Faster!
Do you want me to make it fly?
(Motorcycle purring)
Drive faster!
Why don't you drive instead?
(Glass Breaks sound)
Oh no!
(Traffic)
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
(Fighting sounds)
Get down quickly.
Hurry up. Someone will show up.
Take this too.
We need to take all the money.
- Open the bag wide.
- Yes. Take some more.
Give it here.
First, learn how to hold it.
Please forgive us.
Sorry. I am a mistake, sir.
Please forgive me, sir.
My sister is getting married.
I need 100,000, sir.
That's why I agreed
to come with them, sir.
Please save me, sir.
Otherwise, my family will get ruined.
Please, sir.
Please forgive me, sir.
I need 50,000, sir.
My mother is in the hospital, sir.
Please forgive me, sir.
I need 50,000.
I need to gift my wife a gold necklace.
Your wife?
She refuses to give me food.
What's your wife's name?
Diya.
- Huh?
- Diya!
Diya!
Wants to gift a necklace!
- Give me just some, sir.
- Get lost!
Give me just some, sir. I am hungry, sir.
(Gun Locking Sound)
- Give me just some.
- Get lost!
She won't give me any food today either!
He ran away, leaving us alone.
First of all, put all the money back.
If I catch you doing this again..
Then your bones will
be found in this trunk.
Got it?
Yes.
You can take 100,000 out of it.
And you too take 50,000.
How much did you need? 50,000?
50,000 right?
Take 50,000 and leave.
Never do such a thing again.
(Police Siren Sound) Got it?
Pick them up.
Count it!
(Car Stopped Sound)
Count!
Count yours.
(Door closed)
Four, five..
- Jai Hind, sir!
- Jai Hind.
Where's Veer?
Veer handed this over to us and left.
- Does it contain all the money?
- No, sir.
150,000 are missing.
He made government
do a charity of 150,000.
Veerey, you will never change.
- You first.
- What about you?
Papa, please, we want ice cream.
Lajwanti..
Didn't I promise you that
I'd give you a tour of Delhi?
See, I fulfilled my promise.
Rubbish, what tour did you take me?
It's so hot in here.
And you didn't even
give me anything to eat.
Tell me, what would you like to eat?
I will get it right away.
I want to eat ice cream.
- The big one.
- Ice cream?
The big one?
Oh shit.
I don't have any money left.
Here, have some rocket ice cream.
I have others too.
- Here's 4,000.
- 4,000!
- Get me some more.
- I'll get them.
Geet!
Mr. Veer Arora, you just wait there!
I'll teach you a lesson today.
What do you think of yourself?
Will I keep waiting for you all my life?
- Sorry, Geet.
- Don't I have anything else to do?
- I won't be late again.
- You don't respect me at all.
Lord Almighty!
When will you learn
to come on time, Veer?
Papa, please. Papa, please.
I am not going to be your wife.
Otherwise, I'll spend
my whole life waiting for you.
What do you think of yourself?
You've had it from me today!
Lord Hanuman, please save my honor.
Here, eat this!
(Bell Sound)
Got it!
Take this.
Didn't I tell you,
I am well respected over here?
Thank you, Lord Hanuman.
Yum!
You want to eat ice cream?
Here, have some more.
I'll teach you a lesson.
You idiot, donkey!
Veer Arora,
you will never stop being late, right?
I will have to keep
waiting for you all my life?
I have no intentions of being Mrs.
Veer Arora.
Got it?
(Whistles)
"Keep me in your heart
and not your mind."
"Don't keep me on the side or behind."
"Keep me in your heart
and not your mind."
"Don't keep me on the side or behind."
"Listen up, girl.."
"I have a huge fan following."
"Don't ignore me,
I am quite mind-blowing."
"He is quite mind-blowing."
"Don't ignore me,
I am quite mind-blowing."
"You can follow me on twitter
or stock me on Facebook."
"I am very famous,
a have millions of fans."
"Let me click a selfie
together and upload it."
"You too will get famous and renowned."
"I agree a little milky.."
"I agree a little
milky is your glowing."
"Don't ignore me,
I am quite mind-blowing."
"My love,
you can check the Whatsapp DP."
"You can ask your friend or trust me."
"Keep your threatening attitude away."
"Tag love a little,
and enjoy heavily bliss every day."
"Let the car.."
"Let the car go slowing."
"Don't ignore me,
I am quite mind-blowing."
"He is quite mind-blowing."
"Don't ignore me,
I am quite mind-blowing."
(Machine sound)
Arora, I am fed up with Ghuggi.
What happened?
What did he do now?
- He rejected that girl as well.
- Really?
He says she doesn't have a good voice.
Arora..
He always does something as
soon as my blood pressure gets normal.
Brother, your son only does something..
My son Veer always
does something drastic.
Really?
I went to Kolkata a few days back.
Only for three days.
Veer looked after the whole factory.
My right-hand man, Shambhu.
He is fifty years old.
He fell in love with a girl
who applies henna in a parlor.
- You know what Veer did?
- What?
He got them both married.
- That's good.
- How is it good?
They got married three months back.
He is still on honeymoon.
Oh.
Brother, all my deliveries got delayed.
I have never said as many
lies as I have in these three months.
And all this is because of Veer.
And Veer is just a pupil.
Really?
- You know my elder brother, Nikku?
- Yes.
Nikku's son, Balli, he is his guru.
Okay.
If Veer is trouble, Balli is big trouble.
I'm warning you, keep your hands away.
You are a queen.
You aren't meant to martyr as a cop.
You are meant to keep
a king like me happy.
(Punch sound)
You..!
Your first crime,
interfering in police's investigation.
Your second crime,
touching a police officer's uniform.
Your third crime,
you touched a female police officer.
Under section 240..
324..
338..
You will all get arrested.
(Bird Chirping)
At least for 11 years.
Police has surrounded you from all sides.
(Indistinct)
Drop your weapons..
Right where you are standing.
Drop your weapons!
Idiots!
What are you doing?
Why should we believe you
that there are cops outside?
- Hey you, go and check.
- Okay, boss.
Why should he go out?
Are you scared of facing a bullet?
He is fooling us, boss.
- There are no cops outside.
- If they aren't here as yet..
..they will be here soon.
There they are.
Police has started to come on time.
Get him! Get everyone!
Sir!
Listen up! Sir!
Actually..
I came here at the right time.
I was on a bike.
But my team got stuck in the traffic.
Hats off to you.
Thank you so much, sir.
Thank you.
I'm Balli.
I work here..
Your work was amazing.
What was so amazing?
It was straight out of the movie Deewar.
Shashi Kapoor had acted
it out in the movie.
I just tried to match up a little.
This is the style big people.
They don't want to take any credit.
But I have to say, we will meet again.
I am Rani Chaudhary.
Inspector Rani Chaudhary.
Golnakkar police station.
Thank you.
Cops shouldn't be thanking anyone.
It is their job to provide the service.
It is the public who should thank them.
Damn!
He ignored Rani Chaudhary!
(Traffic)
Sir, if I may..
I extinguish the lamps at dusk..
Extinguish them.
Someone's memory sparks
my heart bright enough.
Someone's memory sparks my heart..
Wonderful..
- Amazing.
- Thank you.
It touched my heart.
Enjoy your drink.
Drink.
It's freeof cost. Drink.
Sir, may I ask something?
Why do you always listen
to sad pain-filled poetries?
What happened?
My heart is full of pain, Mr. Ghumra.
(Instrumental Music)
Oh.
I met a girl.
I fell in love.
Great.
And I also go an opportunity
to take things forward.
You should try the
Balushahi (sweets), sister.
No, thank you.
Well, I try to avoid
sweets to maintain my figure.
- There..
- Okay.
Come on, why should anyone avoid sweets?
Take it, otherwise aunt..
Actually, after my parents passed away..
..aunt was the one who brought me up.
No one can be a better
aunt or a better mother than her.
And in near future, no one would
be a better mother-in-law than her.
- There, even uncle is here.
- Look, he too is here.
Wonderful.
This house seems quite lively today.
- He's..
- Hello.
- He's my uncle.
He has played a double role.
As my father and as my uncle.
- Hello.
Hello, uncle.
I had given my approval
right after I saw your picture.
Balli..
I hope you have told
Sughanda about Mallika.
You haven't told her?
I'd suggest that you should
tell her everything before marriage.
You will face trouble if things
come out in the open after marriage.
He was crazy about Mallika.
- Please have the Samosas.
- Please.
You don’t have to take this seriously.
He loves to joke.
You know the forest behind Barrakhamba?
- Stop him.
- He spent three nights with her there.
I told him to at least
change his underwear.
- What are you waiting for Sughanda?
- He is joking.
- Who is Mallika? Underwear.
- Please sit down.
Sister! Sister! Sister!
- Please listen to me.
- We have heard enough.
Please listen to me.
Sughanda!
Sughanda, listen to me!
I had just fallen in love..
And uncle's joke ruined it all.
(Cell Phone Ringing)
Sughanda, I have been trying
to call you from so long.
The Mallika they are talking
about is Mallika Sherawat.
I am her fan.
I have seen Murder 25 times.
I was with her in Barrakhamba's forest.
But that's because they were
using my cars for her movie's shooting.
Look, I am Anu and not Sughanda.
Sughanda's friend.
Sughanda's phone is with me.
Oh.
Hello, Anu.
Before the palace of
my love turns to dust..
..please help me talk to Sughanda.
By the way Mr. Balli..
Sughanda is taking her
third vow at the moment.
The palace of your love
has already turned to dust.
What?
Damn..
That..
Now the situation is such that..
I find peace not when
I try to heal the wound..
..but when I try to reopen it.
How about another one?
Hey!
(Tickles)
(Snoring)
Damn you!
(Cell Phone Ringing)
Hello?
Well done, uncle.
You are having a good night's
sleep after ruining my life?
Leaving this 35-year-old
unmarried man to wander..
..in the desert of loneliness,
you lie there hugging your wife?
Have some shame.
You will get cursed.
You will not get married
for the next seven lifetimes, uncle.
You can go to sleep now.
Who was it?
Who else could it be..
..providing peace to my
soul in the middle of night?
Balli.
He loves you a lot.
Mom, I would like to say a few words.
Go on, say it.
Thank you.
What does he want to say?
He is just a kid.
Let him do it.
I would like to say something.
Today is a very big day for all of us..
..because today is
my grandfather's birthday.
I don’t know what a son
should do to honor his father.
But someone of my age should learn,
and I do just that.
I learn, when my father
does something for my grandfather.
When my father honors my grandfather..
When he does charity in his name..
It makes all of us very happy.
And today, to share that
happiness with all of you..
..dad has decided that all
of you get a month's salary as bonus!
(Claps)
There he goes again.
Hold on.
What are you doing?
A month's salary as bonus!
Did you ask uncle?
He was his father as well.
He was my grandfather too.
You didn’t ask me.
How can you just declare
a month's salary as bonus?
You won't get a month's salary as bonus.
You will 2 months' salary as bonus.
(Background Laughs)
Okay?
Amazing.
Thank you, Balli sir!
Mr. Balli..
There they do another charity.
Two months' salary as bonus!
You two have made me lose 7 million.
Dad, you are only thinking
about losing your 7 million.
Have you ever thought how much helpful..
- ..this 7 million will be for all
the workers? - Right?
It will help someone's sister
get admitted into a nice college.
Someone will be able to
get his mother's eye operated.
Someone will be able
to change his kneecaps.
to go on a pilgrimage.
Someone will be able to go abroad.
If some poor fellow is if your age..
..then he will be able to enjoy
a five days package in Thailand.
- Right?
- Exactly.
You will get so many blessings, dad.
You will live a long life.
Oh God!
- Take this.
- And yes, we aren't doing this for you.
We are doing all this for aunt.
My aunt should dress up like
this for another 200-500 years.
- Right, aunt?
- Yes, sure.
That's why I want you two
to continue with your good work.
You should give out a
few months' salary as bonus..
..on every birth anniversary
of your grandfather.
I will handle him.
Right?
Oh..
Our love will grow
if we eat in one plate.
You can do all that after we get married.
You are so mean.
Okay listen..
Why don’t you think about our marriage?
I am thinking about that only.
First, let my grandson get married.
Otherwise, people will say..
"Look there,
the grandson of the marriageable age.."
"..and the grandfather got married."
Look!
Then why don’t you tell them?
What should I tell them, sweetheart?
That we want to get married.
Don’t worry.
If they are worried about their son..
..they will find a suitable
girl for him on their own.
Okay, I will call them right away.
(Cell Phone Ringing)
- Hello?
Father.
- I seek your blessings, father.
- God bless you.
Is everything fine?
Yes, with your blessings.
I wanted to talk to you about something.
Tell me, what is it?
Have you found any
suitable girl for Veer?
We are looking.
You should hurry up.
We are trying.
Okay, I will hang up now.
Happy now?
We still haven't found
any suitable girl forever.
Sir, how many times have I told you..
..that forget 70 acres,
I'm not even ready..
..to sell even a small piece of land.
'Gopichand Bhalla is renowned.'
'He owns a confectionery shop.'
'He is only worried
about high blood pressure.'
'And there's a name
which makes him go mad..'
Listen, what did you say your name was?
Prabhu Dayal, Prabhu.
Hang up!
Disconnect it.
Cut the phone!
'He disconnects it.'
'For now it's just the phone call..'
Sir, we have received a big order.
'You will see what happens later.'
Prabhu and Prabhu industries..
Sorry, sir. Sorry.
Why are you taking that name?
- Tell me the address.
- Sorry, sir.
You deliver the order at
the address and not on the name.
- Sir..
- Go.
- Go and get the order ready. - You are
bound to get sweets at the sweetshop.
You can pack whatever you want.
Strange.
- Geet!
- Hello, papa.
- Hello.
- Here's your lunch.
What happened?
- Why are you out of breath?
- No, it's nothing.
Just..
Tell me.
Nothing. Just pack some
'Russmalia' (sweets) for me.
Okay.
- Nitesh.
- Yes, sir?
Pack that for Geet.
What is it called?
That..
What did you say?
Papa, Russmalia.
- Yes, Malia.
- Okay.
Russmalia.
Pack it for her.
Are you fine?
Yes, I am fine.
I am good.
It's was just that..
(Murmering)
Go on.
Go.
(Cell Phone Ringing)
- We are sitting inside.
- Okay.
Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Yes.
Yes, hello?
Yes, Juhi?
Listen, I have sent
holy offerings in lunch box.
Okay.
Give it to everyone in the shop.
Okay, listen..
What's playing in the background?
Prabhu's (Lord's) hymns.
Juhi, how many times have I told you..
..not to mention P-Ra-Bhu at one go?
I don’t know why this name
makes my blood pressure shoot up.
My sugar levels rise.
I start shivering.
I am not listening to it, Phoolan is.
I will switch it off.
Listen, if your blood pressure
is high then take a pill.
Okay.
I don’t know why everyone
is mentioning this name today?
You have Dahi Bhallas (snacks)?
Pack three pieces of them.
- Pack it.
- I'll pack them.
- Three will be enough.
- Okay.
- It will be ready in a few minutes.
Yes.
We should also pack some samosas, right?
- Good evening, ma'am.
- Good evening.
Also pack a dozen samosas.
- Okay, madam. Right away.
- Let's go.
Geet, tell me something..
Why was uncle scolding
auntie for mentioning Prabhu..
- Don’t say Prabhu.
- Why?
Papa will scold us too if he hears it.
But why?
When mamma was in college,
she had a boyfriend.
- Boyfriend?
- Boyfriend!
His name was Prabhu.
(Bell Sound)
- Really?
- I swear.
Mom made a mistake.
She told papa everything
about him before they got married.
- She told him everything?
- Yes.
From the time papa learnt about him,
he started feeling insure.
We aren't even allowed to mention
Prabhu during prayers at home.
(Bell Sound)
- Really?
- Seriously.
I'm telling you, just mentioning
the name makes him furious.
- You are a donkey.
- What's happening out there?
Wait.
What is going on out here?
Do you come here to work or to fight?
No, sir! How dare you say that!
What's happening out there?
Have you two gone mad?
Why are you two fighting like animals?
Let go!
- Nitesh.
- Yes, sir?
Settle their accounts,
wish them goodbye and send them away.
Okay, sir.
You two know that
I prefer non-violence.
I don’t like one person hitting another.
Sir, he called me a donkey.
He said it and you believed
that you are a donkey?
And if you are a donkey then
you should sound like one too.
You don’t need to say anything.
Pack your stuff and leave.
Goodbye!
Come on, let me settle your accounts.
Let's go.
(Traffic)
Here son, have some butter.
You work really hard.
It is necessary to strength
your mind and body.
After all, you are carrying the burden
of whole Delhi on your shoulders.
- Right, Tolaram?
- Eat, son.
Yes, sir.
You are absolutely right.
I too have started getting
a lot of respect because of him.
I swear.
I don’t even have to
pay parking charges anymore.
They say:
Mr. Tolaram, you may proceed.
Would you like to go home, Tolaram?
No, I will go to the kitchen.
And check on the lentils.
What are you doing, dad?
You should eat some butter.
You need it more.
You are carrying a heavier burden.
Along with the factory,
you look after Balli bro and me too.
Enjoy it, dad.
Get healthy.
Your uncle in Phagwada had called.
He isn't my uncle.
He is like a father to me.
Yes, him.
He was asking when we
were getting Veerey married.
He has nothing else to do.
He keeps getting people married.
He didn’t say anything wrong.
It is not so easy to find suitable girls.
It takes time.
First ask Veer, is he interested
in getting married to a girl..
Or a boy.
What if this mother's
boy has changed tracks?
You keep quiet.
If you continue with this you won't let..
..neither Balli nor Veer get married.
Oh.
You are talking about getting me married?
I didn’t know.
I am feeling so shy.
Let me do one thing..
Let me get out of here.
- I am getting late.
- Listen..
You are always getting late.
But what are you always late for?
You think I am a useless,
good for nothing, loafer, right?
Let me finalize the Japanese deal..
..I will make my brand
get global reorganization.
Get the car.
What, Mr. Ghumra?
No new poetry today?
- I am not high as yet.
- Not fair.
You will have to recite one for me.
Let the evening set in..
- Excuse me?
- Yes.
Don’t mind, but why are you laughing?
This photograph?
My bro.
His name is Balli.
He is a very simple man.
- Don’t mistake him for a funny one.
- No, it's not that.
In the collection of vintage
models of tragedy kings..
This new addition looks good.
Nice one.
Is she making fun of him or praising him?
It isn't clear to me.
They ask who Galib is..
Someone tell me what should I tell them.
Meaning?
You should get them together right away.
With great difficulty,
we have found him an admirer.
Don’t let her go.
Go.
Hello?
Yes, tell me.
Whom do you wish to talk to?
Mr. Balli?
Yes, I will give the call to him.
No problem.
That's great.
Nowadays a lot of people
seem to be interested in him.
Anyway, now what do I tell you about him?
He has the Shahrukh's
charm that he had in DDLJ.
Add Aamir's simplicity.
Also include,
the intensity Sunny Deol had in Ghayal.
And the light emotions
like Sanjay Dutt had in Saajan.
Cuteness of that Salman had in Santaan.
Mix all this and in the end add..
..Kamal Hassan's bad
luck that he had in Sadma.
That's it.
The personality that
you finally get is Mr. Balli.
I suggest you meet him.
You will know how nice
he is only after you meet him.
If you don’t like him,
I'll offer your lifetime serving free.
(Cell Phone Ringing)
What kind of a phone do you guys give me!
I don’t know..
These Chinese dual sim
phones are very strange.
I don’t get it,
how does one receive call on one..
..when I am busy
in a call on the other.
It's okay.
Do one thing.. send the
documents of the car home.
- Okay?
- Sure.
How did I go?
The Chinese phone's
excuse was a little lame.
But the rest of the build up was fine.
Now it depends on Mr. Balli's faith..
..whether he turns this
into happiness or sadness.
And the way Pammi ran away from there..
- He ran?
- Yes.
That's what I have been
trying to tell Chandan.
He just doesn’t get it.
How can I run?
Pammi won't run even if there's
fire anywhere in the world.
And what if we are trapped in a fire?
Bros are treated differently.
Anyway, you aren't the ones
who will get trapped in a fire.
You are the ones who start the fire.
(Vehicle vrooming)
Look there.
Two more.
- That's 37. - 35. (Car Stopped Sound)
I too am keeping a score.
Still two short.
No, you made a mistake while counting.
(Car door close)
It's 37, I know.
You have no shame.
- You are staring at girls over here?
- No, no, no.
I got Samosas and Jalebis
from papa's shop..
..so that we can have lunch together.
But we have just..
No, you are a very busy man.
Go and stare at girls.
Shameless fellow.
- Don’t talk to me.
- Hey sweetheart!
- Hello!
- Take me along!
She feel shy.
Oh no.
Sorry! I made a mistake!
You are misbehaving with girls?
Let us go!
You have come here to eve tease?
Veer doesn’t come here to eve tease.
He comes here to save them.
The Romeo gang trouble them a lot.
Everything has calmed down from the time
Veer has started sitting over here.
When a few like them have a death wish,
they show up here.
Get lost.
(Motorcycle Engine starts)
If I saw you again. I'll beat you.
Don't show me your face again.
- Come on. Let's go.
- Let's go.
Come let's go. Where did they came from?
Come on. Now say sorry and move on.
Forgiveness is part of life.
Girls look more preety
when they are angry.
Sorry.
- Sorry.
(Motorcycle Horn)
Jaggi, where are you?
Papers are ready.
We need to deliver the car.
I was about to some, bro..
..but I had some rotten
Bhatures (snack) last night.
I keep visiting the
restroom every two minutes.
Wait, let me drink the medicine.
It is very bitter.
I'll suggest why don’t
you deliver the car?
You know that we have to
deliver the car to a girl's place.
And I stay away from girls.
I know, bro.
But the thing is that I cannot make it.
Those Bhatures have messed up my system.
You..!
(Traffic)
What are you doing?
Mr. Balli is such a nice person.
Why are you cheating him?
I am doing this so
that I can become an uncle.
Wait, let me explain.
The thing is Mr. Balli stays
away from girls. - Okay.
- And he isn't ready to get married.
- Okay.
But I have decided that
I'll get him married anyhow.
Listen to me, Neelu.
Papa has found match for me.
Some Major Gulati.
Papa cannot stop praising him.
- Rinky!
- Yes, papa.
I'll call you back later.
- Rinky, listen..
- Yes?
Come dear. Sit.
Look dear, I have made this decision..
..to secure your future
and your happiness.
I don’t want to delay
your marriage any further.
We will go to Chandigarh tomorrow..
..to meet Major Gulati and his family.
- But papa..
- Either start packing for Chandigarh..
..or within three
minutes prove it to me..
..that you like someone else.
Papa, give me some time at least.
Yes. It's will be on time.
Hey, I have been trying to call you.
Thank God you are here.
Come in.
Papa, you were asking who's in my life?
Papa, it's him.
My love, my future, my everything!
- Thank God you came.
- But I have come to..
Yes, it's okay.
Papa, he's the one.
I..
- Okay..
- The documents..
Very nice.
It's a pleasure.
It's indeed a pleasure.
I am Colonel Vohra.
Balwinder Arora, Balli.
Oh, very nice.
Do you love each other or just..
No, papa.
He loves me a lot.
Right?
You know what?
You have come at the right time.
Papa was trapping me.
Actually, I would've been totally
trapped if you hadn’t showed up.
Papa has chosen someone for me.
But I don’t like him at all.
I mean I cannot marry
someone who is like papa.
But it's not that there
isn't anyone in my life.
There is someone.
(Traffic)
His name is Tillu.
And he too likes me.
Actually, I too.. I too like him a lot.
That's why I did all this drama.
I am so sorry. So sorry!
It's okay.
These are the documents of your car.
Well..
Take them.
I am really very sorry
for what happened inside.
I didn’t mean that.
I was just doing drama.
Please.. I was really just pretending.
I am so sorry. Listen..
Please listen.. hello!
(Cell Phone Ringing)
Hello?
Hello, Balli, it's me, Rinky.
Actually, you know what?
There is a lot going
on in my mind and heart.
And I cannot handle it.
I tried calling Kanika.
Her phone is switched off.
Then I tried calling Kanchan.
She is entertaining guests at home.
And Neelu, her phone is unreachable
since the past two days.
No one has time to talk to me.
Okay, can I talk to you?
Yes, tell me.
You know what?
I have had a motherless childhood.
Papa brought me up.
And you know what?
Papa only does what he wants.
What he thinks is right.
I mean it is going to happen.
When and with whom it will happen,
that subject..
Look Balli, I know that
we have had just a small meeting.
But I know.
Okay listen, I have decided that..
..I should leave with
Tillu while handling your case.
There are hardly any
days left in November.
I will leave with him.
And on top of that Bhasin and Goldie!
Their pressure is something
different all together.
And the person I love,
Tillu, he is so dumb!
I just don’t understand.
I am dreaming about Gulati nowadays.
He jumps four times
and five men fall flat.
Balli, hello, are you listening to me?
Yes, I am listening.
Yes, of course, I am.
Gulati killed four people.
Go on.
Thank you so much.
Okay then, you go to sleep.
And thank you once again.
Good night.
Jaggi.
- Coming, bro.
- Jaggi.
What's the problem with Bhatia's car?
He has already called
me 2 times since morning.
Forget his car, bro.
I will handle it.
There's a girl waiting for you inside.
Which girl?
Colonel's daughter.
She said she wants
to talk to you urgently.
I'd suggest if things look
positive then you should go for it.
The wedding season is on.
You..!
I'll see you later.
Lord Almighty, please be with him.
Balli, I couldn’t sleep last night.
I don’t know what I am doing.
And I don’t know whether
what I am doing is right or wrong.
I don’t know.
I had that with Tillu..
what just happens..
And a girl does that only..
..when it happens to her
for the first time in life.
And you know what?
I don’t have that with Tillu.
I have that..
I have that with you.
Yes.
You..
What is it that you..
Don’t have with Tillu
and have it with me?
Love.
I don’t love Tillu.
I love you.
And.. I want to marry you.
Yes, I agree that I was going to
marry him before you entered my life.
I used to love him as well.
But you know what?
From the time, you have entered my life..
It's you I see everywhere and not Tillu.
I think you..
You should get your mind checked.
Not my mind, my heart.
And only you can do that.
Look, please..
Please don’t reject me.
If you reject me then
I won't be able to live.
Do you..
..know what you are saying?
Yes, I know.
And I am not saying so, my heart is.
Look, listen..
Whatever I had with Tillu,
it was my childishness.
But..
But you are the one
I am actually in love with.
That's amazing!
That's amazing, bro!
I knew that you two
are made for each other.
God has answered my prayer.
Jaggi's wish has come true!
- That's amazing!
- Hey!
She is your sister-in-law.
Being possessive, bro?
No problem,
she can be my sister-in-law.
"Not my fault."
"I like you, that's all I know."
"It was meant to be hence
I fell in love with you."
"I say it with all my heart,
it's true."
"It was meant to be hence
I fell in love with you."
"I say it with all my heart,
it's true."
"I only belong to you."
"So many faces.."
"I came across.."
"But my heart fell for you."
"Love has brought me.."
"To a path unknown.."
"I find it difficult to survive.."
"It was meant to be hence
I fell in love with you."
"I say it with all my heart,
it's true."
"I only belong to you."
"I love you.."
Veer, why is it so loud?
Keep the volume down, son.
Mom, please.
What please?
- Mom, sit in the other room.
- Volume..
Keep the volume down..
So that we can at least talk.
This is not the place to talk.
Hey!
(Cell Phone Ringing)
There, Balli is calling.
- You want to talk him?
- No.
Hello?
Aunt, your wish is getting fulfilled.
I am getting married.
The truth, Balli?
Yes, I have found someone.
You should prepare for our wedding.
Come soon.
You see..
Balli has found a nice girl.
Good.
Now tell me about your girl.
Huh?
Tell me about your girl.
Mom, please.
Listen..
My friend's niece is very beautiful.
She is lovely.
Should I talk to her family?
Mom..?
Dad wouldn’t like that.
He likes you.
I am talk about you.
Okay.
Mom, I am still just a child.
And when will you grow up?
Mom, please.
Let me play.
Do you want to spend
your whole life playing, son?
When will you get married?
And listen, what about that girl..
..you take on drives
and burn so much gas?
Tolaram told me.
Mom..
Tolaram is a blabbermouth.
Forget the blabbermouth.
If you like her then
take things forward..
..and introduce her to me.
I will handle the rest.
I have been telling Veer
to introduce me to everyone.
But he doesn’t listen to me, auntie.
Auntie?
Don’t address me as auntie, dear.
Call me mom.
Mom?
Mom..
It sounds so nice.
Listen..
He loves to hum Lataji's
songs while eating parathas.
She is my favorite.
I love her.
- Really?
- Yes.
If he asks you to hum a little,
please do that for him.
- Okay, sure.
- Mom.
Her name is Geet,
but she cannot sing at all.
Veer!
He is always pulling my leg, mom.
- Don’t worry, dear.
- I sing quite well.
Of course you do, dear.
And he likes to have
kidney beans with paratha.
Right, Veer?
I don’t know how to cook kidney beans.
My paratha got burnt.
Mom, it's charred.
Mom, the tea!
Switch it off!
Now.. this..?
I cannot do all this.
I cannot do this acting.
This is how the paratha
I make looks like.
They get burnt or whatever.
This is how I make them.
I told you before. Why are you laughing?
Forget about the food..
What's more important that
she should have a good heart!
And she has a good heart.
You ate that charred paratha?
Veer, this is the first time in your
life you have done something right.
You have found a nice girl.
Right?
Heard that?
She isn't a good cook.
Geet, you know, I had gone my village.
My grandfather made me go crazy.
He has chosen some boy for me.
And even my father
cannot speak against him.
Are you getting me?
What kind of a boy he must
be if my grandfather likes him?
No, no, no. Wait a minute.
You didn’t meet him
and he finalized everything?
No!
All these oldies are just the same.
Anyway, my grandfather
listens to his moustaches..
..and does what he thinks is right.
This is a limit.
Seriously.
Could you like some tea?
No.
Got liquor?
Whiskey or Vodka?
Here's my wedding invitation.
Are you serious?
You fixed a date and
even got the invites printed.
Yes.
Eager much?
Eager, really?
Rahul?
Such a filmy name.
It's a pretty invite though.
Thanks.
Tell me something..
What's your status with Veer?
I'm under a lot of stress.
Why?
I still haven't told my family.
Oh.
You better hurry up.
Otherwise, you too will have
to marry someone your parents choose.
Only you can do that.
Send 10 kilo Barfi (sweets)
and 5 kilo Balushahi (sweets)..
..along with cashews to Mr. Gupta's..
Hello, uncle.
Ria!
I will call you later.
- Hello, uncle.
- Hello, dear.
When did you come back from Rivadhi?
We came yesterday.
Okay.
And here's my wedding invite.
That's great.
Your wedding invite.
Congratulations.
It's quite nice and cheap.
Papa!
I'm just joking.
- Uncle, all of you have to attend it.
- Yes, all of us will attend it.
The whole family.
Dear, you should someone for yourself.
Now you should find someone
for your best friend too.
Papa!
Uncle, there's Veer..
Veer?
Who is he?
Geet's boyfriend.
Mad..
Boyfriend?
No.. Shutup..
Geet..
Why are you making such gestures?
This is good news.
Why do you look so worried?
You should ballroom in the room.
Ria, she solved our problem in no time.
Look dear, if you like
someone then introduce him to us.
We will talk to him.
We will take things
forward and finalize it.
Okay?
Bye.
I'll go and give the
good news to your mother.
Okay?
Juhi!
Oh my God! Oh my God!
How did this happen?
- I don’t know.
- Veer!
I'll inform Veer.
- What are you looking at?
- Show it to me, please.
- No.
- Please!
- No!
- Please.
Listen..
Don’t talk much in front of papa.
Papa loves to talk.
I know.
How do you know?
Because all the fathers are the same.
Listen..
Don’t share the tales
of your bravery with papa.
He hates people who fight.
Will you remember what all I taught you?
Please?
What have you taught me?
Madam..
I am quite mind-blowing.
I agree.
Son, I was drowning..
I started shouting for help.
- A lifeguard came to save me.
- Thank you.
But poor thing, instead of saving me..
..he himself got into trouble.
It's okay, papa.
Now I will teach you how to swim.
Papa?
He got worried.
Fine.
I learnt how to drown..
you can teach me how to swim.
Very good.
- Hey, you scoundrel!
- What happened?
What are you doing?
- Get lost!
- Karan.
What did you say?
Are you trying to be smart.
Say it again. What did you say?
Hey! What are you doing?
Who are you?
Where are you, bro?
Mummy, you didn’t have anything.
I am, son.
I don't care about this world.
Veer..
You should try the Thandia papa makes.
Dear, you know that I haven't
made it since a long time.
No, papa.
You should make some for Veer.
Thandia keeps the mind calm.
No. You are mistaken, dear.
You don’t need Thandia to keep calm.
You need control to
yourself to keep calm.
You need to control your anger.
Hey you guys. Stop.
Anyway, he doesn’t need Thandia.
Does he get angry?
Does he pick up fights?
Does he beat up people?
He doesn’t need Thandia, dear.
No, I don't think so.
Papa, I will be right back.
- Veer, the food will go cold.
- Let him go, dear.
You can go later.
I will be right back.
Papa..
Come back soon, son.
Okay?
Look, your daddy's here.
See, how he's bashing them up.
What is that noise?
Is someone fighting?
No papa, something must
be having on the street.
- Let it be, papa.
- Let me go and check, dear.
Papa, why are you interfering
in someone else's matters?
Mamma, tell him..
Calm down.
Let him go.
Let's run.
Idiot!
He thinks I will let
my daughter marry him.
(Cell Phone Ringing)
- Veer, I will call you back.
- Geet!
- Papa!
- Give me your phone!
Hey you..
Whatever your name is..
Get this straight.
Never try to meet or call Geet again.
I don’t want my daughter
to marry someone..
..who raises his hands on others.
Someone who is a goon.
Goodbye.
Papa, please..
Mamma, papa..
Yes, father.
We have found a very
nice girl for Veerey.
Yes.
You should make your preparations.
We will soon fix an auspicious date.
Yes.
(Water Sound)
What?
They rejected you?
Yes, brother.
Don’t worry.
I'll talk some sense into Bhalla.
Bhalla!
Who is Bhalla?
How can you just barge in?
Didn’t the security guard stop you?
Who are you?
What's going on?
I am Balli, Veer's elder brother.
So you think Veer is a goon?
Our family fights for the country.
You know my grandpa captured
dacoit Durjan Singh.
We come from a family of fighters.
And you think we are goons!
No matter how hard you try,
you won't a boy better than Veer.
I have only come here to tell you that..
..if my brother's feelings get hurt..
..then I will start a fire
right here and fry Immartis (sweets).
I will make heartbroken
lovers sing outside your house.
Taiyab Ali hates love, shame on you!
You will lose your image.
And forget about your girl's wedding..
No one will even show
up to buy your sweets.
Got it?
You have 48 hours.
Come home and accept the proposal.
Hey.
Keep quiet.
(Bell Sound)
Now only Prabhu can save us.
(Door Close sound)
Balli, what you did was not right.
She is still not our daughter-in-law.
She is their daughter.
Wait till the evening.
He will come bearing gifts.
(Cell Phone Ringing)
You just wait and watch.
She is right.
Why did you have to go there?
Hello?
- He got a call.
- Have you gone crazy?
Is your whole family crazy?
Why?
What happened?
What happened!
Your brother.. What is his name?
Malli?
What is his name?
- Balli bro?
- Yes, him.
What does he think of himself?
He threatened my papa.
Papa is right.
You are a goon,
your whole family is full of goons.
You guys just don’t have any sense.
Good that your brother came
and showed us his true colors.
I had a narrow escape.
And yes, there is a message
for your parents as well.
Papa asked me to tell
them not to commit the sin..
..of trapping an innocent
girl from a good family.
They should look for
a girl from a family of goons.
I am deleting your number.
Don’t try to come after me.
I am warning you.
These days government is
doing a lot to protect girls.
Cops have been given thick batons,
so you better beware.
Bye.
(Instrumental Music)
Sorry.
I ruined it for you.
It's okay, bro.
You didn’t know.
Please have the juice.
Have some sweets too.
Brother, you won't find
such sweets anywhere in Delhi.
But you will find the complete
taste of Delhi in them.
Gets the Immartis (sweets).
Our special guest is here.
By the way,
what did you say your name was?
Prabhu Arora.
- Just Arora.
- Okay.
Mr. Bhalla, my son..
Not a son, a goon.
Younger one is a goon.
And the elder one is a super goon.
One shamelessly breaks
bones on the streets.
And the other wants to come to my
house, start a fire and fry Immartis.
And now their father has showed up.
The leader of those goons.
So, what have you brought with you?
Firearm?
Gun?
AK47?
Atom bomb?
What have you brought?
Mr. Bhalla, please listen to me.
What's there to listen?
Goons don’t talk.
They use their hands and legs to explain.
Look, even if you point a gun here..
..I won't let my
daughter Geet marry Veer.
I think you are done
with the refreshments.
You should stand up and leave now.
Go.
Goodbye.
Sorry, Mr. Prabhu.
I think he doesn’t like my name.
Bye.
He wants Geet to marry his son.
Now it's my turn to trouble
him in the middle of the night.
(Cell Phone Ringing)
Who is calling me at this hour?
Hello?
Hello, is that Mr. Prabhu Arora?
Yes, speaking.
Mr. Arora, I just had a fresh dream.
Do you know what I dreamed about?
I dreamed that a lunatic
is eating watermelon in the market.
When I took a closer at him,
I realized that it is P.K. Arora.
Mr. Arora,
I can see signs of lunacy in you.
You know what, you should
show yourself to a good doctor.
It will keep the lunacy in control.
Bye.
Who was it?
What happened?
Lunatic.
Whom were you talking
to so late in the night?
A lunatic.
A lunatic?
Have you lost your mind?
Oh Prabhu!
I hope I don’t go crazy.
Good evening, sir.
Good evening.
Is the report ready?
What's the name of the patient?
Gopi Bhalla.
Wait for a minute, please.
Hello?
Hello, yes?
Hello, I can't hear you.
Hello?
Yes?
One, two, three?
Check up, check up?
Hello? Hello? Hello?
Hello? Why can't I hear you?
You can’t hear me?
But I can hear you.
I don't know what is going on?
Is my report ready?
Yeah, here's your report.
- Give me the report, sir.
- Thank you.
Let me try again.
Mad. He is completely mad.
Blood pressure, okay.
Uric acid, okay.
Cholesterol, okay.
Sugar..
Sugar, 600!
Juhi, my sugar is 600!
- Phulan, stop adding sugar in my tea.
- Okay.
I will give your bitter
gourd juice from tomorrow.
Oh.
(Cell Phone Ringing)
600! 600!
- Hello?
- Not hello, bellow!
When one's sugar level reaches 600,
he bellows.
And you are saying hello?
Remember my name, Prabhu Arora.
Gopi..
This isn't your report.
Look at the patient's name.
It's Mr. Thakur.
Yes, it says Mr. Thakur.
Yes.
- So that means it isn't my report.
- No.
- It is someone else's report.
- Yes.
- That means I don’t have diabetes.
- No.
- It is normal.
- Absolutely.
Phulan!
Don’t forget to add sugar in my tea.
(Traffic)
What does your father think of himself?
What?
Your father loves to play pranks?
Not hello, bellow!
When one's sugar level reaches 600,
he bellows.
And you are saying hello?
Who talks like this?
You know what your father told mine?
What did he say?
"That you were wearing torn clothes
and having watermelon in the market."
Yes, so here the matter ends.
Listen..
We cannot be together
if our fathers can’t get along.
What?
Why did you call me?
Do you want to sing a duet with me?
I am not interested in hearing you sing.
I wanted to find out
what's your mental condition.
Oh, thank you very much.
It's absolutely fine.
And now that you are leaving,
it's even better.
Listen Veer, our paths are different.
Same here.
Then why don’t you delete
my number from your phone?
(Water Sound)
Wow!
Beautiful house.
Thank you.
Let's go.
You stay alone in such a big house?
Don’t you feel scared?
I do.
That's why I have brought you with me.
Come.
This is my bedroom.
(Door Close)
Sorry, it is a little dull.
You can add whatever colors
you want to it after marriage.
Look Balli,
I want to say something to you.
I don’t want to hear anything.
I agree to all your conditions.
You just agree to get married to me soon.
Balli, I met Tillu for two hours.
And in those two hours I realized that..
..Tillu loves me a lot.
And if I am not with
him then he will die.
Look, he is the only
brother to three sisters.
And he is the only support
of his parents and old grandma.
If.. if anything happens to
him then his poor mother will die.
And if his mother dies
then his old grandma..
She too is gone.
She will die too.
Though she can live.
Her knees, eyes and everything
else are working fine.
Everything is working fine.
In fact, she can recognize
from a distance..
..that her favorite
Rinky is coming to meet her.
Balli, I hope you understand
what I am trying to say.
I mean, you are quite sorted
and I know that you understand me.
Balli, listen..
Please adjust in this lifetime?
I will spend the rest of
the seven lifetimes with you.
Are you leaving?
Or should I throw you out?
'God, you are great.'
'You must have pondered
a lot before writing his fate.'
'You first made Sughanda
leave him and now her.'
'This girl too is gone.'
'35-years-old Balli
still remains unmarried.'
Damn her!
(Cell Phone Ringing)
Go and get water.
Hello?
Where are you?
You haven't visited the
garden since the past two days.
I hope everything's fine.
I haven't seen you
since the past two days.
You have seen my face enough.
- But Shabbo..
- Now if you want to take things forward..
..then get married to me.
If you can’t marry me then
should I find someone else?
Shabbo!
Shabbo, listen to me.
(Cell Phone Ringing)
Just a second.
Hello?
Prabhu, right?
Yes, father.
You are old.
You have aged.
But how can you forget
such an important thing?
What's the status of Veer's wedding?
We are working on it, father.
What are you working on?
Hurry up.
Life isn't just your
undergarment business.
It is much more than that.
I am not into undergarment
business, father.
Don’t tell me what you do.
You don’t do what you are supposed to do.
'Now will I get married
if Veer doesn’t?'
(Traffic)
Did you talk to her?
What did she say?
I'd suggest we should kidnap the girl..
..get married in a temple,
seek blessings at the Gurudwara..
..and there the matter ends.
No.
Let me know if there is any other option.
I agree with Pammi.
You shouldn’t run too far after girls.
It gets difficult to come back.
I have brought a new one for you.
What are you saying, Balli bro?
- Look at her, you might like her.
- I don’t want to, bro.
- There..
- No, I don’t.
"Let me drink with your eyes."
Even if there's no light in my abode..
"I wann be an alcoholic tonight."
..my buddy's should always be well lit.
"I feel like flying away with you."
"I say goodbye to the
world and hello to you."
"I feel like flying away with you."
"I say goodbye to the
world and hello to you."
"Get ready, be my buddy.."
"Open up a little,
o baby don’t be shy."
"Where are you going all alone,
tonight?"
"Baby, where are you off to, tonight?"
"Where are you going all alone,
tonight?"
"Baby, where are you off to, tonight?"
"Where are you going all alone?"
"Where are you going all alone,
tonight?"
"Baby, where are you off to, tonight?"
"Where are you going.. all alone?"
"Why wander here and there."
"Come on baby, let's get drunk."
"You make my heart sing."
"You are like breaking news."
"You cause a sensation."
"What's your view about me, honey?"
"Oh baby, don’t be crazy."
"Come on, let's get a little tipsy."
"Because all is forgiven tonight."
"Black dress,
backless, seeks my interest."
"Rebellious, but what
make me rebel is your hotness."
"Your eyes are like a 90ml shot."
"The high fails everyone,
but I am all set."
"I feel like with you I belong."
"If you say yes,
I will take you along."
"All night, about love, we shall talk."
"I'll sit with you on the rooftop."
"I feel like with you I belong."
"If you say yes,
I will take you along."
"All night, about love, we shall talk."
"I'll sit with you on the rooftop."
"This spark of love is shines bright."
"I would like to romance
you under candle light."
"I don’t want to be alone, tonight."
"Baby, I want to be with you, tonight."
"I don’t want to be alone.. tonight."
"Move it baby on the beat."
"I don’t want to.."
"Lost in your eyes.."
"I wanna to be drunk tonight."
(Traffic)
So this is the problem.
- Okay.
- Madam..
I get it.
My name is Rani Chaudhary.
You cannot hide anything
from Rani Chaudhary.
70,000 bucks is involved.
- Rampal.
- Yes, ma'am.
Go inside and gather all men here.
- Okay?
- Yes, ma'am.
Can I leave, ma'am?
Have a seat, madam.
Rashida, give her some water.
She already had water.
Then give her a cold drink.
Okay, madam.
(Cell Phone Ringing)
Hello?
Tell me your name.
Idiot, why don’t you stop it?
How many times do I need to
tell you that I am not Rani Mukherjee?
- I am Rani Chaudhary.
- Your cold drink.
Stop troubling me, I am working.
Hang up.
Manager! Give me the details.
70,000 bucks is at stake.
A complaint has been registered.
And I need to find
out who is the culprit.
There are so many characters around you.
Do you suspect anyone?
Can I say something, madam?
This is what Rani Chaudhary wants.
You should open your
mouth and say something.
I..
Madam, please sit down.
Don’t worry.
- Rashida..
- She's already had a cold drink, madam.
Then get her an ice cream.
What flavor would you like, madam?
- Please tell us. - Vanilla, madam.
(Cell Phone Ringing)
Idiot! Don’t you get it! I'm
in the middle of something important.
I am working, you..
- Sir!
- Here's your ice cream.
Yes, sir.
- No, sir.
- What all we have to do!
Okay, sir.
Okay. Okay, sir.
- Rampal!
- Yes, madam?
By mistake, we have made a mistake.
The incident took
place at some other mall.
We are at the wrong mall.
- Rashida..
- Yes, madam?
Let's go.
- Okay, madam.
- Manager, please forgive us.
By mistake, I made a mistake.
You sometimes end up making mistakes
while doing your duty seriously.
- Sorry, I got too serious.
- Okay.
Madam, you too may leave.
Now I will leave only
after I finish the ice cream.
As you wish.
Let's go.
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Search everyone!
All those who have given
money by Bunty, please pay up..
..otherwise,
you will be sent to prison.
Bunty, you fooled me and came to a mall?
You are having a good time over here!
You are giving 500 Rs as in tip.
Take him along!
You fool Rani Chaudhary!
What are you saying?
I don’t understand.
Let me explain that again.
Cancel one Sherwani and two Kurtas.
Okay.
The rest is as it is.
But the Sherwani is for the groom, sir.
Why are you looking at me?
I am not the groom.
So you are asking me to cancel
the two turbans for the groom?
Not both the turbans.
Cancel one turban.
But the turban is for the groom, sir.
You are repeating the same thing again.
This turban is for my brother
Veerey who is getting married.
- Got it?
- And your wedding?
(Sighs)
(Indistinct chatters)
Look there are three single men.
Rahul, Salman-bhai and me.
We have decided that we
will all get married together.
Now do you get me?
He wants to know about my marriage.
(Footsteps)
Listen up!
I have handled the clothes too.
You refuse to recognize me!
I smiled and yet you didn’t recognize me.
If even I smile at someone just once,
he will never forget me.
My name is Rani Chaudhary.
Why should I remember you?
Are you Katrina?
Kangana?
Aishwariya?
Even if you are,
it makes no difference to me.
That day you reached before
the team and got into trouble.
Today you must have surely
caused trouble in the mall.
Why will anyone want to remember you?
(Indistinct chatters)
You aren't worth remembering.
Rani Chaudhary is so polite to you.
But you.. you don’t seem
to let go of your attitude.
I too have some respect here.
You can try being polite?
A little, maybe?
(Vehicle Pass by)
I am in a mess today.
Please spare me.
(Horn Honking)
It's a big deal that
I am even talking to you.
Mr. Balli!
(Tyres screeching)
(Vehicle vrooming)
(Car Door Opening)
Sorry if I was rude. (Car Door
Closing) (Vehicle ignition sound)
Do the duty with all your heart, okay?
(Horn Honking)
(Gasps)
(Cicada Sound)
Hello?
Listen, we will have to
find a girl for Veerey soon.
Darling, I will come directly
home from the factory.
I will get a few girls
along if I find any on the way.
If you like any of them,
you can finalize her.
Hey, we are talking about
our son's wedding here.
This isn't like grocery shopping.
We should find a suitable one.
The way your father was talking..
..it felt like he is
all set to get married.
He was saying that he'd
go to Switzerland on honeymoon.
- Switzerland!
- Really?
If he goes to Switzerland
for his honeymoon..
..then we'll have to go to
the moon to find a girl for our Veerey.
All our relatives will laugh at us.
Okay, we will talk once I reach home.
I'll hang up now.
He never listens..
Oh God!
The situation in my
house is quite different.
(Indistinct chatters)
My grandfather's brother
wants to marry for the second time.
- What?
- Can you believe it?
- He's 90 plus.
- Yes!
And my family wants
me to be done with my first.
This is great.
Mummy shows me pictures
of new girls every day.
Sometimes it's this girl
sometimes it's that girl.
Her brother does this,
her father does that.
I told her to get me married
to any girl that she likes.
- Really?
- Then what!
- Well, I will have to listen to her.
- Of course..
..you should always
listen to your mother.
Of course, you should.
Right.
Papa has started looking
for suitable boys for me.
- And you are cracking jokes over here.
- Geet.. Okay, fine.
But please listen to me.
So, the first one looks like
Aishwariya Rai. (Horn Honking)
She has blue eyes.
Perfect big eyes.
She is just a shade darker than me.
But that's okay, it doesn’t matter.
Color doesn’t matter.
The second one,
she is exactly like Katrina.
- Oh.
- Really.
If both of them stand together,
no one will be able to differentiate.
She is a little short, but that's okay.
She'll match with my height.
- Doesn’t matter.
- Oh, you are so adjusting.
- Obviously.
- Right.
Yesterday,
I told mom that she has me in a fix.
When I turn over on the bed I night,
on one side there's Katrina..
..and Aishwariya on the other.
Listen..
(Horn Honking)
These Katrina,
Kareena, Aishwariya, Naagina, Paseena..
..whoever they are, whatever
you want to do with them, do it.
Got it?
There is just one girl made for you,
Geet Bhalla.
The sooner you understand
that the better.
SIsn't tonight enough to understand?
- Who are you?
- Sit down!
Veerey, Mr.
Bhalla has called this guy, Amardeep..
..to talk about marriage with Geet.
So you want to be Bhalla's son-in-law?
Get some snacks.
Have some.
Have you seen Geet's picture?
(Indistinct chatters)
Yes.
Have you started dreaming about her?
Yes, bro.
She is awesome.
We are here to help you.
Right?
We have brought you here
so that you don’t get rejected.
This poor guy got rejected.
Tell him what had happened.
Bro..
He asked me, do you have courage?
I said, yes, I do.
Then he asked, can you hit ten
people on the streets all by yourself?
I said.. I can manage to hit a few.
If there are many then I
can use a rod to hit on their heads.
And I told him what
happened at the petrol pump.
I hit five people with hockey sticks.
Your turn.
Don’t ask what happened with me.
He had beaten two, he had beaten five..
If you can see my size and guess..
I didn’t get you.
- He had beaten two, he had beaten five..
- He still doesn't get it.
Explain it to him, Veerey.
Coming to the point, Mr. Bhalla
needs to know what your hands can do.
The strength in your hands.
He wants to know how
strong my hands are, right?
I understood.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Yes, uncle.
Son, tell me something..
Yes, uncle?
What did you say your name was?
- Amardeep.
- Amardeep, very good name.
It's a very good name.
What's your education level?
And what special
talent do you have that..
..I should get my
daughter married to you?
I don’t want to praise myself..
..but my talent lies
in my hands, uncle.
(Indistinct)
Uncle, I started raising
my hands in college itself.
I don’t even need a hockey stick.
I thrashed many goons
using these very hands.
Yes.
Uncle, all my friends used to say..
..that there are only
two real men in this world.
One's Sunny Deol and the other, Amardeep.
That is me.
Okay, uncle?
Uncle, though I don’t raise my hand much.
But when I do, oh the way I do!
Let me tell you what
happened day before yesterday.
I thrashed a guy so badly that
the poor guy is still in the ICU.
He's in coma.
Uncle, power!
The power of the hands!
Take a look.
- I just need your blessings, uncle.
- Here you go.
What did you do?
People offer milk to a snake,
I am offering him buttermilk.
Then?
Then what?
Papa bathed him in
buttermilk and threw him out.
Oh no!
Sorry Geet,
but your dad is one piece in the world.
Only one piece.
Tell me, what are you
doing with the next one?
Relax, relax.
Balli bro is handling our this case.
And remember one thing..
It is quite important for Mr.
Bhalla to know..
..how a man starts his married life.
Honeymoon.
Make sure you talk about honeymoon.
Wow uncle, buttermilk!
I love buttermilk.
If you don’t mind, auntie and uncle..
..can I just try some buttermilk?
Sure, why not?
Thank you.
- It's from our shop.
- Wonderful.
Amazing.
Son, what do you plan
to do after the wedding?
(Indistinct)
I've planned to go to
Switzerland for my honeymoon.
(bicycles bell )
We will shop in Dubai for the first
two days. (Airplane Take-off)
After that a chartered
flight to Switzerland.
But uncle,
if we don’t like the climate there..
..then we will go to Paris.
Paris!
- We don’t need to worry since
it is a chartered plane. - Yes.
I believe in having a great honeymoon.
Uncle, this will be my first honeymoon.
Is this a first for
your daughter as well?
(Indistinct.
Hey Mr. Frequent Flyer!
- What is it, uncle?
- Stand up.
- What happened?
- And get out.
And not hug me before you leave..
I believe in non-violence.
If I get violent then I'll
squeeze you to then when you hug me.
Go, and fly in your plane..
..and go on a honeymoon with a girl
who has already been on a honeymoon.
- Get lost!
- Uncle! Uncle!
- Security!
- Uncle!
Escort him to his plane.
He wants to go on a
honeymoon with my daughter.
Idiot.
(Crowd applause)
(Camera Shutter)
Dude.
Hey dude.
That's it.
This western "dude" culture
is making the young of our country..
..stay away from milk
and ghee (clarified butter).
They like burger more than their home.
They like pizza more
than their brother-in-law.
And momos more than their uncles.
That's why our company is trying to..
..keep the youth of country healthy..
..with milk,
ghee, yogurt and buttermilk.
That's why after Tau Ghee,
soon our company..
..is also going to
launch Tau buttermilk.
Because east or west Haryana is the best.
Its milk and yogurt
are better than the rest.
Long live our soldiers!
(Crowd applause)
Thank you.
- Sir! Sir! Sir!
- One picture, sir!
- K. K. sir! - What's the reason
behind launching Tau Ghee?
- Please tell us, sir.
- Why Tau Ghee, sir?
Tau Ghee will soon
be available in the market.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- Move.
Come this way, sir. Come.
Mr. KK! Mr. KK!
- It's okay.
- Hello.
Hello.
First of all, I would like to thank..
- ..for ordering sweets from my shop.
- Yes.
Secondly,
after listening to your thoughts..
..I have become a huge fan of yours.
Thank you.
You have a great style.
Dude!
You have a great style and a great heart.
You are linked to your roots.
Thank you for your polite words.
But I don’t think I
have anything special in me.
Being a human being it
is our duty to love each other..
..and respect our elders.
What a noble thought!
Excuse me, I need to leave now.
I need to attend a mass marriage.
I have taken up the responsibility
of marrying a few poor couples.
That's great.
After hearing this I have
become a double fan of yours.
- Bye.
- Goodbye.
Goddess, he needs to
be a part of Geet's life.
- Mamma, I am leaving.
- I'm coming, Geet.
Okay, bye.
- Bye.
- See you.
Whose bag is that?
Your papa's.
He is going with you.
Come on, mamma, doesn’t he trust me?
(Dog barking)
I am going to attend my friend's wedding.
I know.
And what will they think.
Their fathers aren't tagging along.
- This is not fair. - Geet, I am not
going with you without a reason.
(Vehicle Pass by)
Ria's uncle had come
to our shop to invite me.
He said to come with the whole family..
..otherwise he won't enjoy the wedding.
We are anyway not going
to enjoy it now, papa.
Mamma isn't coming, so why are you?
I don’t know why she isn't coming.
I need to mediate on Prabhu's name.
Mamma, you know, right?
She has never been to
any wedding other than her own.
She wouldn't have attended
that either if I wasn’t there. - Mother.
He's so dramatic. I won't go with him.
Don’t say that.
Mamma, who does this?
(Horn Honking)
Smile and leave, my child.
Mamma loves you.
(Vehicle Pass by)
Yeah.
"Back off!"
"Back off, uncle!"
"Let me get drunk and dance."
"I am high.."
"I am high and ready to fly."
"Let me get drunk and dance."
"I have no control over myself today."
"I will get drunk and dance."
"Let me get drunk and dance."
"You can invite Shakira."
"You can make us compete."
"My moves.."
"My moves have a lot to say today."
"Let me get drunk and dance."
"I am high and ready to fly."
"Back off!"
"Back off, uncle!"
"I won't let the music stop."
"I won't sleep,
I won't let anyone sleep."
"I won't let the music stop."
"I won't sleep,
I won't let anyone sleep."
"I will cause a commotion.."
"I will cause a commotion
using my emotions."
"Let me get drunk and dance."
"I am high and ready to fly."
Veer?
What are you doing here?
Papa too is here.
You will get beaten up.
Go away.
Why should I fear when you are near?
Getting cheesy?
You will get beaten
up if papa hears that.
Veer, papa.
Don’t you have any shame?
How can you stoop so low?
- Sir..
- You are a goon.
Papa!
But even goons have a character.
You don’t even have a good character.
I am feeling very angry but..
..since someone's happiness
and honor are at stake..
..I have kept a check on myself.
Let's go, dear.
- Papa, please.
- You won't say a word, Geet.
You saw what the boy
of your choice can do, right?
Now you will do as I say.
I have finalized a very nice boy for you.
And I know that you
will be very happy with him.
Papa!
Let's go.
(Vehicle Pass by)
Call up my uncle.
I need to give him the good news.
'He's an uncle from Haryana,
a philanderer.'
'He loves English and Englishwomen.'
'He couldn’t learn English.'
'But he has thought the Englishwomen
how to speak Haryanvi.'
'Balli knows him quite well.'
'After all, he had sold him a car.'
I too will go with you.
What will an old hag like you do there.
What will you do there?
Young girls will go there.
Hot chicks.
Me too.
(Mobile ringing)
Yes, nephew?
- Uncle, your nephew is getting married.
- Married?
(Indistinct)
Yes.
I think you have finally
ready to bite the apple.
Do attend my wedding, uncle.
Of course, I will.
My marriage will be no fun without me.
True. Who will do all the rituals?
Don’t worry.
I will come there as soon
I am done with my honeymoon.
- I will surely be there.
- Okay, uncle.
He is getting married instead
of concentrating on the business.
Uncle has four wives to entertain him.
And I have not even been
able to get engaged even once.
We get work according to our status.
I stay in heaven along with the angels.
But I am sweeping floors there.
He has given me a gun
and made me a cleaner.
Uncle, your car is ready.
Let's go if you are done here.
(Mobile ringing)
Veer! Veer! Veer!
How are you?
Did you like the design of the card?
I am sure you must have the name.
I am sure you are well educated.
So the thing is, I want you
to engrave something in your mind.
Geet is my fiancée.
If I see you anywhere
close to her henceforth..
..then no one will
be able see you anymore.
The thing is, you still quite young.
You have a long life ahead of you.
- Hey!
- Veer!
How dare you come here!
Security!
Who let him in?
Sometimes it's the elder
one and sometimes it's the younger.
- Gopi.. Gopi!
- Come on, leave!
- Get out! Leave!
- Gopi!
Calm down.
At least hear him out.
You can listen to this goon. I won't.
Sorry, Veer.
Sir, you invited me
a lot at that wedding.
I could have answered
you back if I wanted to.
But I too was aware that we
were there celebrating someone's joy..
Someone's honor was at stake.
I tolerated all your questions.
And a single reply from
me could have been enough for you.
May I say something, sir?
I can kidnap Geet whenever I want.
But I won't do that.
Because both of us don't want that.
Because if a father doesn’t
give his daughter away happily..
..then that relationship
holds no value for us.
Geet and I won't get
married to each other..
..till we don’t have your permission.
One more thing, sir.
That day,
I didn't go there because of Geet.
It was my friend's brother's wedding.
I didn’t even know
that Geet could be there.
I too have a character.
I don’t show up just anywhere.
It's from your shop.
(Horse neigh)
Come, sir.
These are our horses, sir.
As white as snow.
All of them are of a good breed, sir.
You won't find a single spot on them.
We have around 50 such
horses in our farmhouse.
You won't get such horses anywhere else.
Mr. Vinod, not every horse
can handle me on its back.
- Okay.
- Got it?
Yes.
So, you do one thing..
Get me a horse from Peshawar.
- Okay.
- Where will you get it from?
Peshawar.
(Footsteps) (Car Door opening)
"Who is this in front of me?"
"My heart skipped a beat."
This is great, Veer.
You too have come to book a horse?
Tell me something..
What will you do with the horse?
You will tour the city on it?
You know, people will think
you are crazy and hit you?
I am taking a horse from
Peshawar to Bhalla's house.
What will you do, mister?
You shouldn’t laugh on
a bad joke and mislead people.
Mr. Groom, you will also
need guests at the wedding.
Teach them some manners.
Otherwise, there'll be just cripples
accompanying you at the wedding.
Do you know who I am?
Why are you hitting me?
I have not done anything.
Juhi, you saw that?
These animals who look like humans are
spreading violence on the streets.
Why are you hitting me?
Can you see how he is hitting him?
He will hit him even more.
And he might also kill him.
Do you know why?
Because none of them is Veer.
It is necessary that
every crowd have a Veer..
..to protect our girls and the weak.
So we got all the permits.
Yes sir.
- Upload all the files by tomorrow.
- Sure, sir.
Just make sure that you copy that.
Hey you idiot!
Uncle!
That's great!
Bhurra!
Put him down.
Get the marbles out of your mouth.
Father!
What do you want to be?
What are you trying to do?
Shut up!
Father!
It has been three months..
..hence I heard about
any crime committed by you.
You didn’t steal anything.
You didn’t do any bank robbery.
You didn’t kidnap anyone.
And now you are getting married.
You have also shattered
your mother's dream.
She wanted you to be greater than Dawood.
There should be reward over your head.
You should be wanted across the world.
And you want to get married, stupid.
Are you done, uncle?
Now listen to your nephew.
Come on.
Come on, uncle.
Don’t get angry.
Come with me.
Don’t you trust your nephew?
Huh, uncle?
You are my uncle.
Mother's brother is like another mother.
This marriage, it is nothing.
Then what is it?
It involve 70 acres of land, uncle.
How many?
- 70 acres!
- 70 acres?
Yes.
Our project Jagdamba City..
This piece of land lies
somewhere in the middle.
Bhalla wasn’t handing it over.
'Sir, how many times have I told you..'
'..that forget 70 acres,
I'm not even ready..
..to sell even a small piece of land.'
But now he will happily give it away.
How?
As dowry, along with his daughter.
Along with his daughter!
The truth?
I never lie, uncle.
I swear.
That's my boy!
Bhurra! Bhurra!
- Quiet.
- We will get the girl and the land.
- Don’t act crazy.
We will get the girl and the land.
Father, but whose?
Bhalla's!
Bhalla's daughter, Bhalla's land!
Bhalla! Bhalla! Bhalla!
I am Bhalla! I am Bhalla!
I am Bhalla!
Father, Bhalla!
Yes.
Gopichand Bhalla.
Brother, today you have made the slogan..
..educate the daughter,
save the daughter meaning in my life.
Look, I educated my daughter.
And you saved her.
Bhalla's daughter, Bhalla's land!
Bhalla! Bhalla! Bhalla!
Goodbye!
How are you, Mr. Bhalla!
Thank you.
Thank you?
You cleared all my doubts.
I was in a dilemma.
You have cleared all my doubts.
Now, don’t even think about
getting married to my daughter.
You won't get married to her.
Mr. Bhalla, don’t start with this now.
I am a simple guy,
but I am not prone to shocks either.
The thing is, everyone
knows that I am getting married.
Only the horse needs to be decorated.
If my honor..
It's not your honor,
but my daughter's life at stake here.
Anyone who tries to
take her happiness away..
Son, I am confectioner.
I make sweets.
But that doesn’t mean
I say only sweet things.
I also know how to start
a fire and fry and roast things.
Got it?
Goodbye.
Bhalla, you think you have
a feast after spoiling my meal?
All hail the Goddess, Bhalla!
Don’t worry, nephew.
Your uncle is still here.
You prepare to get married.
Things will go as your
uncle wants them to go.
Anyone who interferes will be done for.
(Horn Honking)
Sorry, brother.
I had painted a very
bad image of Veer in my mind.
He is a very nice boy.
I am bad.
Born in '56.
My old school thoughts and stubbornness..
..didn't understand her heart,
her love or her understanding.
I am a very bad father.
Third-class.
But now I want to become first-class.
Hence, I request you to
please get Veerey married to Geet.
Accept her.
I have been feeling
burdened since last night.
I couldn’t even sleep.
Mr. Bhalla,
you should unburden yourself.
I too have done so.
Today, I realized that
my Veer is a very nice boy.
Thank you. Thank you.
"Everyone is happy,
today's Veerey's wedding."
"Dance, dude.. Today's
Veerey's wedding."
- "Everyone is happy."
- Everything good?
"Today's Veerey's wedding."
"Veerey's wedding.."
Mother.
Bhalla!
Today I will make you a belle!
Bhurra!
Go and get Geet.
I'll get her, father.
Why don’t you just kill me?
I'll get you your wife, bro.
Geet! Geet! Geet!
Help!
Who are you?
Father!
- Hey beardy goon, who are you?
- What is it?
- Father!
- Get me down!
- Father, I have brought Geet!
- Geet!
- I am not Geet!
You idiot, she isn't Geet!
(Footsteps) (Indistinct chatters)
Slap him!
Father, I'll go and get Geet.
Uncle, why do you go close to yogurt
when you know you're allergic to it?
Nephew, I didn’t go close to it.
It came to me.
- Okay, so it can walk?
- Geet! Geet!
She is looking so beautiful.
Just like an angel.
I don’t feel like disturbing her.
(Mobile ringing)
I'm getting a phone call.
- Oh great, it's brother-in-law!
- Shut up.
Hello?
What are you doing, Geet?
Getting henna applied.
Great.
- Can we meet?
- Now?
Yes.
- Are you close?
- Very.
- Come over.
- Okay.
Come over.
Count till ten and I will be there.
- Should I?
- Come over.
Come over, Mr. Groom.
Because this groom
is already with his bride.
The thing is, if she agree,
then we will get married..
..and if she doesn't
then I will kidnap her.
Now let's see whether
I kidnap her or you save her.
How do girls run wearing
such heavy dresses?
Catch your sister-in-law!
Geet!
Hello. Hello, police?
Don’t run! Your dress will get ruined.
You will fall into the pool!
Be careful. Don't hurt her.
(Indistinct) (Gasping)
What happened, son?
Why did you stop?
Veer?
You are here?
Look, Veer is here now.
Son, we had called the police,
but you showed up.
God bless you.
You have come at the right time.
Come on son, go for it.
Violence?
No, no, no!
I don’t raise my hand on anyone.
Okay, okay, okay.
Then what's this?
This? Broke it with my leg.
- Okay.
- Get him.
Do you want me to Whatsapp
you the instructions? Get him!
- Hey!
- Veer!
Papa!
"Your beloved is here."
"And my bride is scared?"
Father-in-law, you should
prepare for our wedding.
Because now your daughter is mine.
Right?
- She hit me!
- Get her, brother!
Stop!
Run!
Well done, Veer.
- Elephant!
- Move away!
Go away!
Uncle!
Your nephew is getting
beaten up over there.
Where are you going?
You too will get thrashed.
Listen, you like Dahi Bhalla, right?
So I got some for you.
Uncle, try some Dahi
Bhalla made by the Bhallas.
Just eat the dumpling in it.
Then just eat the yogurt.
Strange. He likes neither
yogurt nor the dumpling.
This is great!
Balli bro?
Veerey?
Geet! Geet! Geet!
Father!
My marbles!
Uncle?
Hello!
What's wrong?
Come here.
What is it? What's wrong?
Why are you sneezing?
Come on, man.
Who is sending the location to you?
You show up from thin air!
You!
Who did put your nose into?
Wipe it.
I am feeling better.
Thank you.
Calm down, calm down.
I cannot speak.
You don’t need to, uncle.
Fear is visible on your face.
And why are you holding this gun?
Why do you need a gun?
One look at your face
and one will pee out of fear.
You should have been in the army.
Or police.
You should have fought for our country.
You would have defeated our enemy.
And your nephew, what is his name?
What has he done for you?
Has he ever sent you anywhere?
- He did.
- Where?
He has sent me to prison, thrice.
Damn him!
I did so much for him.
I robbed banks.
I stole from other people.
I committed murders.
I escaped encounters, thrice.
Look at this, a bullet mark.
Oh no.
All uncles are generous.
But even the nephew
should be considerate.
I will send you to London.
Everything there will be fair.
Fair girls.
Fair boys.
Uncle! Come back!
- Come on!
- Let go!
Let me go!
- Father!
- Let me go!
- I brought her!
- Who have you brought?
Geet!
I am not Geet, stupid!
Stop kidnapping girls.
My nephew turned me into an evil man.
If not for this love, you would
have been a colonel in the army.
Enough..
You have opened my ears.
At least get the saying right, uncle.
Hey!
You have opened my eyes.
Uncle!
Has he changed for good?
Hey!
I am warning you, I'll shoot you!
Where did I get the umbrella from?
Here it is!
I have not loaded it as I was in a hurry.
But I will hit you with it.
My aim is very good.
Someone shot me on my bum!
Call for an ambulance. I will die.
- Come on, get going from here!
- Good work, Rani Chaudhary.
- Arrest him!
- Take them away!
They should manage to escape!
Come on, take them away.
Let's go, scoundrels.
I will get you married in the prison.
Come on.
Thank you.
You..!
Come on!
- Geet!
- Let me go!
Too much attitude, Rani Chaudhary?
Two slaps and you got impressed?
I handle half the cases of this city.
Anyway, whether or not it falls
under my area, SP always send me.
This falls under my area,
that's why I am here.
I am sure you must be dying to praise me.
But I don’t have time to waste.
Hey!
Save him!
Veer!
Don’t let go of my hand, I will die!
I am telling the truth, I will fall.
I am telling the truth.
Don’t let go!
Uncle!
Bro.
- Should I let you go?
- No, no, no.
- No, please.
- Should I?
Please, don’t let go
of my hand at any cost!
- Uncle!
- Veer, don't!
I am telling the truth.
This is what's called humanity.
This boy is full of it.
From today,
I stop all my illicit businesses.
I have learnt a lesson.
If you fall down..
If he lets go of your hand..
Then you will die for sure.
This boy deserves to be with Geet.
He deserves her!
Bro! Bro! Bro!
I am totally getting
what uncle is trying to say.
I am telling the truth.
You can have Geet.
You can have the 70 acres of land too.
You can have Geet's father.
You can have meet too, bro.
You should get married, bro.
I will dance at your wedding.
I swear.
Please pull me up, bro.
Look..
The thing is that I
just got impressed by you.
So, I am thinking of taking a chance.
If you try to act
smart then you know that..
That's enough, Mr. Balli.
How hard are you going
to make me fall for you?
Rani Chaudhary is
already crazy about you.
I will dance at your wedding!
Veer!
I think you should switch
back to non-violence now.
Come on.
Let go of everything.
- Should I let go?
- No, don’t let go!
- He will fall!
Pull him up!
Pull him up, bro!
- Don’t let go, please!
- Pull him up!
Very good.
What are your intentions?
To get married.
That's your decision?
Yes.
Is your decision considered
the final decision in your house?
Yes.
Do you have any Tillu in your life?
Tillu?
No.
Balli bro!
She agreed!
'Finally Balli found his queen, Rani.'
'Veerey got married to Geet.'
'And the ones who danced
the most at the wedding were..'
'Uncle..'
'And his nephew!'
"Into our lives,
happiness has made a smooth landing."
"Sister-in-law looks like an angel.."
"Bro looks like a king."
"When the groom will
get ready and look dashing.."
"All the guests will start dancing."
"Then all the guests
will start dancing."
"Dance will continue nonstop.."
"Nonstop for a month."
"Uncle will dance.."
"So will the idiot
who stands no chance."
"Dance will continue nonstop.."
"Nonstop for a month."
"Uncle will dance.."
"So will the idiot
who stands no chance."
"Even the drums won't stop rocking."
"All the guests will start dancing."
"Then all the guests
will start dancing."
"If you don’t know to dance,
just move your hips.."
"Let this party become a hit!"
"If you don’t know to dance,
just move your hips.."
"Let this party become a hit!"
"Even the DJ said I ain't stopping!"
"All the guests will start dancing."
"Then all the guests
will start dancing."
"It is time to celebrate,
I am so happy!"
"Move away, girl, get out of my way."
"Let me swirl as
I have got a chance..."
"Today at Veerey's.."
"Today at Veerey's wedding,
let me dance."
"Today at Veerey's.."
"Everyone is happy,
today's Veerey's wedding."
"Veerey's wedding.."
"Dance, dude.. Today's
Veerey's wedding."
"Veerey's wedding.."
"They make a cute couple,
it's my bro's wedding!"
"Veerey's wedding.."
"Everyone is happy,
today's Veerey's wedding."
"Veerey's wedding.."